Mr TIMI ALAIBE Executive Director Project, Niger Delta Development Commission, Old Secretariat Complex, Victorial-Island, Lagos. Tel:+2348037778976 Dear Sir, I am TIMI ALAIBE, the Executive Director Finance with the Niger Delta Development Commission ( NDDC ). My commssion - The Niger Delta Development Commission(NDDC)-which is in charge of managing and supervising the disbursement of oil sales revenues for the Nigerian government which covers payment to foreign and local contractors that have executed contracts for the Federal Government.The revenue under our control runs into several hundred of millions of dollars monthly.Myself and other colleagues in the NDDC are currently in need of a foreign partner with whose bank account we shall transfer the sum of Thirty Million United States Dollars($30m). This fund was accrued from various over invoicing of foreign contractors' payments made over the years. The Total fund is presently waiting in the Government Account named CBN/FGN INDEPENDENT REVENUE account Central Bank of Nigeria.However, by virtue of my position as civil servant and staff of the NDDC, I cannot acquire this funds in my name. This is because as top civil servant, I are not allowed by law of the land to own or operate bank accounts outside our country for now. I have been delegated as a matter of trust by my colleagues, to look for an overseas partner in whose account we would transfer the fund,hence the reason for this mail.We shall be Transferring the money to your account with the company's name you provide as the beneficiary, under the guise that you are being paid for a contract which you/your company executed for our country through the Commission. For your support and partnership,please reply me to negotiate your fees or the percentage you wish to be paid when the funds arrive your bank account. You must however note that this transaction, with regards to our disposition to continue with you, is subject to these terms. Firstly, our conviction of your transparency.Secondly, that you treat this transaction with utmost secrecy and confidentiality. Finally and above all, that you will provide an account over which you have absolute control . The transaction, although discrete, is legitimate and there is no risk or legal lliability either to ourselves or yourself now or in the future as we have put in place the neccesary machinery that will ensure a hitch free transfer into your account upon acceptance. The transfer will be effected to your account within five - seven (5-7) working days from the date we reach an agreement and you furnish me with a suitable bank account and company name with your contact numbers including fax number. I am looking forward to doing business with you and do solicit your confidentiality in this transaction, Please mail back your response through this email address for me to update you on our plans as to how we intend to actualize this transaction. Sincerely yours, Mr TIMI ALAIBE Private Email: zezi@www.com website:www.nddconline.org

Dear sir/madam, I am Ms. KIMAEVA LIOUDMILA, a personal secretary to Mikhail Khodorkovsky the richest man in Russia and owner of the following companies: Chairman CEO: YUKOS OIL (Russian Largest Oil Company) Chairman CEO: Menatep SBP Bank (A well reputable financial institution with its branches all over the world). I seek your partnership to accommodate the sum US$423M for us. My Boss got arrested for his involvement on politics in financing the leading and opposing political parties (the Union of Right Forces, led by Boris Nemtsov, and Yabloko, a liberal/social democratic party led by Gregor Yavlinsky) which posed treat to President Vladimir Putin second tenure as Russian president before he was reelected On March 14, 2004. You can catch more of the story on this http://newsfromrussia.com/main/2003/11/13/51215.html The fund (US$423M) in question was approved by the Government of Russia for payment of various YUKOS OIL contractors/suppliers to prevent them from loosing the money they invested in the numerous contracts they executed for the above firm. The Government had already concluded plans to frozen all the accounts in my boss name (Mikhail Khodorkovsky) both corporate and personal before I connived with the Accountant General of YUKOS OIL (who is also my partner in this transaction) to raise a memo stating that YUKOS OIL owe contractors the above amount which was finally approved for payment after some deliberations. Actually, we have paid all our contractors both local and foreign because they agitated for their payment when they had that my boss was arrested. YOUR ROLE: I will present you / your company as one of the contractors we are owing so that you can stand as the beneficiary of the above quoted sum or part of the fund according to your financial strength or the strength of your company. I will arrange for the documentation which the payee bank will need to transfer the sum to you. I have decided to use this sum to relocate to American continent and never to be connected to any of Mikhail Khodorkovsky conglomerates. The transaction has to be concluded before as soon as possible. You will be rewarded with 10% of the total sum for your partnership. Can you be our partner on this transacton? As soon as I get your willingness to assist us in this deal, I will give you more details. Thank you very much . NOTE: PLEASE REPLY TO THIS MAIL kimaeva@k.ro. Regards MS.KIMAEVA LIOUDMILA __________________________________________________________________ Tiscali Adsl 2 Mega Free: naviga gratis tutto l'anno! Supera tutti i limiti di velocita' con Tiscali Adsl 2 Mega Free. Sei libero da costi fissi e, se ti abboni entro l'8 novembre, navighi gratis tutto l'anno. http://abbonati.tiscali.it/adsl/

FROM MR OMARU AMINU, AUDITING AND ACCOUNTING UNIT. FOREIGN REMITTANCE DEPT. INTERNATIONAL BANK OF AFRICA OUAGADOUGOU, BURKINA FASO. Sir, I am MR OMARU AMINU,the director,in charge of Auditing and Accounting section of International Bank of Africa Ouagadougou Burkina faso,in West Africa in due respect and regards.I have decided to contact you on a business transaction that will be very beneficial to both of us at the end of the transaction. During our investigation and auditing in the bank, my department came across a very huge sum of money belonging to a deceased person, a foreigner who died on november 2000 in a plane crash and the fund has been dormant in his account with the bank without any claim of the fund in our custody either from his family or relation before our discovery to this development. Although personally,i kept this information secret within myself and partners to enable the whole plans and idea be profitable and successful during the time of execution.The said amount was USD$14m (fourteen million united states dollars). As it may intrest you to know, I got your contact through international business enquiry on internet. I believe you will be viable and capable to champion a business of such magnitude without any problem. Meanwhile all the whole arrangement to put claim over this fund as the bona fide next of kin to the deceased, get the required approval and transfer this money to a foreign account has been put in place and directives/needed information will be relayed to you as soon as you indicate your interest and willingness to assist us and also benefit your self to this great business opportunity. In fact I could have done this deal alone but because of my position in this country as a civil servant,we are not allowed to operate a foreign account and would eventually raise an eye brow on my side during the time of transfer because I work in this bank.This is the actual reason why it will require a second party or fellow who will forward claims as the next of kin with affidavit of trust of Oath to the bank and also present a foreign account where he will need the money to be re-transfered into on his request as it may be, after due verification and clarification by designated bank account. I will not fail to inform you that this transaction is 100% risk free. On smooth conclusion of this transaction, you will be entitled to 30% of the total sum as gratification, while 10% will be set aside to take care of expenses that may arise during the time of transfer such as telephone bills etc, while 60% will be for me and my partners. Please,you have been advised to keep top secret as we are still in service and intend to retire from service after we conclude this deal with you. I will be monitoring the whole situation here in the bank until you confirm the money in your account.And ask us to come down to your country for subsequent sharing of the fund according to percentages previously indicated and further investment,either in your country or any other country you may advice us to invest in.All other necessary information will be sent to you when I hear from you.I suggest you get back to me as soon as possible stating your wish in this deal. Yours faithfully, MR OMARU AMINU. _________________________________________________________________ Express yourself instantly with MSN Messenger! Download today it's FREE! http://messenger.msn.com/

FROM: MR. SOLOMON ADJEI TRUST SECURITY COMPANY LTD ACCRA-GHANA TEL: + 233-244-514-523 Dear Friend, My name is Mr Solomon Adjei, I work in executive capacity with TRUST SECURITY COMPANY (ltd) Accra Ghana. I joined the services of this company in 1991. I got the information concerning you and your company from our Chamber of Commerce here and after due consultation, I decided to contact you believing that by the grace of God that you will be my partner in this business. I have worked with this company for over 12 years, within this period of time I watched with meticulous precision onhow African Head of State and government functionarieshave been moving huge sums of money (Dollars, PoundSterling, French Franc, Cash)with the aid of their foreign partners abroad. They bring in these consignment of money cash and secretly declare the content as jewelries, Gold, Precious Stones, Family Treasure, Documents,etc. Mobutu Sese Seko of Zaire, Fodey Sankoy of Sierra Leone, Felix Houphet Buigny of Ivory Coast, Konnan Bede of Ivory Coast, etc. These people have at one time or the other deposited consignments with us and their foreign partners, relatives and Next of Kin are Claiming most of these consignment and a lot more are laying here unclaimed for as much as 7 years, as no available information to anybody except the depositors, and most of them are dead. Since the inception of the year 2003, TRUST SECURITY COMPANY LTD Management changed the procedure of claiming of consignments. As soon as you are able to produce all the secret information as contained in the secret file of the company as regard the consignment, it will be released to you upon demand. From our records, more than 10 consignments belonging to these people has been claimed in the past six months and this is why I am seeking for your co-operation and assistance. Mr. Martin Greenberg was an American,he worked with one of the top ministers of President Robert Mugabe who was in charge of the campaigning for re-electing Mr. Mugabe into office in their last election. He deposited this consignment containing 35.5 million United State Dollars ($35.5m USD)early in 1999, this money according to him was to be used for further political programmes. He died in the plane crash of 31 October 1999 with the Wife (on the Egyptian 990) with reports on CNN as you can verify via the CNN website as state below:(http://www.cnn.com/us/9911/02/egyptair990.list/index.html) He died alongside with other passengers aboard without leaving any relations as his wife died as well in the same plane crash. Since his death, no one knows about this transaction with TRUST SECURITY COMPANY ltd except me who acted as company attorney when he deposited the consignment. I have finished every arrangement for you to come and claim the consignment as the next of Kin Mr.MARTIN GREENBERG. The procedure is very simple: - Apply officially to the Director of operation Trust security company Ltd Accra - Ghana, for the release of consignment No.TSC/15031964. They will demand for some documents and the security code of the consignment, you will call on me to supply you with every detailed Information as regard the consignment. As soon as they have confirmed it to be correct, the company will invite you for the collection. Nobody will ever know that I am involved in the deal, I suggest upon conclusion, we share it on the Ratio of 50%-40%and 10% will go for humanitarian service ie, motherless babies home, more also you will make an arrangement on investments that I will invest my money in your country. I assure you that this business is very secure and risk free. Plese, if you are interested on this proposal, kindly let me know to ebable me know my stand and hope on you. you are advise to contact me through my telephone nuber: 233-244-514-523 for an oral clarification and detailings. Thanks Mr Solomon Adjei __________________________________________________________________ Win 12 amazing weekend breaks, one every month for a year to Dublin, Milan, the Alps, Paris and beyond http://www.tiscali.co.uk/travel/competitions/brilliant_weekends.html

From: Dr. Rasheed S. Abubakar, Dear Friend, My Compliment to you, I guess this letter may come to you as a surprise since I had no previous correspondence with you. I am sending you this mail on behalf of the chairman tender board of Independent National Electoral Commission (INEC) MR. SETTLEY DAZE. We got your contact in our search for a reliable person to handle a very confidential transaction involving the transfer of Forty Nine Million, Five Hundred Thosand United States Dollars US$49.5Million. The above fund is not connected with arms, drugs or money laundering. It is the product of an over invoiced Contract awarded in 2001 by INEC to a foreign company for the construction of high rise estate in the federal capital territory. The contract has long been executed and payment of the actual contract amount has been paid to the foreign contractor leaving the balance, which my colleague and I now want to transfer out of Nigeria into a reliable foreign account for our personal use. As civil servants we are not allowed to run foreign accounts. Hence we have chosen you to front and support us as the beneficiary to be paid. If you are interested in the proposal kindly get back to me by sending me your letter of acceptance along with your direct telephone and fax numbers, For your support and partnership, please reply me to negotiate your fees or the percentage you wish to be paid when the funds arrive your bank account. Further details about this transaction will be discussed in the subsequent correspondence. Note also that the particular nature of your business is irrelevant to this transaction and all local contacts and arrangements are in place for a smooth and successful conclusion of this transaction. Be informed that we are aware of the way email proposals of this type are being sent from this part of africa and as regards that, you should please treat this with utmost attention knowing fully well that you cannot and will not be compelled to assist us if you are not disposed to. Contact me via my email account or you also reach me on this email account she_rashabubakar@yahoo.com with your contact telephone and fax numbers on response, I will call you for a discussion. Thank you as I await your response. Sincerely, Dr. Rasheed S. Abubakar.

FROM MR.SESAY MASSAQUOE. PLEASE RESPOND TO MY PRIVATE EMAIL ADDRESS....>sesmassa@di-ve.com DEAR FRIEND, THROUGH THE COURTESY OF BUSINESS OPPORTUNITY, I TAKE LIBERTY ANCHORED ON A STRONG DESIRE TO SOLICIT YOUR ASSISTANCE ON THIS MUTUALLY BENEFICIAL AND RISKFREE TRANSACTION WHICH I HOPE YOU WILL GIVE YOUR URGENT ATTENTION. I AM MR.SESAY MASSAQUOE I AM MOVED TO WRITE YOU THIS LETTER ,THIS WAS IN CONFIDENCE CONSIDERING OUR PRESENT CIRCUMSTANCE AND SITUATION. I ESCAPED WITH MY WIFE AND CHILDREN OUT OF SIERRA- LEONE TO UNITED KINDOM THROUGH THE AID OF THE UNITED NATIONS EVACUATION TEAM WHERE WE ARE NOW PRESENTLY RESIDING ON TEMPORARY POLITICAL ASYLUM. HOWEVER DUE TO THIS SITUATION I DECIDED TO CHANGE MOST OF MY BILLIONS OF DOLLARS DEPOSITED IN SWISS BANK AND OTHER COUNTRIES INTO OTHER FORMS OF MONEY CODED FOR SAFE PURPOSE BECAUSE THE NEW HEAD OF STATES AHMED TEJAN KABBA MADE ARRANGEMENTS WITH THE SWISS GOVERNMENT AND OTHER EUROPEAN COUNTRIES TO FREEZE ALL MY TREASURES DEPOSITED IN SOME EUROPEAN COUNTRIES,HENCE I AND MY WIFE ALONG WITH MY CHILDREN, DECIDED LAYING LOW IN A TEMPOERY POLITICAL ASYLUM CAMP HERE IN THE UNITED KINGDOM TO STUDY THE SITUATION TILL WHEN THINGS GETS BETTER,SINCE PRESIDENT TEJAN KABBA TAKING OVER GOVERNMENT AGAIN IN SIERRA-LEONE ONE OF MY CHATEAUX IN SOUTHERN FRANCE WAS CONFISCATED BY THE FRENCH GOVERNMENT,AND AS SUCH WE HAD TO CHANGE OUR IDENTITY SO THAT OUR INVESTMENT WILL NOT BE TRACED AND CONFISCATED. I HAVE DEPOSITED THE SUM OF THIRTY MILLION,FIVE HUNDRED THOUSAND UNITED STATES DOLLARS(US$30,500,000)WITH A SECURITY COMPANY FOR SAFEKEEPING. THE FUNDS ARE SECURITY CODED TO PREVENT THEM FROM KNOWING THE ACTUAL CONTENTS. WHAT I WANT YOU TO DO NOW IS TO INDICATE YOUR INTEREST THAT YOU WILL ASSIST ME AND MY IMMEDIATE FAMILY BY RECEIVING THE MONEY ON OUR BEHALF. THE ACCOUNT REQUIRED FOR THIS PROJECT CAN EITHER BE PERSONAL,COMPANY OR AN OFFSHORE ACCOUNT THAT YOU HAVE TOTAL CONTROL OVER,YOUR AREA OF SPECIALISATION WILL NOT BE A HINDERANCE TO THE SUCCESSFUL EXECUTION OF THIS TRANSACTION. ACKOWLEDGE THIS MESSAGE,SO THAT I CAN INTRODUCE YOU TO MY FAMILY AS OUR FOREIGN TRUSTED PARTNER WHO SHALL TAKE CHARGE OF OUR INVESTMENT ABROAD WHERE WE NOW PLAN TO SETTLE. I WANT YOU TO ASSIST US IN INVESTING THIS MONEY,BUT I WILL NOT WANT OUR IDENTITY REVEALED.I WILL ALSO WANT TO BUY PROPERTIES AND STOCKS IN MULTI-NATIONAL COMPANIES AND TO ENGAGE IN OTHER SAFE AND NON SPECULATIVE INVESTMENTS. WE HAVE BEEN THROUGH A LOT OF HEALTH AND SPIRITUAL TURMOIL,HENCE WILL NEED YOUR UNDERSTANDING AND ASSISTANCE. MAY I AT THIS POINT EMPHASIZE THE HIGH LEVEL OF CONFIDENTIALITY WHICH THIS BUSINESS DEMANDS AND HOPE YOU WILL NOT BETRAY THE TRUST AND CONFIDENCE WHICH WE REPOSE IN YOU.I SHALL PUT YOU IN THE PICTURE OF THIS BUSINESS,I.E TELL YOU WHERE THE FUNDS ARE CURRENTLY BEING MAINTAINED AND ALSO DISCUSS OTHER MODALITIES INCLUDING REMUNERATION FOR YOUR SERVICES. I SHALL INFORM YOU WITH THE NEXT LINE OF ACTION AS SOON AS I RECEIVE YOUR POSITIVE RESPONSE. IS THIS PROPOSITION ATTAINABLE?IF IT IS,PLEASE KINDLY FURNISH ME IMMEDIATELY BY E-MAIL WITH YOUR DIRECT TELEPHONE AND FAX NUMBERS TO ENHANCE THE CONFIDENTIALLITY WHICH THIS BUSINESS DEMANDS. PLEASE REPLY TO MY PERSONAL EMAIL ADDRESS............>sesmassa@di-ve.com BEST REGARDS MR.SESAY MASSAQUOE.

FROM THE DESK OF OKOFOR DAVID Branch Accounts Manager, Prudent Bank Nigeria Limited, Falomo Office Complex, Ikoyo, Lagos. Nigeria. DEAR FRIEND, On SUNDAY, February 2, 2003, a bomb blast explosion took place on the Lagos Island, right inside My bank; So far a total lost of about US$20.5 million has been recorded, this includes both cash and property of the bank. Please View the Link below: http://www.cnn.com/2003/WORLD/africa/02/03/lagos.explosion/index.html However as the Accounts Manager of the BANK,I discovered Most of our Data on accounts has been lost as well, as there has not been anyback up or network trace even from the HEADQUARTERS;therefore all losses would be artributed to the! Explosion. The lagos State Government has taken charges to pay for all losses. I found out i still have Data's of foreign Customers who are contractors in Nigeria and who own accounts with the Branch, Particularly that of an American oil contractor Hsu Ben, who was reported Dead in a plane crash[Korean Air Flight 801] with the whole passengers aboard on August 6,1997.And for your perusal you can view this website: http://www.cnn.com/WORLD/9708/06/guam.passenger.list/ who's contract payments has been Made and would be tranfered to his foreign accounts from the CENTRAL BANK OF NIGERIA, upon our confirmation of his foreign designated account as well as a beneficiary to his funds and payments. Mr Hsu Ben, while our customer never left a trace of his next of kin, and His contract Payment which is about US$15M, would be made to no one as we( the bank) has! none of his Data/next of kin's contact. My proposal is that I will like you as a foriegner to stand in as the next of kin to Mr Hsu Ben, so that the fruits of this old man's labor will not get into the hands of some corrupt government officials, Besides the Bank which i work in has been blown up, i have no Job for now, i have to make a living and only me knows the information so far about this. This is simple, I will like you to provide immediately your full names and address so that the Attorney will prepare the necessary documents and affidavits which will put you in place as the next of kin. We shall employ the service of an Attorney for drafting and notarization of the WILL and to obtain the necessary documents and letter of probate/administration in your favour for the transfer. A bank account in any part of the world which you will provide will then facilitate the transfer of this money to you as the beneficiary/next of kin. The money will be paid into your account as payment for his Contract by t! he CENTRAL BANK OF NIGERIA upon my submission of the Contract information and your application as his next of kin for us to share in the ratio of 70% for me, 20% for you and 10% will be use to cover all the expensives that will come-up in the course of this transaction. There is no risk at all as all the paperwork for this transaction will be done by the Attorney and my position as the Branch Accounts Manager guarantees the successful execution of this transaction. Upon your response, I shall then provide you with more details and relevant documents that will help you understand the transaction. Please observe utmost confidentiality, and rest assured that this transaction would be most profitable for both of us because I shall require your assistance to invest my share in your country. Your phone and fax number are need for easy communication. Awaiting your urgent response. Your Faithfully. MR. OKOFOR DAVID

ATTN:YOU CONTRACTOR Dear Sir, Sequel to the secretive arrangement in regards of the shipment of your contract sum, I wish to inform you that all necessary modalities have been automatically concluded and have left Nigeria to London via your Country today by Express Cargo Flight. Note carefully the content of the crate is "MONEY" but I did not disclose it to the Courier Services as Money, rather I informed them that the crate contain Vital "DIPLOMATIC DOCUMENTS" belonging to my client (that?s you). Furthermore, the weight of the consignment is 90kg but I manage to pay 45kg, which cost US$9,000.00. On no account should you disclose the content of the crate with the Diplomatic Courier Services for fear of betrayal. So do not allow them to know that the content is money. In the meantime, contact the Global Trust Dipomatic Courier Services to the Attn. Edy Smithkline on Tel: 44-77-46065722 or Email :g_s1@o2.pl to know the actual situation with the consignment and also give them your address where the consignment will be delivered and then get back to me as soon as possible so that I can give you the shipment document. Meanwhile, I will be coming over to your country immediately the consignment arrives in your Country for my 10% share. Please update me as you contact the Global Trust Diplomatic Courier Services for more details you may need from me. Congrats and remain blessed. Best Regards, Yours faithfully, Dr. PETER BELLO

X-Sieve: CMU Sieve 2.2 Date: Fri, 5 Nov 2004 14:24:42 GMT Message-Id: <200411051424.iA5EOfg16776@servicos.te.pt> X-Authentication-Warning: servicos.te.pt: apache set sender to amir_04@educacao.te.pt using -f From: "Amir Ebrahimi " <amir_04@educacao.te.pt> To: amir_04@educacao.te.pt Reply-To: amirebrahimi@virgilio.it Subject: IMPORTANT NOTICE!!! X-Mailer: NeoMail 1.22 X-IPAddress: 81.134.37.121 MIME-Version: 1.0 Content-Type: text/plain; charset=iso-8859-1 Status: RO FIRST MERIT BANK SWINDON,UNITED KINGDOM Dear Partner PRIVATE AND URGENT. I am Mr Amir Ebrahimi, and I am contacting you on business transfer of a huge sum of money from a deceased account. Though I know that a transaction of this magnitude will make anyone apprehensive and worried, but I am assuring you that all will be well at the end of the day. I decided to contact you due to the urgency of this transaction. PROPOSITION; I am the account officer to Mr Abdullah Saleh (deceased) one of our foreign customers. While he banked with us, I oversaw his accounts and other official/financial obligations as my office demanded being his accounts officer.Unfortunately, he died along with his entire family in the plane crash of 31 October, 1999 on board the Egyptian Airline 990 alonside other passengers. Please consult the British Broadcasting Corporation website below for verification. http://news.bbc.co.uk/1/hi/world/americas/502503.stm While he was alive, none of his family members was ever known to me other than his immediate nuclear family.Since his death, none of his next-of-kin or relations has come forward to lay claims to this money as the heir. I cannot release the fund from his account unless someone applies for claim as the next-of-kin to the deceased as indicated in our banking guidelines. Having made a very exhaustive search for any family member that would lay claim to this fund, I decided to take my chance with you.I now seek your permission to have you stand as next of kin to the deceased as I have all documentations including his certified Death Certificate that will facilitate your stand as next of kin to him as he had a closing balanced of 5,500,000.00 Five million five hundred thousand British pounds sterling) here in our bank in united kingdom. I also have secured from the probate an order of mandamus to locate any member of deceased family to become beneficiary of this fund. Please acknowledge receipt of this message in acceptance of our mutual business endeavour by furnishing me with the following; 1. Full name and address 2. Direct Telephone and fax numbers These requirements will enable me make some internal re-adjustments and file your name in form A2ag and other vital forms as next of kin which before now was left blank by the deceased upon opening of the account six years ago. Upon your reply, I will advice the way forward. I must assure you that if you are serious and follow my lead religiously, then this funds will be released to you within a seven-working-day period. If this proposal is acceptable by you, do not take undue advantage of the trust I have bestowed in you, I await your urgent mail. Please reply Regards, Mr.Amir Ebrahimi

DEAR SIR, VERY URGENT, PLEASE SAVE MY SOUL. I AM KUDIRAT DANJUMA (MRS.), WIDOW OF THE LATE COL. RICHARD DANJUMA THE FORMER GOVERNOR OF KANO STATE OF NIGERIA MY LATE HUSBAND WAS ONE OF THE VICTIMS OF THE NOVEMBER 7TH 1996 NIGERIA A, D, C AIRCRAFT BOEING 727 THAT CRASHED IN LAGOS. I HAVE BEEN INFORMED BY MY FAMILY ATTORNEY, BARRISTER BENJAMIN SAMSON THAT MY LATE HUSBAND OPERATED A SECRET ACCOUNT WITH FICTITIOUS NAME IN A NIGERIAN BANK INTO WHICH A TOTAL SUM OF TWENTY-FIVE MILLION, FIVE HUNDRED THOUSAND U.S DOLLARS ($25.5M) WAS TRANSFERRED AND CREDITED IN HIS FAVOUR, THE ATTORNEY NOW ADVISED ME TO SEEK IN CONFIDENCE A FOREIGN ACCOUNT INTO WHICH THIS FUND COULD BE TRANSFERRED FOR DISBURSEMENT AS DIRECTED BY MY LATE HUSBAN IN HIS "WILL".IT HAS BEEN RESOLVED THAT 25% WILL BE YOUR SHARE FOR NOMINATING AN ACCOUNT,FOR THIS PURPOSE AND ANY OTHER ASSISTANCE YOU WILL GIVE IN THIS REGARD, 5% HAS BEEN MAPPED OUT TO PAY BACK ALL LOCAL AND INTERNATIONAL EXPENSES WHICH MAY BE INCURRED IN THE TRANSFER PROCESS AND 5% HAS BEEN CONCEDED TO THE LOCAL BANK MANAGER HERE ASSISTING IN FACILITATING THE TRANSFER. FINALLY,65% WILL COME TO MYSELF AND MY CHILDREN AND A GOOD PARTY OF THIS SHALL BE DIRECTED TOWARDS EXECUTING HIS "WILL" WHICH IS TO BUY SHARES ANDSTOCKS IN FOREIGN COUNTRIES TO SECURE HIS CHILDREN FUTURE.TO FACILITATE THE CONCLUSION OF THIS TRANSACTION, IF ACCEPTED, DO SEND TO E-MAIL MY FAMILY ATTORNEY THE FOLLOWINGS: ON E-MAIL NO. barrister_bensam@mail2ben.com 1. FAX 2. TEL AND E-MAIL ADDRESS THROUGH WHICH YOU WILL BE CONTACTED PROMPTLY WHENEVER YOUR ATTENTION/ASSISTANCE MAY BE REQUIRED. PLEASE NOTE THAT I HAVE BEEN ASSURED THAT THE TRANSACTION WILL BE CONCLUDED IN A SHORTEST BANKING WORKING DAYS UPON MY RECEIVING FROM YOU THE ABOVE LISTED INFORMATION. I SHALL COMMENCE THE PROCESS OF RETRIEVING THE FUND IMMEDIATELY I HEAR FROM YOU.MAY I AT THIS POINT, EMPHASIS THE HIGH LEVEL OF CONFIDENTIALITY, WHICH THIS BUSINESS DEMANDS, AND HOPE YOU WILL NOT BETRAY THE TRUST AND CONFIDENCE, WHICH I REPOSE IN YOU. HOWEVER, YOU MAY NEED TO GIVE ME SUFFICIENT ASSURANCE THAT YOU WILL NOT SIT ON THIS FUND WHEN IT IS FINALLY REMITTED INTO YOUR ACCOUNT. PLEASE GIVE THIS MATTER A PROMPT AND QUICK REPLY. PLEASE CALL OR DIRECT YOUR RESPOND TO MY FAMILY ATTORNEY/BARRISTER BENJAMIN SAMSON AS INDICATED BELOW AND DISCUSS WITH HIM TOWARDS EFFECTIVE COMPLETION OF THIS TRANSACTION. CONTACT MY FAMILY ATTORNEY BARRISTER BENJAMIN SAMSON ON EMAIL: barrister_bensam@mail2ben.com BEST REGARD, KUDIRAT DANJUMA (MRS). _________________________________________________________________ Suchen Sie etwas?- http://www.regon.de

Republic of South Africa    inno1983@yahoo.com   Dear Sir Subject: Investment Proposal. Re: Transfer of Fifty Million United States Dollars, (US$50,000, 000.00) I am Hon. Mr. Hope Sithole one of the Personal Assistants to the young President Joseph Kabila of Democratic Republic of Congo (DRC), since he assumed power.Sincerely speaking, my agitation is real, and my word is my bond in this proposal. This money in question is part of the budget made by our President Mr. Joseph Kabila, in the fear that members of the United Nations (UN) could perhaps be mandated to offer their respective supports in forcing Iraq to disarm themselves. Eventually, his dreams do not match up with realities and as a result he (the President) started using the money on personal ground because nobody could question/probe his actions, as he believed. As his closest personal assistant and with the help of two other officials one of whom was the then deputy Director, Safety and Security Department, we were able to escape with two boxes containing the aforementioned sum. At present the boxes were deposited in a reputable Security firm here in South Africa and were registered as family belongings. We had agreed on the need for a foreign assistance with a legitimate bank account abroad, that will stand as, the beneficiary and partner as well in order to avoid suspicion, since we are existing as refugees here. Copies of certificate of Deposit as well as all necessary documents from the Security cc. are available for a hitch-free transaction. In addition, you are also required to come/send a representative (as far as you trust the person representing) to the Republic of South Africa for the purpose of the transfer, but only if, by one reason or the other you cannot embark on a Five working (5) days trip by yourself, according to the expert from within the bank. As things are now we had not really agreed on the actual amount that should be your remuneration for your kind assistance, which to us is no big deal. The crux of this subject in particular is the declaration of your interest after-which we enter into negotiations with you over the (percentage) issue. Other details of which you may want to know shall be discussed in due course. Please be kind enough to acknowledge this proposal by responding through the above E-mail address for a high level of confidentiality in this business deal. Best regards, Hon. Mr. hope sithole tel _27832378499

Do you Yahoo!? Check out the new Yahoo! Front Page. www.yahoo.com

Dr.Morgen Akin Best Lagos-Africa Dear Friend, I, on behalf of my colleagues from the Federal Government of Nigeria owned parastatals decided to solicit your assistance as regards transfer of US$21,500,000.00 (Twenty-one Million, five Hundred Thousand US Dollars) into your bank account. These funds emanated from unclaimed contractual proceeds of foreign contracting firms who could not meet their financial obligations to their creditors. We, as holders of sensitive positions in our various parastatals, were mandated by the Federal Government to scrutinize all payments made to certain Foreign contractors and we discovered that some of the contractors have not been paid their contractual entitlement which collectively left the sum of US$35,500,000.00 (Thirty-Five Million, five Hundred Thousand US Dollars) lying in a suspended Account. However, from our investigations, we discovered that the foreign beneficiary companies have since been liquidated, and to all intents and purposes no longer exist in Nigeria, thus providing us with this Opportunity, provided that we have a capable partner, to execute a transaction of this nature. We agreed that the said amount would be transferred into an overseas Bank Account to be provided by a Reliable foreign firm/associate. This is because as serving Government workers the Civil Service Code does not allow us to operate foreign Account. In our initial attempt to do this, we succeeded in transferring part of this amount US$14m (Fourteen Million Dollars) into a United States Dollar Account in Beirut, Lebanon, but our foreign associate failed to honour our mutual agreement insisting instead that the total amount be transferred into the Account before we can share the money. As a result, we have lost confidence in the ability of our Lebanese partner to see this matter to its logical conclusion, and until the initial transaction is satisfactorily resolved, we have cancelled further transactions with him. In the light of the foregoing, it is clear that we require a partner that is not only capable of rendering assistance and cooperation in executing this matter, but will honour the terms of agreement when we reach the concluding stages of this transaction. We therefore offer the amount of 20% of the entire sum in return for services/assistance rendered in successfully carrying out this project. We trust that you appreciate the sensitive nature of this matter and the need for initial caution on our part, but when a Relationship is confidently established and operations commence you will be provided with all relevant information. I remain at your disposal to entertain any questions/enquiries relating to this proposition and you may contact me as a matter of urgency via e- mail, for further information on the procedures and requirements of this transaction. In your reply, remember to indicate a safe telephone number where I can always reach you. Hope to hear from you soon. Please treat with the strictest confidentiality and expediency. Yours faithfully, Dr.Morgen Akin Best

Federal Ministry of Works & Housing Radio House, Herbert Macaulay Way(south) P.M.B 111, Garki, Abuja (Opposite the International Conference Centre) Dear Sir/Madam, This is to invite you to freely participate in a business venture on behalf of my partners and I.We especially need you to act as the chief beneficiary of a contract sum worth $14M in the Ministry of Works & Housing, Nigeria. For your benefit of doubt, we [ my partners & I] are management officials in the board team of the above named government parastatal. In addition, we are members of the internal audit reveiw panel set up to reconcile all bonifide contract debts being owed to foreigners by the government of Nigeria. In the course of our auditing, we came across the siad sum of $14m floating in the ministry escrow account as an accrued debt payable to a yet un-identified contractor since 2001.On thorough examination,it was discovered that the $14M was a debt brilliantly created by the former Director General in favour of a company that she was about to incorporate locally here with the help of a foreign partner. We made consultations with the former DG and eventually struck an agreement with her.The masterplan she created remains the same.The plan is to make you the chief beneficiary to the $14M by way of advancing you/your company as the real contractor to whom the sum is owed by the Ministry for a project executed between 2000/2001.As a matter of fact,all the modalities needed to acheive this has already been perfected. The overall plan is 100% foolproof and will be carried out legally in every aspect of the transaction. Specifically,your duty will be to act in correspondence (viaE-mails,Faxes & Telephone)- with the local Ministry of Finance as well as the Apex Bank authorities; until your total claims are verified,approved and the money paid into your advised bank account. Whereas we would like to maintain our full confidentiality for now, we shall however provide you with more details as to the masterplan and the entire time frames involved. We will do so when you indicate your interest to become a partner with us. Looking forward to a cordial business partnership with you. Sincerely, Engr.Idris Lanre. ______________________________________________________ Please reply to my private e-mail :engridrislanre_2005@fastermail.com ______________________________________________________ Engr. Idris Lanre. Federal Ministry of Works & Housing Radio House, Herbert Macaulay Way (south) P.M.B 111, Garki, Abuja (Opposite the International Conference Centre) E-mail: engridrislanre_2005@fastermail.com www.nopa.net/Press_Release/messages/24.shtml Fax: 2349-5229634 ___________________________________________________________________________ Mail sent from WebMail service at - http://IzzitSO.com

DEAR CONFIDENTIAL / URGENT PROPOSAL Firstly,I must solicit your confidence in this transaction.I know that a transaction of this magnitude will make any one apprenhensive,but be assured that at the end all concerned would smile.I decided to contact you due to the urgency of this transaction. Let me introduce myself.I am Frank Map, a staff of UNION BANK OF NIGERIA.I got your contact via my private search and decided to ask for your personal involvement because of the urgency of this business. THE PROPOSAL:A Foreigner,Late Mr Peter Creek an Expertriate engineer,who was involved in oil merchant/contractor with the Federal Government of Nigeria,until His death over two years ago in a ghastly car accident,banked with us here and a closing balance as at the end of March,2000 of USD 35. 2Million(thirty five million,two hundred thousand dollars)equivalent in the local currency,which the bank now expects a next of kin to claim as beneficiary.All efforts by bank to contact any of his relatives proved unseccesful. As a result of this the Board of Directors are about to place the fund as"UNCLAIMAMBLE"and it has been decided that the funds shall be shared among themselves. In order to prevent this,some of my colleagues and i now seek your assistance to have you stand in as the beneficiary's next of kin.All documents to enable you claim this fund will be carefully obtained from the federal high court of justice. This Proposal is 100% risk free on your side because i will obtain a court ruling order that you are the beneficiary's next of kin.We have agreed that 25% of the total fund when remitted would be your share. Again take note that up to 10% of would stand as incidental expenses,The remaining 65% would be our share,more details would follow with time.If this proposal is acceptable to you ,kindly contact me through my private E-mail address(frankmap333@yahoo.com) shown above and foward to me your telephone and fax numbers for easy communications and indicate your interest urgently. PLEASE TREAT THIS AS A VERY URGENT AND CONFIDENTIAL MATTER. Thanks Yours Faithfully, Frank Map

Dear Sir , Compliments of the day to you, how is your family and the good people around you, I hope and assume they are in good condition if so thanks to the Almigthy God for his good work. I am Mr. Joseph Gogo, presently promoted to Auditor General of Eco Bank Plc here in Cotonou Du Republic of Benin. During the course of our auditing last week, I discovered a floating fund in an account opened in the bank in 1996 and since 1998 nobody has operated on this account again, after going through some old files in the records, I discovered that the owner of the account died without a will, hence the money is floating and if I do not remit this money out urgently it will be forfeited for nothing. Believe God in all you are doing. I urge you to treat it serious. I and my collueges, want to transfer to an oversea account (US$6,700.000.00) Six Million, Seven Hundred Thousand United States Dollars) from Eco Bank Plc here in Cotonou, Republic of Benin. I want to ask you, If you are capable to or will quietly look for a reliable and honest person who will be capable, Honest and trustworthy to provide either an existing bank account or to set up a new Bank account as soon as posible to receive this money, as long as you will remain honest to me . I pray for your understanding. The owner of this account, Mr. Morris Thompson, an American and great industrialist, resident of Alaska, who unfortunately lost his life in the plane crash of Alaska Airlines Flight 261 which crahsed on January 31 2000, including his wife and their only daughter who was surposed to be his next of kin if, You shall read more news about the crash on visiting this site: (http://www.cnn.com/2000/US/02/01/alaska.airlines.list/) and ( http://www.alaskaair.com/E_latest.asp) May their soul rest in perfect peace Amen. Be informed that no one knows about this account or any thing concerning it, the account has no other beneficiary and my investigation proved to me as well that the account is a secret account. The total amount involved is Six million Seven Hundred Thousand United States Dollars only [US$ 6,700.000.00] and we wish to transfer this money into a safe foreigners account abroad. But do not know any foreigner. I pray for your understanding. I am only contacting you as a foreigner because this money can not be approved to a local person here, but to a foreigner who has information about the account, which I shall give to you upon your positive response. God is in control. Finally, we have made arrangements upon the reciept of your readiness and confirmation of go ahead we shall distroy all documents of such mentioned person to avoid further cross check in future as I will use my position and influence to obtain all legal approvals for onward transfer of this money to your account with appropriate clearance from the relevant ministries and foreign exchange departments. I pray for your understanding. At the conclusion of this business, you will be given 25% of the total amount, 70% will be for us, while 5% will be for expenses both parties might have incurred during the process of transferring. I look forward to your earliest reply. I pray that God gives you wisdom and understanding. You can as well send to me eith through this mail or my alternative email as state (josgogo@jumpy.it) your full names and address, direct telephone and fax number for easy communication , as I seriously believes on oral communications than email . I pray for your understanding . I await your urgent response . Mr.Joseph Gogo . Alt Email: josgogo@jumpy.it PLEASE TREAT VERY URGENT . ________________________________________ Metti il faccione di Shrek sul tuo cellulare! http://www.specialeshrek.canale5.com

Dr.David Clovis (Esq.) Rue Portin X Blaize Diagne St.Louis Senegal. Email:davidchambers@katamail.com. Attention:The President/CEO. I am barrister David Clovis (Esq.), an English speaking Senegalese Solicitor & Financial Attorney/Consultant.I was the personal attorney to late Daniel Thorp who was an expatriate mining consultant/contractor with Teaser Petroleum Corporation in St Louis-Senegal.Mr. Daniel Thorp here-in-after referred as my client was also a Diamond/Gold Merchant. Mr.Daniel Thorp made a numbered time (Fixed) deposit for US$12,500,000.00 (Twelve Million Five Hundred Thousand US Dollars Only) in a bank in Dakar, capital of Senegal with standing statement/agreement with the bank that all correspondences in respect to the fixed deposit contract must be sent to him through my humble chambers. Upon maturity, the routine notification was sent to me whom I dispatched to his forwarding address as usual without no reply. After a month, I sent areminder which I received from the bank without any reply again. Finally, I discovered from my client’s contract employers- Teaser Petroleum Corporation that he died among many others in the Kenya Airways flight of 31st January, 2000 that crashed into the Atlantic Ocean in Abidjan, Cote D’Ivoire. On further investigations, I found out that he died without making any WILL and all attempts to trace his next of kin was fruitless. I also discovered that Mr. Daniel Thorp did not declare any kin or relations in all his official documents, including his fixed deposit contract with the bank in Dakar-Senegal. I am contacting you based on the official letter I just received from his bankers reminding me that Senegalese law states that at the expiration of 5 (five) years the money will revert to the ownership of the Senegalese Government if I do not confirm the next of kin to claim the fund. Consequently, my proposal is that I will like you as a foreigner to stand in as the next of kinto Mr. Daniel Thorp so that the fruits of this old man’s labor will not go into the hands of some corrupt government officials. Note that this transaction is simple and risk free because I will provide expert legal services that will guarantee the successful execution of this deal. I wish to point out that after the claims, I would want 20% of this money to be shared among charity organizations, while the remaining 80% is shared equally between us. Most importantly, I would also require your assistance towards investing my share in your country or anywhere as you may advice. If you are interested, please contact me via my email address :davidchambers@katamail.com. Upon your response, I shall provide you with more details and how we shall proceed with the claims. I expect you to observe utmost confidentiality and be rest assured that this transaction would be profitable for both of us. Awaiting your urgent reply via my email. Thanks & Regards Dr.David Clovis (Esq.) ________________________________________________________________________ Cerchi un laboratorio fotografico aperto 24 ore su 24? Stampa le tue foto digitali su Kataweb e le ricevi a domicilio in 48 ore. http://www.kataweb.it/foto

FROM THE OFFICE OF DAVID MORGAN. JOHANNESBURG. SOUTH AFRICA. E-MAIL: davidmorgan@classicmail.co.za TEL: +27-73-583-9881 ATTN: Sir/Madam, I know that this message will come to you as a surprise since we don?t know each other, but for purpose of introduction, I am DAVID MORGAN. The bank manager of AMALGAMATED BANK OF South Africa (ABSA). There is an account opened in this bank in 1982 and since 1990, nobody has operated in this account again. After going through some old files in the records, I discovered that if I do not remove this money out urgently, it would be forfeited for nothing. The owner of this account is MR. ADAMS COLEMAN, a foreigner, and a miner at Kruger gold company, a geologist by profession and he died since 1990. No other person knows about this account or anything concerning it, the account has no other beneficiary and my investigations proved to me as well that his company does not know anything about this account. The amount involved is US$18m (EIGHTEEN MILLION UNITED STATES DOLLARS). I am only contacting you as a foreigner because this money cannot be approved to a local bank here, but can only be approved to any foreign Account because the money is in US Dollars and the former owner of the account is MR. ADAMS COLMEAN is a foreigner too. I know that this message will come to you as a surprise as we don?t know ourselves before. We will sign an agreement, but be sure that it is real and a genuine business. Please reply or call me urgently so that I will inform you the next step to transfer this fund to your resident Bank Account immediately. Send also your private telephone and fax numbers including the full details of the account to be used for the deposit. I want us to meet face to face or sign a binding agreement to bind us together so that you can receive this money into a foreign account or any Account of your choice where this money will be safe. And I will fly to your country for withdrawal, sharing and other investments. I am contacting you because of the need to involve a foreigner with foreign account and foreign beneficiary. I need your full co-operation to make this work fine because the management is ready to approve this payment to any foreigner, who has correct information of this account, which I will give to you later immediately, if you are capable and willing to handle such amount in strict confidence and trust according to my instruction and advice for our mutual benefit because this opportunity will never come again in my life. I want you to be truthful in this business, because I don?t want to make mistake, I need your strong assurance and trust. With my position now in the office, I can transfer this money now to any foreigner?s reliable account, which you can provide with assurance that this money will be intact bending my physical arrival in your country for sharing. I will destroy all documents of transaction immediately you receive this money, leaving no trace to any place. You can also come to discuss with me face to face after whom I will make this remittance in your presence and two of us will fly to your country at least two days ahead of the money going into the account. I will apply for my annual Leave to get visas immediately I hear from you that you are ready to act and receive this fund in your account. I will use my position and influence to effect legal approvals and onward transfer of this money to your account with appropriate clearance forms of the ministries and foreign Exchange departments. At the conclusion of this business, you will be given 25% of the total amount, 70% will be for me, and while 5% will be for expenses both parties might Have incurred during the process of transferring. I look forward to your earliest reply through my e-mail or you give me a call through my office line. Regards, DAVID MORGAN. AMALGAMATED BANK OF SOUTH AFRICA (ABSA).

Dear Friend, This letter might come to you as a surprise since we have not had any previous correspondence nor met. This is as a result of the helpless situation I found myself into. I got your contact during my search for a reliable, capable and trustworthy person that can assist me in this darkest moment of my life. I am a native of Liberia and I lost my father, mother and two sisters with our family house during this recent war raging in Liberia. I am alive writing you now from Nigeria where I and other lucky victims who escaped alive from the rebel attack are like refugees. No house, no good food, no good job and I'm just getting assistance from well meaning individuals and a couple of Nigerians who came back from Liberia too. Before my father's sudden death, he deposited a consignment labelled as a personal effect of classified DOCUMENTS AND VALUEBLES. But consealed in it is the sum of US$5000,000.00 (Five Million US Dollars) in cash with a Private security vault overseas, which he intended to use for Politics. While my father was alive he explained to me that he had such fund and had to keep it in a security company abroad due to the unstable polity in Liberia and considering that he is a politician, he would not want the Government to seize the money if deposited into the bank in Liberia. Now that he is late and am the only surviving son, I am writing you to assist me receive this money in your country, invest it in a profitable business and help relocate me to join you immediately. As a result of insecurity of life and property here, I do not want to stay in Africa any longer. You have my permission/authority to have/collect 30% of the funds on receiving it, for your timely assistance. Please indicate your readiness to assist me immediately so that all the information about this fund will be passed to you immediately and we can execute this transaction within seven working days. Send to me immediately the following information: 1. Your full legal names including contact address 2. Your mobile telephone and fax numbers for easy communication 3. Date of birth, sex and marital status for documentation purposes. As soon as I receive your call or reply mail I shall give you further details on how and where to receive the fund on my behalf. The legal documents will also be sent to you immediately and I shall pass instructions to the security company to contact you for the delivery of the funds to you. With the help of symapatizer I was able to secure a mobile phone which is very important for me at this stage to enable me transact this important business for which I am contacting you. Please reply me immediately you receive this mail via my Private E-mail: brown--tijani@163.com. Looking forward to hearing from you, Best Regards, Brown Tijani.

>From the Desk of: DR. YINKA CRAIG. URGENT BUSINESS PROPOSAL I AM A SENIOR ACCOUNTANT WITH THE NIGERIAN LIQUIFIED NATURAL GAS (NLNG) HERE IN LAGOS. I HAVE BEEN ASSIGNED BY MY COLLEAGUES TO SEEK FOR A FOREIGN PARTNER WHO WILL ASSIST US IN THE TRANSFER OF THE SUM OF US$27.5M (TWENTY SEVEN MILLION, FIVE HUNDRED THOUSAND UNITED STATES DOLLARS). THIS MONEY AROSE FROM A DELIBERATE OVER-INVOICING OF A PARTICULAR CONTRACT AWARDED BY MY CORPORATION IN 2001. MY COLLEAGUES AND I HAVE AGREED THAT IF YOU OR YOUR COMPANY PROVIDES AN ACCOUNT FOR RECEIVING THIS MONEY, THE SHARING RATIO WILL BE THUS: 1. 60% FOR US HERE IN NIGERIA “THE OFFICIALS INVOLVED”. 2. 30% FOR YOU OR YOUR COMPANY THAT PROVIDE THE ACCOUNT. 3. 10% FOR EXPENSES INCURRED BY BOTH PARTIES IN THE COURSE OF THIS TRANSACTION. NOTE: THE NATURE OF YOUR BUSINESS IS IRRELEVANT TO THIS TRANSACTION. TO EFFECT THE TRANSFER OF THE ABOVE SUM, WE REQUIRE THE FOLLOWING FROM YOU: *YOUR NAME OR COMPANY’S NAME, ADDRESS, TELEPHONE, FAX AND TELEX NUMBERS. AND AS SOON AS THESE REQUIREMENTS ARE RECEIVED, THE MONEY WILL BE TRANSFERRED INTO YOUR ACCOUNT OR YOUR COMPANY’S ACCOUNT FOR SAFE KEEPING PENDING OUR ARRIVAL FOR SHARING. EVERY ARRANGEMENT HAS BEEN CONCLUDED FOR A SUCCESSFUL AND HITCH-FREE TRANSFER FOR THIS MONEY INTO YOUR ACCOUNT OR COMPANY’S ACCOUNT. PLEASE KEEP THIS TRANSACTION SECRET. INDICATE YOUR INTEREST IN THIS BUSINESS THROUGH THIS MAIL (ycraig2003@walla.com) NOTE: WE EXPECT YOUR IMMEDIATE RESPONSE VIA E-MAIL FOR SPEEDY TRANSACTION. FURTHER INFORMATION WILL BE CONVEYED TO YOU AS SOON AS I RECEIVE YOUR ACCEPTANCE LETTER. BEST REGARDS, DR. YINKA CRAIG. (ycraig2003@walla.com) -- No virus found in this outgoing message. Checked by AVG Anti-Virus. Version: 7.0.289 / Virus Database: 265.4.1 - Release Date: 11/19/2004

Dear Sir/Madam, Do accept my sincere apologies if my mail does not meet your personal ethics. I will introduce myself as Gordon, a staff in the accounts management section of a well-known bank here in the United Kingdom. One of our accounts with holding balance of £15,000,000(Fifteen Million British Pounds) has been dormant and has not been operated for the past 4 years. >From my investigations and confirmations, the owner of this account a foreigner by name Austin Martins died in August 2000 and since then nobody has done anything as regards the claiming of this money because he has no family members who are aware of the existence of neither the account nor the funds. Also Information from the National Immigration states that he was also single on entry into the UK. I have secretly discussed this matter with some of the bank officials and we have agreed to find a reliable foreign partner to deal with. We thus propose to do business with you, standing in as the next of kin of these funds from the deceased and funds released to you after due processes have been followed. This transaction is totally free of risk and troubles as the fund is a legitimate and does not originate from drug, money laundry, terrorism or any other illegal act. On your interest, let me hear from you. Regards, Gordon. DISCLAIMER: This message contains confidential information and is intended only for specified addressee. If you are not the named addressee you should not disseminate, distribute or copy this e-mail. The sender therefore does not accept liability for any errors or omissions in the contents of this message, which arise as a result of e-mail transmission. Please note that we reserve the right to monitor and read any emails sent and received under the Telecommunications (Lawful Business Practice) (Interception of Communications) Regulations 2000. __________________________________________________________________ Tiscali Adsl 2 Mega Free: l'adsl piu' veloce e' gratis! Naviga libero dai costi fissi con Tiscali Adsl 2 Mega Free, l'adsl Free piu' veloce in Italia. In piu', se ti abboni entro il 13 dicembre 2004, navighi gratis fino al 31 marzo 2005 e non paghi il costo di adesione. http://abbonati.tiscali.it/adsl/

CORPORATE TEL& FAX: +27-11-5075379. HOME TEL: + 871-762-535915 HOME FAX: + 871-762-535916 Email: tutu288@latinmail.com URGENT BUSINESS TRANSFER I know that this will come to you as a surprise since we don't know each other before. For the purpose of introduction, I am MR JOB TUTU the chief auditor of amalgamated bank of South Africa (ABSA). When I was going through some old files in the record I discovered that there is an account opened in this bank in 1980 and since 1990 nobody has operated on this account again. The owner of this account is Mr. Smith B Andréa's, a foreigner/contractor and a miner at Kruger gold mining Pty., a geologist by profession who died since 1991. no other person knows about this account or any thing concerning it and the account has no beneficiary and investigation on this account proves to me that his company is not aware of this account and the amount involved is US$18.3M ( Eighteen Million Three Hundred Thousand United States Dollars Only). I am only contacting you as a foreigner because this money can not be approved to a local bank account here, but can only be approved to any foreign account because the money is in us dollars and the former owner of the account Mr. Smith B. Andréa's is a foreigner too. So if you find this proposal interested kindly indicate your interest by contacting me and also send to me your private telephone and fax numbers for easy and confidential communication. Please be inform that this transaction is risk free for all arrangements on how to transfer this money to your account has be made ready because I will use my positions to get all internal documentations to back up the claims, only waiting for your approval of agreement to assist me. And for your personal assistance, you will be given 25% of the total sum while 5% will be for expenses made by both parties during the transfer and 70% will be use to establish a lucrative business/ investment for me in your country through your assistance because I cannot bring one dollar back to my country. Moreover, I need your trust and confidentiality promising you will not take advantage of the situation that makes you the beneficiary to this account and hoping that you can be able to handle such amount of money in strict confident till I come over to your country for appropriate disbursement and investment. I wait for your urgent response by Email, Call or Fax. Thanks And God Bless Yours Truly, Mr. Job Tutu 108 GRAYSTON DRIVE, SANTON CITY JHB, SOUTH AFRICA, TEL& FAX: +27-11-5075379.

FROM: MR. TONY SMITH DIRECTOR AUDIT AND ACCOUNTS UNIT, AMALGAMATED BANK OF SOUTH AFRICA (ABSA) 142,WEST STREET SANDOWN 2196 JOHANNESBURG, SOUTH AFRICA. TEL:+27-83-52-75788 E-MAIL: tonysmith115@hotmail.com Dear With due honor and respect, I introduce myself to you for a better relationship. I am Mr,TONY SMITH the Director in charge of Audit/Accounts unit, Foreign Remittance Department of AMLGAMATED BANK OF SOUTH AFRICA(ABSA). Your contact is courtesy of Business online network via Internet as I decided to contact you for this beneficial transaction that is 100% risk free. During auditing, verifications/investigations in our bank at the end of last fiscal (financial) year, I discovered the sum of (US$17.5M}SEVENTEEN MILLION FIVE HUNDRED THOUSAND UNITED STATES DOLLARS in a dormant account belonging to an Australian international businessman who died along with his family in the November 5th,2001 plane crash in Abidjan west Africa. Our investigations revealed no survival or NEXT OF KIN/RELATIONS for claims as we have long been expecting someone to forward applications for claims as it applies to our banking regulations. Information / verifications from reliable sources confirmed that his supposed ?NEXT OF KINS? died with him in the crash. Hence this for your perusals. However, I kept this information (SECRET) confidential within my jurisdiction to enable us submit claims and transfer this fund through trustworthy person whom we shall present to our bank as the BONAFIDE ?NEXT OF KIN? to the deceased. We intend to credit this fund into any of your nominated (designated) offshore bank account for investments.Meanwhile, all domestic arrangements for claims has been put in place awaiting your acceptance to participate. I will give you directives and all needed information as soon as I receive your positive response. Kindly understand that we could not carry out this on our own as based on the simple facts that we are civil servants and secluded from operating foreign account and too, it will raise eyebrows on our side in terms of transfer being staff of the bank. Moreover, this fund belongs to a foreigner and demands same as next of kin to claim it. Hence your contact for successful operation. My colleagues and I has resolved to offering you 20% of the, total sum as commission, We will invest 75% of our share in your country provided it is profit oriented. 5% of the total fund will be set aside to re-emburse all expenses to be incurred in the course of running this transaction such as telephone and other minor expenses. I am assuring you of a smooth and successful transaction provided you display maturity and observe confidentiality. And it will interest you to know that the Reserve Bank(Apex) will approve credit of this fund into your account as contract payment to abstain you from all queries regarding the source (originality) of this fund and will provide you (beneficiary) with contractual (data) details to certify your bank or government if the need arises. Therefore, be kind to clarify the following for my consideration: 1. Can your account accommodate this fund in your local bank without government intervention or do you have an account outside your country where you may consider safe for this fund ?. 2. What are taxation in your country like as I desire a low/free tax zone?. 3. What are the interest rates on long/short term fixed deposit in your local banks?. 4. What other lucrative investments would you suggest as I intend banking, real estate and hotels if they are good business venture in your Country?. 5. Can you be able to make residential documents and purchase a house for me and my family to relocate and settle in your country?. Kindly indicate your private telephone and fax number for more effeicient communication. Looking forward to your anticipated urgent response. Best regards, (MR TONY SMITH) _________________________________________________________________ Challenge your buddies with online games - get MSN Toolbar! http://messenger.msn.co.za?DI=1054&XAPID=2532

>From MrI.Kamara TEL +27 83 486 2761 DEAR , This letter was borne out of my sincere desire to establish a business/mutual relationship with you. I got your contact through the international trade and commerce (ITCC). My name is Ibram Kamara the son of late Chief Abraham P.Kamara (the former deputy minister of finance under the ousted civilian government) who was killed and mutilated by the military junta led by major, Paul Koroma after overthrowing the elected government of president Tejan. Through, I do not know to what extent you are familiar with events and disturbance in Sierra-Leone but the pressure of war drove my mother and I out of Sierra -Leone into exile in South Africa where we have been living under political asylum for years. Sadly, my mother died of cancer 2 months ago and was buried here in South Africa . Prior to her death, she handed me over a certificate meant for a secret deposit, which my father made in a security/finance company in europe the deposit that worth US$25,000,000 ( Twenty five million U.S dollars) this was the money paid to his corporation by it's overseas customers in the heat of the conflict. He made the deposit in his name and also deposited it as a family tresures, with the hope of converting it to his personal use at the end of the war but he was killed when the conflict intensified as a result of his opposition to the rebel forces. I have contracted the Security/finance Company to confirm the deposit and establish ownership. Due to the death of my Mother, I have decided to solicit for the participation of an honest and trustworthy person or company that will assist in acting as my representative who will jointly signed the agreement for the safe keeping of the money in the security/finance company. The security/finance company don't know the content of the consignment, they believe that it is African artefact. As contained in 2 trunk boxes. Unfortunately, My mum who is surpose to assist me in releasing the consignment has died of cancer that is why I am looking for your assistance. I cannot do it alone due to my present social status and total ignorance of the business world. I shall also give you 20% of the funds for your assistance to relocate this fund to your country and for re-investment while the rest will be kept in any account of your choice for inverstmant purpose. i would have done the transfer myself as my name is written as the next of kin,but because of my present status in this country as a refugee i will not be allowed to handle such money or else it will be confisticated by the goverment if found in my possetion,and also i will not be allowed to open an account as a refugee not even to talk of inversting such an amount of money,these are the reasons why i need your assistance,If you are interested in helping me out of this my present situation, contact me immediately through my email and i will funish you with other details you need to conclude this transaction.this transaction is absolutely risk free and of biliteral benefits as i have all neccesray legal documents backing it up.please get back to me with your full name,tel.no fax no and also your home addres so as to enable me introduce you to the security/finance company handling the consignment as my representative.after all these you will then make an arrangement on how we are going to meet face to face and discuss in details. Meanwhile, I cannot travel out because i have no travelling documents for now,i also hope that after everything you will secure a visa for me to join you in your country so that i can continue my studies over there. I hope to hear from you soon Best regards, MR IBRAM KAMARA _________________________________________________________________ Cut through the clutter - search faster with MSN Toolbar! http://toolbar.msn.co.za?DI=1054&XAPID=2083

Even though I walk through the darkest valley, I fear no evil; for you are with me; Your rod and your staff they comfort me. Psalm 23:4. Beloved in Christ, It is a priviledge to hear from God and it gives me joy to relate my testimony to you haven recieved instruction from God through divine revelation.I was a Moslem and a retired top officer in Estrada Government in Philippines that served under past Mr Estrada regime. I was the financial secretary to the Estrad Ruling Council in Philippines (ERC).With my position as a financial secretary, I was able to divert up to $15,000,000.00( Fifteen million U.S Dollars, into my personal Bank Account, hoping to invest the money when I am retired.Immediately I got retired, I was converted from Moslem to Christian when I was preached the words of God through my cousin Pastor HANRY FRED. I then gave my life to Christ and became a born again Christain. Since I gave my life to Christ, I had no rest of mind.Some times I think of my dubious ways I diverted my countrys money into my Personal Bank Account. I then decided to seek the face of God for forgiveness and after fasting and prayer through Divine Revelation, the Almighty God revealed to me that the only way I could have rest of mind is when I used all my money to do the work of God. I immediately disclosed my revelation to my Pastor and he was happy with me.I have been thinking of the particular thing to do for my God before this present civilian president of my country set up a panel ( Panel) to probe the Bank Account of the past Civilan officers like me. Instead of loosing this money to my Government,I quickly withdrew my money out of my Account and packed it in a Trunk before i deposited it with the finance and security company as an valuable gift for safe keeping.My Pastor has adviced me to sow this money into a ministries work abroad. I have decided to sow this money into a ministry. I am making arrangement to come over to your country but you need to receive this money as a consignment from the finance and security company in a trunk box before I come over. declared to the security company containing Valuable Gift items in a consignments trunk box and it's ready for shipment but the security company requires the address of the receiver. Please send to me your names, address and your telephone and fax number where I can fax the Airway Bill to you to I will be coming over to your Country with my family for thanks givingas soon as I sent out this money to you. Please act fast because I dont want the panel to know that intention to leave now that the probe is going on. I look forward to your response God bless you. YOURS FAITHFULLY HUGO ERIC.

Mr.Soo Cho CHO HUNG BANK. 14 1-ka Namdaemun-ro Chung-ku Seoul, Seoul 100-757 South Korea. www.chohungbank.co.kr I am Mr.Soo Cho, credit officer of CHO HUNG BANK. I have an urgent and very confidential business proposition for you. On July 8, 2000, a British Oil consultant/contractor with the South Korea Solid Minerals Corporation, Mr. Phillip Morris made a numbered time (Fixed) Deposit for twelve calendar months, valued at (Twenty-eight Million Three Hundred Thousand American Dollars only) in my branch. Upon maturity,I sent a routine notification to his forwarding address but got no reply. After a month, we sent a reminder and finally we discovered from his contract employers, that Mr. Phillip Morris died from an auto-mobile accident. On further investigation, I found out that he died without making a WILL,and all attempts to trace his next of kin was fruitless. I therefore made further investigation and discovered that Mr.Phillip Morris did not declare any kin or relations in all his official documents,including his Bank Deposit paperwork in my Bank.This sum of $28,300,000.00 is still sitting in my Bank and the interest is being rolled over with the principal sum at the end of each year. No one will ever come forward to claim it. According to Laws of South Korea, at the expiration of (five) years,the money will revert to the ownership of the South Korea Government if nobody applies to claim the fund. Consequently, my proposal is that I will like you as a foreigner to stand in as the next of kin to Mr. Phillip Morris so that the fruits of this old man's labor will not get into the hands of some corrupt government officials. This is simple, I will like you to provide immediately your full names and address so that the attorney will prepare the necessary documents and affidavits that will put you in place as the next of kin. We shall employ the services of an attorney for drafting and notarization of the WILL and to obtain the necessary documents and letter of probate/administration in your favor for the transfer. A bank account in any part of the world that you will provide the will, then facilitate the transfer of this money to you as the beneficiary/next of kin. The money will be paid into your account for us to share in the ratio of 70%for me and 25% for you and 5% for Expenses Incurred in the course of the transaction . There is no risk at all as all the paperwork for this transaction will be done by the attorney and with my position as the credit officer guarantees the successful execution of this transaction. If you are interested, please reply immediately to my email box. Upon your response, I shall then provide you with more details that will help you understand the transaction. Please send me your confidential telephone and fax numbers for easy communication. You should observe utmost confidentiality, and rest assured that this transaction would be most profitable for both of us because I shall require your assistance to invest my share in your country. Regards, Soo Cho N.B:Endeavour to send your reply through my alternative e-mail address:soo@financesource.com

Dear Sir, Is a pleasure to write you this letter, and i hope it will not be a surprised to you, i got your contact through internet connector for urgent help. I think this letter will meet your favourable considration.. I am a rebel soldier from Angola, with a rank of Major in the Army and a rebel leader as well. We have been in the bush for more than 15yrs, my name is Major John Ogari born 48 yrs ago in Angola and a member of the Angola rebel leaders committee.. The federal forces are impressing us badly that we can not have a way to be in the city, all our contacts closed. Please kindly help. Indeed, we never give up since we are fighting for good of our country as our present leaders are bad. Here is the help we urgently needed from you, we have in our custody the sum of Nine million four hundred and twenty one dollar. 9.421.000 million,dollar, with 103 kg of gold. i need your help to bank this in your account as i can not go out nor operate any account. I give you this trust as God will be in between us and you will benefit more than expected if you did not think other wise.. This can be transfered hand to hand through security company we operate with, i am hundred percent sure of that, and they will take care of the goods till it get to your hand safely. Although the secourity company did not know what is inside as we locked the money and gold inside a safe box and deposited as family treasure. There is no risky involve or distorbance easy transfer. My aim is to invest in a profitable business in your country. I hope you will help us in this our request. For further directives of how to achieve this feat. Reply and ask question if any and do not forget to furnish me with your cofidential telephone and fax number, to enable me contact you for immediate transacion. You will be made a co-beneficary to his treasure. Note that there is no risky involve in this busniess like i said earlier, and a good percentage will be given to you at end of this business. On arrival of the treasure safe to your destination i will come along with key to the safe box. Looking forward to hear from you soon. Best regard Maj. John Ogari.

FROM: MR. RICHARD WILLIAMS. 1A PRESIDENTIAL ROAD, ENUGU, ENUGU STATE NIGERIA. ATTENTION PLEASE! THIS IS NOT A SPAM MAIL: WITH ALL DUE RESPECT, I GUESS MY LETTER WILL NOT EMBARRASS YOU, SINCE I HAS NO PREVIOUS CORRESPONDENCE WITH YOU. I GOT YOUR CONTACT THROUGH THE FOREIGN TRADE OFFICE OF THE NIGERIA ASSOCIATION OF REALTORS. I STRONGLY BELIEVED, I WOULD NOT REGRET APPROACHING YOU IN THIS MATTER . IT IS MY BELIEF THAT I CANNOT CONTINUE LEAVING A MONOTONOUS AND UNAMBITOUS EXISTENCE; THE KIND OF LIFE THE HUNDREDS OF THOUSANDS OF YOUNG MEN LIVES, WHO HAVE NO PROSPECT AND WHO WILL BE DOING THE SAME THING IN ANOTHER TWENTY YEARS TIME AS THEY ARE DOING NOW. I AM MR. MR. RICHARD WILLIAMS, CHIEF AUDITOR-GENERAL CONTINENTAL TRUST BANK LIMITED, ENUGU MAIN BRANCH. ,FOR REASONS WHICH WILL COME TO LIGHT AS YOU READ ON. I OBTAINED YOUR ADDRESS PARTICULARLY FOR THE SAKE OF THIS BUSINESS PROPOSITION.PLEASE EXERCISE SOME PATIENCE AND READ THROUGH MY MESSAGE.I HAVE A VERY URGENT AND CONFIDENTIAL BUSINESS TO PROPOSE TO YOU. ON THURSDAY JUNE 6TH 2000, AN OIl CONSULTANT/CONTRACTOR WITH THE NIGERIA OIL MINISTRY, MR. YOUSEFF ABDULLAH, AN IRAQI NATIONAL,MADE A NUMBERED TIME FIXED DEPOSIT FOR TWELVE CALENDAR MONTHS, VALUE US$8 MILLION DEPOSIT IN MY BRANCH. ON MATURITY, WE SENT A ROUTINE NOTIFICATION TO HIS FORWARDING ADDRESS BUT GOT NO REPLY.AFTER A MONTH, WE SENT A REMINDER AND FINALLY, HIS EMPLOYERS,WROTE TO INFORM US THAT MR. ABDULLAH DIED IN AN AUTO MOBILE ACCIDENT. THAT HE DIED WITHOUT MAKING A WILL WHILE ATTEMPT TO TRACE HIS NEXT OF KIN THROUGH THE IRAQI EMBASSY PROVED FRUITLESS. AT FIRST, I WAS SURPRISED THAT I DID NOT RECEIVE MUCH OFFICIAL CO-OPERATION IN MY ENQUIRIES IN ORDER TO TRACE HIS KIN IN IRAQ AND INFORM THEM ABOUT MR.ABDULLAH?S DEPOSIT OF US$8.4 MIILLION PLUS ACCRUED INTEREST. FURTHER INVESTIGATION REVEALED THAT MR. ABDULLAH WAS ACTIVELY OPPOSED TO IRAQ GOVERNMENT OF LEAD BY THE FORMER PRESIDENT SADDAM HUSSEIN OF IRAQ AS A RESULT, HE WAS DRIVEN INTO EXILE. BEING AN OIL EXPERT, MR.ABDULLAH SUBSEQUENTLY OBTAINED A JOB IN NIGERIA HERE, AND SETTLED IN NIGERIA. THEREAFTER HE WALKED INTO MY OFFICE TO MAKE THE AFORE-MENTIONED DEPOSIT OF US$8 MILLION. HE DID NOT DECLARE HIS KIN IN HIS APPLICATION PAPER WORK. WHEN I ASKED HIM, HE INFORMED ME THAT HE WISHED IT SO.IN THE CONSERVATIVE MANNER OF OUR BANK. (MY EMPLOYER), I DID NOT TURN DOWN HIS WISH BUT RATHER HONOURED IT ESPECIALLY GIVEN HIS HIGH NET WORTH. IN REALITY,NO ONE KNOWS THE SOURCE OF HIS MONEY SINCE APPARENTLY, THE TIME FRAME OF HIS EMPLOYMENT HERE DOES INDEED PRECLUDE SUCH A LARGE AMOUNT OF MONEY. IT IS THEREFORE PRESUMED THAT HE BROUGHT IN HIS MONEY FROM IRAQ ALTHOUGH THIS IS OPEN TO SPECULATION. THE POINT HOWEVER IS THAT THE EMPLOYERS ARE NOT AWARE OF HIS MONEY,THEREFORE ONE CAN SAFELY INFER THAT NO ONE WILL EVER COME TO THIS MONEY. THIS FUND,TOTALLING US$8.4 M(INCLUSIVE OF ACCRUED INTEREST) IS STILL SITTING IN MY BANKS DORMANT ACCOUNT PORTFOLIO. ACCORDING TO NIGERIA BANKING LAWS AND ACT OF 1993,THE MONEY WILL AUTOMATICALLY REVERT TO THE NIGERIA GOVERNMENT TREASURY AFTER FIVE YEARS, ESPECIALL IF THE ACCOUNT OWNER IS A FOREIGNER WHO HAS BEEN CERTIFIED DEAD AND THERE IS NO VALID CLAIM, THIS INDEED, IS THE SITUATION. I AM THUS LOOKING FOR A FOREIGNER WHO WILL STAND-IN AS THE NEXT OF KIN TO MR. ABDULLAH.IT IS NOT NECESSARY TO BE A BLOOD RELATION TO MR.ABDULLAH, EITHER IS IT NECESSARY TO BEAR THE SAME SURNAME WITH HIM. IT IS EVEN NOT IMPORTANT FOR THE STAND-IN NEXT OF KIN TO BE AN IRAQ NATIONAL.READY, I HAVE WORKED OUT MODALITIES FOR ACHIEVING MY AIM OF APPOINTING A NEXT OF KIN AS WELL AS TRANSFER THE MONEY ABROAD FOR US TO SHARE. IT IS MY INTENTION TO ACHIEVE THIS TRANSFER IN A LEGITIMATE WAY BY SIMPLY USING AND ATTORNEY(REPRESENTING YOU AS BENEFICIARY) TO EXECUTE A SERIES OF AFFIDAVITS IN SUPPORT OF YOUR CLAIM THIS WILL BE APPROVED. THE MONEY TRANSFER PAPER WORK ITSELF WILL INCLUDE A CERTIFICATE OF ORIGIN SO THAT THE RECEIVING BANK DOES NOT ASK QUESTION OR WORSE STILL REFUSE THE FUND ACCEPTANCE ON GROUND OF LAUNDERING. ALSO, THE PAPER WORK WILL INCLUDE PROPER CERTIFICATION THAT THE FUND BEING TRANSFERRED IS FROM NON-CRIMINAL SOURCES.IN SHORT THIS WILL BE A PROPER AND LEGAL MONEY TRANSFER WITH APPARENTLY NO RISK INVOLVED! THE ATTORNEY WILL HAVE TO PROCESS THE INITIAL PAPER WORK TO OBTAIN APPROVAL FROM THE PROBATE REGISTRY OF THE MINISTRY OF JUSTICE FOR THE LETTER OF ADMINISTRATION EMPOWERING YOU AS THE SOLE TRUSTEE/EXECUTOR TO THE ESTATE OF MR. ABDULLAH. IF YOU THEREFORE AGREE TO BE THE OFFICIAL BENEFICIARY,THEN PLEASE NOTE THAT YOU WILL NOT BE REQUIRED TO SIGN ANY MONEY RANSFER DOCUMENTS, AS THE APPOINTED ATTORNEY WILL DO ALL THAT. ALSO, YOU WILL NOT BE REQUIRED TO VISIT NIGERIA.I WILL ALSO NEED THE ABOVE INFORMATION ONCE I HAVE THE REQUIRED INFORMATION AS ABOVE, I WILL INITIATE THE PROCESSING OF THE TRANSFER, AND IN ABOUT TEN (10)WORKING DAYS, THE FUND WILL BE IN YOUR NOMINATED BANK ACCOUNT FOR US TO SHARE IN THE RATIO OF: 65%FOR ME 30% FOR YOU WHILE 5% HAS BEEN SET ASIDE FOR LOCAL AND INTERNATIONAL EXPENSES. THE TRANSACTION IS GUARANTEED TO SUCCEED WITHOUT ANY PROBLEMS. AS SOON AS I HEAR FROM YOU, I SHALL PROVIDE YOU WITH FURTHER CLARIFICATION THAT YOU MAY NEED. I LOOK FORWARD TO YOUR URGENT REPLY. BEST WISHES, MR. RICHARD WILLIAMS NOTE:IN THE EVENT YOU ARE NOT WILLINGLY TO ASSIST, KINDLY NOTIFY ME TO PREVENT ME FROM MAKING FURTHER CONTACT.

Dear friend, It is indeed my pleasure to write to you this letter, which I believe will be a suprise,as we are both complete strangers. As you read this, I don't want you to feel sorry for me, because I believe everyone will die someday. My name is Miguel Wayne, a former merchant in Dubai, in the U.A.E. I have been diagnosed with Esophageal cancer which was discovered very late, due to my laxity in caring for my health. It has defiled all forms of medicine, and right now I have only about a few months to live, according to medical experts. I have not particularly lived my life so well, as I never really cared for anyone not even myself but my business.Though I am very rich, I was never generous,I was always hostile to people and only focus on my business as that was the only thing I cared for,but now I regret all this as I now know that there is more to life than just wanting to have or make all the money in the world. I believe when I have a second chance to come to this world I would live my life a different way from how I had lived it, now that it is dark for me, I have willed and given most of my properties and assets to my immediate and extended family members and as well as a few close friends. To correct my wrong past life, I have decided to give alms to charity organizations,as I want this to be one of the last good deeds I do on earth. So far, I have distributed money to some charity organizations in the U.A.E, Algeria and Malaysia. Now that my health has deteriorated so badly,I cannot do this my self anymore. I once asked members of my family to close one of my accounts and distribute the money which I have there to charity organization in Bulgaria and Pakistan, they refused and kept the money to themselves. Hence, I do not trust them anymore, as they seem not to be contended with what I have left for them. The last of my money which no one knows of is the huge cash deposit of four million dollars that I have with a Fiducial Company Abroad, I will want you to help me collect this deposit and dispatched it to charity organizations and you must be sending me informations of how it was disbursed either by email or otherwise . I have set aside 10% for you for your time and patience. Thanks. Miguel Wayne. NB Please do not share my email addess with anyone as I have received some emails from some unscrupulos people claiming to be charity organisations and other weird stories. NOTE:You must reply this mail to me through : miguelwayne@velocall.com for the above reasons I have told you about. ------------------------------------------------- sent by Excite Inbox - http://inbox.excite.co.uk powered by Excite UK - http://www.excite.co.uk

From: SUSAN TIJANI Attn: President/ Director Dear, I am SUSAN TIJANI the only daughter of late former Director of finance, Chief Vincent R. TIJANI of Sierra-Leone diamond and mining corporation. I must confess my agitation is real, and my words is my bond,in this proposal. My late father diverted this money meant for purchase of ammunition, for my country,during the peak of disastrous civil war in my country, now he I am residing under political Assylum with my younger brother LAWRENCE TIJANI who is 18 years old,Now the war in my country is over with the help of ECOMOG soldiers, the present government of Sierra Leone has revoked the passport of all officers who served under the former regime and now ask countries to expel such person at the same time freeze their account and confiscate their asset, it is on this note that I am contacting you, all I needed from you is to furnish me with your bank particulars: 1) Account name 2) Account number 3) Bank address, telephone and fax number 4) your private telephone /fax numbers For you to assist me transfer this money in your private bank account, the said amount is Eleven Million Dollars (US$11.000.000.00 Million).I am compensating you with 20 % of the total money amount, now all my hope is banked on you and I really wants to invest this money in your country, were their is stability of Government, political and economic welfare.Honestly I want you to believe that this transaction is real and never a joke. My late father Chief Vincent gave me the deposit slip issued to him by the BANK on the date of deposit, for you to be clarify because, I do not expose my self to anybody I see, I believe that you are able to keep this transaction secret for me because this money is the hope of my life, it is important. Please write me immediately after you must have gone through my message fill free and make it urgent. That is the reason why I offered you 20 % of the total money amount, and in case of any other necessary expenses you might incure, I am resolving to give you an addition of 5% during this transaction. N.B Try and negotiate for me some profitable blue chip investment opportunities which is risky free which I can invest with this money when it is transferred to your account, personally I am interested in estate management and hotel business, please advise me. And promise me and my younger brother to be our guardian considering our situation and not to betray us. And my late father used me the only daughter as the beneficiary / next of kin on the day of deposit and also told me I need an assistance of a foreigner with a egitimate bank Account abroad who will stand as co-beneficiary and partner abroad to ensure a successful hitch free transfer of the fund abroad. Thanks and God bless. Yours truly, SUSAN TIJANI ________________________________________ Metti il faccione di Shrek sul tuo cellulare! http://www.specialeshrek.canale5.com

MR KENNY COLUBAN, NO,542 YOFF RUE, DAKAR-SENEGAL, TEL.00221 1692 7750, FAX.00221 1864 2389 , E-MAIL.kencolubanjr@yahoo.com.(or)zam_zam20002000@yahoo.com INVESTMENT ASSISTANCE AND PARTNERSHIP. ------------------------------------------------------- Dear Sir/MAdam. I wish to introduce myself to you. I am Mr.KENNY COLUBAN. the managing Director (LIZNETINVESTMENT ),And also the son of Chief.WILLIAMS COLUBAN. from IVORY COAST,ABIJAN,in west africa ,So my father instruct me to look for an foreign pertner who is going to be trustworthy and God infearing who will able to help us in investment assistance in his/her company or if it is not ok for your company,you just look for stuitable business in your country ,And i got you contact while i was searching at the net ,i came across it your mail address i decided to mail you , and i will be well pleade for your assistance and now we are in senegal -Dakar doing business in Dakar ,so we deceided to move over to europe for a investment . And my father map out about 5,000,000USD ( five million usD) for a investment in any european,And in west africa we have about three branch office,The Gambia,Abijan ivory coast and Senegal-Dakar. And another things we want you to do ,if you will able to assist us,And what we want from you is to just open an acount were the money for the investment ,you will send me letter of invitation to come over for the investment,And why we want to move to european for an investment is because of political reason in Africa. At the conclusion of this business you will be given 25% of the total amount while 60% will be for me and my family while 5% will be for expenses both parties may incure in the course of making this transaction succesful. However, if you are not disposed to assist kindly destroy the letter in view of the families interest and personal security. I count on you greatly for your assistance.Please,if where i contacted you is not okay with you,do not hestiate to tell me and provide another address where i will be contacting you.A good percentage awaits you for your assistance. Expecting to hear from you soon. Yours Faithfully, MR.KENNEY COLUBAN JR. __________________________________ Do you Yahoo!? Yahoo! Mail - Easier than ever with enhanced search. Learn more. http://info.mail.yahoo.com/mail_250

FROM:MR.ALEX JOMOH #505 LOUISE BORTHA,ROAD JOHANNESBURG,SOUTH AFRICA TEL:27-73-179 -0425. EMAIL:alexjomoh0007@hotmail.com KINDLY ATTEN:THE DIRECTOR/CEO APPEAL FOR ASSISTANCE. With warm heart I offer my friendship, and greetings and I hope this mail meets you in good time. However strange or surprising this contact might seem to you, as we have not met personally nor had any dealings in the past, I humbly ask that you take due consideration of its importance and immense benefit. I also sincerely seek your confidence, as I make this request to you as a person of integrity. However,First and foremost I wish to introduce myself properly to you. my name is Mr.Alex Jomoh ,the elder son of Mr. Jomoh.c.Benard of Zimbabwe.This might be a suprise to you about where i got your contact address.Igot your address from a reliable source here in Johnnesburg ,South Africa in South African Information Exchange. During the current war against the farmers in Zimbabwe from the supporters of our President. Robert Mugabe to claim all the white -owned farms to his party members and his followers,he ordered all the white farmers to surrender all their farms to his party members and his followers. My father being one of the few rich and successful black farmers in our country was also victimised because of his opposition to Mugabe's policies. And because he did not support Mugabe's ideas,Mugabe's supporters invaded my fathers farm and burnt everything in the farm,killing my father and made away with a lot of items in my father's farm. However with the benefit of hingsight, owing to the looming but deteriorating crisis in my country Zimbabwea,my father had, before his unfurtunate death deposited with one of the Security Company in Johannesburg , SOUTH AFRICA the sum of US$18 Million (EIGHTEEN MILLION UNITED DOLLARS )After the death of my father,we decided to move to the Republic of South Africa where he had deposited the money in the Security Company as valuables. So I decided to contact overseas firms and individuals that will assist me to move this money out of South Africa because, as asylum seekers we are not allowed to operate any bank accont within South Africa.We have agreed to offer 15% of the total sum for your assistance,5% will mapped out for any expenses that may be incurred in the course of this transaction and 80% will be for me and my family to Invest in your country. Please,I need the following clarifications from you: 1. Would taxation be much in your country as I desire a low/free tax zone. 2.What other lucrative businesses would you suggest as I intend Real Estate,tourism as well as industry and production or our farming business investments?. 3. What are your Government incentives to foreign investors in your locality?. I am believing that you will be sincere enough and of good assistance to me in this issue All I want you to do is to furnish me with your entire details including your readiness to assist me achieve this transaction for investment purposes in your country under your supervision.You can contact me on the above telephone or email address for further details on how to achieve this transaction. Note that this transaction is 100% risk free and should be treated with absolute confidentiality. PLEASE NOTE CONTACT ME ON MY ALTERNATIVE EMAIL ADDRESS AS SOON AS POSSIBLE, EMAIL:alexjomoh_za2002@yahoo.com Thanks and God bless. Best regards Mr.Alex Jomoh.(for the family).

Kindly permit me the opportunity to narrate my ordeal to you and as such seek your understanding in my proposal to you as below. I am WILLIAMS WRETCHER the only son of the special Adviser on finance and Economic planning to Mr. Charles Taylor, erstwhile president of Liberia. My father Prince Dada Fidaye Wretcher the Special Adviser to Charles Taylor was killed in the renewed war alongside my mother all this because of the tussle for power in Liberia as reported by international media. During the heat of the war in Liberia recently, immediately the opposition group killed my father, the Nigerian president offered Asylum to Charles Taylor with some of his [[Charles Taylor] aides and Loyalist to be in Nigeria as a ? Peace Map? to the Liberia Crisis and the American president did approve of the above as he stated during his five working day visit to Africa upon this, I succeeded in coming to Nigeria where I am presently as a refugee in the refugee camp in Oru, Ogun- State, Nigeria . The above because of the serious war in Liberia and all my father?s houses, properties burnt and his bank accounts frozen by the Liberia Warriors who have taken over power. However, my father told me of some fund he deposited in a security trust service company in Europe before his death and he handed over all the document and information to me which are with me here in Nigeria Secretly and the funds were moved through diplomatic means to Europe as African Artifacts contained in the security box. The total amount inside is US $12 Million and all I need from you at this point is your acceptance to help me claim the consignment deposited by my late father. I also require your utmost sincerity and faithfulness in working with me to get the consignment claimed and the funds deposited in your account while I meet with you in your country on completion of the transaction to get my share and invest it in a viable business over there based on your advise and for me to start a new life alone as an Orphan. You will get 10% of the sum for your assistance while 5% will be for expenses incurred for traveling, communication and other miscellaneous items. You are to respond to me urgently with your direct telephone number and personal details to enable me forward the complete procedures and modalities to you. Once again I solicit for your understanding cooperation and urgent response please, I am in pains here. You can as well reach me via my alternative mailboxes: williams_wretcher@movemail.com as above Yours in need, WILLIAMS WRETCHER ----------------------------------------- Kunjungi pusat informasi Batam. http://www.ibatam.com/

HANG SENG BANK LTD. DES VOEUX RD. BRANCH, CENTRAL HONG KONG, HONG KONG. Dear Sir, Let me start by introducing myself. I am Mr. Wang Qin credit officer of the Hang Seng Bank Ltd. I have a concealed business suggestion for you.Before the U.S and Iraqi war our client General. Ibrahim Moussa who was with the Iraqi forces and also business man made a numbered fixed deposit for 18 calendar months, with a value of Twenty millions Five Hundred Thousand United State Dollars only in my branch.Upon maturity several notice was sent to him, even during the war early this year. Again after the war another notification was sent and still no response came from him. We later find out that the General and his family had been killed during the war in bomb blast that hit their home.After further investigation it was also discovered that Gen. Ibrahim Moussa did not declare any next of kin in his official papers including the paper work of his bank deposit. And he also confided in me the last time he was at my office that no one except me knew of his deposit in my bank. So, Twenty millions Five Hundred Thousand United State Dollars is still lying in my bank and no one will ever come forward to claim it. What bothers me most is that according to the to the laws of my country at the expiration 4 years and 6months the funds will revert to the ownership of the Hong Kong Government if nobody applies to claim the funds. Against this backdrop, my suggestion to you is thatI will like you as a foreigner to stand as the next of kin to Gen.Ibrahim Moussa so that you will be able to receive his funds. WHAT IS TO BE DONE: I want you to know that I have had everything planned out so that we shall come out successful. I have contacted an attorney that will prepare the necessary document that will back you up as the next of kin to Gen. Ibrahim Moussa, all that is required from you at this stage is for you to provide me with your Full Names and Address so that the attorney can commence his job. After you have been made the next of kin, the attorney will also fill in for claims on your behalf and secure the necessary approval and letter of probate in your favor for the move of the funds to an account that will be provided by you.There is no risk involved at all in the matter as weare going adopt a legalized method and the attorney will prepare all the necessary documents. Please endeavor to observe utmost discretion in all matters concerning this issue. Once the funds have been transferred to your nominated bank account we shall share in the ratio of 70% for me, 25% for you and 5% for any expenses incurred during the course of this operation. Should you be interested please send me your private phone and fax numbers for easy communication and I will provide you with more details of this operation. Your earliest response to this letter will be appreciated. Kind Regards, Mr. Wang Qin ___________________________________________________________________________ Message composé depuis le module WebMail de REA S2 - http://www.reas2.ch/

Dear Good day!!. Compliments of the day and my best wishes to you and family!!!. I know this letter will come to you surprisingly but let it not be a surprise to you, for nature has a way of arriving unannouced and an adage says 'originals are very hard to find but their echo sounds louder'. So, I decided to contact you myself for you to assure me of safety and honesty if I have to entrust any amount of money under your custody. I am Mr Micheal Bangura, the son of late Mr Thaimu Bangura who was the minister of finance in Sierra leone but was killed during the civil war. Knowing your country as being economical condusive for investment and your people as transperant and trustworthy to engage in business on which premise I write you. Before my father death, he had the sum of twenty-three million united states dollars(us$23,000,000.00) which he kept away from the rebel leaders during the course of the war and deposited it in a security company for saftey and safe-keeping. this fund was supposed to be used for rehabilitation of water reserves all over the country before the outbreak of war. when the war broke out, the rebel leader demanded that this fund be given to him, my father insisted that the money was not in his possesion but he was killed because of his refusal to release the fund. Meanwhile my mother and i is the only person who knows about this fund,because my father always confide in me since i am the only child in the family.When my father was killed,I quickly made an arrangemnt with a red cross rellief worker who used his official van to move me and my mother to lungi airport in freetownfor our safety because the rebels also wanted to kill us too. The fund was deposited by my late father as a family inheritance with a safe relaible security company in Dakar senegel where I was only given temporary asylum with my mother.I do not want to invest this money in senegel due to unfavourable economic climate and so close to my country. Also, I still kept this money also for security reasons as the present administration is investigating the existence of such fund of which I denied knowledge of it, claiming that my father did not tell me about such money. The only assistance I need from you which i believe you would do for me are the following: 1.Assist me invest this money in your country when it is release to you on our behalf by the security company. 2.Assure me that you will not sit on my share when this fund gets to your country. You will have 15% of the money for yourself as you guide me further to invest the remaining 80% in any valueble business venture while 5% is earmarked to cover expenses contingencies. Most importantly, i will like to buy a personal house where i and my mother will reside.Upon confirmation of your interest to help me as my foreign partner to invest this money, i will link you the details of this transaction to be scheduled in your favo ur by the security company. While thanking you for your anticipated understanding and cooperation, I look forward to your urgent response. please note that this transaction is strictly confidential and must be treated with utmost secrecy. Best regards, Mr. Micheal Bangura. Please you can contact me on this E-mail Address mbangura@worldemail.com

>From The Desk of Mr.Haitham Sharaff. Manager National Bank of Abu Dhabi Dubai Unted Arab Emirate (U.A.E.) Email:sharaff3@simbamail.fm I am Mr.Haitham Yousuf Branch Manager National Bank of Abu Dhabi), I have urgent and very confidential business proposition for you. A British Oil consultant and contractor with the Kruger Gold Company, Mr.Remond Beck made a numbered time (Fixed) Deposit for twelve calendar months, valued at US$12,000,000.00 (Twelve Million United State Dollars ) in my branch. Upon maturity, I sent a routine notification to his forwarding address but got no reply. After a month, we sent a reminder and finally we discovered from his contract employers, the Kruger Gold Company that Mr. Raymond Beck died in a plane crash along with his wife Mr. and Mrs. Remond Beck died in a plan crash along with his wife in Egypt Air Flight 990, 1999 air crash (for more information about this crash and person you can contact this website: http://www.s-t.com/daily/11-99/11-02-99/d08ho174.htm Since we got this information about his death and on further investigation, I found out that he died without making a WILL, and all attempts to trace his next of kin was fruitless. I therefore made further investigation and discovered that Mr. Remond Beck did not declare any kin or relations in all his official documents, including his Bank Deposit paperwork in my Bank. This sum of US$12,000,000.00 is still sitting in my Bank and the interest is being rolled over with the principal sum at the end of each year. No one will ever come forward to claim it. According to Laws of United Arab Emirates, at the expiration of 7 (seven) years, the money will revert to the ownership of the (U.A.E) Government if nobody applies to claim the fund. Consequently, my proposal is that I will like you as a foreigner to stand in as the next of kin to Mr. Remond Beck so that the fruits of this old man's labor will not get into the hands of some corrupt government officials. This is simple, I will like you to provide immediately your full names and address so that the attorney will prepare the necessary documents and affidavits that will put you in place as the next of kin. We shall employ the services of an attorney for drafting and notarization of the WILL and to obtain the necessary documents and letter of probate/ administration in your favor for the transfer. A bank account in any part of the world that you will provide will then facilitate the transfer of this money to you as the beneficiary/next of kin. The money will be paid into your account for us to share in the ratio of 60% for me and 40% for you. There is no risk at all as all the paperwork for this transaction will be done by the attorney and my position as the Branch Manager guarantees the successful execution of this transaction. If you are interested, please reply immediately via the private email address above. Upon your response, I shall then provide you with more details and relevant documents that will help you understand the transaction. Please send me your confidential telephone and fax numbers for easy communication. Please observe utmost confidentiality, and rest assured that this transaction would be most profitable for both of us because I shall require your assistance to invest my share in your country. Awaiting your urgent reply via my confidential email address. Regards. Mr.Haitham Sharaff.

FROM THE DESK OF BILL AND EXCHANGE MANAGER, DR. EJIMEGO  ALOTA, BANQUE INTERNATIONALE DE ABIJAN. ABIJAN,COTE D, IVOIRE.

ATTN I am the manager of bill and exchange at the foreign remittance department of Banque internationale de Abidjan (BIAO). I am writing following the impressive information about you through my research from your country directory. its assured me of your capability and reliability to champion this businees opportunity. In my departmentn i discovered an abandoned sum of $11.5m US dollars eleven million, five hundred thousand U.S dollars) . In an account that belongs to one of our foreign customer who died along with his entire family in a concord plane crash in the year 2000 in paris that almost took the whole life of the pasengeres on board Since we got information about his death, we have been expecting his next of kin to come over and claim his money because we cannot release unless somebody applies for it as next of kin or relation to the deceased as indicated in our banking guidelines but unfortunately we learnt that all his supposed next of kin or relation died alongside with him at the plane crash leaving nobody behind for the claim. It is therefore upon this discovery that I now decided to make this businness proposal to you and release the money to you as the next of kin or relation to the deceased for safety and subsequent disbursement since nobody is coming for it and we don't want this money to go into the Bank treasury as unclaimed Bill. The Banking law and guideline here stipulates that if such money remained unclamed after three years, the money will be transfered into the Bank treasury account as unclaimed fund. The request of foreigner as next of kin in this business is occasioned by the fact that the customer was a foreigner and an Ivoirean cannot stand as next of kin to a foreigner.I agree that 30 % of this money will be for you as foreign partner, in respect to the provision of a foreign account, 10% will be set aside for expenses incured during the business and 60 % would be for me . There after I will visit your country for disbursement accoding to the percentages indicated. Therefore to enable the immediate trnansfer of this fund to you as arranged, you must apply first to the bank as relations or next of kin of the deceased indicating your bank name, your bank account number, your private telephone and fax number for easy and effective communication and location where the money will be remitted . Upon receipt of your reply, I will send to you by fax or email the text of the application. I will not fail to bring to your notice that this transaction is risk free and that you should not entertain any atom of fear as all required arrangements have been made for the transfer . You should contact me immediately as soon as you receive this letter. Trusting to hear from you immediately. Yours faithfully, DR. EJIMEGO  ALOTA  .[bill and exchange manager bib] Private line (0022507537741 . N/B.my intention of writing you through email is because i belive it is very Confidential

Do you Yahoo!? The all-new My Yahoo! – Get yours free!

As list administrator, your authorization is requested for the following mailing list posting: List: Researchers@lists.si.UM From: william_k@o2.pl Subject: reply me soon Reason: Post by non-member to a members-only list At your convenience, visit: http://lists.si.UM/mailman/admindb/researchers to approve or deny the request.

Dear Friend,

      Greetings to you,With warm heart I offer my friendship, and greetings, and I hope this mail meets you in good time. However strange or surprising this contact might seem to you as we have not met personally or had any dealings in the past, I humbly ask that you take due consideration of its importance and the immense benefit it will be to you.

     After careful consideration with my children, we resolved to contact you for your most needed assistance on this mutually beneficial and riskfree transaction which i hope you will give your urgent attention. I duly apologize for infringing on your privacy, if this contact is not acceptable to you, as I make this proposal to you as a person of integrity. First and foremost I wish to introduce myself properly to you.

   I  am Mr.William Koroma  I am moved to write you this letter, this was inconfidence considration,for our present circumstances and situation, i escaped with my wife and children out of Sierrial-Leone to The Nedelands through the aid of the United Nations Evacuation Team where we are now presently residing on temporary political asylum.

     However, due to this situation I decided to change most of my Billions of  Dollars deposited in Swiss Bank and other countries into other forms of money coded for safe purpose because the new head of state Ahmed Tijjan Kabba made arrangement with the Swiss Goverment and other European countries to freeze all my treasures deposited in some european countries, hence i and my wife along with my children,decided laying low in this our tempoery political asylum camp here in Grou Jirnssum in the Nedelands to study the situation till when things gets better, since president Tijjan Kabba taking over goverment again in Sierria Leone. One of my chateaux in Southern France was confiscated by the French Goverment, and as such we had to change  our identity so that our investment will not be trace and confiscated.

  I  have deposited the sum of Twenty-eight Million Dollars only{US$28,000,000.00} with a security company for safekeeping.

  The funds are security coded to prevent them from knowing the actual content .  What I want you to do now is to indicate your inetrest that you will assist me and my immediate family by receiving the money on our behalf.

     The  Account required for this project can be personal, company or an offshore account that you have  total control over, your area of specialisation will not be a hinderance to the successful execution of this transaction.    Ackowledge this message, so that I can introduce you to my family as our foreign trusted partner who shall take charge of our investment abroad where we now plan to settle.

    I want you to assist us in investing this money,but I will not want  our identity revealed. I will also want to buy properties and stocks in multy- national companies and to engage in other safe and non speculative investments.

   We have been through a lot of health and spiritual turmoil, hence will need  your understanding and assistance.    May I at this junction emphasize the  high level of confidentiality which this business demands and hope you will not betral the trust and confidence which we repose in you.I  shall put you in the picture of this buiness, i.e tell you where the funds are currently being maintained and also discuss other modalities including remuneration for your services.

   I   shall also inform you with the next line of action as soon as i receive your response.Is this preposition is attainable? If it is, Please kindly funish me immediately by E-mail with your direct telephone number and fax number to enhance the confidentiality which this business demands.

  Best Regards, Mr.William Koroma

If you reply to this message, keeping the Subject: header intact, Mailman will discard the held message. Do this if the message is spam. If you reply to this message and include an Approved: header with the list password in it, the message will be approved for posting to the list. The Approved: header can also appear in the first line of the body of the reply.

MRS. SAMBU LIZZY DANANI REFUGEE CAMP C/O ROCK OF AGES EVANGELICAL MINISTRY Accra,Ghana Hello Please, With the best compliments of the year, I wish to solicit your help in migrating to your country and investing my funds. I am a Sierra Leonean National and the wife of late Dr. SIMON SAMBU. Until his death, my husband was the General overseer of the Gold and Diamond Mining Corporation in Kanema Sierra Leone. During the crisis the military forces loyal to the Government of AHMED TIJAN KABBAH invaded the Diamond and Gold mine and assassinated my husband, mistaking him for his brother MR.MIKE SAMBU who is the deputy to the leader of the Revolutionary United Front (RUF ) FODAY SANKOH. When the news reached me, I hurriedly gathered some valuables in our family villa and escaped for my dear life in the company of my only son SILAS SAMBU and left some other valuables since I was in a haste and lost some. Among the valuables I collected was a file that contained details of a Deposit in a Vault my husband made in a security company in Europe. He deposited US$8M (Eight Million U.S Dollars) contained in one box in the name of our son SILAS SAMBU. He did not disclose the real contents of the Box to the Security Company. He Declared the contents as Family Valuables for safety reasons. This is the money he made from the sale of Gold and diamonds during his time as the General overseer. Now that we are in Accra,Ghana and verified the transaction, we need your assistance to move this funds out of the security company for investment in your country as we cannot invest here due to its nearness to our country and the insecurity still going on there. We ask you to scout for a viable and lucrative business, so that we can invest wisely. We have it in mind to give you 10% of the total sum of (8 million US Dollars), and 12% share for you in any investment we will embark upon with our share of 90% if you assist us. We will also set aside 5% of the funds for ancillary expenses which you will make in course of this transaction. This fortune of ours we have revealed to you should remain CONFIDENTIAL as it is only you who we have told about it. Kindly indicate your interest and willingness to assist us on receipt of this message for us to clarify you on how to proceed. Note that this transaction is risk free. May the shelter and care of God be upon you as you assist us. Remain blessed. Yours Sincerely, MRS.SAMBU LIZZY Do respond to me through the e-mail address below; sambulizzy5@hotmail.com

FROM:THE DESK OF THE ACCOUNTANT OF ICONSHORE INVESTMENT AND FINANCE BANK.. ATTENTION : REQUEST FOR BUSINESS RELATIONSHIP. Dear Sir/madam, I am Mr.Donald Gage, credit officer of IconShore Investment & Finance Bank.I have an urgent and very confidential business proposition for you.On June 6, 2002, a British Oil consultant/contractor with the Chinese Solid Minerals Corporation,Mr.David Huckerby made a numbered time (Fixed) Deposit for twelve calendar months, valued at US$28,000,000.00 (Twenty-eight Million Dollars only) in my branch.Upon maturity,I sent a routine notification to his forwarding address but got no reply. After a month, we sent a reminder and finally we discovered from his contract employers, the Hong Kong Solid Minerals Corporation that Mr. David Huckerby died from an automobile accident. On furtherinvestigation, I found out that he died without making a WILL, and allttempts to trace his next of kin was fruitless.I therefore made further investigation and discovered that Mr.David Huckerby did not declare any kin or relations in all his official documents, including his Bank Deposit paperwork in my Bank. This sum ofUS$28,000,000.00 is still sitting in my Bank and the interest is being rolled over with the principal sum at the end of each year. No one will ever come forward to claim it. According to Laws of Iconshore Bank,at the expiration of 5(five) years, the money will revert to the ownership of the Federal Government,if nobody applies to claim the fund.Consequently, my proposal is that I will like you as a foreigner to stand in as the next of kin to Mr. David Huckerby so that the fruits of this old man's labor will not get into the hands of some corrupt government officials. This is simple, I will like you to provide immediately your full names and address so that the attorney will prepare the necessary documents and affidavits that will put you in place as the next of kin.We shall employ the services of an attorney for drafting and notarization of the WILL and to obtain the necessary documents and letter of probate/administration in your favor for the transfer. A bank account in any part of the world that you will provide will then facilitate the transfer of this money to you as the beneficiary/next of kin. The money will be paid into your account for us to share in the ratio of 70% for me and 25% for you and 5% for expenses incurred in the course of the transaction.There is no risk at all,as all the paperwork for this transaction will be done by the attorney and with my position as the credit officer guarantees the successful execution of this transaction. If you are interested, please reply immediately to my personal email box: your response, I shall then provide you with more details and relevant documents that will help you understand the transaction. Please send me your confidential email and fax numbers for easy communication as my spoken english is not very good. You should observe utmost confidentiality, and rest assured that this transaction would be most profitable for both of us because I shall require your assistance to invest my share in your country.Awaiting your urgent reply. Thanks and regards Mr.Donald Gage.

From:Mike Rossman E-MAIL:mikefamily11@netscape.net TEL:27 73 268 8646 To err is human they say and to forgive is divine; but how do you start to forgive the killers of your younger brother if you do not know who the faceless persons are and if you are still living in fear of them? I am Mike, Simba Rossman's son; I'm a student at the University of Cape Town in South Africa where my two brothers and I were schooling; In line with the prevailing festive seasons, I feel it is not out of order to wish you and yours a happy festive season and God's blessings and abundance in this year. My younger brother was was pushed in front of an oncoming train that crushed the life out of his young body. We know he was murdered because my other brother and I have also had attempts made on our lives twice now and we have told our father about it. Kindly allow me digress a little bit, I am not telling you all of this to scare you please, I made my mind over and decided to write to you after having given much thought to our situation; My Father Dr. Simba Rossman, was the former Minister of Finance and Economic Development in Zimbabwe under the Government of Mugabe, his so called policies were not too popular with the other zombie-like cronies of our so-called president who openly questioned his loyalty to Mugabe. That was when the problems all started, he got death threats from people we did not know but suspected to be party loyalists, his car was burnt on one occasion when we were on a visit in Zimbabwe last year. The police did not even bother trying to investigate the matter; Mugabe finally removed him for openly and honestly declaring to the world that Zimbabwe faced a major and crippling food crisis at the height of the state-sponsored illegal land invasions. My younger brother varnished from our flat in Cape Town one afternoon and his body was found drugged and battered and all through his life he never smoked a stick of cigarette, not even a stimulant. It was obvious that die-hard supporters of Mugabe murdered him to spite or break my father's spirit, for my father loved him the most like we did. This brings me back to why I write you; I write to solicit for your help. My father was a successful businessman before he was called to serve in Mugabe's cabinet and he had business interests all over Africa, over here in South Africa our family has US$14.7 Million held in trust on our behalf by a Holden Agency, this was made possible by our father years ago with the help of his advisor who runs a finance company based here in South Africa. According to my father, the deposit was not made in his name but in the name of a company that was registered by him and leaving room for another partner with 82% controlling shares in the business; then the business was registered both in South Africa and in Zimbabwe, so that no one can claim that he was the owner of the money. My father cannot travel down to South Africa as he is being watched by agents of the state back home, he consulted with his advisor who is in South Africa and came up with this idea to help claim the funds and ferry my brother and I out of South Africa to a place of relative safety like the United States or England where we can continue with either schooling or working. If you decide to assist us, you will be required to discuss with us on Tel:2773 268 8646: we has been authorized by our father to open discussions with you if you signify your interest in assisting us. I can also be contacted on my via e-mail address Currently, my brother and I are living in South Africa and after deliberating with our father, he sees no need for us to return to Zimbabwe. Please note that by your offering to assist us we will on your contacting us by phone or Fax, discuss a suitable compensation for you and also I would like to mention too that this transaction must be conducted within a legal framework as we have our father's good name to protect and another major thing I demand from you is an honest answer if you have handled any transaction of this kind of magnitude before and assurance from you that our family has your complete trust and assurance that the funds will be safe once transferred to your account. We thought that the recent elections in Zimbabwe would maybe oust Mugabe and give us new hope to go back, but the outcome of it has left us with a stronger resolve NEVER to go back to Zimbabwe again.So you see that we are really in dire need of assistance to begin our lives anywhere away from Zimbabwe. Please assist us. Yours Sincerely, Mike Rossman. __________________________________________________________________ Switch to Netscape Internet Service. As low as $9.95 a month -- Sign up today at http://isp.netscape.com/register Netscape. Just the Net You Need. New! Netscape Toolbar for Internet Explorer Search from anywhere on the Web and block those annoying pop-ups. Download now at http://channels.netscape.com/ns/search/install.jsp

Dear Sir, ACT ACCORDINGLY AND PRIVATELY I am Evans Timothy the bills and exchange director at African Express Bank Plc. Though I know that a transaction of this magnitude will make any one apprehensive and worried, but I am assuring you that everything has been taken care of and all will be well at the end of the day. I decided to contact you due to the urgency of this transaction. MY PROPOSITION; I am writing this letter to solicit for support and assistance from you to carry out this business opportunity in my department.Lying in an inactive account awaiting liquidation is the sum of USD $10.7million belonging to a foreign customer(Herve Garboudes) who was an petroleum/gas consultant/contactor with the Nigeria National Petroleum coporation who happens to be deceased during a business trip. He died with his wife (Christine Garboudes) on board the Swissair Flight 111 , which crashed into the Atlantic off Nova Scotia in september 2nd 1998. The news of this crash was on the news which we have notified his relatives to no avail. See links below for more detail informaion: http://cnnstudentnews.cnn.com/WORLD/9809/swissair.victims.list/ http://cnnstudentnews.cnn.com/WORLD/americas/9809/08/swissair.02/ http://cnnstudentnews.cnn.com/WORLD/americas/9809/05/swissair.transcript s/ Ever since he died the bank has been expecting his next of kin to come and claim these fund, the NDIC could not liquidate the account because I have filled a motion that a next of kin wrote in to the effect. To this effect, they can not release the money unless someone applies for it as next of kin, as indicated in our banking guideline. At this juncture i have decided to do business with you in collaboration with some officials in the bank, to this effect we solicit your assistance in applying as the next of kin and beneficiary to Herve Garboudes then the money will be released to you. As we do not want this money to go into the bank treasury as an unclaimed bill,or our superiors taking the funds for their own personal use. The banking law and guideline stipulates that if such money(s) remains unclaimed for a period of up to seven years(7yrs) the money will be transferred into the banks treasury as an unclaimed bill. Our request for a foreigner as next of kin is occasioned by the fact that the customer was a foreigner and a Nigerian cannot stand as next of kin. To effect the immediate transfer of the fund to you as agreed, you must apply first to the bank as the next of kin to the decease, The fund shall then be transferred to you legally in accordance to all laid down procedures governing closure of account and transfer of funds. If you are willing to assist us, we have agree to give you 20 Percent of USD $10.7 million Note that this transaction is legal,safe and 100% risk free. Upon receipt of your reply which should includes the following: 1) Your Full Name 2) Your telephone number for easy communication between us. I will confidentially work out all modalities for the successful transfer of this money to you as the beneficiary, and send to you by fax or email attachement the text of the application, as soon as you receive the text I will further clarify you in details on how to effect the business. Await to hear from you Best Regards Evans Timothy.

FROM THE DESK OF MR. STEVE BAKER DEPARTMENT OF PETROLEUM RESOURCES MAITAMA DISTRICT, GARKI-ABUJA I am Mr. Steve Baker, a member of the Contract Award Committee of the above department. Terms of Reference: My term of reference involves the award of contracts to multinational companies. My office is saddled with the responsibility of contract award, screening, categorization and prioritization of projects embarked upon by Department of Petroleum Resources (DPR) as well as feasibility studies for selected projects and supervisig the project consultants involved. The DPR is now compiling beneficiaries to be paid for the first Fiscal Quarter of 2005. The crux of this letter is that the finance/contract department of the DPR deliberately over -invoiced the contract value of the various contracts awarded. In the course of disbursements, this department has been able to accumulate the sum of Thirteen Million, Seven Hundred and Thirty One Thousand U.S Dollars as the over-invoiced sum. This money is currently in a suspense account of the DPR account with the Debt Reconciliation Committee (DRC). We now seek to process the transfer of this fund officially as contract payment to you as a foreign contractor, who will be fronting for us as the beneficiary of the fund. In this way we can facilitate these funds into your nominated account for possible investment abroad. We are not allowed as a matter of government policy to operate any foreign account to transfer this fund into. However, for your involvement in assisting us with this transferinto your nominated account we have evolved a sharing formula as follows: (1) 25% for you as the foreign partner (2) 75% for I and my colleagues We shall be relying on your advice as regard investment of our share in any business in your country. Be informed that this business is genuine and 100% safe considering the high-power government officials involved. Send your private fax/telephone numbers. Upon your response we shall provide you with further information on the procedures. Expecting your prompt positive response as I Look forward to a good business relationship with you. Sincerely, Steve Baker

FROM: MRS,JANE ABBAS Phone:+27-736112897 ATTN:DIRECTOR/CEO Iam Mrs. JANE ABBAS, the wife of the former adviser suliman H. Abbas, who is in charge of arms and acquisition to the current president of Sierrelone, His excellency, Ahmed Kabbah.Following the civil war in my country, the head of state delegated my husband to arrange for arm purchase from republic of south Africa through independent arms dealer. He was directed to purchase arms worth TWENTY FIVE MILLION UNITED STATES DOLLARS (US$25 000,000.00.) On arrival in South Africa through diplomatic means, he deposited the in a private company with the name of our first son Ahmed Abbas and declared it to be official consignment belonging to his foreign affiliate in holland On getting back home he was hijacked and killed by unknown people, I became widow over night. God so kind, all the papers for deposition of this with the company is with us, I did not waste time to run away with my sons and daughter to the republic of south Africa. On getting to South Africa, we could not find it easy to bring the consignment out off the Company, they demanded for foreign partner information that is bassed in holland. Due to these, For that we are looking for a reliable trustworthy person who can help us to transfer this to His or Her private account oversea. I ran into your name through net work search and I decided to contact you and see if you could be of any help to us. We intend to compensate you with 25% of the total sum, if you agree in transferring this into any of your account oversea. 5% will be mapped out in case of any country of which you will be guide to us in your country. Please should this meet your utmost consideration, please contact me through the above specified email addresss, please feel free to ask a question you consider necessary. This transaction is 100% risk free,Please include your private telephone and fax number for easy communication. Remember to keep this transaction secret for reason. I expect your urgent call as soon as possible or [e-mail:janeabbs13@yahoo.co.in / thanks and remain blessed. Best Regards MRS. JANE ABBAS. __________________________________ Do you Yahoo!? Yahoo! Mail - now with 250MB free storage. Learn more. http://info.mail.yahoo.com/mail_250

MR OLAJIDE LUCAS Gulf Coastal Internatoinal bank, Victoria Island Branch, Lagos, Nigeria. ATTN, I am MR OLAJIDE LUCAS Branch Manager with Bank of the North Victoria Island Branch Lagos Nigeria,I have an urgent and very profitable business proposition for you that should be handled with extreme confidentiality. On January 6,1999 a Foreign Oil Consultant and contractor with the Nigerian National Petroleum Corporation (NNPC) Mr. James Herbert by name made a numbered time Fixed Deposit for twelve calendar months valued at US$38.6M(Thirty Eight Million, Six Hundred United States Dollars Only) in my branch. Upon maturity I sent a routine notification in accordance with the Bank policy to his forwarding address but got no reply. After a month we sent a reminder and finally wediscovered from his contract employers the Nigerian National Petroleum Corporation (NNPC) that Mr. James Herbert died from an automobile accident. On further investigation, we found out that he died without making a Will and all attempts to trace his next of kin was fruitless. I therefore made further investigations and discovered that Mr. James Herbert did not declare any next of kin or relations in all his official documents including his Bank Deposit paperwork in my Bank,and according to Nigerian Law, at the expiration of 5 years the money will revert to the ownership of the Nigerian Government if nobody applies to claim the fund. This prompted us to contact you.We will like to front you as the next of kin of our late client thereby making you the legal beneficiary of the sum of $38.6 million U.S Dollars that is presently in my branch. I contacted you because it is against our code of ethics to own and operate foreign accounts and your assistance would be needed to claim the money in the Security Company . We have unanimously agreed that 25% of the entire sum would be for you if you agree to take part in this profitable transaction,70% for me and 2 of my colleagues while the remaining 5% would be used to pay back the expenses that may be incurred during the course of the transaction by both parties after the fund has been claimed as the next of kin. In the event that you are genuinely interested in the transaction,there are some information would be needed from you to commence transaction. FULL NAME,CONTACT ADDRESS,PHONE AND FAX NUMBER. The transaction is 100% risk free as all modalities has been perfected to ensure the hitch free success of the transaction. I await your urgent response THANKS FOR CO-OPERATION MR OLAJIDE LUCAS

Dear Sir, I know this email will reach you as a surprise, but need not to worry as we are using the only secured and confidential medium available to seek for foreign assistance in a business. It is with heartfelt hope that I write to seek your co-operation and assistance in the context stated below: May I first introduce my self: I am Dr.(Mrs.) MARIAM ABACHA, the wife of Late General Sani Abacha (former Military head of state and President of the Federal Republic of Nigeria) who died suddenly on 8th June 1998. I got your contact on the internet as I was making contact for a honest foreigner who will help save my life and my children, hence our country has been frustrating us since the death of my husband. I have lost confidence with anybody within the country. Having noted the confidence reposed on your person , I became convinced of your capability and goodwill to assist me in receiving the sum of US$8 Million secretly willed in my favour by the late general (my husband). This money was kept in a Security Company in Amsterdam Holland and I have all documents with me as of when it was deposited in a Security Vault for safe keeping. This money has been defaced for Security reasons and also to avoid it been spent by unauthorized persons. it is not an ill gotten wealth rather, it was generated from my organisation "FAMILY SUPPORT PROGRAM" (F.S.P). I will enlighten you more of this organisation if you indicate a helping interest to secure this money on my behalf. On your acceptance to render this assistance to me to invest this fund abroad in a confidential manner until we came to a conclusion to use it to buy houses and part of it will be used for non-speculative investments in your country.However,the current civilian administration of retired General Olusegun Obasanjo(The President of the Federal Republic of Nigeria) is seeking vengeance on the Abacha family because of the life prison jail sentence confirmed on him by my late husband while in office. In pursuit of this vendetta, the present Government have resolved to freeze all known assets of General Sani Abacha including properties at home and abroad and are presently embarking on to seize the various bank accounts of my husband in Swizerland,UK,Australia. In fact, the attack on our family (The Abacha's) is so devastated to an extent of seizing our travelling passport ,family accounts and even trying some members of our family in court for offences allegedly committed by my late husband. In view of this grievous threat to our Economic and personal survival, our family trustee have secretly protected the will ,The Security Company has called me to do something about claiming this consignment because of the demurrage it is incurring and I told them we would come and claim it very soon. but my son seriously advised me to move the fund into an overseas accuount, hence the reason why I have chosen you and hope that you will come to my full assistance and unlimited co-operation. In the meantime, there is a travelling embargo on us(the whole family members) and our local accounts are seized. We are currently living on goodwill of people who believe we annot be held responsible for the sins of my late husband. In view of this plight, I expect you to be trustworthy and kind enough to respond to this distressed call to save me and my children from a hopeless future. And if you agree to help, we will compensate you sincerely for your candid effort in this regard with 25% of the total amount of $8 Million US Dollars. In that case,when the money ($8 Million) is moved into your discrete account, you will be allowed to withdraw 25% in your favour ,while 10% has been set aside for any expenses you might incur or tax as your government may require . The remaining 65% will be invested meaningfully for my children's future. My cousin (Dr.yemi musa) has perfected arrangements with the Trust Company concerned and has been assured 100% risk free and safe operation. What I demand from you now is to arrange to visit the Finance Company where this money is being deposited and claim it as the bona-fide owner. And in due course, all contacts must be made through cousin Dr yemi musa whom is presently staying in Senegal through this E-mail: ma23200210@zipmail.com.br and ma232002@box.az and phone:+221-5478858.I look forward to your quick response while thanking you for your co-operation. In view of all above details, I request you to keep this letter and co-operation highly confidential. Best wishes, MRS. MARIAM ABACHA pls reply to ma232002@box.az

I sincerely write to seek your co-operation and trust. >From the desk of Mr.Donatus Okobi, Email ;donatus_okobi@excite.com Senior manager, Bills and Exchange, Nill Bank of Nigeria PLC, Lagos, Nigeria. Reply To: donatus_okobi@excite.com Attn: Dear Friend, I sincerely write to seek your co-operation and trust to enable my colleagues and I carry out an urgent business opportunity in my department. I work with the Nill Bank of Nigeria PLC; currently I am the senior manager of bills and exchange at the foreign remittance department of my bank. I was the account officer to one Mr. Ali B. Ashan who died along with his family on the 8th of November 1997 in an ADC Boeing 727 plane crash at Egirin River. All 141 passengers on board were feared dead. He left in his domiciliary account the total sum of $25.5m,{Twenty Five million, five hundred thousand USA Dollars}. Since the management got the information of his death we have been expecting any of his relation or his next of kin to come up and claim his money. Unfortunately, From the day of his death till the time of this letter none of his relation or friends has come up for the claim.The banking and financial law of Nill Bank of Nigeria PLC stipulates that if such fund remained unclaimed after a period of (7)seven years, it will be transferred into the bank treasury as unclaimed bill. On this discovery sir, I and two other senior staffs now decided to do business with you and release the money to you as the next of kin to Mr. Ali B. Ashan for safety and subsequent disbursement. I will soon proceed for my retirement leave this year, and I personally do not want this fund to be transferred into the bank treasury as unclaimed bill. That is why I wanted the fund to be move out of the bank before I proceed on my retirement from the banking services by December 15th 2005. The need for a foreigner as next of kin in this project is occasioned by the fact that the customer Mr. Ali B. Ashan was a foreigner and a Nigerian cannot stand as his next of kin or heir. We have agreed that 30% of the Fund would be for you as foreign partner; thereafter my colleague and I will visit your country for disbursement according to the percentages indicated. To enable the immediate transfer of the fund into your nominated account, you will first apply to the bank as the next of kin of the deceased, indicating your bank account number and location where in the money will be remitted. Upon receipt of your acknowledgement indicating your interest, I will send to you the text of the application that you will send to the Nill Bank of Nigeria PLC authority for an approval to submit your claims. Send your reply through my direct and Private: donatus_okobi@excite.com Indicate your direct Fax and telephone numbers for effective communication that this transaction needs. Do not reply through the Nill Bank email address because it's belonged to the senior staffs for public use. Please note that you are not to appear in person, as everything regarding this project will be strictly on documentations and every banking documents needed for this transaction will be taken care of by myself. Looking forward to urgently hearing from you. Yours Faithfully, Mr.Donatus Okobi PLEASE REPLY ME ON MY ALLTERNATIVE EMAIL:donatus_okobi@excite.com

DEAR SIR/MADAM This letter may come to you as a surprise due to the fact that we have not met.The message could be strange but real if you pay some attention to it. Please accept my sincere apologies.In bringing this message of goodwill to you, I have to say that I have no intention of causing you any pains. My name is SENATOR VICTOR OYOFO,representing Edo North FederalConstituency,(<http://www.nigeria.gov.ng/government/Nationalass.htm).member>, Pension Funds Committee in the senate of the Federal Republic Of Nigeria. I am writing you to earnestly Solicit your assistance in helping to receive some sum of money. I got your e-mail address on the Internet while searching for a reliable and reputable person to handle this transaction. THE PROPOSITION: We have the sum of US$25,200,000.00 (Twenty Five Million Two Hundred Thousand Dollars) that we intend to transfer overseas through the assistance of a foreign partner.This money came as a result of the unclaimed pension funds belonging to a British expatriate petroleum engineer with the Nigerian National Gas Company,Engr.John Bruno. After all other pensioners have been paid their entitlements, we deposited this unclaimed sum of US$25,200,000.00,with the Debt Management Committee. In a bid to make sure Engr.John Bruno gets his due,I sent a routine notification to his forwarding address but got no reply. After a month, we sent a reminder and finally we discovered from his contract employers, the Nigerian Gas Company that Engr.John Bruno died, from an automobile accident. On further investigation, I found out that he died without making a WILL, and all attempts to trace his next of kin was fruitless. I therefore made further investigation and discovered that Engr.John Bruno did not declare any kin or relations in all his official documents. This sum of US$25,200,000.00 is still sitting in an account of the Debt Management Committee and the interest is being rolled over with the principal sum at the end of each year.No one will ever come forward to claim it. According to Nigerian Law,at the expiration of 2 (two) years,the money will revert to the ownership of the Nigerian Government if nobody applies to claim the fund. Consequently, my proposal is that I will like you as a foreigner to stand in as the next of kin to Engr.John Bruno so that the fruits of this old man's labour will not get into the hands of some corrupt government officials. This is simple, I will like you to provide immediately your full names,address,telephone and fax numbers so that I can prepare the necessary documents and affidavits that will put you in place as the next of kin to Engr Bruno. Upon this,we would then obtain the letter of probate/administration in your favor from a Federal High Court.A bank account in any part of the world that you will provide will then facilitate the transfer of this money to you as the beneficiary/next of kin. The money will be paid into your account for us to share in the ratio of 65% for me and my partners,30% for you and 5% for any expences incured,during the course of this transaction. There is no risk at all as all the paperwork for this transaction will be done at the high court and my position as a member of the Committee guarantees the successful execution of this transaction.The fund shall be transferred to you legally in accordance to all laid down procedures governing transfer of funds. If you are interested, please reply immediately via my email address. Upon your response, I shall then provide you with more details and relevant documents that will help you understand the transaction.Please observe utmost confidentiality,and rest assured that this transaction would be most profitable for both of us because I shall require your assistance to invest my share in your country. Awaiting your urgent reply via my email address. Thanks and regards, Sen.Victor Oyofo.

Mr. Adam Winpoe. Bojanala House, 90 Protea Road, Chislehurston, Johannesburg 2196. South Africa. Email: adamwinpoe@web-mail.com.ar Kindly accept my apology for sending unsolicited mail to you. Although we have never met before but I have every reason to believe that you are a highly respected personality, considering the fact that I sourced your profile from a human resource profile database on your country. Though, I do not know to what extent you are familiar with events and fragile political situation in Liberia but it has formed insistent headlines in the CNN, BBC news bulletins, My name is Mr. Adam Winpoe from Liberia, a Country in West Africa. My Uncle is MR JOHN Y. WINPOE, former DEPUTY MINISTER OF NATIONAL SECURITY in LIBERIA. My uncle was falsely accused of plotting to remove the then PRESIDENT OF LIBERIA (CHARLES TAYLOR) from office. Without trial, Charles Taylor killed him. You can verify this from your country. You can also check in some of the international newspapers posted in the web sites below: http://www.usatoday.com/news/world/2003-07-15- Liberia_x.htmhttp://www.unwire.org/UNWire/20030716/449_6621.asp Before he was killed, my uncle instructed me to escape with his family to a hide out in JOHANNESBOURG SOUTH AFRICA, and he confined on me that he left some money in a Diplomatic Trust Company in Abroad, (name withheld for security reasons) he handed me over a certificate meant for a secret Deposit, which he made in the Security Company. If you may ask why do I need a foreign assistance or why can't I take the cash transfer and myself? The answer is that there was an exclusion clause in the original agreement between the company and my uncle which states unambiguously that 'nobody, not even himself, can have access to the consignment in the company, and it has to be transferred to a foreign beneficiary outside Africa. This was done because he envisaged his arrest and this clause were inserted to prevent any seizure or infiltration of the fund. My decision to contact you is therefore, informed by this and due to my present social status and total ignorance of the business world. I believe you will appreciate the enormity of trust I repose on you by placing the fortunes of our family in your care. Permit me to request that you should reassure me that you would not let me down in any way. On my part, this is my assurance and guarantee to you. In as much as you follow my instructions carefully, religiously and promptly my guarantee of a hitch-free success remains unshakable. I have contacted the Diplomatic Security Firm to confirm the deposit, which is worth $21.5Million,(Twenty-One Million Five Hundred Thousand United State Dollars Only) which I presumed my uncle made from the purchase of arms and ammunitions for the Liberia Army. You will be given 20% of the total sum at the end of the transaction. If you will be willing to assist us claim the money and invest it in your country. I want to assure you that all modalities are in place and it is a risk free transaction. Kindly confirm in your reply if you can come over to enable us conclude this transaction. Kindly include your Private Telephone and Fax numbers where you can always be reach, Your Residential or Company Address to enable me send some other important information across to you. This proposal is highly restricted and should be handled as an urgent transaction requiring trust and Confidentiality. Thanks while looking forward to hearing from you urgently. Thank you. Sincerely, Mr. Adam Winpoe For the Family. ___________________________________________________________________________ Mail sent from WebMail service at - http://www.ca-vn.net

Good Day, I hope this mail meets you in good health and spirit; i am, Rawlings Ometie, a sierra Leonie. Presently, I live as a refugee in republic of Ireland, with my younger sister, Sarah. I am the son of late Chief Dr. Wilfred Ometie, the assassinated former assistant director Of Sierra Leone gold and Diamond-mining Corporation, a victim of the war in my Country. My father was killed with other government officials during official hours when the rebel troops stormed and raided the mining corporation office at the heat of the crisis in my country. A few weeks later, the rebels also invaded our residential building in which my mother and two of our security men were killed in the compound while I was out for a special research program and my younger sister was in school. I had a singular shock and trauma, which compelled us to flee from the country to republic of Ireland with the help of an army colonel, who is a close friend of my late father, I have degree in marketing and I would have further my education if not for the death of my parents. I have never worked to earn my living since my late parents had enough wealth for us. I am contacting you now because of the present difficulty i am facing. Unfortunately my father's two accounts in West Africa have recently been frozen, however this did not affect the twenty million six hundred thousand US Dollars (us$ 20,600,000.00), which he deposited with a security company in UK. For now, I am having every information and document needed for the collection of the deposit with the security company and i want you to act as the beneficiary of the deposit for easy and smooth collection to your account abroad for investment purposes. You will no doubt be adequately compensated with as well as a percentage of the profit from investment of the fund. Also you will see to it that my sister and I come over to your country at the earliest possible time. I am making this request to you with tears in my eyes and I feel that god almighty will touch you with his spirit to listen to my cry for help and answer me without delay. Since our Parents is no more and this is the only hope for life. Your positive response will give me the greatest joy and relief. God bless you for your kind assistance we have agreed to offer you 20% of the total sum. Seriously waiting for your urgent reply. Best regard. Rawlings Ometie.

+27-73-244-79-98   Mr. Kenneth Fuzane Daniel Nyerere, 18, Pretoria Street, Johannesburg, South Africa.   Dear Sir,   RE:  MR. KENNETH FUZANE DANIEL NYERERE BUSINESS PROPOSAL   I do foresee the surprise this letter will bringto you as it comes from a stranger. But be rest assured as it comes with best of intentions. However, your address was courtesy of a business journal at the World Trade Centre in Johannesburg. But after ueconsideration from your profile, I became aware and  assured of your credibility of handling this trust and  my future.Thus, after my humble decision to solicit  for your understanding and co-operation in this  transaction, as it will be beneficial to all of us involved. My name is  MR. KENNETH FUZANE DANIEL NYERERE from Tanzania.     I am the son of the Late President of Tanzania, JULIUS MWALIMU NYERERE who died about two years ago.  My father used his position then to make for himself and us the family some fortune. My father died after a protracted illness. I was studying overseas when my  father died and I was forced to return for the  funeral. His attorney notified me and my family about  my father's WILL with his chambers.   When I was going through the WILL, I discovered that my late father had used his  position  then to make some  money, which he brilliantly transferred and deposited with a private Security company here in Johannesburg, Republic of South Africa.   He deposited this consignment as valuables.The Security Company does not know that this consignment contains cash money, except the attorney and I. The amount is (Eighteen  million United States Dollars USD 18,000,000.00 MILLION). However, my aim of contacting you is for you to help me lodge the whole  sum into your nominated account in your country or any other part of the world. Secondly, you will also help me look for profitable investment overseas because I don't have knowledge of  international investments.   As a result of my present situation, I won't be able to conclude this transaction alone. If you are interested in helping me out, try and contact me with the above telephone number or my above  e-mail address indicating your interest to help me,not forgetting to include your private phone and fax numbers for easier communication. I will then  furnish you with more details.   I have mutually agreed to compensate you with 25% of the total sum for your ssistance,   Then the remaining 75% will remain for my family and I, which you will help us invest. Be informed that this transaction needs utmost trust and confidentiality. Note also that the transaction attracts no risk on your side hence all the modalities for safe, smooth and successful transaction have been arranged by me.   Looking forward to receiving your urgent reply. Yours faithfully for:  THE FAMILY OF LATE JULIUS MWALIMU NYERERE   MR. KENNETH FUZANE DANIEL NYERERE

Do you Yahoo!? Yahoo! Search presents - Jib Jab's 'Second Term'

Do you Yahoo!? The all-new My Yahoo! – Get yours free!

Dear Friend, My name is Mr. Micheal Ipenza, I am an auditor in Standard Bank of South Africa . I am contacting you of a business transfer, of a huge sum of money from a deceased account. Though I know that a transaction of this magnitude will make any one apprehensive and worried, but I am assuring you that everything has been well taken care off, and all will be well at the end of the day. I decided to contact you due to the urgency of this transaction. To ease your apprehension, I got your contact from the British chambers of commerce and industry, foreign trade division. An account was open by a foreigner named Gerald Welsh who died in an air crash along with his wife on the 31st October 1999 in an Egyptian airline 990 with other passengers on board. PROPOSITION; Since his death, none of his next-of-kin are alive to make claims for this money as his heir, because they all died in the same accident(May his soul rest in peace). We cannot release the fund from his account unless someone applies for claim as the next-of-kin to the deceased as indicated in our banking guidelines. Upon this discovery, I now seek your permission to have you stand as a next of kin to the deceased, as all documentations will be carefully worked out by a lawyer for the funds Twenty- five million United States dollars (US$25,000,000.00) in a domiciliary account to be released in your favour as the beneficiary's next of kin. Because after six years the money will be called back to the bank treasury as unclaimed bills and the money shared amongst the directors of the bank. so it is on this note i decided to seek for whom his name shall be used as the next of kin/beneficiary to this funds rather than allow the bank directors to share this money amongst themselves at the end of the year. It may interest you to know that we have secured from the probate an order of mandamus to locate any of the deceased beneficiaries. Please acknowledge receipt of this message in acceptance of our mutual business endeavor by furnishing me with the following information if you are interested. 1.A Beneficiary name;. In order for me to prepare the PAPER WORK for transfer of the funds in your name. And also I want you to come down to South Africa to open a non-resident account for onward transfer to your overseas account, and for us to see face to face. 2. Details, particulars of your contact address. 3. Direct Telephone and fax numbers;. For our personal contact and for the confidentiality of this transactions. I shall be compensating you with 25% of the total sum on final conclusion of this project for your assistance, as I have also thought of doling out 5% to charity organisation from your locality based on your recommendation another 5% for the services of the lawyer while the balance 65% shall be for me for investment purposes in your country as I cannot bring back this cash to my country. If this proposal is acceptable by you, please endeavor to contact me immediately. Do not take undue advantage of the trust I have bestowed in you by informing you of this transaction from my bank as I will advise you to kindly desist from responding at all if you do NOT intend to render any assistance. Endeavor to respond via this my confidential direct e-mail address michealipenza1@netscape.net. Thanks and best regards, Mr. Micheal Ipenza.

Dear Partner, With great pleasure, I am writing this proposal for the benefit of both of us. I got your information through my personal search on the internet, hence I decided to seek your cooperation, due to the sensitivity of this transaction and my commitment as a Banker. My name is Mr. Charles Sherman (British Citizen), I work for FDTB London / Germany. Mr. Raymond Beck, an American Citizen, Engineer by profession who died since 1999, in an Egyptin Airline (Flight 990), on the 31st October along with other passengers on board. For your perusal,you can confirm this from the website below:- http://www.s-t.com/daily/11-99/11-02-99/d08ho174.htm Before his death, he has a huge sum of money (US$35 Millions), which I was his account officer until his death. This money has no other Beneficiary or Next of Kin. Since his death in 1999, none of his family member or Next of Kin has come forward to claim this funds as no one has the knowledge that he had such amount deposited in our bank. As the account officer to the Late Mr. Raymond Beck, I secured from the Probate an Order of Mandamus to locate any of the deceased Beneficiaries to enable the bank release this fund, before the fund will be called back to the bank Treasury as unclaimed bills and the money will be shared amongst the Directors of the Bank. My constraint is to be able to source a foreigner partner who is honest and trustworthy individual, that I will present to the bank as his Next of Kin / Beneficiary of the said funds (US$35,000,000.00) This transaction is 100% risk free provided you treat it with utmost secrecy and confidentiality, as I had also made arrangment with an Attorney that will provide all the needed documentation in your favour. I am ready to compensate you with 30%, while I receives 60% and the balance of (10%) for taxes and other miscellaneous expenses. Furthermore, your area of specialization is not a hindrance to the successful execution of this transaction. Kindly contact me through this email address charlesis@zwallet.com with the following information(s). 1. Your first and last names 2. Complete Home address 3. Direct Telephone and fax numbers. 4. Age, Sex and Marital Status. Thank you and God Bless, MR. CHARLES SHERMAN.

Dear Beloved in Christ, It is by the grace of God that I received Christ,knowing the truth and the truth have set me free.Having known the truth I had no choice than to do what is lawful and right in the sight of God for eternal life and in the sight of man for witness of God´s mercy and glory upon my life. I am Mrs Caroline Solange Haafkens from Netherlands.I am married to Dr.Franklyn Haafkens who worked with Chevron/Texaco in Nigeria for twenty years before he died in the year 2001.We were married for twenty-seven years without a child,He died during one of the riots in the Niger Delta region of Nigeria.He was held hostage and slain to death by protesting youths of the region before his death we were both born again christians. Since his death I decided not to re-marry.When my late husband was alive he deposited the sum of 8.6 million dollars (Eight Million six hundred thousand U.S.Dollars)with a bank in the Netherlands. Presently this money is still with the bank and the management just wrote me as the beneficiary to come forward to receive the money or rather issue a letter of authorisation to somebody to receive it on my behalf if I can not come over. I am presently with my laptop in a hospital where I have been undergoing treatment for cancer of the lungs, I have since lost my ability to talk and my doctors have told me that I have only a few months to live.It is my last wish to see that this money is invested and at the end of every year distributed among charity organisation. I want a person that is God fearing that will use this money to fund churches,orphanages and widows propagating the word of God and to ensure that the house of God is maintained. The Bible made us to understand that Blessed is the hand that giveth. I took this decision because i know that there are alot of poor people suffering from different kind of disease and nobody to come to their aid.With God all things are possible. As soon as I receive your reply I shall give you the contact of the bank.I will also issue you a letter of authority that will prove you as the new beneficiary of this fund.You will be entitled to 10% of every profit you make in a year. Please assure me that you will act accordingly as I stated herein. I await your urgent reply. Yours in Christ, Mrs Caroline Haafkens ___________________________________________________________________________ Mail sent from WebMail service at PHP-Nuke Powered Site - http://blygen.net

FROM THE DESK OF : GENERAL VICTOR MALU NATIONAL PETROLEUM INVESTMENTS MANAGEMENT SERVICES (NAPIMS), FEDERAL SECRETARIATE COMPLEX, MAITAMA SULE, ABUJA F.C.T. email: genv_malu@123mail.cl ATTENTION : DEAR FRIEND, The Petroleum Investment Management Services (NAPIMS) in the Exploration & Production (E&P) Directorate is the Upstream arm of NNPC that oversees the Federation investments in the Joint Venture Companies (JVCs),Production Sharing Companies (PSCs) and Services Contract Companies (SCC). NAPIMS is, therefore, set up to earn margin arising from investments in the JVCs, PSCs and SCs with the multinationals and also protect the nation's strategic interests in the JVCs.In addition, NAPIMS engages in frontier exploration services in basins where the multinationals hesitate to venture, like the Chad Basin. Vision: To be a world class oil investment management outfit. Mission Statement: To optimize the benefits accruing to the Federation from its investments in the Upstream Sector of the Petroleum (Oil & Gas) Industry. Major Strategic Roles of NAPIMS: To maximize Petroleum Profit Tax (PPT) and guarantee a higher Margin (Rate of Return) on Investment, through efficient cost monitoring reduction mechanisms.To ensure that a reserve base is maintained and reserve addition targets are attained. These are:30 billion barrels by year 2002 and 40 billion barrels by year 2010. To ensure increased production capacity from the current 2.5 2n barrels of oil per day (bopd) to 3 million (bopd)by year 2003 and 4 million bopd by year 2010 . To encourage gas utilization and commercialization To promote local content input in engineering and construction, supplies and materials utilization through in country technological capability. To enhance Nigerianization in the industry and facilitate technology transfer. To promote maximum co operation in communities of oil and gas producing areas as well as ensure that environmental protection do as are strictly maintained. As an executive director of the above named agency I am involved in the award of major contracts to foreign contractors. One of the numerous contracts we awarded was to refurbish our moribund four national refineries. However, they are still not working to 100% capacity utilization. This has resulted in serious crisis in the oil industry and necessitated in the price increases of petroleum products. There has been mounting pressure on the Nigerian government to probe the NNPC and its subsidiaries. As a matter of fact the National assembly has already started this probe exercise. To avoid the imminent shakeup, which has already taken its toll on the former Group Managing Director of Nigeria National Petroleum Resources(Dr. Jackson Gaius-Obaseki), has been dismissed from office and has been replaced by Mr. Funsho Kupo-lokun, from the aftermath of this forgoing. I am looking for foreign investor I could front as partner. This investor will assist us invest the sum of US$59.5M (FIFTY NINE MILLION FIVE HUNDRED THOUSAND UNITED STATES DOLLARS). Please if interested, get back to me with my above private email so that I could discuss further details and modality of the transaction with you. I thank you. Sicerely, Gen. Victor Malu (RTD) _________________________________________________________________ Gesendet mit WEBMAIL - www.jenbach.net

Alternate email address: josemartinezguzman1940@yahoo.es Dear friend, Greetings to you and your family! This mail might come to you as a surprise and the temptation to ignore it as unserious could come into your mind; but please consider it a divine wish and accept it with a deep sense of humility. My name is Jose Martinez Guzman. I am a 65 years old man, I am Cuban currently residing in Madrid (Spain). I was formerly living in Cuba and served under Castro`s government but had to run into self exile after the ruling Government of Fidel Castro closed in on my family on accusations of anti-government statements, I was once married with two children but my family could not escape before the deadly hands of Castro`s goons fell on them. l did made a lot of money serving Castro and on getting to Spain, I have been a merchant here in Madrid dealing in Ornamentals, Oriental Carpets and Artifacts and life was very smooth for me until about three(3) years ago when I was first diagnosed of Cancer of the Larynx. Before this happened my business and concern for making money was all I lived for, I never really cared about other values in life. But since the loss of my family and hometown, I have found a new desire to assist helpless families. I have been helping orphans in orphanage/motherless homes. I have once donated some money to orphans in war ravaged Eritrea, Somalia, Sudan and some East European Countries. Before I became ill, I kept $US 5.5 Million in a long-term deposit vault of a bank and I didn`t state any next of kin when the money was deposited and if I died without stating any the money will automatically go into the coffers of the bank and I don`t want this to happen. I have left the hospital and presently receiving treatment in an acupuncture clinic, I have been undergoing treatment for Oesophageal Cancer at the hospital. I have since lost my ability to talk and my doctors have told me that I have only a few months to live. It is my last wish to see this money distributed to charity organizations, because relatives and friends have plundered so much of my wealth since my illness, I cannot live with the agony of entrusting this huge responsibility to any of them. Please, I beg you in the name of God to help me collect the deposit and distribute it amongst charity organizations and the incident that happened in Asia too. Use your judgement to distribute the money and feel free to reimburse yourself when you have the money for any cost you incur during the process of collecting and distributing the money to charity organizations. I am going to send you vital documents to back my claims and I am willing to offer you a reward If you are willing to help, please reply as soon as you can on my alternate email address: josemartinezguzman1940@yahoo.es Looking forward to hearing from you soonest. Regards, Jose Martinez Guzman

FROM MRS LINDA SULE Hello, Permit me to inform you of my desire of going into business relationship with you. I believe you are a reputable and responsible and trustworthy person I cando business with from the little information so far gathered about you during my search for a partner and by matter of trust I must not hesitate to confide in you for this simple and sincere business. I am MRS LINDA SULE the only Wife of late MR SIMON SULE, my husband was assassinated by therebels during their attacked in our country cote d´ivoire and took over our town BOUAKE. I ran to Abidjan the economical capital of cote d ivoire from were I am contacting you. Before the deathof my husband he told me that he has a sum of usd $24,000,000 (twenty-four million united statesdollars) kept in a private security company in Cote d' Ivoire in the name of my only son as the next as the of kin. in the capacity of the next of kin, I am contactingyou with due sence of humanity and responsibility and with few awareness that you will give ita sympatheticand mutual consideration. Now that we are in Abidjan and verified the transacting, we need your assistance to help us move this funds out of Cote d"Ivoire for investment in your country as we cannot invest here due to our country and the war still going on there. By this mail, you are now requested to arrange a visit down to Abidjan so that we shall know our selves and arrange on how to transfer this money to your country. But if you can not come down, then let have your full details so that I will plan on how to transfer thismoney out of Africa immediately for investment in yourcountry. There is need for urgent actions because I pay US$50 daily as demurrage to the security company for keeping this consignments. Your services will also be required on advising us forproper investment programs in your country after this transfer is concluded. This is subject to my acceptances of charges you required. Please treatthis issue as confidential andcontact me immediately with the above yahoo private e-mail address mrssulel@yahoo.fr for more information about this transaction. Reply me this message immediately. Thanks, Wishing you God richest blessing Yours Faithfully Mrs. Linda SULE Découvrez le nouveau Yahoo! Mail : 250 Mo d'espace de stockage pour vos mails ! Créez votre Yahoo! Mail sur http://fr.mail.yahoo.com/

PLEASE REPLY VIA THIS E-MAIL: bemmanuel_citibank@omnimail.sm RE: SEEKING FOR PARTNERSHIP FOR INHERITANCE FUND OF $10.5MUSD. Dear Friend, My name is MR EMMANUL BRIGGS. I am a staff of CITIBANK NA, LAGOS-NIGERIA in Africa with our head office in USA. I work in the operations dept where I serve as account officer to numerous customers. One of the customers whom I worked as his account officer was a wealthy diamond merchandise. He lost his family, a wife and two children in a plane crash. Because this man was good to me when he was alive, I took it upon myself last month, to search if I could locate any of his close relations. But my efforts were abortive so I did not present any official report of my findings to the bank. Now there are two things I could do with regards to the dead mans money. First, as his accounts officer, I could formally notify the bank authorities that the man is dead and has no next of kin. In this case the money would be forfeited to the government treasury. As a matter of fact this is the proper thing I am supposed to do. Another thing I can do is to arrange for someone else, a foreigner, to act as the next of kin to the late man so that he will claim the money. This is the option that I can do to help anybody and myself since the money actually is now a public fund due to the fact that my friend was a close ally to the late brutal military president that looted government treasury and that is why I have chosen to do it. I want you to be my partner in this deal. I will be investing most of my share into real estate business. All you would have to do is act as the next of kin of the dead man and the whole money in the account will be transferred to your account after due process. As the accounts officer to the late man, I have certificate of the deposit of the fund here our custody and I will also through a local attorney that I will hire, secure all the necessary documents that will empower you legally to claim the money from the account. The funds will be paid to you as inheritance money. The total deposit made in the account is USD10.5 million. We shall discuss and agree further on the percentage sharing ratio for both of us and this will be drafted and seal with an agreement letter on black and white that will bind both of us and guarantee our shares. Note that upon completion of the legal paper work that will make the deal legitimate for you to claim the money as the next of Kin here, the final transfer will be made to your authorize bank account through our correspondent bank in America (CITIBANK FSB MIAMI FOLRIDA or CITIBANK LONDON). All the approved documents and the wiring instructions will be fax to you for your documentation and to enable you approach your bank for confirmation. If you found this proposal worthy enough to benefit, please furnish me urgently with the followings to enable us apply officially for the claim immediately. (1) YOUR FULL NAMES AND ADDRESS. (2) YOUR AUTHORISED BANKING DETAILS (3) YOUR PRIVATE TELEPHONE AND FAX NUMBERS AND EMAIL ADDRESS. Please reach me immediately on the above email address to furnish you more details of operation and the modalitie. Above all, please handle this deal with maturity and absolute confidentiality I wish you a prosperous New Year. Thanks and God bless you. Regards, MR EMMANUEL BRIGGS. PLEASE REPLY VIA THIS E-MAIL: bemmanuel_citibank@omnimail.sm _____________________________________ This mail was sent using pro-webmail.

Hello, This is confidential... My name is Kojo William; I am 21years old from Kwame Nkrumah Street Kasua of Accra the capital state of Ghana, West Africa. My late father Kofi Williams was the formal bank manager of Eco-bank of Africa for the period of ten years. The resent 26th December 2004 tsunamis earthquake disaster of Asia that claims the life of many people also claimed the life of my father on his December 24th trip to visit his business partner for investment in Asia Indonesia. just last week when I was searching through my father's brief-case, I discovered a lot of document and one of the document reveals that my father has deposited $10.5M (ten million and five hundred thousand dollars) in a bank vault in Europe and my name is the next of kin.but i and my mother has never been to Europe before, but your country is my dream country where I will like us to invest this fund. i like your country and i believe you are honnest and serious people when it comes to agreement and business transaction and when it comes to striking deals. I am seeking for your assistance to sponsor this transaction in which you will help me to come to Europe, so that we can meet ourselves face to face. This will give us the opportunity to familiarize ourselves to go together to the bank and order them to transfer the fund to your bank account in your country. I want you to stand for me as a proxy person that's my late father 's foreign business partner so a s to get the fund out of the bank and to transfer it to your bank account in your country where we can make use of it in lucrative business investment in your country. My mother and I have agreed to compensate you with 20% out of the total sum and 5% for your expenses.can't yourself lucky my dear friend, but remember that we must strike this deals by its rules as my mother told me that i should negotiate with a reliable person that will help us claim this cash. nobody should cheat or have any bad plans against eachother. if you don't have the capacity of bringing $10.5M into your account, then you have to look for somebody who is capable, then you will combine with him and meet me in Europe. The transaction is only known by you, I and my old sick mother who is presently in the hospital because she had heart-attack immediately she hard that my father is dead. The secrecy and confidentiality of this transaction should be maintained. It's a secret of my life; Indicate your fax and telephone number so that I can reach you when necessary and for more information.you can also mail me via "kojowilliam2005@hotmail.com" Awaiting your urgent response. Regards, KOJO WILLIAM.

Dear Friend, My name is SALIM IBRAHIM a merchant in Dubai, in the U.A.E. I have been diagnosed with Esophageal cancer. It has defiled all forms of medical treatment, and right now I have only about a few months to Live, according to medical experts. I have not particularly lived my Life so well, as I never really cared for anyone (not even myself) but my business. Though I am very rich, I was never generous, I was always hostile to people and only focused on my business as that was the only thing I cared for. But now I regret all these as I now know that there are more to life than just wanting to have or make all the money in the world. I believe when God gives me a second chance to come to this world I would live my Life a different way from how I have lived it. Now that God has called me, I have willed and given most of my property and assets to my immediate and extended family members as well as a few close friends. I want God to be merciful to me and accept my soul so, I have decided to give also to charity organizations, as I want this to be one of the last good deeds I do on earth. So far, I have distributed money to some charity organizations in the U.A.E, Algeria and Malaysia. Now that my health has deteriorated so badly, I cannot do this myself anymore. I once asked members of my family to close one of my accounts and distribute the money which I have there to charity organization in Bulgaria and Pakistan, they refused and kept the money to themselves. Hence, I do not trust them anymore, as they seem not to be contended with what I have left for them. The last of my money which no one knows of is the huge cash deposit of $20,500,000.00(Twenty Million Five Hundred Thousand U.S Dollars) that I have with a finance/Security Company abroad. I will want you to help me collect this consignment and dispatched it to charity organizations. I have set aside 15% for you, then 5% for any expenses insured. God be with you. SALIM IBRAHIM NOTE: PLEASE I WISH TO SINCERELY ADVICED THAT I CAN BE REACHED ON MY WEBMAIL ADDRESS BELOW: salim_ib@myway.com ___________________________________________________________________________ Mail sent from WebMail service at http://frenchdog.ru/

FROM AUDITOR HEAD OF DEPARTMENT BANK OF SCOTLAND UNITED KINGDOM 25/2/2005 ATTENTION! ATTENTION! ATTENTION! (CONFIDENTIAL BUSINESS) DEAR FRIEND I WANT TO TRANSFER OUT (FIFTEEN-MILLION POUNDS STERLINGS) FROM OUR BANK HERE IN SCOTLAND. I HAVE THE COURAGE TO LOOK FOR A RELIABLE AND HONEST PERSON WHO WILL BE CAPABLE FOR THIS IMPORTANT TRANSACTION, BELIEVING THAT YOU WILL NEVER LET ME DOWN EITHER NOW OR IN FUTURE. I AM, DR FRANK JIM, THE AUDITOR AND COMPUTING STAFF OF A BANK HERE IN SCOTLAND UNITED KINGDOM. THERE IS AN ACCOUNT OPENED IN THIS BANK IN 1995 AND SINCE 2001 NOBODY HAS OPERATED ON THIS ACCOUNT AGAIN, AFTER GOING THROUGH SOME OLD FILES IN THE RECORDS, I DISCOVERED THAT IF I DO NOT REMITT THIS MONEY OUT URGENTLY, IT WILL BE FORFEITED FOR NOTHING. HOW THE MONEY CAME ABOUT: THE OWNER OF THIS ACCOUNT IS MR JOHN HUGHES A FOREIGNER AND THE MANAGER OF PETROL CHEMICAL SERVICE HERE IN LONDON, A CHEMICAL ENGINEER BY PROFESSION AND HE DIED SINCE 1995.AND THEN,SINCE 2001, NOBODY KNOWS ABOUT THIS ACCOUNT OR ANYTHING CONCERNING IT, THE ACCOUNT HAS NO OTHER BENEFICIARY AND MY INVESTIGATION PROVED TO ME AS WELL THAT HIS COMPANY DOES NOT KNOW ANYTHING ABOUT THIS ACCOUNT AND THE AMOUNT INVOLVED IS (15,000,000.00) POUNDS STERLINGS I WANT TO TRANSFER THIS MONEY INTO A SAFE FOREIGN ACCOUNT ABROAD BUT I DON'T KNOW ANY FOREIGNER, I AM ONLY CONTACTING YOU AS A FOREIGNER BECAUSE THIS MONEY CAN NOT BE APPROVED TO ANY LOCAL BANK HERE IN SCOTLAND, BUT CAN ONLY BE APPROVED TO ANY FOREIGN ACCOUNT BECAUSE THE MONEY IS POUNDS STERLINGS AND THE FORMER OWNER OF THE ACCOUNT IS MR. JOHN HUGHES AND HE WAS A FOREIGNER TOO. WELL, I GOT YOUR EMAIL ADDRESS FORM MAGAZINE ADVERT. I KNOW THAT THIS MESSAGE WILL COME TO YOU AS A SURPRISE AS WE DON'T KNOW OUR SELF BEFORE, BUT BE SURE THAT IT IS REAL AND A GENUINE BUSINESS. I BELIEVE IN GOD THAT YOU WILL NEVER LET ME DOWN IN THIS INVESTMENT. WHEN THE TRANSFER IS APPROVED AND PAYMENT SCHEDULE IS ALLOCATED OVERSEAS,THROUGH THE OFFSHORE PAYING DELEGATE FOR FINAL CLEARANCE AND SIGNING OF THE PAYMENT RELEASE FORM BY THE BENEFICIARY, I WANT US TO SEE AT THE OVERSEA PAYING CLEARANCE OFFICE FACE TO FACE OR SIGNING OF THE ORIGINAL BINDING AGREEMENT TO BIND US TOGETHER SO THAT,WE CAN RECEIVE THIS MONEY INTO A FOREIGN ACCOUNT OR ANY ACCOUNT OF YOUR CHOICE WHERE THE FUND WILL BE REMITTED. I AM CONTACTING YOU BECAUSE OF THE NEED TO INVOLVE A FOREIGNER WITH A FOREIGN ACCOUNT AS THE REAL BENEFICIARY. I NEED YOUR CO-OPERATION TO MAKE THIS WORK FINE, BECAUSE THE MANAGEMENT IS READY TO APPROVE THIS PAYMENT TO ANY FOREIGNER WHO HAS THE CORRECT INFORMATION TO THIS ACCOUNT,WHICH I WILL GIVE TO YOU WHEN SURE OF YOUR CAPABILITY TO HANDLE SUCH AMOUNT IN STRICT CONFIDENCE AND TRUST. ACCORDING TO MY INSTRUCTIONS AND MY ADVICE FOR OUR MUTUAL BENEFIT BECAUSE I DON'T WANT TO MAKE ANY MISTAKE, I NEED YOUR STRONG ASSURANCE AND TRUST. I SHALL DESTROY ALL DOCUMENTS CONCERNING THIS TRANSACTIONS IMMEDIATELY WE RECEIVED THIS MONEY LEAVING NO TRACE TO ANY PLACE. I WILL USE MY POSITION AND INFLUENCE OF OTHER STAFFS TO EFFECT THE LEGAL APPROVALS AND ONWARD TRANSFER OF THIS MONEY TO YOUR ACCOUNT WITH APPROPRIATE CLEARANCE FROM FOREIGN PAYMENT DEPARTMENT. WITH ASSURANCE THAT THIS MONEY WILL BE INTACT PENDING MY PHYSICAL ARRIVAL TO YOUR COUNTRY FOR THE SHARING AND OTHER INVESTMENT. PLEASE DO REPLY ME THROUGH: {auditorcole05@yahoo.com} OR YOU CALL ME WITH TELEPHONE NUMBER {44-879292806} VERY URGENT CONTACT . PS;You should have this as a notice,that after the success of this transaction,you will be having 25%(i.e; 3,750,000.00 pounds sterling) as your share and the rest of the money awaits my presence in your country. THANKS SINCERELY COMRADE COLE.... <br><br> Direccion.com<br> ________________________________________________<br> This mail was sent by Direccion.com 2.0

Dear friend, I MAKE THIS APPEAL WITH THE UNDERSTANDING THAT ANY FACTS OR OPINION EXPRESSED BY ME ARE GIVING IN CONFIDENCE AND SOLELY FOR YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION AND USE. I am MR. Thomas Sarr, the manager of bill and exchange at the foreign remittance department of my Bank. In my department I discovered an abandoned sum of US$8.5m,(Eight Million, Five Hundred Thousand US Dollars) with account number 14-2558-5976 that belongs to one of our foreign customers who died along with his wife and only daughter in a plane crash of Alaska Airlines Flight number 261 which crashed on 31 January, 2000. You shall read more about the crash on visiting this site http://www.cnn.com/2000/US/02/01/alaska.airlines.list/ The owner of this account is Mr. Morris Thompson an American and great industrialist and a resident of Alaska. It is therefore upon this discovery that I now decided to make this business proposal to you and for our bank to release the money to you. You have to follow the instructions which I will send to you as the next of kin or relation to the deceased for safety and subsequent disbursement since nobody is coming for it and I don't want this money to go into our bank treasury as unclaimed bill. The banking law and guidelines here stipulates that if such money remained unclaimed after three years, the money will be transfered into the bank treasury as unclaimed fund. The money has now stayed more than three years and I am preparing documentations to prove that this money has been transfered to our bank treasury. It will be between me and you only that will know that the money is not transfered into our treasury. The request of foreigner as next of kin in this transaction is occasioned by the fact that the customer was a foreigner and a Senegalese cannot stand as next of kin to a foreigner. In appreciation of your assistance, I am offering you 30% of the total sum. 5% for contingencies (cost of transfer/other charges) likely to be incurred during the course of transaction, while the remaining 65% is for me. Upon receipt of your reply, I will send to you by fax or email the text of the application which you will complete and forward to our bank asking for this money to be paid to you as the next of kin to Mr. Morris Thomson. I will not fail to bring to your notice that this transaction is hitch-free and that you should not entertain any fear as all required arrangements have been made for the transfer. You should contact me immediately as soon as you receive this mail through the above email. PLEASE DO NOT HESITATE TO CONTACT ME IMMEDIATELY. PLEASE DO CONSIDER MY REQUEST AS URGENT. You may contact me also at sarrthom1@lycos.com. Yours Faithfully, Thomas SARR

This is an official notification of the availability of a package deposited in your name and it is not a sales solicitation or SPAM. We are Diplomats that use our immunity and status to safekeep special and valuable packages and baggage in trust for reputable clients that are honest and trustworthy. We work in collaboration with top firms and Governments of various countries as we have earned a name as a service whose hallmarks in reliability and confidentiality are revered. International missions, Fellow Diplomats and Embassies of the world have used our services to satisfaction. A benefactor whose identity can not be disclosed because of the Non Circumvention and Non Disclosure Agreement that was signed with the said benefactor when the packages were being deposited made you the beneficiary of a package containing some amount of money and stated clearly that you should only be contacted when the time signed for it to be in our care elapses and the time has already elapsed that is why you are being contacted. The Non Circumvention and Non Disclosure Agreement signed with the benefactor mandates us to fully divulge and disclose the benefactor's identity 18 months after the beneficiary has received the funds. The funds in the package is USD1.5M (One Million,Five Hundred Thousand U.S.Dollars) and we confirm that these funds are fully free of any liens, or encumbrances and are clean, clear and non-criminal origin and are available in the form of CASH. You are hereby advised to send your Full Contact Information as well as the name of the closest airport to your city in the format stated below so that the funds would be brought to your Country of residence by 3 Diplomats who would accompany you to your bank (if you want them to) to deposit the funds in your name and submit all documentations that has to do with the origin of the funds in other to exonerate you from any form of investigations or interrogation and to authenticate the fact that the funds are clean and has no links whatsover with either drugs or terrorism. The Requested Information is to ensure that no mistake or error is made and it should be forwarded in the manner stated below: Your Full Name: ______________________________ Your Complete Address: ________________________________ Name of City of Residence: ____________________ Name of Closest Airport to your city of Residence:_________________________________ Direct Telephone Number:____________________________________ The Telephone number is very necessary because the number would be called by the Diplomats before the funds would be handed over to you so as to ensure that the package is handed over to the right person. So,its mandatory you send your Direct Telephone Number preferably your Mobile or Cell Phone Number. Complete the above and send back to me as soon as possible. Congratulations in advance. Thank you and I sincerely Remain Anna Holmes annaholmes2@web-mail.com.ar annaholmes3@web-mail.com.ar ___________________________________________________________________________ Mail sent from WebMail service at PHP-Nuke Powered Site - http://dirot4sales.com

FROM THE DESK OF MR PAUL DOLL AUDITING AND ACCOUNTING MANAGER, BANK OF AFRICA (B.O.A) DAKAR-SENEGAL. Branch. PHONE:+221-547-8858 Dear Friend, I feel quite safe dealing with you in this business proposition having gone through your remarkable profile on the Internet. Though, this medium (Internet) has been greatly abused, I choose to reach you through it because it still remains the fastest, surest and most secured medium of communication. However, this correspondence is purely Private, and it should be treated as such.I am the AUDITING AND ACCOUNTING MANAGER BANK OF AFRICA (B.O.A) here in DAKAR-SENEGAL. Branch. In my department we discovered an abandoned sum of US$6.5m dollars (Six Million Five Hundred Thousand Dollars) in an account that belongs to one of our foreign customer (MR. ANDREAS SCHRANNER from Munich, Germany) who died along with his entire family in Jully 2000 in a plane crash. FOR MORE INFORMATION VISIT THIS SITE BELOW; http://news.bbc.co.uk/1/hi/world/europe/859479.stm Since we got information about his death, we have been expecting his next of kin to come over and claim his money because we cannot release it unless some body applies for it as next of kin or relation to the deceased as indicated in our banking guidlings and laws but unfortunately we learnt that all his supposed next of kin or relation died alongside with him at the plane crash leaving nobody behind for the claim.It is therefore upon this discovery that I now decided to make this business proposal to you and release the money to you as the next of kin or relation to the deceased for safety and subsequent disbursement since nobody is coming for it and we don't want this money to go into the bank treasury as unclaimed bill. The banking law and guidline here stipulates that if such money remained unclaimed after fours years, the money will be transfered into the bank treasury as unclaimed fund.nobody applies to claim the fund .Consequently, my proposal is that I will like you as a foreigner to stand as the next of kin to MR. ANDREAS SCHRANNER so that the fruit of this old man's labor will not get into the hands of some corrupt Government officials. This is simple, The request of foreigner as next of kin in this business is occassioned by the fact that the customer was a foreigner and a SENEGAL cannot stand as next of kin to a foreigner.I agree that 30% of this money will be for you as a respect to the provision of a foriegn account ,10% should be for expenses, tax as your government may require. and 60% would be for me Thereafter, I will visit your country for disbursement according to the percentage indicated Therefore,to enable the immediate transfer of this fund to you arranged,you must apply first to the bank as relation or next of kin of the deceased indicating your bank name, your bank account number, your private telephone and fax number for easy and effective communication and location where in the money will be remitted. Upon receipt of your reply, I will send to you by fax or email the text of the application . I will not fail to bring to your notice this transaction is hitch-free and that you should not entertain any atom of fear as all required arrangements have been made for the transfer.I guarantee that this will be executed under a legitimate arrangement that will protect you from any breach of the law, as this transaction is 100% risk free. You should contact me immediately as soon as you receive this letter.Trusting to hear from you immediately. Yours Faithfully, MR PAUL DOLL. (B.O.A) TREAT AS URGENT AND CONFIDENCIAL PLS: REPLY TO pd232002@box.az YOU CAN CALL ON MY PHONE:+221-547-8858

Dr. Taylor Akintola, United Bank For Africa, ILupeju Branch, Lagos, Nigeria Reply: jtaylor75_20@yahoo.com ATTN: Sir/Madam I am Dr.Taylor Akintola, Branch Manager with United Bank For Africa,ILupeju Branch, Lagos, Nigeria. I have an urgent and very profitable business proposition for you that should be handled with extreme confidentiality. On January 6,1998 a Foreign Consultant and contractor with the Nigerian Railway Corporation Mr. Abbas Gumeri by name made a numbered time Fixed Deposit for twelve calendar months valued at US$38.6M (Thirty Eight Million, Six Hundred United States Dollars Only) in my branch. Upon maturity I sent a routine notification in accordance with the Bank policy to his forwarding address but got no reply. After a month we sent a reminder and finally we discovered from his contract employers Nigerian Railway Corporation that Mr. Abbas Gumeri died from an automobile accident. On further investigation, we found out that he died without making a Will and all attempts to trace his next of kin was fruitless. I therefore made further investigations and discovered that Mr. Abbas Gumeri did not declare any next of kin or relations in all his official documents including his Bank Deposit paperwork in my Bank. This sum of US$38.6M has been carefully moved out of my bank to a Financial and Security Company in Europe for safekeeping. No one will ever come forward to claim it and according to the Law of my country, at the expiration of 7 years the money will revert to the ownership of the State (Government) if nobody applies to claim the fund. This prompted us to contact you.We want to front you as the next of kin of our late client thereby making you the legal beneficiary of the sum of $38.6 million U.S Dollars that is presently in a Financial and Security Company in Europe. I contacted you because it is against our code of ethics to own and operate foreign accounts and your assistance would be needed to claim the money in the Financial and Security Company in Europe. We have unanimously agreed that 25% of the entire sum would be for you if you agree to take part in this profitable transaction,65% for me while the remaining 10% would be used to pay back the expenses that may be incurred during the course of the transaction by both parties after the fund has been claimed and lodged in your account. In the event that you are genuinely interested in the transaction,the following information would be needed from you to expedite action. 1) Your Full Name . 2) Your Residential or Company Address. 3) Your Private Mobile,Telphone and Fax numbers where you can be reached at all time because this transaction entails constant communication. The transaction is 100% legal and totally free of risks as all modalities has been perfected to ensure the hitch free success of the transaction. If you are interested, send the requested information via email" jtaylor75_20@yahoo.com as soon as possible so that we can proceed and after sending it you call me. I await your response urgently. Regards, Dr. Taylor Akintola

Dear Greetings To You And Your Family, This mail was first sent to you two months ago via post mail but uptill today,I have not heard from you.Based on this,I decided to reach you through this means though I know fully well that this is not the best and safest means to reach you for security reasons but was left with no other viable option since there's this urgent need to reach you. Firstly,I would want to assure you that this mail is no junk,spam,ilusion nor mere imagination.I appeal to you for the inconveniences this may cause you by going through an unsolicited mail,but I assure you that you will be satisfied after given me your due attention by carefully and attentively going through this.I know that we have not met before nor known to each other but never to worry as I will explain better. For clarity sake,I am Mr Kayode Abiola, 22 years old and a third year micro biology student of the Federal University of Lagos.I am one of the sons of late Chief M.K.O Abiola who won the 1993 presidential elections as the President of the Federal Republic of Nigeria. Firstly,before I go further to unfold my main objective of contacting you,I would advice that you visit this site maybe you can from here have an insight of my family background and my personality.I am fully aware of the numerous scam mails my fellow country men has been bombarding through the net looking for some one to defraud.I am telling you that I am from a respectable family and will not for any reason engage myself in any indecent act that will ruin the image of my family. I am going to throw more lights on the family,my mothers assasination by the gun men from the military junta Late Gen Sani Abacha,The killing of my father through poison while under detention. Please,kindly stop here and go through this websites,atleast it will help to enrich and broaden your knowledge on what has happened to my family: The annullement of june 12th 1993 Presidential elections: www.ngex.com/personalities/voices/politics.htm www.vanguardngr.com/articles/ 2002/politics/p525072004.html allafrica.com/stories/200407120112.html www.ainfos.ca/A-Infos97/3/0497.html www.thisdayonline.com/archive/ 2001/03/24/20010324cov04.html www.stormfront.org/archive/t-13985 My Mother's assasination: www.amnesty.it/news/1996/14401096.html www.motherlandnigeria.com/women www.h-net.org/~africa/obituaries/msabiola.html www.cohdn.ca/news2/tribute1-3.html www.africaaction.org/docs96/nig9606.htm www.africaaction.org/docs97/nig9711.htm www.fraudaid.com/ScamSpeak/ Nigerian/abacha/sanionlinenewshour.htm My Father's death: www.africamasterweb.com/BanjoOnTaylor.html www.nigeriancp.net/arijo.html allafrica.com/stories/200108080221.html www.nigeriavillagesquare1.com/Sanusi.htm I believe that the above sites has given you a wider perspective of how I lost my parents.My father was known to be a polygamist,my own mother was the second wife.Since the death of my father,things are no longer the same within the entire household.My elder brother who is the son of the first wife has taken allmost everything under the pretence that we are still in school.promising to establish us as soon as we graduates. Going through my Mother's documents, I stumbled on a document which proved that my father had a deposit of $15 Million U.S.A dollars (fifteen million united states of america dollars) with a Finance Company abroad. I have made contact to the Finance Company and was told that I could come for the claims so long as I have the certificate of deposit or That I can send a representative but should equip him with the certificate of deposit and a power of attoerney. Based on this that I am mailing you seeking your consent to assist me go for the claims of this funds deposited with the security company since I am still in school. I am going to send to you all the documents given to my father by this security company on the day of the deposit. I am willing to offer you 25% of the total sum on completion of the clearing excercise from the Finance Company, I maped out 5% for refund of expences incured in the cause of this transaction, knowing fully well that this deposit must have by now accumulated some demurrages. The balance of 70% will be kept for me,or should be invested and managed by you untill I graduates.I appeal to you,to understand that despite the fact that we dont know each other,I am puting this trust on you,based on the recommmendations I got while making my own private consultations and investigations on a reliable person or firm to entrust this fund into his care. Please,I beg you in the name of god,not to sit on this money when finally released to you by the Finance Company. I am doing this because I dont want my Elder Brothers to have the knowledge of this fund. If this proposition interest you, and you really want to assist me, kindly forward the following information to me: (1) Your complete names starting with your surname first (2) Your private phone numbers including mobile (3) Your private fax number (4) Your present contact address. You should understand that these information requested will enable my Lawyer to prepare the power of attorney in your favour and as well enhance communication. I strongly advice that you treat this with utmost secrecy and absolute confidentiality,You are permited to make further enquiries on this issue, you can as well contact the Nigerian High Commission or Embassy nearer to you for comfirmation if you are not satisfied with your findings on the giving sites but please dont for any reason disclose the subject matter to anybody for security reasons. Endeavour to send further correspondences through my secured private email address:kayodeabiola@netscape.net I am looking forward to hearing from you and at the same time thanking you for your kind assistance/anticipated cooperation. Best regards Kayode Abiola. ___________________________________________________________________________ Mail sent from WebMail service at PHP-Nuke Powered Site - http://yoursite.com

from john_ishmeal Abidjan Cote D` Ivoire West Africa E-mail= john_ishmeal2@yahoo.fr Dear One, I wish to write you about this business proposal and urgent assistance. Towards my life and inheritance. I am JOHN ISHMEAL ,20years old and the son of  late Mr.and Mrs THODER ishmeal.My father was a highly reputable busnness man-(a cocoa merchant)who operated in the capital of Ivory coast during his days. It is sad to say that he passed away mysteriously in France during one of his business trips abroad year 13th  feb. 2002.Although his  death was linked or rather suspected to have been masterminded by an uncle of his who travelled with him at that time. My mother died when I was just 3 years old,and since then my father took me so special. Before his death he called the secretary who accompanied him to the hospital and told him that he has the sum of Nine million,seven hundred thousand United State Dollars.(USD$9.700,000) left in fixed deposit account in one of the leading banks.   In his farms here he still has worth of (USD$700,000) Seven hundred thousand United State  dollars cocoa which will be ready for exportation in 6 weeks time.   He further told him that he had changed the name used  in depositing the money in my name,and finally issued a written instruction to his lawyer whom he said is in possession of all the necessary and legal documents to this fund and the bank.   I am just 20 years old, and really don't know what to do.Now I want an account overseas where I can transfer this fund and to continue my education because of the risk of insecurity to my live.My uncle has been after me,ever since he understand that My Father willed all his assest to me.The death of my father actually brought sorrow to my life. Therefore I am in a sincere desire of your humble assistance in this regards.Your suggestions and ideas will be highly regarded. Now permit me to ask these few questions:- 1.Can you honestly help me as your son? 2.Can I completely trust you? 3.What percentage of the total amount in question  will be good for you after the money is in youraccount? 4.Can you help me in investing in a proper  and profitable way and not regreting associating with you. Please,Consider this and get back to me as soon as possible.So that i can known my faith and what next to do. Contact.= john_ishmeal2@yahoo.fr Thank you so much. My Regards.And God Bless You JOHN ISMEAL

Do you Yahoo!? Yahoo! Mail - Helps protect you from nasty viruses.

Dear friend, I wish the best in life for you and your family, and I hope you will receive this mail in good spirit and respond quickly with ultmost secrecy and confidentiality,I got your address through my professional relationship in discharging of my duties for my government. My name is Gen. Anthony Johnson. and I was the chief of security and operations for former president Charles Taylor of Liberia.Please protect this mail for the safety of my life and that of my family to avoid us being tortured or killed by his left behind secret agents. Please I humbly beg you from the bottom of my heart to listen very carefully,the situation in my country is very critical and chaos, uproar and hostilities had brought the country to its knees and from intelligent report the center cannot hold anymore for former president Charles Taylor and his government. The intense pressure from united states, united nations, international community and west African peace keeping to[Ecomog] had made him former president Charles Taylor to step aside and gone on exile and also pressure to face war crime charges against humanity. Listen very carefully, you know my country Liberia is very rich with diamonds,and with my position as former chief of security and operations I have accumulated so much diamonds which I had sold to generate close to $30 Million over the years and it is this fund that I want to move to you for safe keeping. The fund are in boxes in dollar denomination and it would be sent to you through diplomatic courier service with your name as the beneficiary within few days. Please would you do me a favour to receive this fund for me? Else the government in power will seize the fund and plunder it. If you are capable and know that you will truly and honestly help me, write me now, time is no more on my side. I will give you 30% of the fund and I will come to your country to take my part. Extend a friendly hand and help me. Please bear in mind that this fund is not a loaned or stolen money but rather a hard earned money generated. If you are willing to help me in this transaction,please furnish me with the followings: (1) Your telephone number, Fax number (Mobile phoneif any) (2) Your postal address (3) Your full name and a little pre-amble about yourself - I mean your age, Marrital status, What you are doing for a living e.t.c please reply back via my private email address for your good interest:- genanthony2000@mail2lawyer.com, Yours Sincerely, Gen.Anthony Johnson. ___________________________________________________________________________ Mail sent from WebMail service at PHP-Nuke Powered Site - http://yoursite.com

DEAR, I KNOW THIS LETTER MIGHT COME AS A SURPRISE TO YOU. PLEASE ACCEPT MY APOLOGY FOR ANY INCONVINIENCES THIS MAIL MAY CAUSE YOU .I FEEL THAT EMAIL CONTACT IS MORE SECURED AND PRIVATE WITH RESPECT TO MY INTENTION. I GOT YOUR CONTACT THROUGH THE DATA CENTRE OF THE CHAMBER OF COMMERCE IN DAKAR, SENEGAL.HOWEVER,I AM DR. JOSEPH TENN,THE PERSONAL PHYSICIAN TO CHARLES TAYLOR WHO WAS THE FORMER LIBERIAN PRESIDENT. MR TAYLOR WAS FORCED TO LEAVE THE COUNTRY AND SOME OF US ( HIS AIDES ) HAD TO LEAVE ALSO FOR OUR OWN LIVES AND FOR SECURITY REASONS. I AM CONFIDING IN YOU HOPING THAT YOU WILL NEVER BETRAY ME AT LAST.MY MOST URGENT CONCERN RIGHT NOW IS FOR YOU TO RECOGNIZE ME AS A FRIEND WHILE ESTABLISHING A LONG LASTING RELATIONSHIP. PRESENTLY,I AM IN DAKAR-SENEGAL WITH THE SUM OF ONE MILLION EIGHT HUNDRED THOUSAND U.S DOLLARS(USD$1,800.000.00M). THE MONEY WAS KEPT UNDER MY CARE WHEN I WAS INCHARGE OF THE PRESIDENTIAL ANNEX CLINIC FOR INTERNAL MEDICAL PURCHASES AND OTHER MANAGEMENT / ADMINISTRATIVE INCIDENTALS. IT WAS THE SITUATION OF WAR AND ALSO,THE FORCEFUL REMOVAL OF CHARLES TAYLOR'S REGIME THAT MADE ME TO MOVE AWAY WITH THE FUND. THE REASON FOR MY CONTACTING YOU IS OF THE NEWS I HEARD IN THE CNN JUST FEW DAYS AGO IN REGARDS TO MY FORMER BOSS MR.CHARLES TAYLOR.THE REPORT HAS IT THAT ANOTHER ALLEGATION IS BEING BROUGHT AGAINST HIM FOR TRYING TO LOOT OUT MORE MONEY FROM OUR HOME COUNTRY LIBERIA TO HIS BASE OF EXILE IN NIGERIA,A NEIGHBOURING WEST AFRICAN COUNTRY,AND WHENEVER ANY ALLEGATION OF SUCH IS BEING MADE AGAINST HIM, ALL EYES WILL NOT BE FOR HIM ALONE, BUT ALSO ON US THE FORMER LEUTENANTS.THE SAME NEWS ALSO APPEARED IN THE BBC NEWS WEBSITE AND YOU CAN CHECK OUT THE NEWS IN THE BBC WEBSITE TO CONFIRM MY FEARS AS I NEED TO TAKE PROPER PRECAUTIONS. http://news.bbc.co.uk/2/hi/africa/3249161.stm PLEASE,I WANT TO TRANSFER THE FUND INTO YOUR ACCOUNT FOR YOU TO SECURE IT FOR ME,PENDING WHEN I WILL COME AND MEET WITH YOU,AND TO HELP ME GET A GOOD PROFITABLE BUSINESS.NOTE THAT SUBSTANTIAL PORTION OF THIS MONEY WOULD BE COMPENSATED TO YOU FOR YOUR ASSISTANCE,PLEASE DO NOT HESITATE TO CONTACT ME SO THAT I WILL KNOW WHAT NEXT. PLEASE KEEP THIS INFORMATION VERY SECRET AND CONFIDENTIAL AS YOU CAN UNDERSTAND MY PRESENT PREDICAMENT AS A REFUGEE. PRESENTLY, THANKS FOR YOUR CO-OPERATION. SINCERELY YOURS Mr,Ahmed .Gueye my email contact: ahmeddy01@yahoo.com.au

Dear Friend, I am Mr.mike lawrences,Bank of london I have urgent and very confidential business proposition for you.On June 6, 2000, an America Oil consultant/contractor with the Chinese Solid Minerals Corporation, Mr.John Lugard made a numbered time (Fixed) Deposit for twelve calendar months,valued at 10,000,000.00pds (Ten Million Pounds) in my branch. Upon maturity,I sent a routine notification to his forwarding address but got no reply. After a month,we sent a reminder and finally we discovered from his contract employers, the Chinese Solid Minerals Corporation that Mr. John Lugard died from an automobile accident. On further investigation, I found out that he died without making a WILL, and all attempts to trace his next of kin was fruitless.I therefore made further investigation and discovered that Mr.John Lugard did not declare any kin or relations in all his official documents, including his Bank Deposit paperwork in my Bank. This sum of 10,000,000.00pds is still sitting in my Bank and the interest is being rolled over with the principal sum at the end of each year. No one will ever come forward to claim it. According to the british banking law, at the expiration of 5 (five) years, the money will revert to the ownership of queen of England as royalty if nobody applies to claim the fund. Consequently, my proposal is that I will like you as a partner to stand in as the next of kin to Mr. John Lugard so that the fruits of this old man's labor will not get into the hands of some corrupt government officials. This is simple, I will like you to provide immediately your full names and address so that the attorney will prepare the necessary documents and affidavits that will put you in place as the next of kin. We shall employ the services of an attorney for drafting and notarization of the WILL and to obtain the necessary documents and letter of probate/administration in your favor for the transfer. A bank account in any part of the world that you will provide will then facilitate the transfer of this money to you paid into your account for us to share in the ratio of 60% for me and 40% for you There is no risk at all as all the paperwork for this transaction will be done by the attorney and my position as the Branch Manager guarantees the successful execution of this transaction. If you are immediately via this email address immediately. Upon your response, I shall then provide you with more details and relevant documents that will help you understand the transaction. Please send me your confidential telephone and fax numbers for easy communication.Please observe utmost confidentiality,and rest assured that this transaction would be most profitable for both of us because I shall require your assistance to invest my share in your country. Awaiting your urgent reply. Reply to:mike_lawrences@mail2world.com Thanks and regards, Mr mike lawrences

VERY CONFIDENTIAL FROM: MR. KARIM SULE ATTN: DEAR SIR I AM THE MANAGER OF BILLS AND EXCHANGE AT THE FOREIGN REMITTANCE DEPARTMENT OF THE ECOBANK MOROCCO PLC. I AM WRITING THIS LETTER TO ASK FOR SUPPORT AND CO-OPERATION TO CARRY OUT THIS BUSINESS OPPORTUNITY IN MY DEPARTMENT. WE DISCOVER AN ABANDONED SUM OF US$30,000,000.00 (THIRTY MILLION UNITED STATES DOLLARS o nLY) IN AN ACCOUNT THAT BELONGS TO ONE OF OUR FOREIGN CUSTOMER WHO DIED ALONG WITH HIS ENTIRE FAMILY IN NOVEMBER 2002 IN A PLANE CRASH. SINCE WE GOT INFORMATION ABOUT HIS DEATH WE HAVE BEEN EXPEC TIN G HIS NEXT OF KIN TO COME OVER AND CLAIM HIS MONEY BECAUSE WE CANNOT RELEASE THE MONEY UNLESS SOMEBODY APPLIES FOR IT AS THE NEXT OF KIN OR RELATION TO THE DECEASED AS INDICATED IN OUR BANKING GUIDELINES. UNFORTUNATELY, NEITHER THE FAMILY MEMBER NOR THE RELATION HAS APPEARED TO CLAIM THIS MONEY, AT THIS DISCOVERY, I AND OTHER OFFICIALS IN THE DEPARTMENT NOW DECIDED TO DO BUSINESS WITH YOU AND RELEASE THE MONEY TO YOU AS THE NEXT OF KIN OR RELATION OF THE DECEASE FOR SAFETY AND SUBSEQUENT DISBURSEMEN T SI NCE NOBODY IS COMING FOR IT AND WE DON'T WANT THIS MONEY TO GO INTO THE BANK TREASURY AS AN UNCLAIMED DEBT. THE BANKING LAW AND GUIDELINES OF ECOBANK MORROCO PLC STIPULATES THAT IF SUCH MONEY REMAINED UNCLAIMED FOR A PERIOD OF THREE (3) YEARS IT WIL L BE TRANSFERRED INTO THE BANK TREASURY AS UNCLAIMED FUND. THE NEED FOR A FOREIGNER AS NEXT OF KIN IN THIS BUSINESS IS OCCASSIONED BY THE FACT THAT THE CUSTOMER WAS A FOREIGNER AND A MORROCO CANNOT STAND AS HIS NEXT OF KIN OR HEIR. WE AGREED THAT 30% OF THE M o nEY WILL BE FOR YOU AS FOREIGN PARTNER, THERE AFTER MY COLLEAGUE AND I WILL VISIT YOUR COUNTRY FOR DISBURSEMENT ACCORDING TO THE PERCENTAGE INDICATED. THEREFORE, TO ENABLE THE IMMEDIATE TRANSFER OF THE FUND TO YOU AS INDICATED. YOU MUST APPLY TO THE BAN K AS A RELATION OR NEXT OF KIN OF THE DECEASED, INDICATING YOUR BANK ACCOUNT NUMBER AND LOCATION WHEREIN THE MONEY WILL BE REMITTED. UPON RECEIPT OF REPLY BY MAIL, I WILL SEND TO YOU BY MAIL THE TEXT OF APPLICATION. AS SOON AS YOU RECEIVE THIS LE TTER YOU SHOULD CONTACT ME IMMEDIATELY AND INDICATE YOUR DIRECT FAX AND CONFIDENTIAL TELEPHONE NUMBER FOR EFFECTIVE COMMUNICATION TRUSTING TO HEAR FROM YOU IMMEDIATELY o n MY E-MAIL: karim_2005@fastermail.com </mailto.cgi?sid=14849331&addr=karim_2005@fastermail.com> YOURS FAITHFULLY, MR. KARIM SULE ECO BANK MOROCCO PLC.

Dear Friend, First, I must apologize if my mode of first contact is not acceptable to you and also solicit your confidence in this transaction; this is by virtue of its nature as being utterly private and top secret. Though I know that a transaction of this magnitude will make anyonea pprehensive and worried, but I am assuring you that you do not have anything to worry as I have perfected every arrangement with my colleague . I decided to contact you due to the urgency of this transaction, as I am aware of the high sense of responsibility placed on you and believe in your discreetness and ability to handle transaction of this nature. Let me start by introducing my self properly to you. I am SILVA FALL (Chief Executive Officer) of my Financial Consortium here in Daka- Senegal .I came to know and pick on you in my Private Search for a Reliable and ReputablePerson to handle this Confidential Transaction, which involves the appropriation and transfer of certain amount of Money to a Foreign Account requiring Maximum Confidence. I found your email and contact on the internet in my reliable search for a partner that I will confide with on the great opputunity. Please the objective of this letter is to first ascertain your sincerity after your perusal of this proposition, reason being I lost a lot of money through a similar transaction in the past being that a trusted partner from Switerland disappeared into tiny air after I transaferred to his custody a huge amount of money.And I have learnt my lession. Please assure me of this in your reply. THE PROPOSITION: A Foreigner from Bahamas, Late Engr. Jeff LEON (Snr.) a precious stone (Diamond) Merchant with THE UNITA rebel movement of Angola, until his death early the year 2000, used our services as his fiduciary agent and account trustees and had a closing balance as at the end of September, 2000 worth US$5,500,000.00 (Five million Five hundred United States Dollars only), and secured through our Wahakila banking services, our firm now expects a next of kin as beneficiary. Valuable efforts are being made by this firm to get in touch with any of the Leon's Family or Relatives but to no success since then. It is because of the perceived certainty of not being able to locate any of Late Engr. Jeff Leon(Snr.)'s relation(He had no wife or children that is known to us). The management under the influence of Our Chairman and fewinfluencial members of the Board of directors, has instructed that arrangement be made forthe fund to be declared "Unclaimed" and subsequently be donated to yet to be specified trust fund.I strongly believe the chairman might be up to something funny with his group. In order to avert this development that will not take care of my interest, one of my trusted colleague and I who are anticipating interest now seek your permission to have you stand as the next of kin to Late Engr. Jeff leon(Snr.) so that the fund US$5,500,000.00 will be released and paid into your account as the beneficiary's next of kin. All documents and proofs to enable you get this fund will be carefully worked out. We have secured from the probate an order of mandamus suspending declaring the money as unclaimed with limited time to locate any of the deceased beneficiary's next of kin, and moreso we are assuring you that this business is 100% risk free involvement. Your share stays while the rest be for myself and my colleague for investment purposes under your management, according to the agreement we shall reach mutually. As soon as we receive an acknowledgement of receipt of this message in acceptance of our mutual business proposal, we would furnish you with the options/modalities we have carefully perfected for you to choose from withour insider information depending on your convenience to accomplish the project and disbursement ratio to suit both parties without any conflict. I will offer you 15% of the fund if you can accept to assit me on this mandate,If this proposal is acceptable by you, please do not make undue advantage of the trust we are to bestow on you. I am expecting your reply. Please, you can aswell reply me through this my alternate email address: silva_fall1@yahoo.com as it is the most confidential for me at the moment Best Regards, Mr.Silva Fall chief of operations

Dear friend, This is a proposal in context but actually an appeal soliciting for your unreserved assistance in consummating an urgent transaction. By way of summarized profile of myself, I am Senator Luisa Pimentel Estrada, a 74years old lady and the first wife of Joseph Ejercito Estrada (former head of state and President of Philippines) who is presently held in detention in a hospital outside manilla,Philippines. However, the current administration of Gloria Arroyo(The President of Philippines) the present Government have resolved to freeze all known assets of Joseph Ejercito Estrada including properties at home and abroad and are presently embarking on to seize the various bank accounts of my Husband in Switzerland,UK and Australia. We cannot be held responsible for the sins of my Husband. In view of this plight, I expect you to be trustworthy and kind enough to respond to this distressed call to save our family from a hopeless future. And if you agree to help, we shall discuss the disbursement ratio in our next correspondence after we have been acquainted. In fact, the attack on our family (The Estrada's) is so devastated to an extent of seizing our traveling passport, family accounts, trying some members of our family in court for offences allegedly committed by my Husband and even restrict us from seeing my husband. Ihave carefully moved out these funds (US$18 million), before my husband was impeached to an offshore Deposit Company.From past experiences, many people I had regarded as close friends has capitalize on my family's travail to run away with my money. In order to avert this negative development, I in conjunction with my son (DANIEL) now seek your permission to allow my attorney do a CHANGE OF OWNERSHIP/REASSIGNMENT OF CREDIT of stated funds from the deposit company to your name, so that the funds (US$18million) would be released to you as the new owner (on behalf of me and my family).In view of this grievous threat to our Economic and personal survival, our family trustee have secretly protected the deposit, you are to assist us to lay claims of the consignment with the aid of all legal documents that will be forwarded to you as time goes on. I am writing because when I deposited the money in the deposit company, I told them that it belonged to a foreign business partner and my present position will not allow me to claim the funds. Consequently, I will present you as the owner of the funds in the Deposit Company so you can be able to claim them. This is simple. I will like you to provide immediately; 1. Full names 2. Contact address 3. Telephone and fax numbers Once I receive this information, we will prepare the necessary documents that will put you in place as the new owner of the funds. The money will then be released to your custody by the Deposit Company, for us to share. No doubt this proposal will make you apprehensive,please we employ you to observe utmost confidentiality and rest assured that this transaction would be most profitable for both of us because we shall require your assistance to invest our share in your country (buying of properties like houses, hotels etc). This is why your urgent action and response is of priority to enable us concluding this transaction in a timely and professional manner. Awaiting your swift response via this email address:lp4estrada@yahoo.co.in indicating your interest pls. Thanks and regards, Luisa Pimentel Estrada.

Hello my dear   I wish to solicit your kind and urgent assistance.My name is Mr.PATRICK AGOLO, a lawyer based in Lagos State of Nigeria.As a lawyer, I was a private legal adviser (for almost two decades) to a white couple who unfortunately lost their lives 3-months ago in a ghastly motor accident here in Nigeria. Prior to their death, this white couple had lived in this country since the 1960?s as missionaries and educationists. Unfortunately, they died childless, with no knownrelatives or next of kin.   The issue at stake, for which I am writing you now, is that the deceased left behind the sum of US$7.8million in their joint account with ECO INTERNATIONAL BANK Nigeria Incorporated. Soon after the burial of the deceased, I had promptly notified the bank,which is awaiting me to present to them the person that is to inherit the account of the deceased.   Incidentally, as I said before, the late couple had no known next of kin or relatives. No one else knows about this.However, it will amount to abuse of privilege for me to lay claim to the wealth and estate of the deceased, since as a black man i couldn't have been their relative. But then funds can't be left to the bank permanently/forever. So I have decided to contact you, to seek your consent to present your name to the bank as the next of kin and the appointed administrator/inheritor of the estates of the deceased.    As a whiteman, you'll fit into the picture.As the lawyer to the deceased, no body can disbelieve me if i present you as the next of kin to the deceased. Moreover, I know the exact legal requirements and documents to secure in your favour to show proof that you are actually the next of kin/inheritor of everything left behind by the deceased. All these will be my responsibility to obtain from the court here in Nigeria. You won?t be needed here in person. I can assure you that this is my specialty and there is nothing for you to be afraid of. I will handle and provide for all that it will take legally.Once everything needful is done, the bank will be satisfied to transfer the monies from the account of the deceased to yours.   My interest is to take 60% of the funds while you take 30%, while the remaining 10% will be disbursed to any Orphanage-Home of our common choice.Please communicate your decision to me urgently, indicating your Telephone number in your reply so that I can call you and talk this thing over with you. Pls. keep these disclosures confidential. Thank you. Sincerely yours, Barrister PATRICK AGOLO(ESQ)

Do you Yahoo!? Read only the mail you want - Yahoo! Mail SpamGuard.

Thank you for giving me your time. Please be patient and read my email to you. I wished to confide in you hopeing that you will not BETRAY or CHEAT me in your country when the fund arrived in your Bank account over there. I'm impressed with your vast knowledge,experience and sincerely believe that you have the capacity to help and assit me by going into partnership and invest the fund legally under your proper management and care in a profitable investment. The most thing i expect from you is to regard this transaction as yours and put in your best towards our achieving set goals,but i must say i will rely solely on your expert advise and guidance because this is my first business and project.The amount is Eight Million United States Dollar(US$8,000,000.00). so if you know that any Investment that will be ok that is alrigth by me since i have not being into project befor Personally,my name is Mr.Patrick Chima,i am 29years of age and a citizen of (Sierria-Leone) but presently staying here in Dakar-Senegal in West-Africa with Refeguee Status,i am seeking you as my foreign partner and you will have interest in any investment you finally confirms okay for us to invest the money into,upon we securing the release and subsequent transfer from Senegal where it is presently been deposited with your help and assistance,and i shall need your assistance in transferring the money outside Senegal based on the fact that the financial laws of this country dose not allow or permit me to handle or transfer such amount of money outside Senegal,but i can successfully do that by bring you in with a better status,hence my contacting you. Be informed that this money is owned by my late father,he was a well known Diamond Merchant and he made the money in sales of Diamonds,and the fund is safely deposited with a Fudiciary Company here in Dakar/Senegal,and the money is due to me as Inheritance. my Father was killed by the rebels in November 2000 because of his relationship with the civilian Government of Ahmed Tejan Kabbah. by the Rebel. These money in question is presently being deposit with a Fiduciary Company here in Dakar/Senegal,and i have on my arrival meet with the management of the company regarding the release of the deposit to me,and after several meetings with the management,the deposit has being approved to be released to me.But i will require a commercial bank account where the money will be transferred into,and the fact is that i don't have any bank account and considering also the fact that my status here is Refeguee,and my priority is to transfer the money outside Africa where their is economic and political stability like your country. Be rest assured of full compensation for all assistance and help you shall expertly render to me for the successefully completion of this transaction before and after.Actually,i want this money to be transferred directly to your private Bank account or any account of your chioce in your country from the fiduciary company here in Senegal where it was deposited by my late father prior to the investment as soon as you confirms your readiness to help or assist me and sincerely protect my interest. I shall provide further informations as soon as i receive your acceptance mail that you are ready,willining to help and assist me,since the financial laws of Senegal does not permit me to transfer such fund out directly,but we can successefully do it with your better status and references.This is the help and assistance i need from you. i am waiting patiently and honestly for your urgent call and reply today sir. Best regards,and have a peacefully and cool day sir. Yours sincerely. Mr.Patrick Chima.

Hello Friend, My name is Mr. PETER k. KHAN the auditor and head of computing department of a bank here in london,UnitedKingdom.There is an account opened in this bank in 1995 and since my inception into office in 2000, nobody has operated on this account again, after going through some old files, I discovered that if I do not remit this money out urgently, it will be forfeited for nothing. In order to transfer out fifteen-million pounds sterling) from our bank here have the courage to look for a reliable and honest person who will be capable for this important transaction, believing that you will never let me down either now or in future. HOW THE MONEY CAME ABOUT The owner of this account was Mr. John Hughes who was a foreigner and the manager of Petro chemical service here in London, a chemical engineer by profession and he died since 1997.And then, since 2001, nobody knows about this account or anything concerning it, the account has no other beneficiary and my investigation proved to me as well that his company does not know anything about this account and the amount involved is (15,000,000.00) pounds sterling.I want to transfer this money into a safe foreign account abroad but I don't know any foreigner, I am only contacting you as a foreigner because this money can not be approved to any local bank here in london, but can only be approved to any foreign account because the money is pounds sterling?s and the former owner of the account is John Hughes and he was a foreigner too. I know that this message will come to you as a surprise as we don't know our selves before neither have we let, but be sure that it is real and a genuine business. I believe in God that you will never let me down in this investment. I am contacting you because of the need to involve a foreigner with a foreign account as the real beneficiary. I need your co-operation to make this work fine, because the management is ready to approve this payment to any foreigner who has the correct information to this account, which I will Give to you when sure of your capability to handle such amount in strict confidence and trust according to my instructions and my advice for our mutual benefit because I don't want to make any mistake, I need your strong assurance and trust. I shall destroy all documents concerning these transactions immediately we receive this money leaving no trace at all.I will use my position and influence on other staffs to effect the legal approvals and onward transfer of this money to your account with appropriate clearance from foreign payment department. With assurance that this money will be intact pending my physical arrival in your country for the sharing and possible investments. I will give you %35 for your help and %65 will be for me. Kindly provide your phone number and your mailling address, for easy communication. Thanks and god bless you Sincerely, Mr PETER KHAN. ¡Sé listo! Contrata el antivirus http://www.pandasoftware.es/tienda/?idpers=109&track=13920

Good Day, May it not be a surprise to receive this letter from me, considering the fact that you do not know me? First I must seek for your understanding and with hope that you will have the wisdom to understand this matter and be in a position to help as you will be surely blessed as you help.I am MR GEORGE ABBEY,I am 41 Years old and also a Branch Manager with a Bank in Nigeria named, UNITED BANK FOR AFRICA{UBA} . I have a Transaction which I think will be of mutual benefit to both of us. In my desire for a befitting foreign partner with whom to do this transaction with, I got your contact from a foreign trade Centre in my Country. As the manager of a branch of UBA, I discovered some Amount of money while I was auditing accounts for the 2001 financial year which has been lying there for over 3 years. On further inquiry, I discovered that this money totaling about USD$2O.5 Million (Twenty Million! Five hundred thousand United States Dollars) including accumulated interest which belonged to one MR. ROBERT LIN, a Chinese National who lived here and died intestate without providing anybody to claim the money. This man died Through a plane crash of ADC airlines in 1998.I have successfully secured the money and with the assistance of powerful contact, the money has been moved out of my bank and deposited in a security company for safe keeping. I am therefore requesting to have your personal information to enable me prepare documents which will authenticate that the funds belongs to you as the next of kin to MR.ROBERT LIN and to enable you claim the money since nobody has come to claim the money. According to the law here if by the end of this year nobody comes up for the money it will be claimed by the Management of my bank.I am sure that you will be in a position to provide a safe account where the money Will be deposited pending my arrival to meet with you. For us to file application of claim to this money as the next of Kin i will need to have your personal information's which includes , YOURFULL NAME AND ADDRESS,TELEPHONE AND FAX NUMBER, AND YOUR FULL BANK DETAILS WHERE THIS FUNDS WILL BE TRANSFERRED TO. This transaction is absolutely risk free with no legal complications as we have made arrangements to secure all the legal documents that will free us from any litigation, I have made all necessary arrangements with the security company, that as soon as I get your confirmation of interest in this venture, we shall put in all the necessary paper which will authorize the security company to process the funds and get it transferred through their offshore bank, to your account. In doing this you must have to maintain a high degree of trust and adequate confidentiality is required and on successful completion of this transfer to your account, I have agreed that you will retain 30% of the total sum while 70% will be for me. Finally I want you to note that we are going to spend money where Necessary to make this venture work out successfully. Therefore, confirm your interest in this transaction immediately by sending the above mentioned information's as to enable us finalize this issue as soon as possible. I need to emphasize once again that a high Degree of trust and confidentiality is required in this transaction. Finally i want to inform You that as soon as the funds are in your account and the sharing completed between us.You will introduce me into lucrative business in your country because i will like to invest most of my money in your country. Please reply through this email: - {georgeabbey43@indiatimes.com } awaiting your urgent response ASAP. Yours Faithfully GEORGE ABBEY Email:- georgeabbey43@indiatimes.com

Dear Friend, TREAT WITH UTMOST SECRECY AND CONFIDENTIALITY My name is John Bruno; I worked in a bank here in the United Kingdom. I am contactingyou of a business transaction, of a huge sum of money from A deceased client of mine.Though I know that a transaction of this magnitude Will make any one apprehensive and worried, butI am assuring you that everything has been taken care off, and all will be well at the end Of the day. I decided to contact you due to the urgency of thistransaction. FACT: I was the account officer of a foreigner named Gerald Welsh who died in an air crash along with his wife on The 31st October 1999 in an Egyptian airline 990 with Otherpassengers on board. You can confirm this from The website below which was published by CNN.WEBSITE.http://news.bbc.co.uk/1/world/americas/502503.stm since his death,none of his next-of-kin are alive to Make claims for this monies as his heir, because they all died in the same accident himself and his wife (May Their soul rest in peace). We could not release the funds from his account unless someone applied for claim as The next-of- kin to the deceased .At that period he had $14,210,045m(fourteen Million two hundred and ten thousand dollars) in his account. After four to five years the money was called back to the bank treasury as unclaimed bills and the money shared amongst the directors of the bank, which has already been done by the directors mid last year. PROPOSITION; Due to the relationship between i and the deceased (Gerald Welsh) he told me of a diamond business which he had to do and left me in care of the” CERTIFICATE OF DEPOSIT” which he used to lodge the funds in a security company in Europe which is to the tune of $8.4m(eight million Four hundred thousand dollars). Note: that I decided to seek for whom his/her name shallbe used as the next of kin/beneficiary to claim the funds at the security company rather than allow the funds to lay unclaimed. It may interest you to know that i have secured from the probate an order of mandamus to locate any of the deceased beneficiaries again and no one was found. Please acknowledge receipt of this message in acceptance of our mutual business endeavor by furnishing me with the following information if you are interested. 1.Full name in order for me to prepare the Document in your name. 2. Direct Telephone and fax numbers for our personal Contact and Mutual trust in each other. I shall be compensating you with 20% percent of the Whole funds on final conclusionof this project for your assistance, while the balance shall be for me for investment Purposes. Because I just retired. If this proposal is Acceptable by you, please endeavor to contact me immediately. Do not take undue advantage of the trust I have bestowed in you. I await your urgent mail. Regards, John Bruno.

Dearest One, Good day and which i believe you will be of great assistants to me that will make the beginning of never-endingfamily relationship. I hope that this proposal will not be an inconvenience or embarrassment to you.I must not hesitate to confide in you this simple and sincere business. My name is Hussam , I am 18 years of age, the only daughter of late Mr and Mrs mattin Gutana, from Nshili District of Gikomgoro Province in Republic of Rwanda. My father before his death was a prosperous Cocoa and Gold merchant in Kigali, Republic of Rwanda before his untimely death, after his business trip to Abidjan -Cote d'Ivoire, to negotiate on a Cocoa and Gold business he wanted to invest in Abidjan - Coted'Ivoire. My mother died when I was little ,and since then my father took me so special. Before his death on 12th November 2002 he told me that he has the sum of nine million,seven hundred thousand United State Dollars.(USD$9.700.000) deposited in a security company in Abidjan Cote d'Ivoire, that he wanted to use this fund to invest his cocoa business in Ivory Coast. After the burial of my late father i came down to Abidjan and went to the security company where the fund is deposited with all the documents regarding to the deposit of the fund that was given to me by my late father. But because of the unstable political problems here last year I instructed the security company to transfer the consignment to their affilliate office in Europe, the fund is presently in Europe now waiting for clearance. I am just 18 years old and a university undergraduate and really don't know what to do.Now I want you to help me claim and transfer the fund for investment in your country because I have suffered a lot of set backs as a result of incessant political crisis here in Ivory coast.The death of my father actually brought sorrow to my life. I am in a sincere desire of your humble assistance in this regards.Your suggestions and ideas will be highly regarded. Now permit me to ask these few questions: 1. Can you honestly help me. 2. Can I completely trust you? 3. What percentage of the total amount in question will be good for you after the money is in your custody. Please,Consider this and get back to me as soon as posible. Thank you so much and God bless you. My sincere regards, Miss Hussam mattin, ________________________________________________________________________ Yahoo! India Matrimony: Find your life partner online Go to: http://yahoo.shaadi.com/india-matrimony

I am MR. KIMAEVA LIOUDMILA,the personal accountant to Mikhail Khodorkovsky the richest Person in Russia and owner of the following companies: Chairman CEO: YUKOS OIL (Russian Largest Oil Company) Chairman CEO: Menatep SBP Bank (A well reputable financial institution with its branches all over the world). I seek your partnership to accommodate the sum US$423M for us. My Boss got arrested for his involvement on politics in financing the leading and opposing political parties (the Union of Right Forces, led by Boris Nemtsov, and Yabloko, a liberal/social democratic party led by Gregor Yavlinsky) which posed treat to President Vladimir Putin second tenure as Russian president before he was reelected On March 14, 2004. You can catch more of the story on this websites <<" href="http://newsfromrussia.com/main/2003/11/13/51215.html" target=_blankhttp://newsfromrussia.com/main/2003/11/13/51215.html>> <<" href="http://www.themoscowtimes.com/stories/2004/10/18/041.html" target=_blankhttp://www.themoscowtimes.com/stories/2004/10/18/041.html>> <<" href="http://www.mosnews.com/money/2004/10/18/yuganskneftegaz.shtml" target=_blankhttp://www.mosnews.com/money/2004/10/18/yuganskneftegaz.shtml>> <<http://www.mercurynews.com/mld/mercurynews/news/breaking_news/9950187.h>> tm?1c <<" href="http://news.bbc.co.uk/1/hi/business/3753804.stm" target=_blankhttp://news.bbc.co.uk/1/hi/business/3753804.stm>> <<" href="http://money.cnn.com/2004/10/18/news/international/yukos.reut/" target=_blankhttp://money.cnn.com/2004/10/18/news/international/yukos.reut/>> <<" href="http://washingtontimes.com/upi-breaking/20041017-064951-5424r.htm" target=_blankhttp://washingtontimes.com/upi-breaking/20041017-064951-5424r.htm>> <<" href="http://www.forbes.com/home/feeds/ap/2004/10/18/ap1595717.html" target=_blankhttp://www.forbes.com/home/feeds/ap/2004/10/18/ap1595717.html>> <<" href="http://www.newratings.com/analyst_news/article_496642.html" target=_blankhttp://www.newratings.com/analyst_news/article_496642.html>> <<<http://www.channelnewsasia.com/stories/afp_world_business/view/112302/1/.h> tml>> <<" href="http://www.washingtonpost.com/wp-dyn/articles/A28041-2004Oct12.html" target=_blankhttp://www.washingtonpost.com/wp-dyn/articles/A28041-2004Oct12.html>> The fund (US$423M) in question was approved by the Government of Russia for payment of various YUKOS OIL contractors/suppliers to prevent them from loosing the money they invested in the numerous contracts they executed for the above firm. The Government had already concluded plans to freeze all the accounts in my boss name (Mikhail Khodorkovsky) both corporate and personal and have on the 18th of October 2004 decided to sell off the assets of all Yukos Oil corporation at a give-away amount to pay the allege taxes which the company owed the Russian Government.refer to the website again. Everybody in the world know that this is a political vendetta to ensure that Mikhail Khodorkovsky comes out of detention as poor and broken man and his companiesare liquidated, that if he is not eventually sent to jail for tax evasion. The Accountant General of YUKOS OIL (who is also my partner in this transaction) and I have decided to raise a memo stating that YUKOS OIL owe contractors the above amount which was finally approved for payment after some deliberations. Actually, we have paid all our contractors both local and foreign because they agitated for their payments when they heared that my boss was arrested and might eventually be jailed by the RussianGovernment. YOUR ROLE: I will present you/your company as one of the contractors we are owing so that you can stand as the beneficiary of the above quoted sum or part of the fund according to your financial strength or the strength of your company. I will arrange for the documentation which the payee bank will need to transfer the sum to you. The transaction has to be concluded before as soon as possible. You will be rewarded with 10% of the total sum for your partnership. Can you be my partner on this? If this proposal is acceptable to you, Please send me your direct and private, telephone and fax number and email address to enable me furnish you with more information as we intend to conclude the transfer within 14 working days. N/B:DO MAKE DIRECT CONTACT TO ME VIA THIS EMAIL ADDRESS: kimmilamilakim@netscape.net Regards MR.KIMAEVA LIOUDMILA

FROM: DR CHUKWUBU EZE

PRUDENT BANK OF NIGERIA

HEAD OFFICE Plot 021, Hight Street,

LAGOS-NIGERIA,P.M.B 0090,

EMAIL:chukwubueze@walla.com

Attn:Dear Friend

I know that you must have recieved the first letter I sent to you by post,but if you have not, here comes a follow-up to the letter. First I must seek for your understanding and pray that God will give you the wisdom to understand my problem and be in a position to help as you will be surely be blessed as you help. I am DR CHUKWUBU EZE,I am 51 Years old and also the chief accountant with PRUDENT BANK OF NIGERIA PLC. I have a transaction which I think will be of mutual benefit to both of us. In my desire for a foreign partner with whom to do this transaction, I stumbled on your contact from a business directory.

As the head of Accounts Department of PRUDENT BANK OF NIGERIA, I discovered some amount of money while I was auditing accounts for the 2002 financial year which has been lying there for over 3 years. On further inquiry, I discovered that this money totalling about USD$15. Million ( fifteen Million  United States Dollars) including accumulated interest belonged to one Mr Gerald Welsh , A United Kingdom Nationale who lived here (lagos-Nigeria)and died intestate with no beneficiary.This man died through a plane crash of 31st October 1999 in an Egyptian airline 990 with Other passengers on board,You can confirm this from The website below which was published by

CNN.WEBSITE.http://news.bbc.co.uk/1/world/americas/502503.stm.

I have Successfully secured the money and with the assistance of my colleague, the money has been moved out of my bank and deposited in a finance company. It was packed in two(2)metal trunk boxes as photographic materials. I would need your particulars to enable me prepare documents which will authenticate that the Consignment belongs to you as the next of kin to Mr Gerald Welsh and to enable you claim the money. I want to be assured of a safe account where the money will be deposited pending my arrival.

This transaction is absolutely risk free with no illegal complications,I have made all necessary arrangements for a successful transaction. Before this money is entrusted into your care, there must be an agreement that will be reached between us stating that:

1.BOTH PARTIES WILL NOT FOR ANY REASON CHEAT EACH OTHER. 2.BOTH PARTIES WILL WORK TOGETHER TO SEE THIS TRANSACTION THROUGH. 3.A HIGH DEGREE OF TRUST AND CONFIDENTIALITY WILL BE APPLIED FOR THE SAKE OF OUR WORK. 4.I AND MY PARTNER WILL STRONGLY BE BY YOUR SIDE AS YOU CLAIM THIS FUND AND I AND MY PARTNER WILL ARRANGE AN ATTORNEY (LAWYER) WHO WILL WORK ON YOURBEHALF TO GET THE NECESSARY PAPERS NEEDED FOR A SMOOTH TRANSACTION. 5.YOU WILL NOT DISAPPEAR WITH OUR FUND AFTER YOU HAVE CLAIMED IT. 6.DISBURSEMENT RATIO WILL BE 70% FOR ME AND MY COLLEAGUE,20% FOR YOU,WHILE 10% WILL TAKE CARE OF OUR MUTUAL EXPENCES.

There is need for you to respond to this offer immediately as the government of my country have concluded plans to apply the money into arms procurement to project wars and unrest in African continent. I must let you know that a high degree of trust is required and also we will like to use our own share to go into any lucrative business with your help/assistance.

Awaiting your urgent response now. Yours Faithfully

DR CHUKWUBU EZE

CHIEF ACCOUNTANT

PRUDENT BANK OF NIGERIA

EMAIL:chukwubueze@walla.com

----------------------------------------------------------------------- SOS Aldeas Infantiles. Ningún niño sin hogar. http://ad.doubleclick.net/clk;15349974;7829128;a?http://ad.es.doubleclick.net/clk;15339847;11200040;r?http://www.aldeasinfantiles.es/aldeas/microsite/index.htm

BILL AND EXCHANGE OF THE FOREIGN REMITTANCE DEPARTMENT OF CITIZENS INTERNATIONAL BANK LTD, LAGOS.NIGERIA. email address at:nzamo__ben@myway.com

Date 8/4/2005.

Dear ,

I am writing to you, following the impressive information about you through the Web,and I believe in your capability and reliability to champion this opportunity.I am the Operations Officer, BILL AND EXCHANGE of THE FOREIGN REMITTANCE DEPARTMENT OF CITIZENS INTERNATIONAL BANK LTD,LAGOS.NIGERIA.In my department,we discovered an abandoned sum of 17.5 million US dollars Seventen million five hundrend US dollars) in an account that belongs to one of our foreign customers who died along with his entire family in 0ctomber,1998 in a plane crash.

Since we got information about his death, we have been expecting his next of Kin to come over and claim his money because we can not release it unless some body applies for it as next of Kin or relative to the deceased as indicated in our banking and financial policies but unfortunately we learnt that his supposed next of kin or relation died with him in the accident leaving nobody behind to claim the money. It is therefore upon this discovery that I and other officials in my department now decided to make this business proposal to you and release the money to you as the next of kin or relation to the deceased for safety and subsequent disbursement since nobody is coming for it and we dont want this money to go into the Bank treasury as unclaimed bills.

The Banking law and guide line here stipulates that if such money remained unclaimed after Six and half years, the money will be transferred into the Bank treasury as unclaimed fund.The request for a foreigner as next of kin in this business is occasioned by the fact that the customer was a foreigner and an indigene cannot stand as next of kin to the deceased family. We agreed that 30% of this money will be for you as foreign partner, in respect of your assistance in this business, and 70 % would be for me and two of my staff in the business.

Thereafter,I and my colleagues will visit your country for disbursement according to the percentages indicated.Therefore, to enhance the immediate transfer of this fund to you as arranged,you must apply first to the Bank as relation or next of kin of the deceased indicating your private, telephone and fax number for easy and effective communication and location where the money will be remitted. Upon receipt of your reply, I will send to you by fax or e-mail the text of the application.I will not fail to bring to your notice that this transaction is hitch free and that you should not entertain any atom of fear as all required arrangements have been made for the transfer.You should contact me on MY E-MAIL, as soon as you receive this letter. I decided to contact you as you have products of interest in your part of the world where we can invest our own percentage to avoid peoples awareness as we are civil servants.

Note that we can conclude this operation within ten banking days.Please keep this very confidential for obvious security reasons. Contact me for more information, all confirmable before you apply if you want. Trusting to hear from you shortly for a detailed information which are confirmable before you can make up your mind to apply.If however,you are not interested,do let me know by return mail too as I will not contact anybody else until I hear from you.Reach me immediately through my private email address at:nzamo__ben@myway.com

May God be with you.

Yours faithfully, Dr Ben Nzamo

Dear Good Friend. My Name is Mr.Stefan Dusza a credit officer with (International Trust House)here in Cotonou Republic Du Benin. In my department i discovered an abandoned sum of US$20M dollars (Twenty Million US dollars) in an account that belongs to one of our late foreign customer (MR. ANDREAS SCHRANNER from Munich, Germany)who died along with his entire family in July 2000 in a plane crash. and please note that my reason why of contacting is base that this is a deal between me and you only. Below is a website which i will apprecaite you go through to read the information. http://news.bbc.co.uk/1/hi/world/europe/859479.stm Since then I have made several enquiries to locate any of the above mentioned person extended relatives, this has also proved abortive. Now the reason while of contacting you is base on trust to enable me present you as the next of kin so that this fund will be released to you as the next of kin or relation to the deceased for safety and subsequent disbursement since nobody as come for claiming of the fund and note it will be very easy to convince the bank since I have the necessary legalised documents that backup the fund and which will present you the rightful next of kin to the deceased customer. I don't want this money to go into the bank treasury as unclaimed bill. The banking law and guidline here stipulates that if such money remained unclaimed after Five years, the money will be transfered into the bank treasury as unclaimed fund. The request of foreigner as next of kin in this business is occassioned by the fact that the customer was a foreigner and an Indigen here cannot stand as next of kin to a foreigner. All I require is your honest co-operation to enable us see this deal through. I guarantee that this will be executed under a legitimate arrangement that will protect you from any breach of the law. I agree that 30% of this money will be for you as a respect to the provision of a foriegn account , 5% will be set aside for expenses incurred during the business,another 5% to help the less previlage and to assist the charity organisations here in Africa and abroad while the rest 60% would be for me Thereafter, I will visit your country for disbursement according to the percentage indicated Therefore, to enable the immediate transfer of this fund to you arranged,you must apply first to the bank as relation or next of kin of the deceased indicating your bank name, your bank account number,your private telephone and fax number for easy and effective communication and location where in the money will be remitted. Upon receipt of your reply, I will send to you by fax or email the text of the application . I will not fail to bring to your notice that this transaction is hitch-free and that you should not entertain any atom of fear as all required arrangements have been made for the transfer. You should contact me immediately as soon as you receive this letter. Trusting to hear from you immediately. Yours Faithfully, Mr.Stefan Dusza.

WARTFORD & WARTFORD CHAMBERS ADVOCATES AND SOLICITORS #100 LAGOS ROAD,NIGERIA 18TH APRIL 2005 FROM THE DESK OF: MARTINS ADE EMAIL:martinsade200@yahoo.co.uk SUBJECT: CONSULTATION ATTN: SIR/MADAM I AM MARTINS ADE A LIBERIAN BY BIRTH. I AM THE PERSONAL ASSISTANT TO LATE MR GERALD SMITH A FOREIGNER (AMERICAN), WHO WAS A CONTRACTOR TO AFRICAN PETROLEUM DEVELOPMENT COMPANY IN NIGERIA. ON THE 31ST OCTOBER, 1999, MR GERALD SMITH AND HIS WIFE BARBARA WERE INVOLVED IN A PLANE CRASH ON EGYPT AIR FLIGHT 990 IN ONE OF THEIR NUMEROUS TRIPS.SINCE THE NEWS WAS WELL ANNOUNCED ON CNN YOU MAY VIEW THE LINK BELOW FOR YOUR RECORD; HTTP://WWW.CNN.COM/US/9911/02/EGYPTAIR990.LIST/INDEX.HTML UNFORTUNATELY THEY BOTH LOST THEIR LIVES IN THE PLANE CRASH.SINCE THEN I HAVE MADE SEVERAL ENQUIRIES TO THE AMERICAN EMBASSY HERE AND THE HOME ADDRESS HE FILLED IN HIS FILE TO LOCATE ANY OF HIS EXTENDED RELATIVES ARE NOT VALID.SINCE I HAVE NEVER BEEN TO THE U.S EVERYTHING HAS PROVED UNSUCCESSFUL. AFTER THESE SEVERAL UNSUCCESSFUL ATTEMPTS, I DECIDED TO USE THE INTERNET TO LOCATE ANY MEMBER OF HIS FAMILY, BUT TO NO AVAIL, HENCE I CONTACTED YOU. I CONTACTED YOU TO ASSIST IN REPARTRATING THE MONEY AND PROPERTY LEFT BEHIND BY MR GERALD SMITH BEFORE THEY GET CONFISCATED OR DECLARED UNSERVICEABLE BY THE BANK WHERE THIS HUGE MONEY IS DEPOSITED. PARTICULARLY, THE FINANCE HOUSE WHERE THE DECEASED HAD AN ACCOUNT VALUED AT ABOUT US$21M (TWENTY ONE MILLION DOLLARS). CONSEQUENTLY,THE BANK ISSUED ME A NOTICE TO PROVIDE THE NEXT-OF- KIN WHICH WAS HIS WIFE OR HAVE THE ACCOUNT CONFISCATED ACCORDING TO THE LAW. SINCE I HAVE BEEN UNSUCCESSFUL IN LOCATING THE RELATIVES FOR OVER 3 YEARS NOW,I SEEK YOUR CONSENT TO PRESENT YOU AS THE NEXT-OF-KIN OF THE DECEASED SINCE YOU ARE ALSO A FOREIGNER SO THAT THE PROCEEDS OF THIS ACCOUNT VALUED AT US$21M CAN BE PAID TO YOU AND I. WE SHALL SHARE THE MONEY THUS: 70% TO ME AND 25% TO YOU, WHILE 5% WILL BE USED TO RE-IMBURSE ANY EXPENSES THAT MIGHT BE INCURRED ON BOTH ENDS AND TO SERVICE THE TAX THAT MIGHT BE INCURRED IN YOUR COUNTRY. I HAVE ALL THE NECESSARY LEGAL DOCUMENTS THAT WILL BE ADJUSTED TO FAVOUR YOU AND TO BACK UP ANY CLAIM WE MAY MAKE. ALL I REQUIRE IS YOUR HONEST COOPERATION TO ENABLE US SEE THIS DEAL THROUGH. I GUARANTEE THAT THIS WILL BE EXECUTED UNDER A LEGITIMATE ARRANGEMENT THAT WILL PROTECT YOU FROM ANY BREACH OF THE LAW. MY EMAIL ADDRESS IS: martinsade@yahoo.co.uk YOURS SINCERELY, MARTINS ADE N.B. PLEASE INDICATE YOUR TELEPHONE AND FAX NUMBERS FOR EASY COMMUNICATION.

Good day, I know this letter will come to you as a surprise; But this letter is borne out Of my desire to establish a mutual business Relationship with you, please keep it confidential! I am Mr. Aliyu Ahmed the son of Dr Ibrahim Ahmed the former deputy finance minister under the ousted civilian government in Sierra Leone. My father was killed and mutilated by the military junta led by Major Paul Koroma after over throwing the elected government of President Tejan Kabba.Though, I do not know to what extent you are familiar with events disturbances in Sierra Leone, but the, pressure of war drove me and my mother out of Sierra Leone into exile in South Africa. Where we have been living under political asylum for three years. Sadly, my mother died of cancer three [3] months ago and was buried here in South Africa. Prior to her death, she handed over to me a certificate meant for a secret deposit which my father made in security/finance company in South Africa. This deposit is worth [US $ 10.000.000.00] ten Million United States Dollars only. And this money is in cash. My father made this deposit in the heat of the conflict then in my country, with the hope to convert it[money] to his personal use at the end of the war, unfortunately he was killed when the conflict intensified as result of his opposition to the rebel forces. After my mother's funeral, I contacted the security company to confirm this deposit and establish ownership as well made an arrangement for this deposit to be moved through diplomatic channel to United Arab Emirates Presently, this sum of U.S$10,000,000.00 (ten million dollars) is currently being deposited in a security vault in Dubai. I am seeking for your honest and sincere participation in the retrievement and reinvestment of this money. I cannot do it alone due to my complete ignorance of the business world, more over I am only 27 years old I will give you a negotiable percentage of the principal sum in deposit if you assist me to retrieve and reinvest this money in any profitable area of business in your country. Please, I need your assistance urgently, because the more this consignment is still with the company, the more the demurrage accumulates. Contact me through the same email address. God Bless You, Thanks you. Aliyu Ahmed Jnr.

FROM: MR.NICHOLAS KULAR TELEPHONE: 0027-83 730 5031 Atten:Nadkov. Dear Sir/Madam, You may be surprise to receive this letter from me as you don't know me in person, but please take this mail into consideration. I am Mr. Nicholas Kular, the son of late Mr. JOHNSON KULAR, who was recently murdered in the land dispute in Zimbabwe. Kindly work with me to handle a very confidential transaction which involves a transfer of fund to a foreign account and I decided to write you, my late father was among the few black Zimbabwean rich farmers murdered in cold blood by the agents of the ruling government of president Robert Mugabe for his alleged support and sympathy for the Zimbabwean opposition party controlled by the white minority. Before his death, he had earlier taken to South Africa the sum of US$ 26.5 Million (Twenty -Six Million Five Hundred Thousand United States Dollars) which he deposited with a Security Company as if he foresaw the looming danger in Zimbabwe. The money was deposited in a box as VALUABLES AND PERSONAL EFFECTS to avoid much demurrage from the Security Company. This money was for purchase of new machinery and chemical for farms and the establishment of new farms in Lesotho and Swaziland. This land problem arose when President Robert Mugabe introduced a new land act that wholly affected the rich white farmers and some few blacks vehemently condemned the "modus operandi" adopted by the government. This resulted to rampant killing and mob action by the war veterans and some political thugs. Precisely, More than thirty-eight (38) people have so far been killed. Heads of governments from the west, especially Britain and United States of America have voiced their condemnation of Mugabe'splan. Subsequently, South African Development Community (S.A.D.C) has continuously supported Mugabe's new land act, it is against this background that I and my family who are currently residing in South Africa have decided to transfer my Father's money into a foreign account. As the eldest son of my Father, I am saddled with the responsibility of seeking a genuine foreign account where this money could be transferred without the knowledge of my government who are tactically freezing our family wealth and South Africa's government seems to be playing along with them. I am faced with the dilemma of investing this money in South Africa for fear of encountering the same experience in future since both countries have almost the same political history. More so, the South African Foreign Exchange policy does not allow such investment hence we are seeking for an "ASYLUM". As a business person whom I entrusted my future and that of my family into his hands, I must let you know that this transaction is 100% risk-free and the nature of your business does not necessarily matter. For your assistance, we are offering you 20% of the total sum, 75% for me and my family while 5% will be mapped out for any expenses we may be incured during the course of this transaction. We wish to invest our part of the money on commercial property based on your advice. Finally, all i want from you is assurance that you will not betray my trust. If this appeal is acceptable to you, please confirm your interest via the above telephone number or better still email. Best Regards. Mr.Nicholas Kular (For the Family).

Dear, Meade First, i must solicit your strictest confidence in this transaction, this is by virture of it nature as being utterly confidential and top secret.study this portion carefully and advice categorically, if you will be able to handle,as i might not want to be exposed of the information considering the source and reputation of my name. I am Mr.Adams Williams the newly appointed chairman, contract reviewing committee(CRC) of the ministry of works and housing (FMW&H) in Lome,Togo. I am seeking your assistance to enable me transfer the sum of US$17,000,000.00 into your account for mutual benefits. This money came about as a result of contract executed on behalf of my ministry,the (ministry of works and housing).This contract was officially assigned to be awarded and executed by two foreign contractors at the tune of US$80,000,000.00,but in the course of our negotiation, we bargaineed with only one foreign contractor, a bulgarian firm which now executed the contract at the cost of US$63,500,000.00.Thus leaving the remaining US$17M to our (members of the CRP) benefits unknown to the contractor any other person in my ministry.This contract has been satisfactorily executed and inspected as the bulgarian firm is presently securing his payment from my ministry. It is however to this effect that i seek your maximum assistance and approval to present your company name alongside with bulgarian contractor as the second foreign contractor to enable me transfer the difference (US$17M) into your account for further investment depending on your advice. On actualization of the transaction, fund will be shared thus: 1. 40% of the money go to you for acting as the beneficiary of the funds. 2. 10% for reimbursement to both parties for incidential expenses that may be incurred in the course of the transaction for insurance,phone bills,documentation etc. 3. 50% for me. All logistics are in place and all modalities worked out for the smooth actualization of the transaction within fourteen working days of commencement after receiving the following information by fax:your company's name, address, phone/fax numbers and the activities of your company. The above information will enable me make application and lodge claims to concerned ministries in favour of your company or name and it is pertinent to state here that this deal is entirely based on trust and the fear of God. If you are able to handle this,feel free to reach at {adams_williams2001@yahoo.co.uk} for a perfect understanding of the transaction. Thanks in anticipation of your positive response. Yours faithfully. Mr.Adams Williams. ___________________________________________________________________________ Con Terra MAIL obtienes 6MB de espacio además de bloqueo ANTISPAM http://terramail.terra.com.mx/TerraMail/ Acceso a Internet 3 x 1, desde ¡$179 pesos al mes! http://www.terra.com.mx/acceso/suscribete/ Encuentra los mejores productos y precios increibles!! Aprovecha nuestra promoción a 12 pagos sin intereses con Banamex y Bancomer http://www.decompras.com/

Greetings Dear Friend Please Permit me to contact you through this medium. I am Barrister Tunji Bello, a solicitor at-law. I was the personal attorney to one of my late clients that used to work with an indigenous company here in my country.In summer 2001, my client, his wife and their three children were involved in an auto-crash while on a picnic-trip. Unfortunately, all occupants of the vehicle lost their lives. Since then I have made several enquiries to his embassy to locate any of my clients extended relatives and this has also proved unsuccessful. After these several unsuccessful attempts, I decided to contact you over Internet. I have contacted you to assist in receiving and accommodating the money left behind by my client before they get confiscated or declared unserviceable by the bank where these huge deposits were lodged. My deceased client had an account balance with his bank valued at about US$9.9million, and I have been issued a notice as his attorney to provide his next of kin or have the account confiscated. Since I have been unsuccessful in locating my client's relatives; I now seek your consent to present you as the next of kin of my deceased client so that the proceeds of his account (US$9.9million) can be paid to you. You and I can then share the money 60% to me and 40% for you. All I require is your honest cooperation to enable us seeing this project through. I guarantee that this will be executed under a legitimate/risk-free arrangement that will protect you and me from any breach of the law. I await your positive response to my private email address at tunji_b333@yahoo.com as soon as you read this email. Best Regards, Barrister Tunji Bello ___________________________________________________________________________ Mail sent from WebMail service at PHP-Nuke Powered Site - http://www.duhe.com

ATTENTION Dear; I am delighted to write this letter to you hoping that you will understand my predicament and answer back without hesitation. I am MRS.MARIAM ABACHA wife of the late Nigerian Head of State GENERAL SANI ABACHA. I got your contact through business inquires from the chamber or commerce as I was making contact for a Honest foreigner who will help save my life and my children, hence our country has been frustrating to us since the death of my husband. I am in possession of $35,000.000 (THIRTY FIVE MILLION U.S DOLLARS) which I want to invest in your country. For your clarification and understanding, this money is in a truck box which was deposited with a security company indisguise as a family treasure DIAMOND AND GOLD since 5th of May 1999. it is not an ill gotten wealth rather it was WILLED to me by my late husband. On your acceptance to render this assistance to me, I will instruct the security company to effect the change of ownership of this fund to your name as the bona-fide owner/my next of kin to enable you retrieve the fund since the box can not be moved out of our country by the family's name. It is very important that you forward to me your full name ,your private telephone and fax numbers/occupation,to enable me send all relevant documents pertaining the deposit of this fund to you. Bear in mind that this transaction demands absolute confidentiality because all properties,assets and bank accounts both local and international bearing the ABACHA'S family name, are been confiscated by the Already elected civilian President of Nigeria so called (President Olusegun Obasanjo)hence I will not want to be exposed this is to aviod losing the money. For your knowledge, 20% of this fund $35,000.000 (THIRTY FIVE MILLION U.S DOLLARS) will be given to you if you assist me to secure this fund and another 10% has set aside for all the expenses you might incur during the process of securing this fund. Example: TELEPHONE/FAX BILLS and any other miscellaneous expenses. And bear in mind that this is the only remaining fund for the survival of my family. Nevertheless if you are in any reason not intrested in this proposal kindly inform me so that i will start to look for another reliable contact Thanks as I wait for your immediate response Please you can view this website and see how my family's name is been messed up; Yours truly. Dr.MRS MARIAM ABACHA

From: Barrister Jim Douglas. Attorneys/Legal Practitioner Dakar Senegal Dear Friend, Compliments of the day. Grace and peace and love >From this part of the Atlantic. Dear Friend, I am Barrister jim douglas, a Solicitor and Advocate, the personal attorney to late Mr. Neil Frazer a National of France, who used to be a private contractor with the Shell Petroleum Development Company in Senegal, herein after shall be referred to as my client. On the 21st of April 2001, he and his wife with their three children were involved in an auto crash, all occupants of the vehicle unfortunately lost their lives. Since then, I have made several enquiries with his country's embassies to locate any of my clients extended relatives: This has proved unsuccessful. After these several unsuccessful attempts, I decided to contact you with this business partnership proposal. I have contacted you to assist in repatriating a huge amount of money left behind by my client before they get confiscated or declared unserviceable by the Finance/Security Company where this huge deposit was lodged. The deceased had a deposit valued presently at $21million US Dollars and the Company has issued me a notice to provide his next of kin or Beneficiary by Will otherwise have the account confiscated within the next thirty official working days. Since I have been unsuccessful in locating the relatives for over 2 Years now, I seek your consent to present you as the next of kin / Will Beneficiary to the deceased so that the proceeds of this account valued at $21Million US dollars can be paid to you. This will be disbursed or shared in these percentages, 60% to me and 40% to you. I have all necessary legal documents that can be used to back up any claim we may make. All I require is your honest Co-operation, Confidentiality and Trust to enable us see this transaction through. I guarantee you that this will be executed under a legitimate arrangement that will protect you from any breach of the law. Please get in touch with me urgently by E-mail: bar_jim123@yahoo.com <mailto:bar_jim123@yahoo.com>. I am presently in Dakar. Please, provide me the following: 1. Full Name 2. Your Telephone Number and Fax Number 3. Your Contact Address. Your urgent response will be highly anticipated and appreciated. Best regards, Truly yours, Jim Douglas, Esq. +221 50 65 447

#20 Louis Botha Avenue, Johannesburg.South Africa. Tel: +874763591545 Fax: +874763591546 (URGENT TRANSFER) Good Day My Dear, We want to transfer to overseas the sum of One hundred and Forfty Two Million United States Dollars (U.S.$142,000,000.00) from a in Africa. I want to ask you to kindly look for a reliable and honest person who will be capable and fit to provide either an existing bank account or to set up a new bank account immediately to receive this oney,though an empty bank account could serve this purpose as long as you will remain honest to me till the end of this important business trusting in you and believing in God that you will never let me down either now or in time to come. I am Mr.Sam White ,the external auditor of a Bank.During the course of our auditing,I discovered a floating fund in an account opened in the bank in 1990 and since 1993 nobody has operated on this account again.After going through some old files in the records, I discovered that the owner of the account died without a Heir apparent to the throne hence the money is floating and if I do not remit this money out urgently it will be forfeited for nothing. The owner of this account who is Mr.Eshed.B.Willey,a foreigner and an industrialist died, since 1990,until now no other person(s) knows about this account or could give any documentary evidence concerning this account. As such this account has no other beneficiary and my investigation proved to me as well that Eshed.B.Willey until his death was the manager Oriental Diamond Company,in South Africa. However, if you are interested in this business we will start the first money transfer with Forfty Two Million U.S.Dollars (U.S.$42,000,000.00) upon successful transaction without any disappointment from you. We shall also re-apply for the payment of the remaining amount to your account. While the total amount involved is One hundred and Forfty Two Million United States Dollars (U.S.$142000,000.00)only. I would want us to make a first transfer of Forfty Two Million United States Dollar.(U.S.$4200,000.00)from this money into a safe foreigners account abroad before the rest. I am only contacting you as a foreigner because this money can not be approved to a local account, without valid international foreign Agreement, but could only be approved to any foreigner with valid international credentials: passport or drivers license and foreign account because this sum is in U.S. dollars and the former owner of the account Mr.Eshed.B.Willey is a foreigner too, thus the money could only be approved into a foreign account. However, knowing all this, we will reach a binding agreement in this regards.As a matter of urgency, I will inform you the next step to take, while you Send your private telephone and fax number including the full details of the account to be used for the deposit.I want us to meet face to face to build confidence and to sign a binding agreement that will bind us together before transferring the money to any account of your choice where the fund will be safe.sharing and investments. I need your full co-operation to make this business a success, because the management is ready to approve this payment to any foreigner who has correct information of this account,which I will give to you,upon your positive response and once I am convinced that you are capable and will meet up with the instructions of a key bank official who is deeply involved with me in this business. I need your strong assurance that you will never let me down. I would like you to send me your information as stated below: (1) Your Private: Tele& Fax Number : (2) Bank Name: (3) Bank Address: (4) Account Number: (5) Account Name: (6) Swift Code / Routing Number if any: With my influence and the position in the bank we can transfer this money to any foreigner's reliable account which you can provide with assurance that this money will be intact pending our physical arrival in your country for sharing. And to build confidence that you can come immediately to discuss with me face to face after which I will make this remittance in your presence and three of us will fly to your country at least two days ahead of the money going into the account. I will apply for annual leave to get visa immediately I hear from you that you are ready to act as directed. To prove the authenticity of the business I will use my position and influence to obtain all legal approvals for onward transfer of this money to your account with appropriate clearance from the relevant ministries,foreign exchange departments, embassy and Board of Internal Revenue services. At the conclusion of this business, you will be given 35% of the total amount, 60% will be for me,while 5% will be for expenses both parties might have incurred during this process. I look forward to your earliest reply. Regards and God Bless, Mr White. -------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- Nueva Barra de Herramientas de OZÚ. Navega Más facilmente por Internet. ¡Descargatela gratis! http://barra.ozu.es/ -------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- Correo enviado desde http://www.ozu.es

>From : Nicholas Mavis Abidjan Ivory coast TEl: +225 0723 6068 private email : ( nicholas_mavis11@yahoo.co.uk <mailto:nicholas_mavis11@yahoo.co.uk>) APPEAL FOR URGENT ASSISTANCE. Dear With due respect and with God all thing were possible that is why I call for help to please Permit me to inform you of my desire of going into business relationship with you. I am Nicholas Mavis the only son of late Mavis Decot, My father was a very wealthy cocoa merchant in Abidjan the economic capital of Ivory coast, my father was poisoned to death by his business associates on the first of January 2004 on their outing for the new year celebration. My mother died when I was a baby and since then my father took me so special. Before the death of my father on january 2004 in a private hospital here in Abidjan he secretly called me on his bed side and told me that he has the sum of 9 million United State Dollars. US(9.m) left in fixed /suspense account in one of the prime bank here in Abidjan that he used my name as his only son for the next of Kin in Depositing of the fund. He told me that I should seek for a foreign partner in a country of my choice where i will transfer this money into and use it for investment purpose such as real estate management or hotel management and also for orphanages, helping the widows, propagating the word of God and to endeavour that the house of God is maintained and building companies where poor God people can work and have their daily feedings with their families. I pray to God to grant you more blessing to your business and for making up your mind that you will be doing this for the denefit of the people who are in need. i know that God will see you through. I am honourably seeking your assistance in the following ways: (1) To provide a new bank account in where this money would be transferred into. (2) To serve as a guardian of this fund since I am only 22 years old. (3) To make arrangement for me to come over to your country to further my education and to secure a resident permit in your country. Moreover, I am willing to offer you 25% of the total sum as compensation for your effort/input after the successful transfer of this fund into your nominated account overseas. All the necessary arrangement has been made at the bank where my late father deposited this money and the Director of the bank told me that as soon as an account of my choice is forwarded to their bank that they will transfer this money to my destination. Please RING me immediately you received this mail on my direct line +225 0723 6068 for us to proceed in this transaction which I beleived that in few days you shall call me for good news that you have comfirm my money in an account which you will provide. Furthermore, you indicate your options towards assisting me as I believe that this transaction would be concluded within (3) days you signify interest to assist me. Anticipating to hear your voice immediately. Thanks and God bless you. Best regards, Nicholas Mavis . All the relevants documents which my late father used in deposting of this money will be sent to you immediately I hear from you for more confirmation and trust and confidence in this transaction. PLEASE GET BACK TO ME ON MY PRIVATE EMAIL / (nicholas_mavis11@yahoo.co.uk <mailto:nicholas_mavis11@yahoo.co.uk>)

NAME:MRS.SUZANA NUHAN VAYE %BARR.JAMES BRODERICK(ATTORNEY) TEL:44-7040120730 FAX:44-870-1348903 EMAIL:brrjmsbroderick@kaixo.com EMAIL:barjmsbroderick@yahoo.com.hk ATTN: MD/CEO Kindly accept my apology for sending my mail to you. I am a true God fearing person, and I want you to trust me and help me out in this my condition. I believe you are a highly respected personality, considering the fact that I sourced your profile from a human resource profile database on your country in the Internet. Though, I do not know to what extent you are familiar with events and fragile political situation in Liberia but it has formed consistent headlines in the CNN, BBC news bulletins. My Name is MRS.SUZANA NUHAN VAYE from Liberia, a Country in West Africa. My late Husband is Issac Nuhan Vaye, Deputy Minister of Public Works in Liberia. My Husband was falsely accused of plotting to remove the then PRESIDENT OF LIBERIA CHARLES TAYLOR) from office. Without trial, Charles Taylor killed him. You can verify this from some of the international newspapers posted in the web sites below: (I)http://www.usatoday.com/news/world/2003-07-15-liberia_x.htm Before my husband was killed, he moved out the sum of $21.5 million through a diplomatic means, and deposited it with a Security Company Abroad. And this money was meant for importation of agricultural machineries. All that is needed is for my lawyer to instruct the company to transfer the funds to your account, I will remunerate you with 20% at the end, but most of all is that I solicit your trust and honesty in this transaction. I have been confined only to our country home and all my calls are monitored, so I will advise you contact my private Attorney Barr. P.O.Williams base in United Kingdom on his contact stated below for onward proceedings: - NAME:BARR.JAMES BRODERICK(ATTORNEY) TEL:44-7040120730 FAX:44-870-1348903 EMAIL:brrjmsbroderick@kaixo.com EMAIL:barjmsbroderick@yahoo.com.hk Kindly include your Full Name, Private Telephone and Fax Numbers where you can always be reached, your Residential or Company Address to enable him send detail information/documents that will enable you receive the fund without any problem either now or in future as all modalities as been perfected. Please your urgent response is needed. Best Regards. MRS.SUZANA NUHAN VAYE (WIDOW) ___________________________________________________________________________ Email enviado desde- http://www.ddklan.org/armageddons

Dearest One, I am Madam.Adele Mbonjo,the former manager of the Central African Republic's former President Bédel Bokassa Boganda. I'm presently in house arrest here in Bangui the state capital, after the military's putch. I found your address in the commercial directory we have in our Chamber of Commerce. First of all, I'm very sorry for the way I get in touch with you for such a matter. But because of poor or un-reliable communication technology and the confidentiality of this business, are the reasons that prompted me to do so. I would like to have a partnership with you, in order to invest a sum of thirty five Million USD(35,000,000 USD) in profitable sectors in your country, as long as you are interested in my offer. I got this money from cash donations by foreign contractors I've granted many contracts in my department. As a close aide to the former President, I couldn't use our banking system to transfer such an amount without a trace. This could cause me a serious problem . Even presently, the new President has decided to freeze all the abroad banking accounts of all those who were close to Mr. Boganda. We are placed under security close watch while my travelling papers are seized. During my tenure in government, I used the government decoy system to carry out this money abroad where know one know about in packaged box. I will inform you as soon as we progress for future claims due to the instability in politics here presently. The security holding company are not aware of the contents hence I coded it as Gold Bar/Personal Effect. So I'm now without any source of Income. The situation above has lead me to ask for your co-operation for the claiming out of the security holding company for further safe-keeping of these funds, for solid and reliable projects of investment. I respectfully suggest a gift of 20% of this sum for your help and your efforts. I mean USD $7,000,000 Million. I rely on you as a respectful and honest person to take care of this transaction with sincerity, confidence and confidentiality. I've decided to look for a confidential co-operation with you in this business, despite the fact that we've never met. I hope you will keep this as a great confidential business because of the nature of this transaction. I will make sure you take possession of the funds, by providing a process without difficulties. I would like to hear from you on receipt of this mail, by showing me your good will and possibilities, so that I can give you more details. This matter requires a particular attention and an absolute confidentiality from you. I will be expecting your response to this mail, whatever the decision you come up with, let me know through this my private email Yours Sincerely, Madam.Adele Mbonjo

Dear Friend. My name is Mr. Felix Kambala, the manager credit and foreign bills of African Developement Bank Ltd Dakar Senegal Branch . I am writing in respect of a foreign customer of my bank with account number 14-255-2004/adb/t, Mr.Gerald Smith who died in a plane crash (EgyptAir Flight 990)which crashed into the Atlantic Ocean on October 31st,1999 with other passengers on board.You can view this web site for more story of the inccident http://www.cnn.com/US/9911/02/egyptair990.list/index.html Since the death of this customer, I personally have watched with keen interest to see the next of kin but all has proved abortive as no one has come to claim his funds of US$13,000,000.00(Thirteen Million Dollars) which has been with my bank for a very long time. On this note I decided to seek for whose name shall be used as the next of kin as no one has come up to be the next of kin. In view of this I got your contact through my country?s foreign trade mission after I was convinced by providence that your name could be used as the next of kin.The request of the foreigner as a next of kin in this business is occasioned by thefact that the customer was a foreigner and a Senegalias cannot stand as the next of kin to a Foreign client I agreed that 30% of this money will be for you as a foreign partner in respect of providing a new bank account or we can use your old accountinformation,while the rest will be for me, thereafter, I will visit your country for disbursement as I am almost due for retirement.Therefore, to facilitate the immediate transfer of this fund to your account as arranged, we must engage the services of a lawyer to apply on your behalf to the bank as a relation to the deceased.I need you to indicate in your response, your private telephone and fax numbers for easy communication and your complete bank information where the money will be remitted into for our mutual benefit. Upon the receipt of your reply, I will send you by fax or e-mail the next step to take. I will not fail to bring to your notice that this business is hitch-free and that you should not entertain any fear as every modality and machinery for the success of this transaction have been put in place. You should contact me immediately as soon as you receive this letter strictly on email for security reasons. Trusting to hear from you. Your respectfully, Mr. Felix Kambala.

FROM: Mr.Daniel Mensah, GRAND FINANCE AND TRUST BANK. RUE CLUB DE L' AMITIE, 0251 B.P. 1625 COTONOU, BéNIN REPUBLIQUE. My Dear Friend, In Oder to transfer to overseas $28.5 million(USD) from GRAND FINANCE AND TRUST BANK,Bénin Republique. I want to ask you to quietly look for a reliable and honest person who will be capable and fit to provide either an existing bank account or to set up a new Bank a/c immediately to receive this money, even an empty a/c can serve to receive this funds quitely. I am Mr.Daniel Mensah, the accountant/auditor of the above Finance Corporation in Cotonou,Bénin Republique and personal confidant to Mr.Alvaro Quesada of Dominican Republic in Caribbean Island who died in a Plane Crash accident(2002-04-19) on his way to attend a weddind ceremony together with his wife and only Child (Alvaro Jr). Mr.Alvaro Quesada, is From Dominican Republic in Caribbean Island, and a prosperous Tobacco merchant, he died in the year 2002 without having any beneficiary to his assets including his account here in Bénin which he opened in the above stated bank in the year 2001 as his personal savings for the purpose of expansion and developement of his company in Africa before his untimely death in 2002.Until his death,he was the president of the Dominican Tobacco Exporters Association. And from my Investigation,i found out that No other person knows about this account because he( Mr.Alvaro Quesada )never knew that he is going to die so soon, and so his purpose was not achieved. If i don't remit this money immediately, it will get lost(may be it will go into the pockets of the corrupt government officials who will never use it for any reasonable thing at all).I dont want to miss this opportunity because it comes ones in a life time. The amount involved is $28.5 million(USD)Twenty eight million,five hundred United States Dollars and no other person knows about this account. I am contacting you for us to transfer this funds to your account as the beneficiary,I want to first transfer $16,000.000.00(Sixteen million USD) from this money into a safe account abroad, after which we will transfer the remaining (12.5M). I am only contacting you as a foreigner because this money cannot be approved to a local person here, without a valid foreign international passport, but can only be approved to any foreigner with valid international passport or drivers license and foreign a/c, this is because the money is in US Dollars and the former owner of the a/c, Alvaro Quesada is a foreigner too, and as such the money can only be approved into a foreign a/c. However, I am revealing this to you with belief in God that you will never let me down in this business.I don't know you and have never seen you before,i only got your contacts from an international directory which my secretary provided for me. You are the first and the only person that I am contacting for this business, so please reply urgently so that I will inform you the next step to take. Send also your private telephone and fax number. I need your full co-operation to make this work because the management is ready to approve this payment to any foreigner who has correct information of this account,which I will give to you, upon your positive response and once I am convinced that you are capable and will meet up with instruction of a keybank official who is deeply involved with me in this business. I want to tell you that this transaction is 100% risk free and legal because all the documents that will back up this transaction will be available, so that no body will question the fund when it is finaly tranfered to your account. At the conclusion of this business, you will be given 40% of the total amount and 60% will be for me. I look forward to your earliest reply through this email. Thanks for your time. Your's faithfully, Mr.Daniel Mensah

Hello My Dear, Please forgive my indignation if this message comes to you as a surprise I got your contact from a database found in internet while searching for a reliable and honest person that will assist us receive a fund intoan account.I was divinely inspired to pick your name among other names found in the Internet database. After series of prayers and fasting for Gods direction. I am Mrs.Angelina Ebony Dazza a citizen of Columbia undergoing currently medical treatment. I am married to Dr. Dazza Lamin who worked with the Malaysia Embassy in South Africa for nine years before he died in the year 2000. We were married for eleven years without a child.He died after a brief illness that lasted for only four days. Before his death we were both born again Christians. Since his death I decided not to re-marry or get a child outside my matrimonial home which the Bible is against. When my late husband was alive he deposited the sum of $15 Million (Fifteen million U.S.Dollars) with a finance/security company in ASIA.The money is inside one trunk boxes, but nobody knew that the boxes contained money apart from me and my late husband, the boxes was deposited as Photographic Materials. Presently, this money is still with the Security Company. Recently, my Doctor told me that I would not live for the next three months due to my cancer problem. Though what disturbs me most is my disability to move around which is a partial paralysis. Having known my condition I decided to donate this fund to a church or a mosque or better still a Christian or a Moslem individual that will utilize this money the way I am going to instruct herein. I want a church or Mosque or the individual beneficiary that will inherit this to use it for churches or Mosque orphanages and widows propagating the word of God and to ensure that the house of God is beautified.They said blessed is the hand that giveth. I took this decision because I do not have any child that will inherit this money and my husband's relatives are not Christians and I don't want my husband's hard earned money to be mis-used by unbelievers. I do not want a situation where this money will be used in an ungodly manner,hence the reason for taking this bold decision.I am not afraid of death because I know where I am going. I know that I am going to be in the bossom of my Saviour. If you feel you are worthy enough to make yourself available in this project, let me know immediately you read my mail. GOD will surely provide for you the power and strenght to accomplish this. All things work together for good for those who love GOD. Waiting for your urgent response. I do not need any telephone conversation in this regard because of my health,and because of the presence of my husband?s relatives who are always around me. I do not want them to know about this development. Thank you and God bless. Yours sincerely, Mrs.Angelina Ebony Lamin.

FROM:                  MARY JOHN

Beloved,

I am the above named person from Liberia, presently staying in England. I am married to Mr. Cletus John who worked with Liberian Embassy in Zambia for nine years before he died in the year 2003. We were married for eleven (11) years without a child and he died after a brief illness that lasted for just four (4) days.

Before his death, we were both born- again Christians, since my husband’s death, I have decided never to re-marry or have a child outside my matrimonial home which the bible is against. When my late husband was still alive he deposited the sum of US$10,500,000.00 (Ten Million, Five Hundred Thousand United States Dollars only) with a Security Company in Europe in my name and this money is still with the Security Company up till this moment. Recently, my doctor notified me that I have less than eight (8) months to live due to my cancer problem but the one that bothers me most is my stroke sickness. Having known my condition, I decided to leave this fund in Europe.

I want an organization or an individual that will use this fund for orphanages, widows, propagating the word of God and to endeavour that the house of God is fully maintained. My Bible tell me that "Blessed is the hand that gives, I took this decision because I do not have any child that will inherit this money and my husband’s relatives are not Christians and I do not want my husband’s effort to be used by un-believers.

I do not want a situation where this money will be used in an ungodly way, this is the reason I am taking this decision, and moreover I am not afraid of death because I know where I am going. I know that I am going to be in the bosom of our Lord. Exodus 14 VS 14 says that the Lord will fight my case and I shall hold my peace. Telephone communications will be minimal in this regard because of my health and also being fully aware of the presence of my husband’s relatives and my doctors who are always around me. I do not want them to know about this development for I know that with God all things are Possible.

As soon as I receive your reply, I will inform the Security Company in Europe that you are the beneficiary of the said consignment and you will need to go and claim this fund in Europe. I will also issue you an authorization letter that will prove that you are the rightful beneficiary to the fund. I want you and your organization to always pray for me because the Lord is my Strength, Shepherd and my Help. My happiness is that I lived a life of a worthy Christian and whosoever that wants to serve our Lord must serve him in spirit and in truth. Please always be prayerful for God is our source and once we are separated from our source, we are dead spiritually which automatically manifests in the physical.

Any delay in your reply will give me room in sourcing for another person for this same purpose. Please assure me that you will act accordingly as I stated herein. If you want to talk by phone, you can send your telephone number by fax so that if my health permits me, I can call you or if you have message, you can equally call my doctor’s telephone number 00447040120051. DR. CHARLES

Hoping to receive your reply soon and remain blessed in the Lord.

Yours in Christ,

MRS. MARY JOHN

Urgent Assistance pls.

Please you are to reply me with this E-mail: barrstevenwa301@yahoo.co.uk

From Barr.Steve Nwa.

Attn: Sir/Madam.

I am Barrister Steve Nwa(SAN), a Solicitor. I am the Personal Attorney to mrs. Ann Parker, a national of your country,. I have an urgent and very confidential business proposition for you.On December 8, 1999, an American Oil consultant/contractor with the Nigerian National Petroleum Corporation, Mrs. Ann Parker. made a numbered time (Fixed) Deposit for twelve calendar months, valued at US$14.6,000,000.00(Fourteen Million, Six Hundred thousand Dollars) in my branch. Upon maturity, I sent a routine notification to her forwarding address but got no reply.

After a month, I sent a reminder and finally i discovered from her contract employers, the Nigerian National Petroleum Corporation that Mrs. Ann Parker. died from a ghastly automobile accident.

On further investigation, I found out that she died without making a WILL, and all attempts to trace her next of kin was fruitless.I therefore made further investigation and discovered that Mrs. Ann Parker. did not declare any next of kin or relations in all her official documents, including her Bank Deposit paperwork in her Bank. This sum of US$14.6,000,000.00 is still sitting in her Bank and the interest is being rolled over with the principal sum at the end of each year. No one will ever come forward to claim it. According to Nigerian Law, at the expiration of 7 (seven) years, the money will revert to the ownership of the Nigerian Government if nobody applies to claim this fund.

Consequently, my proposal is that I will like you as a foreigner to stand in as the next of kin to Mrs. Ann Parker. so that the fruits of this woman's labuor will not get into the hands of some corrupt government officials.

This is simple, I will like you to provide immediately your full names and address so that i will prepare the necessary documents and affidavits which will put you in place as the next of kin.

I will drafting and notarization of the WILL and to obtain the necessary documents and letter of probate/ administration in your favour for the transfer. I would need you as a Foreigner acting as the next of kin and sole benefactor to the inheritance of Mrs. Ann Parker. to travel and claim this money in a SECURITY COMPANY based in Europe which is used by her bank as an offshore payment center to the bank. The money will be paid to you for us to share in the ratio of 60% for me and 30% for you then 10% for any expensee that may come up. There is no risk at all as all the paperwork for this transaction will be done by me with my position as Attorney guarantees the successful execution of this transaction. If you are interested, please reply immediately. Upon your response, I shall then provide you with more details and relevant documents that will help you understand the transaction.

Please observe utmost confidentiality, and rest assured that this transaction would be most profitable for both of us because I shall require your assistance to invest my share in your country.

Awaiting your urgent reply

Thanks and regards.

Barr. Steve Nwa. AlternativeE-mail: ifoma_n@yahoo.co.uk

DR. MORGAN XHOSA, DEPARTMENT OF MINERALS AND ENERGY, PRETORIA, SOUTH AFRICA. EMAIL:morganxhosa2005@workmail.co.za ATTN:Sir/Madam, STRICTLY CONFIDENTIAL & URGENT It is my great pleasure to write you this letter on behalf of my colleagues. Your information was given to me by a member of the South African Export Promotion Council (SAEPC) who was with the Government delegation on a trip to your country for a bilateral conference talk to encourage foreign investors. I have decided to seek a confidential co-operation with you in the execution of the deal hereunder for the benefit of all parties and hope you will keep it confidential because of the nature of this business. Within the Department of Minerals & Energy where I work as a Director of Audit and Project Implementation and with the co-operation of two other t! ! op officials, we have in our possession an overdue payment in US funds. The said funds represent certain percentage of the total contract value executed on behalf of my Department by a foreign contracting firm, which we the officials over-invoiced to the amount of US$26.500,000.00 (TwentySix Million Five Hundred Thousand US Dollars). Though the actual contract cost has been paid to the original contractor, leaving the excess balance unclaimed. Since the present elected Government is determined to pay foreign contractors all debts owed, so as to maintain good relationship with foreign governments and non-government agencies, we included our bills for approvals with the Department of Finance and the South Africa Reserve Bank (SARB). We are seeking your assistance to front as beneficiary of the unclaimed funds, since we are not allowed to operate foreign accounts. Details and change of beneficiary information upon application for claim to reflect payment and approvals will be secured on behalf of you/your Company. I have the authority of my partners involved to propose that should you be willing to assist us in this transaction your share as compensation will be US$6.625m (25%), while my colleagues and I receive US$17.225m (65%) and the balance of US$2.650m (10%) for taxation and miscellaneous expenses incurred. The business is completely safe and secure, provided you treat it with utmost confidentiality. It does not matter whether you/your Company does contract projects, as a transfer of powers will be secured in favour of you/your Company. Also, your area of specialization is not a hindrance to the successful execution of this transaction. I have reposed my confidence in you and hope that you will not disappoint us. Kindly notify me by my email address:morganxhosa2005@workmail.co.za for further details upon your acceptance of this proposal. T! ! hanks for your co-operation. Regards, DR.MORGAN XHOSA. N.B Please email your confidential Telephone number to enable me contact you for further clarifications.

>From Mr.Joseph Cabutti 20 SILVER CRESCENT, Enugu,Nigeria. Compliment of the day I am Joseph Cabutti the consulting auditor with one of the prime banks here in Nigeria. My search for a trustworthy individual/firm has led me to you. I came across your contact while looking for a worthwhile investments or projects that I can be affiliated with. I am writing you this letter to ask for your support and co-operation to carry out this transaction. The proposition An industrialist and a foreigner who was customer of my client bank, who died on the 25TH JULY, 2000 in CONCORDE PLANE CRASH [Flight AF4590] with the whole passengers on board. During the course of my auditing discovered an account opened in the bank in 1998 by this great late NDUSTRIALIST who died without a written or oral 'WILL' attached to the account. Since his death, I further investigated with kin interest to see if I can get any relative of the late industrialist but all has proved abortive as no one has come to claim his funds and no other person knows about this account or anything concerning it. The account has no other beneficiary and until his death he was the CEO of his company work with my client bank, he had a balance of $36,000,000.00 USD {Thirty six million united states dollars} which the bank now expects a next of kin to claim as beneficiary, Valuable efforts are being made to get in touch with any of the relatives but to no success. It is because of the perceived possibility of not being able to locate any the next of kin and the beneficiary. The management under the influence of the Chairman and members of the Board of Directors of the bank, are making arrangement for the funds to be declared "UNCLAIMED" and will be lost to the Federal Government or subsequently be donated to the Trust Fund for Arms and Ammunition to further enhance the course of war in Africa. In order to avert this negative development, I now seek your permission to have you stand as a next of kin to late beneficiary so that the funds USD36m would be released and paid into your account as the beneficiary next of kin. We wish to start the first transfer with $10,000,000.00[Ten million] and upon successful transaction without any disappointment from your side; we shall re-apply for the transfer of the remaining balance to your account. I have secretly discussed this matter with a close confidant attorney whom I must involve in order to assist us produce legal back-up documents which would substantiate your claims and also enable us have a smooth and successful transfer of the fund to any foreign bank account which you are going to nominate. On this note, We have secured from the probate an order of mandamus to locate any of deceased beneficiary and more so we are assuring you this business is 100% risk free involvement you should not entertain any fear as all modalities for fund transfer can be finalized within 7 to 9 banking days, after you apply to the bank as the beneficiary of the fund from the deceased. At the conclusion of the transfer 65% of the fund will be for me, I will give you 20% of the total transfer sum, 10% for charity both in Africa and in your country while the remaining 5% will be set aside to settle expenses both parties might incure during the transfer process. If this proposal is acceptable by you do not make undue advantage of the trust we have bestowed on you, then kindly get to me immediately. Please furnish me with your private Telephone and Fax Number for easy and safe communication. Respectfully yours, Joseph Cabutti.

From: Mrs. Mary Kobe, 17 Stuttgart Avenue, Randburg, Johannesburg, Republic of South Africa. Dear Sir, VERY CONFIDENTIAL PLEASE I have been waiting for the Military to hand-over government of Sierra Leone to the Civillian. I am Mrs. Mary Kobe, widow of late General John Kobe. I procured your contact information from my search for a reliable person who is capable of handling such a proposal of such a magnitude, as my late husband has made it that this proposal herein will be at the betterment of his family, as the person to be the foreign partner will take good care of his investment and family as well. My late husband was one of the victims of the Civil war. I have been informed by one of our family's attorney who is a South African citizen with the name Barrister Barrister cliff Alexaandern that my late husband operated a secret account with a fictitious name in the FIRST NATIONAL BANK here in Johannesburg. In this account, he has (Thirty-nine Million Dollars) $39,000,000 only, which was credited in his favour. In my husband's 'WILL' he stated that one of his partners overseas will take care of his family/properties. The attorney is waiting for my late husband's partner overseas who is to take care of his family/properties according to his WILL. Since no mention was made in the WILL as to who the said partner is, I want you to take advantage of this upon receipt of this email, you are to contact the family attorney with the following information: Name: Barrister cliff Alexaander. Address: 17 Brixton Street, Orange Groove, Johannesburg. RSA> Phone: +27=83-540-6943. Fax: +27-86-640-4824. Email: cliffattorneys@webmail.co.za.or:cliff@mailbox.co.za Try to contact this lawyer as urgent as possible with the following reference: Amount deposited: $39,000,000 US Dollar. Bank: First National Bank of South Africa. Month/Year of Account: July, 1999. Secret Code: 43/99FNB/MBW/13.00131/7. It has been resolved by the family that 20% of the total fund shall be your share for presenting yourself for this purpose/assistance you will give in this regard,while 10% mapped-out for the re-enbursement of all local and international expenses, which will be incurred in the transfer process. Finally the remaining 70% is for myself and my children, which a good part of this fund shall be directed towards executing my husband's WILL, which is to buy shares and stocks in foriegn countries, in order to secure our children's future. To facilitate this transaction, please send your telephone and fax number, throough which you will be contacted immediately by our attorney, which his information is written above. Note: This is our life and I trust you with it. I want you to reciprocate the same trust, which I repose in you. Give this matter a prompt and quick response. Please, direct your response VIA to our family attorney whom the information is written above and discuss with him towards the effective conpletion of this transaction/how to get this fund out of the bank. My assurance to you is that this transaction is hundred percent risk-free. Best regards, Mrs. Mary Kobe.

Dear Sir/Madam, My name is Mr. Jenif Davix, I work as the operational manager in account management section in charge of credit and foreign bills of one of the prime banks here in South Africa. On a routine inspection I discovered a dormant domiciliary account with a Balance Of US$48,223,000. 00 (Forty eight million two hundred and twenty three thousand U.S dollar).On further discreet investigation, I also discovered that the account holder has died long ago with his family on a fatal Auto-accident leaving no beneficiary to the account and no other person knows about this account. I am in close contact with the manager of the bank here who is my partner and he is willing to approve the transfer to any reliable and trustworthy foreigner with foreign bank account because the former operator of the a/c is a foreigner and from Australia in particular. I am certainly sure that he has no writen or oral WILL attached to the account , no beneficiary and nobody will come again for the claim of this money. It is only a foreigner who can claim this money with legal claims to the account holder which I will provide to you if you are interested, therefore I need your cooperation in this transaction. The difference in country of origins is not a hindrance to the success of this transaction. This money will remain useless in this dormant account if I did not transfer the fund out to a foreign account. I will provide the necessary information and documents needed in order to claim this money. I only need your cooperation as a foreigner to provide your safe bank account information for the transfer. All arrangement that will ensure a smooth transfer of the fund to the account which you are to nominate is already in place.You should also provide me with your direct phone lines for easy communication. I wish for utmost confidentiality in handling this transaction. At the conclussion of this transaction, your share will be 25% of the total transfer sum, 70% for me and my partner while 5% will be set aside for any expenses both parties might incure during the process of the transfer. The fund will be transferred to your account in two parts. I will first transfer USD 20 Million to your account. I will fly over to meet you after the successful transfer for sharing according to the agreed percentages. I will have the remaining balance of USD28,223 Million transferred to your account only after the successful sharing of the first transfer without any disappointment from your side. Have a nice day as I entrust this transfer into your hands. Finaly reply to this e-Mail address bellow if you are willing to do this business with me. <jenifdavix@timemail.com> Best Regards, Mr. Jenif Davix. FAX:874-76-2533361 TEL:874-76-2533360

for your kind attention sir, I am martin Arap Moi, the son of The former president of Kenya Mr Daniel Arap Moi. I came to know you in the course of my search for a reliable And GOD fearing partner, and I decided to contact you, Because I believe you are a reputable person and I feel You can help me and my mother over this confidential matter. I count on your integrity and honesty to be able to handle this Business. My father, Mr Arap Moi, was the former president of Kenya , In East Africa, During his reign as the president , he had so many Monetary dealing with a lot of European companies in my country And out side my country, and he uses these companies as a means Of transferring funds to foreign accounts in Europe ,America and Asia., all these funds where gotten from the sales of Gold and Diamonds, Amongst the companies he registered was GOLDENBERG COMPANIES, Which he uses as front for funds deposit, he made a transfer of $56,000,000. million American Dollars. to this company which never existed, the said company has since been declared bankruptcy and liquidate, and the said funds has been deposited with a security company where it is kept from for safekeeping. For more information you can click on this website: (1) http://news.bbc.co.uk/2/hi/africa/3338023.stm or , (2) http://news.bbc.co.uk/2/hi/africa/3025878.stm% And as the only child of my mother who is the 6th wife to my father he has given to us as our own share, which is this funds that is with the security company.. The money is kept in one trunk box and was registered as precious substances, thus there is nobody that knows that it is money that is in the box. I am looking for somebody that is capable and willing to travel to the security company to receive the trunk box of money on behalf of my mother and I from the security company.We need a trust worthy and experience person that will help us to invest the funds in profitabe business since we have no knowledge of business and investment. as soon as you in control of the $566m, you will assist us come to your country and assist us well to buy a house where we will live. We are expecting to hear from you, please contact me on my Confidential email address: victor_arap_moi@indiatimes.com Thanks for your anticipated co-operation , please include your Telephone/fax number on your reply. Best Regards martin Arap Moi

URGENT BUSINESS RELATIONSHIP I am Alhaji Mohammed Abacha, the son of the late Nigerian Head of State who died on the 8th of June 1998 while in active services. Following the sudden death of my father, General Sani Abacha, the present Civilian Government has thrown my family and I into a state of utter confusion, frustration,and hopelessness. I have been subjected to inhuman physical and physiological torture, incarceration by the security Agents in my country. I was only recently released from detention after been arraigned before the Federal High Court of Nigeria for an offence committed by my late father. The incumbent civilian administration of Chief Olusegun Obasanjo has intensified his probe into my late father's activities while in the office and he has frozen all our local and foreign accounts together with other assets of my family as a retaliation for what my late father did to him when he was alive as the Head of the Military regime in Nigeria. As a matter of fact, we have been declared bankrupt and they are not relenting to make us poor for life. As a man that is so traumatized, I have lost confidence with anybody within my country as all those who benefited immensely during the regime of my late father have openly abandoned all my family. MY REASONS FOR CONTACTING YOU. I got your contacts through my personal research and out of desperation decided to reach you through this medium. You must have heard over the media reports and the Internet on the recovery of various huge sums of money deposited by my late father in different Banks and security firms abroad. Some of these banks and security firms willingly gave-up/divulge their banking secrets and disclosed to the present civilian administration of Chief Olusegun Obasanjo, all my family's cash lodgement and monetary transactions with them. Please my dear, I repose great confidence in you and I hope you will not betray my confidence in you. I have secretly deposited the sum of $20,000,000.00 with a security firm abroad whose name is withheld for now until we open communications. The money is contained in a metal box consignment with Security Deposit Number. I shall be grateful if you could receive this fund into your Bank account for safekeeping. This arrangement is known to you and my junior brother (Abbas) only. So I will deal directly with you. I am proposing a 20% share of the fund to you for your kind assistance. I shall provide for you all the documents of the fund deposit with the security firm, and raise a power of attorney `to enable you claim and receive this fund into your bank account. Also this transaction demands absolute confidentiality. On no condition must you disclose it to anybody irrespective of your relation with the person. Remember, Loose lips sinks ship I am looking forward to your urgent and positive response via my email above. Best regards Alhaji Mohammed Abacha. ___________________________________________________________________________ Mail automatico enviado desde www.espana2000.org/castellon

ATTN; Sir, Good day, I know you'll receive this proposal with a total surprise and some kind of scepticism, based on the fact that we never had any prior discussion to this matter nor have we seen or known ourselves before, nevertheless I would like you to treat this proposal as a matter of its urgency and accord it every necessary attention required. I got your contact in cause of a serious search for a reliable person of foriegn origin who could help us. I'm Mr Addonis Johnson, son of late Mr. Solomon Johnson, the former Director General of Sierra Leonian (diamond mining) Procurement Agency, Who died some years ago when the revolutionary united front rebels attacked Makeni town, Sierra leone. Following the cease fire agreement reached last year with the help of United Nation peace keeping troops(UNASIL), I used the oppoturnity to leave the country with a very important document containing (US$5.500.000) five million five hundred U.S Dollars deposited by my late father in a bank in Dakar, Senegal in my name as the next of kin. This money was realised from diamond export, now I and my brother are seeking asylum in the Senegal under (UNHCR). My main reason for contacting you is that I received an information from the bank warning that I should make haste to dislodge the money or I loose it to my home government investigations on ex-governmental officials accounts. They advised I should present an individual, organisation or company as the beneficiary to the account since the money cannot be released to me as a client considering my status here as a refugee. All the accounting information are with me right here in senegal. For your assistance and cooperation we have decided to give you 10% of the total sum realised after the sucessful transfer of this money to your account for our investments in your country. Please kindly communicate your acceptance of this proposal through this email address so that we can discuss the modalities of seeing this transaction through, We count greatly on you for assistance. Awaiting to hear from you soon. Thanks. Yours Sincerely Adonis Johnson.

FROM MISS SAVANA PRISCA ABIDJAN.IVORY COAST. COTE D'IVOIRE. APPEAL FOR URGENT ASSISTANCE. Dear Sir, Permit me to inform you of my desire of going into business relationship with you.Though this letter will be a surprise to you since you dont know me personally I got your contacts recent .during my search for a stranger that can cooperate help me in this mutual transaction. and I prayed over it and selected your name among the other names due to its esteeming nature and the recommations given to me as a reputable and trust worthy person that I can do business with and by the recommendation, I must not hesitate to confide in you for this simple and sincere Business. I am MISS SAVANA PRISCA, the only daughter of late Mr. And MrsSAVANA My father was a very wealth cocoa merchant in Abidjan, the economic capital of Ivory Coast, my father died during the political war crisis that going on in my country here in ivory coast(cote d'ivoire)My mother died when I was a baby when she was about to delivers a new baby and since then my father took me so special. Before the death of my father on november 2002 in a private hospital herein Abidjan he secretly called me on his bed side and told me that he has the sum of Eight Million,Five Hundred Thousand United State Dollars. USD($8.500,000) left in one of the private security/finances trust services house here in Abidjan Ivory Coast ,as a family treasures that he used my names her only daughter for the next of kin in depositing of the fund. He also explained to me that he might not survive the situation he was at that present. However That I should seek for a foreign partner in a country of my choice where I will transfer this money and use it for investment purpose such as real estate management or hotel management. Sir,I am in a sincere desire of your humble assistance in this regards again.Your suggestions and ideas will be highly regarded. Now permit me to ask these few questions:- (1)Can you help me for the retrievements of this fund on my behalf in the security custody here to your end? (2)Can you stand as a guardian of this since fund since I am only 22 years old? (3)Can you make an arrangement for me to come over to your country to further my Education and to secure a resident permit in your country? (4) Can you honestly take me as your own and help me? (5) Can I completely trust you? (6) What percentage of the total amount in question will be go for you after the money is in your account? Please,Consider this and get back to me as soon as possible so that i can forward the documents to you after we have agreed on the conditions for your assistance. My life is not safe here and i need to be out of here as soon as possible because now that my father is dead and with me only as a female child, firstly the political war crisis are still going on here in my country and secondly my uncles are seeking to kill me so that they can have all my fathers properties. I really don't want to struggle anything with them in terms of properties but my presence will still be disturbing them. thank God they are not aware of this fund in the company here hence, I want to leave here as soon as you help me to have the consignment cleared from the security company here and lodge it into a safe account in your stable country and then send me some amount to enable me prepare to meet you. without your help, i will find it difficult to travel and clear it myself alone with my little or no experience. I am waiting for your urgent reply with your contact phone number so that i can give you the contact of the security for you to contact them as if you are my guardians. and in due course I will provides you the secret code for opening the consignment when you are ready to come on my behalf. Thank you so much. Best Regards, MISS SAVANA PRISCA EXP:Mlle SAVANA PRISCA ABIDJAN,COTE D' IVOIRE. URGENCE POUR ASSISTANCE CHER, MR OU MADAME. Permettez-moi de vous informez de mon désir de traiter avec vous. En effet j'ai obtenu votre contact et j'ai prié beaucoup pour que vous soyez l'homme évident parmi les noms que j'ai sélectionnés par apport à sa nature estimable, comme étant un homme de parole et de confiance auquel je peux traiter avec conformément à votre grandeur je saurais hésiter à me confier à vous pour se simple et sincère business. Permettrez moi de me présenter à vous. Je suis Mlle SAVANA PRISCA la seul fille du regretté Mr ou Mme SAVANA Mon père était l'un des riches homme marchand de cacao en Cote d'Ivoire, dans la capitale économique, il a été empoisonné par ses collègues pendant qu'ils était en bateau pour l'importation du cacao. Quant à ma mère elle est morte quant j’étais encore bébé pour ses raisons mon père ma traité convenablement, avant sa mort dans un clinique privé a Abidjan en novembre 2002 il m'a secrètement appelé sur son lit d’hôpital pour me dire qu'il possède la somme de huit million cinq cent mille de dollars ($8.500,000) la gauche dans une compagnie privée de sécurité et de finances entretient la maison ici en Côte d'Ivoire d’Abidjan, as des trésors d'une famille, qui porte mon nom donc, je suis la personne qui peut accéder à cet argent il m'a expliqué que c'est à cause de son argent qu'il à été empoisonné. Dans se ca il m'a dit de chercher un partenaire étranger de mon choix ou je pourrais transférer l'argent et de l'exploiter dans des différents secteurs comme dans le domaine de l'immobilier ou dans l’hôtellerie. Cher Mr ou Mme je cherche honorablement votre assistance. Suivez l'instruction ci- dessous. je vous demande humblement votre aide ainsi que des suggestions et des idées venant de vous seront grandement appréciées. Maintenant, je voudrais vous poser quelques questions: 1)Pouvez vous m'aider pour les retrait de ces fonds en mon nom dans la garde de sécurité ici à votre extrémité.? 2)pourriez-vous m'aider à venir dans votre pays pour finir mes études en m'assurant le gîte et le couvert? 3)pourriez-vous garder cet argent parce que je n'ai que 22 ans? 4)est-ce que,je puis complètement vous faire confiance? 5)pouvez-vous honnêtement me prendre en tant que vos propres et m'aider? 6)quel pourcentage exigerez-vous une fois l'argent dans votre compte? Je vous prie de bien vouloir me donner une réponse rapide pour que je puisse vous expédier les documents nécessaires pour cette transaction. Ma vie n'est pas en sécurité ici car mes oncles veulent attenter à ma vie pour prendre les autres biens de mon père car heureusement ils ne sont pas au courant de cet argent. J'attends donc votre numéro de téléphone ainsi que le fax. merci, Mlle SAVANA PRISCA ___________________________________________________________________________ ¡Terra Banda Ancha, tu conexión permanente a Internet desde $348 al mes! http://www.terra.com.mx/bandaancha ¡Nunca fue tan fácil tener tu página en Internet! http://sitebuilder.terra.com.mx Encuentra los mejores productos y precios increibles!! http://decompras.com.mx

Mr Lewis Musasike Development Bank of Southern Africa. 1258 Lever Road Headway Hill, MIDRAND Republic Of South Africa. Email:lmusasike@dearriba.com Hello, I am Mr Lewis Musasike, General Manager(Treasury) of Development Bank of Southern Africa.This is an urgent and very confidential business proposition. On May 27, 2001,a Foreign Oil consultant/contractor with the South African Institute of Mining and Metallurgy, Mr.Kelvin Smith made a numbered time(Fixed) Deposit for twelve calendar months, valued at US$10,500,000.00, (Ten Million, five hundred thousand Dollars). Upon maturity,I sent a routine notification to his forwarding address but got no reply. After a month,we sent a reminder and finally we discovered from his contract employers, the National Petroleum Corporation that Mr.Kelvin Smith died from an automobile accident.On further investigation,I found out that he died without making a WILL,and all attempts to trace his next of kin was fruitless. I therefore made further investigation and discovered that Mr.Kelvin Smith did not declare any kin or relations in all his official documents,including his Bank Deposit paperwork in my Bank. This sum of US$10,500,000.00 has carefully been fixed in my bank for safekeeping. No one will ever come forward to claim it.According to South African Law,at the expiration of 5 (five) years, the money will revert to the ownership of the Government if nobody applies to claim the fund. Consequently, my proposal is that I will like you as a Foreigner to stand in as the owner of the money which was fixed deposited in my bank. I am writing you because I as a public servant,i cannot operate a foreign account. I want to present you as the owner of the funds so you can be able to claim them with the help of my attorney. This is simple.I will like you to provide immediately your full names and address so that the Attorney will prepare the necessary documents which will put you in place as the beneficiary of the funds. The money will be moved out for us to share in the ratio of 60% for me and 40% for you. The paperwork for this transaction will be done by the Attorney.If you are interested, please reply immediately via my email address and Upon your response,I shall then provide you with more details and relevant documents that will help you understand the transaction.Please observe utmost confidentiality, and be rest assured that this transaction would be most profitable for both of us because I shall require your assistance to invest my share in real estate within your country. Awaiting your urgent reply via my email Above. Thanks and my regards. Lewis Musasike. ------------------------------------------------------------------------------ deArriba me paga por navegar. Vos tambien podes ganar $$$ navegando. Entra a www.dearriba.com.

>From : Stella Dikko Samba Abidjan, Ivory Coast West Africa. TEL +225 07 81 95 57 APPEAL FOR URGENT BUSINESS ASSISTANCE. ATT: DIRECTOR MY Dear , Permit me to inform you of my desire of going into business relationship with you. I got your name and contact from the Ivoirian chamber of commerce and industry. I prayed over it and selected your name among other names due to its esteeming nature and the recommendations given to me as a reputable and trust worthy person that I can do business with and by the recommendation , I must not hesitate to confide in you for this simple and sincere business . I am Stella Dikoo Samba the only daughter of late Mr. and Mrs. Dikko samba. My father was a very wealthy cocoa merchant in Abidjan , the economic capital of Ivory coast, my father was poisoned to dearth by his business associates on one of their outings on a business trip . My mother died when I was a baby and since then my father took me so special. Before the death of my father on January 2002 in a private hospital here in Abidjan he secretly called me on his bed side and told me that he has the sum of seventeen million ,five hundred thousand United State Dollars. USD ($ 17.500,000) left in fixed / suspense account in one of the prime bank here in Abidjan ,that he used my name as his only daughter for the next of Kin in depositing of the fund. He also explained to me that it was because of this wealth that he was poisoned by his business associates. That I should seek for a foreign partner in a country of my choice where i will transfer this money and use it for investment purpose such as real estate management or hotel management . Sir, I am honourably seeking your assistance in the following ways: (1) To provide a bank account into which this money would be transferred to . (2) To serve as a guardian of this fund since I am only 22years. (3) To make arrangement for me to come over to your country to further my education and to secure a resident permit in your country. Moreover, sir i am willing to offer you 15% of the total sum as compensation for your effort/ input after the successful transfer of this fund into your nominated account overseas. Furthermore, you indicate your options towards assisting me as I believe that this transaction would be concluded within fourteen (14) days you signify interest to assist me. Anticipating to hear from you soon. Reply ma in my private mail box:jim_naya@yahoo.fr Thanks and God bless. Best regard STELLA DIKKO SAMBA

Attn: MD/CEO RE: REPATRIATION OF $30.5M Following the approvals received by this office recommending for the immediate repatriation of the above referenced fund and having been listed in category "A" foreign creditors, you are by this notice informed that your assistance is required in receiving the approved fund floating in an offshore Payments Account in London.This is as result of grossly over invoiced contracts which were executed by a (Deceased) national of your country on the Oil Refineries in Saudi Arabia. This contract was deliberately over invoiced to the tune of US$30.5m Million Dollars.This was a deal by my committee to benefit from the project. I have therefore been mandated as a matter of trust to look for a foreign partner into whose account we could transfer the sum of USD30,500,000.00 (Thirt Million, Five Hundred Thousand Us Dollars Only). We have agreed to share the funds thus: 80% for us and 20% for account owner (you).If you are interested,please forward the following information to : smtt100@yahoo.co.uk (1) Your Name/company's name and full address. (2) Your banker's name, Swift code,address, telephone and fax numbers. (3) Your contact Tel/Fax No. (4) Your Occupation (5) Valid ID Upon the receipt of the above details,Payment will be activated by the feeding of your data into the payment system, followed by a signal that will be sent to the paying bank to remit funds into your nominated bank acount within 7 official working days of receipt of the above information. Your swift response will be highly appreciated. Sincerely Yours. Mr. Edward Smith Protocol Officer Mr. Edward Smith Protocol Officer Elstree Way Borehamwood Hertfordshire WD6 1GA,London, United Kingdom

SADDAM PALACE Dear Sir, I got your contact from the World Trade Organisation directory of the US,Canada& European Union and I am very sorry to interrupt your peace since you are not expecting to receive any mail from me. However, I was obliged to do so due to the importance and urgency of the message. I crave yourindulgence,and want to reassure you that I mean Well and that it is only for our mutual good.So please do not be embarrassed. My name is Dr.Michael Hammer ; I am a social worker with an international-Governmental/Voluntary organization based in Switzerland.I am the Accounts/ Project Director in-charge of the Middle East regional representation. Our organization,through local NGO'S and other Agencies and in partnership with theUnited Nations High Commission for Refugees, UNHCR, UNESCO, etc works and sponsors development projects and social services in some third world/developing countries,assistance and re-settlement of victims of natural disaster, civil wars and Refugees,displaced/oppressed children and minority people around the world. I am just back from Iraq where in the cause of performing our duties we found a huge amount of cash in an abandoned Palace, I reached an agreement with the members of my team whom are UN officials and we agreed to keep this money to ourselves and then moved the box out of Iraq to Europe (with their immunity as UN officials they are not searched at borders or airports). Now, I am in need of a reliable and trustworthy person or company overseas whom I can confidently work with since my work does not permit me to own a foreign bank account or any personal business until retirement, I have the honor to confide this information in you and to request for your pleasure to assist to receive and secure the money in your account,pending our retirement from service. Please understand that my approach to you is based only on my positive reasoning and on the belief that you will not disappoint or betray me at last. The amount is fairly huge and we have agreed that on completion of the deal, you will retain some reasonable percentage of the money(20%) as a compensation for your assistance.the amount of the money is TWENTY MILLION UNITED STATES DOLLARS To consider our official positions,reputation and integrity, especially,the opportunities in the business itself, it is very necessary that all due care be taken so that we do not miss the opportunity due to carelessness. You are therefore expected and advised to display high degree of maturity,responsibility and understanding in handling this information.I will give you all the details in my next mail when you have indicated your interest and commitment to work with me. Alwaysremember that this is the highest confidence and trust any person can repose on the other, especially when it is considered that we did not know ourselves before.I hope you will honor me too. We can come over to join you for sharing and to guarantee that we have unlimited access to you before and when the funds hit your account.Moreso for an effective and easy communiation I will advice that you furnish me with your telephone, cell and I eagerly await yourpositive response. Best regards, Michael Hammer, Dr. Please reply only to this email address michael_hammer88@yahoo.it

Dear Friend, In my quest to discover and properly scrutinize record of digits in my office, as an experienced banker. I got this to tell you, I discovered a DORMANT ACCOUNT worth (US$26,000,000.00) Twenty Six Million U.S. Dollars, in our bank. Anyway, I am Dr. Ateeq Rahman KHAN, the Auditor and Computing Manager of UNITED TRUST INTERNATIONAL Bank (UTIB) Dubai-UNITED ARAB EMIRATES. There exist an account opened in this bank in 1998 and since 1999 nobody has operated this account. I discovered from records that Mr. Jean-Marie LEVEQUE, a foreigner and the manager of the Petrol Chemical Service, and also Chemical Engineer by profession owns this account. Moreso, this money will be forfeited if not claimed and only a foreigner can effect claim this money. Secondly, no local bank here will be allowed to have this money, so it can only be claimed with foreign account owing to the fact that the former owner was a foreigner too and the money is in US dollars. So let this not be a surprise, I am contacting you on trust and because you are a foreigner as well. In fact, I want us to claim this money into a foreign account or any account of your choice. When the transfer is approved and payment schedule is allotted overseas, through the offshore paying delegate for final clearance and signing of the payment release form by the beneficiary; I would want us to see at the overseas payment clearance office or during the signing of the Original Binding Agreement, which binds us together and will also enables us receive this money into foreign account. This transaction will be 100% risk free and in accordance with the lay down rules, guiding the transactions in the banking industry. The bank is ready to approve the payment of this money to any foreigner who has the correct information to this account, which I will give to you. When I am sure of your capability to handle such money in strict confidence and trust, according to the instructions and advise for our mutual benefit. Because I wouldn't want to make mistakes. So your assurance and trust is very important here. I shall destroy immediately documents concerning this transaction after we must have received this money, thereby leaving no trace. With my position in the bank, there will be no hindrance in legal approvals and onward transfer of this money to your account with appropriate clearance from foreign payment department, with assurance that this money will be intact pending my arrival abroad to take my share. Conclusively, you will be given 25% of the total amount, 70% will be for me, while 5% will be for expenses both parties must have incurred during the process of this transaction. I look forward to your swift response. Best regards, DR. ATEEQ RAHMAN KHAN

Dear I am Miss Franca Roland and my brother Mr David Roland, the first and only son of late Mr Mputa Roland and my aged mother, my father was murdered in the land dispute in Zimbabwe, Before the death of my father, he had deposit the sum of US$4,000,000 (FOUR MILLION US DOLLARS), in a private security and Finance company, as if he foresaw the looming danger in Zimbabwe. This amount was meant for the purchase of chemicals and tractors for the development of our new farms in Swaziland. This land problem came when the Zimbabwe president Mr Robert Mugabe introduced a new land reform act, which wholly affected the rich white farmers and some black farmers. This result to killing and mob action by Zimbabwean war veterans and some lunatics in the society lot of people have been killed because of this land-reform act, which my father is one of them. You can hook up to CNN news every day for what is happening in the country, if you are in doubt, you can also go to the internet to www.dailynews.co.zw , it is against this backdrop that my family and I who are currently in Dakar Senegal decided to transfer our fathers money to any foreign account since the Senegal law prohibits refugees (asylum seekers) to operate any type of bank account or to be involved in any huge financial transaction. As the eldest child of my father, I am seeking for a genuine foreign partner who can help us transfer this money into his or her oversea account. On the other hand, the senegal government seems to be playing along with them. We are therefore faced with the dilemma of investing this money in Senegal for the fear of going through the same experience in future, since both countries have similar political history. As a business man whom I will entrust my future and that of my entire family in his or her hands , I must let you know that this business is completely 100% risk-free. As we cannot accept to venture into any dangerous deal with our fortune, if you therefore accept to assist us, which I know that you will. Please I will like you to contact me through the receipt of this mail urgently. Feel free to ask all questions you deem necessary. For you assistance , we have proposed two options for you. 1)You may go into partnership with me for the proper profitable investment of the money in your country. 2)If you do not prefer a partnership, I am willing to give you 15% of the sum while the remaining 85% will be my family prior for investment in your country, while the remaining 5% will be used to defray all the expenses that may incur during the process of this transaction. You are therefore required of absolute confidentiality of this matter. God bless you. Yours truly, Miss Franca.

Good Day I know that this mail might be a surpriseing to you but do consider it as an emergency. In a nut shell, My name is Joy kwame from the republic of Sierria-Leone in west Africa, now seeking for refugee in Dakar -Senegal under the(UNHCR). I am looking for someone who can take me as child I promise to be obidient to you and I will bring happiness to your life I want you to assist me in this transaction. My late father was the managing director of Rainbow Gold and Diamond Mine company in (KENEMA) Sierra-Leone. But he was poisoned to death alongside with my mother by his business associate,On one of their outing to discuss a business deal in oversea However,Befor the death of my father in a private hospilat in Sierria Leone. He Secretly called me on his bedside and to me that he has a sum of US (US$6.2M)Six million two hundred thousand U.S Dollars Deposite in Finance Firm. He also explained to me that it was because of this wealth that he was poisoned by his business associates,after their death I managed to stay with his younger brothers. Them take away all my father treasury and properties away from me just to put me into suffery and starvation. When the war broke out in my country I escape to refugee camp in senegal by the help of the UN with some important files of my father. The deposit documents indicate me as the next of kin.Presently, I am saddled with the problem of securing a trust worthy foriegn personality to help me. (1) you will Stand on my behalf as the beneficiary for the claim of the inheritance from the Finance Firm since the management of the Finance Firm adviced that I should solicit for an individual or corporate organization to claim the deposit for me as they cannot release it directly to me due to my refugee status in Senegal. (2) Help me secure my travelling documents to meet you as soon as my late father money is released to you so that i can get back to School again. Furthermore,you can contact the Finance Firm for confirmation and I will issue a letter of authorisation on your name,that will enable the Finance Firm correspond with you on my behalf. I am giving you this offers as mentioned with every confidence on your acceptance to assist me or adopt me as your Child if possible and manage the money for me. Conclusively I wish you send me a reply immediately you recieve this proposal. Until then,I remain with the best , Regards Joy Kwame

FROM THE DESK OF MR. MARK ELLIS CHIEF FINANCIAL OFFICER CCTB BANK, LONDON-ENGLAND. PRIVATE EMAIL: mark_7ell6@yahoo.co.uk ATTENTION, RE: YOUR ASSISTANCE IS NEEDED IN ACTUALIZING THIS GOAL Let me start by introducing myself. I am MR. MARK ELLIS, CHIEF FINANCIAL OFFICER of the CITY CENTER TRUST BANK.I have an obscured business suggestion for you. I honestly apologize and hope I did not cause you much embarrassment by contacting you through this means for a transaction of this magnitude, but this is due to confidentiality and prompt access reposed on this medium, sorry my English is not very good. Before the U.S and Iraqi war our client MAJOR FADI EL AMIN who was with the Iraqi forces and also business man made a numbered fixed deposit for 18 calendar months, with a value of Ten millions United State Dollars only in my branch. Upon maturity several Notices was sent to him, even during the war early this year. Again after the war another notification was sent and still no response came from him. We later find out that the Major and his family had been killed during the war in bomb blast that hit their home. After further investigation it was also discovered that MAJOR FADI EL AMIN did not declare any next of kin in his official papers including the paper work of his bank deposit. And he also confided in me the last time he was at my office that no one except me knew of his deposit in my bank. So, Ten millions United State Dollars is still lying in my bank and no one will ever come forward to claim it. What bothers me most is that according to the laws of my country at the expiration 3 years the funds will revert to the ownership of the England Government if nobody applies to claim the funds. Against this backdrop, my suggestion to you is that I will like you as a foreigner to stand as the next of kin to MAJOR FADI EL AMIN so that you will be able to receive his funds. Please endeavor to observe utmost discretion in all matters concerning this issue. Once the funds have been transferred to your nominated bank account we shall share in the ratio of 70% for me, 30% for you. Should you be interested please let me know and finally after that I shall provide you with more details of this operation. Your earliest response to this letter will be appreciated. N.B: Reply me using my private mail address: mark_7ell6@yahoo.co.uk Kind Regards Mr. Mark Ellis Chief Financial Officer CCTB BANK, LONDON-ENGLAND

Barclays Bank Plc 65/66 St. Mary Axe London EC3A 8LE I am Mr. Gary Adams, Senior Credit Officer, Barclays Bank Plc London. I am writing following an opportunity in my office that will be of immense benefit to both of us. In my department we discovered an abandoned sum of £12.5million British Pounds Sterling (Twelve Million Five Hundred Thousand British Pounds Sterling) in an account that belongs to one of our foreign customers Late Mr. Morris Thompson an American who unfortunately lost his life in the plane crash of Alaska Airlines Flight 261, which crashed on January 31 2000, including his wife and only daughter. You shall read more about the crash on visiting this website. http://www.cnn.com/2000/US/02/01/alaska.airlines.list/ http://www.nativefederation.org/history/people/mThompson.html Since we got information about his death, we have been expecting his next of kin or relatives to come over and claim his money because the Bank cannot release the funds unless somebody applies for it as next of kin or relation to the deceased as indicated in our banking guidelines. Unfortunately I learnt that his supposed next of kin being his only daughter died along with him in the plane crash leaving nobody with the knowledge of this fund behind for the claim. It is therefore upon this discovery that I and two other officials in this department now decided to do business with you and release the money to you as the next of kin or beneficiary of the funds for safe keeping and subsequent disbursement since nobody is coming for it and we don't want this money to go back into Government treasury as unclaimed bill. We agreed that 20% of this money would be for you as foreign partner, while the balance will be for my colleagues and I. We will visit your country for the disbursement according to the percentages indicated above once this money gets into your account. Please be honest to me as trust is our watchword in this transaction. Note that this transaction is confidential and risk free. As soon as you receive this mail you should contact me by return mail whether or not you are willing to enter into this deal. In the event you are not interested, I sincerely ask that you disregard this email and tell no one about it. I am very careful on truncating my banking career should you mention this to someone else. I hope you can be trusted in this regard. Please note that all necessary arrangement for the smooth release of these funds to you has been finalized. We will discuss much in details when I do receive your response. Please in your response include your telephone and fax numbers for a better communication between us. You can reach me on the email below Best regards Gary Adams Email: garyadams@sify.com Fax: + 44 - 7092044703

FROM THE DESK OF MR ISIAKA AKIDA BILL AND EXCHANGE MANAGER FOREIGN REMITTANCE DEPT. BANK OF AFRICA (BOA) OUAGADOUGOU,BURKINA FASO.  REPLY TO MY PRIVATE EMAIL: isiaka_akida@yahoo.fr Dear Friend, First, I must solicit your confidence in this transaction.This is by virtue of its nature as being utterly CONFIDENTIAL AND TOP SECRET. However after series of petition was recieved by this present regime from foreign contractors and inability of the BANK OF AFRICA (BOA)to fulfill their obligation for the payment to its foreign creditors, in conjunction with the council of ministers, they mandated us to carry out a careful and comprehensive review of all overdue payments to foreign contractors and to effect payments immediately. During the above mentioned process, we discovered an abandoned sum of US$10.M (Ten million US dollars) in an account that belongs to one of our foreign customer who died along with his entire famil in a plane crash that happened in Kenya, East Africa. Since we got information about his death, we have been expecting his next of kin to come over and claim his money because we cannot release it unless some body applies for it as next of kin or relation to the deceased as indicated in our banking guidelines and laws but unfortunately we learnt that all his supposed next of kin or relation died alongside with him at the plane crash leaving nobody behind for the claim. Please I want you to visit the website below for more information about the Plane Crash: www.cnn.com/2003/WORLD/africa/07/20/kenya.crash/index.html It is therefore upon this discovery that I and other officials in my department now decided to make this business proposal to you and release the money to you as the next of kin or relation to the deceased for safety and subsequent disbursement since nobody is coming for it and we don't want this money to go into the bank treasury as unclaimed bill. I agree that 40% of this money will be for you as a foreign partner, in respect to the provision of a foreign account,and 50% would be for me, while 10% will be for expenses incure during the transaction. There after I will visit your country for disbursement according to the percentage indicated. Therefore, to enable the immediate transfer of this fund to you as arranged, you must apply first to the bank as relation or next of kin of the deceased indicating your bank name, your bank account number, your private telephone and fax number for easy and effective communication and location wherein the money will be remitted. Upon the receipt of your reply, I will send to you by email the text of the application to fill and send to the bank. I will not fail to bring to your notice that this transaction is hitch-free risk and this transaction will only take us 14 banking days because as a banker, I know what to do and move the fund into your account without any delay and thatyou should not entertain any atom of fear as all required arrangement have been made for the transfer. You should contact me as soon as you receive this letter so that I will send you the text of the application to apply to the bank. Yours faithfully. MR ISIAKA AKIDA Bill & Exchange Manager, BANK OF AFRICA (BOA) ------------------------------------------ Faites un voeu et puis Voila ! www.voila.fr

Attin/Dear . I would like to apply through this medium for your co-operation and to secure an opportunity to invest and do joint business with you in your country. I have a substantial capital i honourably intend to invest in your country into a very lucrative business venture of which you are to advise and execute the said venture over there for the mutual benefits of both of us. Your able co-operation is to become my business partner in your country and create ideas on how money will be invested,properly managed and the type of investment after the money is transferred to your custody with your help and assistance. Meanwhile,on indication of your willingness to handle this transaction sincerely by protecting our interests and upon your acceptance of this proposal,I would furnish you with the full detailed information, procedure,amount involve and mutually agree on your percentage interest or share holding for helping me to secure the release of the deposit and investing the money. I shall be glad to reserve this respect and opportunity for you,if you so desire,but do urge you to give the matter your immediate attention it deserves. If this proposal is acceptable by you,please do not make undue advantage of the trust i bestow on you,and your urgent call and reply is highly needed,for more detailed informations and oral talks. Looking forward to your urgent call and positive response today and a mutual healthy businessrelationship with you. Best regards,and have a great day. Yours Faithfully, Mr.Johnson Kaun. -- No virus found in this outgoing message. Checked by AVG Anti-Virus. Version: 7.0.323 / Virus Database: 267.9.2/52 - Release Date: 19/07/2005

Dear Sir/Madam, I am pleased to introduce a business opportunity to you to transfer to your overseas account a huge amount of money deposited in one of the Prime Banks here in Dakar-Senegal. I urgently want to know you and if you are capable of handling and accomodate this magnitude of funds until I resign and come over to join you for an investment in your country. What I need is a reliable and honest individual/organisation that would be capable and fit enough to provide either an existing bank account or set up a new Bank Account immediately to receive this funds. Even an empty bank account can serve to receive this funds as long as you will remain honest to me till we actualise this interest. My name is Dr. Salif Mamadou, the Director of Bill and Exchange at the Foreign Remittance Department of the same bank. I am writing following the impressive information about you through one of my friends who runs a consultancy firm. He assured me of your capability and reliability to champion this business opportunity. In my department we discovered an abandoned Sum of $18.5M USD Eighteen Million, Five Hundred Thousand US Dollars), in an account that belongs to one of our foreign customers an American by name: Mr.Neal Walker who died along with other passengers in EgyptAir Flight 990 - October 31, 1999. We have been expecting his next of kin to come over and claim his money because we cannot release it unless somebody applies for it as next of kin or relation to the deceased and the person must be foreigner as indicated in our banking guidelines. Futher investigation, we discovered that the owner of the account died without a [Heir/WILL] hence the money is floating and if I do not remit this money out urgently it will be forfeited for nothing. It is therefore upon this discovery that I and other officials in bank now decided to make this businness proposal to you and release the money to you as the next of kin or relation to the deceased for safety and subsequent disbursement since nobody is coming for it and we do not want this money to go into the Bank treasury as unclaimed Bill. The Banking law and guideline here stipulates that if such money remained unclamed after five years, the money will be transfered into the Bank treasury account as unclaimed fund. The request of foreigner as next of kin in this business is occasioned by the fact that the customer was a foreigner and I can not stand as next of kin to a foreigner,it is also against our the banking law, guideline and ethics of banks here in my country. We have agreed that 20 % of this money will be for you as foreign partner, in respect to the provision of a foreign account, 10 % will be set aside for expenses incured during the business and 70 % would be for me and my colleagues. There after I and my colleagues will visit your country for disbursement according to the percentages indicated. Therefore to enable the immediate transfer of this fund to you as requested to provide the following: Your full name and address, Your direct telephone and fax number and your bank information. All the requested information will enable me perfect all the necessary things in your favour for smooth transfer of the fund into you account as you will provide. If you are interested, please contact me via my email address: m_salif@yahoo.com <mailto:m_salif@yahoo.com> and also call me on my telephone for more details: 00221 699.9741. Upon your response, I shall provide you with more details on how we shall proceed with the claims. I expect you to observe utmost confidentiality and be rest assured that this transaction would be profitable for both of us without any risk involved. Awaiting your urgent reply. Thanks & Regards. Dr. Salif Mamadou.

GORVERMENT RESIDENTIAL AREA BANDAR SERI BEGAWAN VILLA 12, BRUNEI. Tel: 006732227412 Assalamu alaiykum , It is my sincere wish that my mail meets you in good health , I'm Mrs. Aminatu Bolkiah fouth wife to Prince Jefri Bolkiah Former finance minister of brunei , My getting to your email info was a coincidence but i beleive it was Allah's divine ways of assuring me of your helping and understanding towards my family. By birth am a bruneian and a musillimah and I strongly hope you'll understand my plight because I am seeking investment opportunites in your country and i do know you are capable to understand and help me with the investment of my family fortunes...I am soliciting your kind understanding due to my husband's arrest over tax related issues. You may know from the BBC international media that the sultan alledged that his half brother ( My husband ) was involve in Tax misconduct and improperity of $30 Billion dollars and order his arrest and froze all his foreign accounts, including his international passport and personal valuables which includes a ban and arrest on his four wifes over the tax related issue please visit the web site: http://www.timeinc.net/asiaweek/magazine/2000/0505/edit.flush.html Futhermore during this unfortunate period,I was adviced to leave my residence for saudi arabia to avoid further prosecution from the sultan and his security operatives, but before i could do that i was arrested and placed under house arrest (above stated with a land phone ) which is highly monitored and restricting me from calling rather they kept an old pentium 4 computer for my use. Before my husband's arrest, He made some special arrangements with some courrier company's in europe and middle east where he deposited our $35m family fortunes in cash in two trunk metal boxes with the documents in my poccession, each of the boxes contains $ 17.5m united states dollars, I sincerely wish you'll understand and give your hands in co-operation towards my investment plans in your country until our problems are over. No compensiation has been discussed yet until i receive your positive response, do notify me of your calling to prevent anyone from having ideal of my soliciting your personal assistance. Allah Afiz , Mrs. Aminatu Bolkiah

Dear Friend , Naturally, this letter will come to you as a surprise since we have not met,permit me however, I am MR.HASSAN GEORGE,a Zimbabwean Farmer. I am contacting you as the need for me to have a foreign partner in your country has become necessary due to my plans to relocate and establish a private company in that region, as the present political instability in my country (Zimbabwe), does not encourage financial investment as the environment is not conducive for investment and most of all security is not guaranteed,just as reported by the International media. I wouldn't go much deep detailing but you can have a look on this web-site if you have the time and see what kind of brutal president we have. http://www.rte.ie/news/2000/0418/zimbabwe. html This problem started when the Zimbabwean government under the leadership of President Robert Mugabe announced a decree on May 31st 2001 to seize more than 6000 white-owned farms. So far, more than 5,400 white owned farms have been invaded, properties confiscated and farm lands seized. During these periods, as reported by the international media and C.N.N, more than 500 white farmers were killed, the government didn't stop at this, as just recently the government have asked all white-farmers to give up their farms to black farmers or risk going to prison. Having lived in this country (Zimbabwe) for more than 35 years, I have no other country to go to, nor can I trace any of my distant relatives. Therefore, I decided to contact you for your assistance so that I can establish a company in your country and relocate there. Also, I must re-iterate the importance of having a citizen of your country to front as the owner of the enterprise, due to the fact that I will be a foreigner in your country. I have deposited in a Security company all the funds realised from the sales of my farmland and other farming equipment which amounted to USD8.5,000,000.00 (Eight million five hundred thousand United States Dollars). These funds was packaged in two trunk boxes and declared as Gemstones to avoid much demurrage from the security company and not to know of the exact content so that they don't steal my money.It is to the knowledge of you and i that it is money that is in the trunk boxes.The trunk boxes of us$8.5m have been arranged and securely sealed, crated and then deposited with a security company ready for shipment abroad via diplomatic courier service so as to make it immune to custom and other bureaucratic checks at the ports. The reason for this is because it is the only way the funds can be transferred without any problems. For now, I stay in U A E because Zimbabwe is highly unsafe for me and my family. You can mail your immediate response to me. Upon your immediate response, I will immediately arrange and send to you all the documentation that will empower your good self in finalizing the transaction with the security company. Let me use this opportunity to also inform you that this transaction is 100% risk free and should also be handled in the most confidential manner. I have options to offer you, first you can choose to have certain percentage of the money for your assistance, or you can go into partnership for a proper profitable investment of the money in your country. Which ever option you choose, feel free to notify me. If for some reasons you do not prefer a partnership, I am willing to give you 25% of the money while the remaining 75% that is meant for me, will be for the investment in your country. So based on the above, it is important you communicatewith me. On the event that you cannot assist me to do the business, I beg you to still keep my contact andexistence of my fund a secret. I also require you to make available to me the following 1)Your Complete name. 2)Your confidential telephone and fax numbers to enable me comminicate with you easily. Sincerely Yours, HASSAN GEORGE .

WILLIAM USMAN UNITED NATIONS REFUGEE CAMP ABIDJAN(COTE D'IVOIRE) CALL FOR HELP DEAR CHILD OF GOD PERMIT ME TO INFORM YOU ABOUT MY DESIRE TO GO INTO BUSINESS RELATIONSHIP WITH YOU. I AM WILLIAM USMAN THE ONLY CHILD OF MR AND MRS.MICHEAL USMAN, MY FATHER WAS A VERY RICH COCOA MERCHANT, BASED IN ABIDJAN, THE ECONOMIC CAPITAL OF IVORY COAST BEFORE HE WAS POISONED TO DEATH BY HIS BUSINESS ASSOCIATES ON ONE OF THEIR OUTINGS TO DISCUSS ON A BUSINESS DEAL. WHEN MY MOTHER DIED ON MAY 24,1996, MY FATHER TOOK ME SO SPECIAL SINCE I AM MOTHERLESS. BEFORE THE DEATH OF MY FATHER ON NOVEMBER 26,2003 IN A PRIVATE HOSPITAL WHERE HE WAS ADMITTED, HE CALLED ME SECRETLY TO HIS BED SIDE AND TOLD ME THAT HE KEPT A SUM OF US$10,500,000 (TEN MILLION FIVE HUNDRED THOUSAND UNITED STATES DOLLARS) IN A BANK IN ABIDJAN COTE D'IVOIRE. THAT HE USED MY NAME WILLIAM USMAN AS THE NEXT OF KIN IN DEPOSIT OF THE FUND HE ALSO EXPLAINED TO ME THAT IT WAS BECAUSE OF THIS MONEY HE WAS POISONED BY HIS BUSINESS PARTNER AND THAT I SHOULD SEEK FOR A FOREIGN PARTNER IN A COUNTRY OF MY CHOICE WHERE I WOULD TRANSFER THIS MONEY AND USE IT FOR AN INVESTMENT PURPOSE, SUCH AS:REAL ESTATE INVESTMENT OR STOCK MARKET INVESTMENT . SIR, I AM HONOURABLY SOLICITING YOUR KIND ASSISTANCE AS FOLLOWS.(1)TO PROVIDE A BANK ACCOUNT WHERE THIS MONEY WILL BE TRANSFERRED TO.(2)TO SERVE AS THE GUARDIAN OF THESE FUND,SINCE I AM A BOY OF 22 YEARS OLD. (3)TO MAKE ARRANGEMENT FOR ME IN YOUR COUNTRY TO CONTINUE MY EDUCATIONAL CAREER AND TO PROCURE ME A RESIDENTIAL PERMIT IN YOUR COUNTRY.I AM INCLINED TO OFFER YOU 15% OF THE TOTAL SUM AS A MODE OF COMPENSATION FOR YOUR EFFORTS AFTER THE TRANSFERING OF THESE FUND TO YOUR ACCOUNT IN YOUR COUNTRY.PLEASE, I WILL BE VERY HAPPY IF THIS TANSACTION WILL BE CONCLUDED WITHIN SEVEN(7)WORKING DAYS FROM NOW. I AM EXPECTING TO HEAR FROM YOU AS SOON AS POSSIBLE N.B:SIR,I WILL LIKE YOU TO GIVE ME YOUR DIRECT TELEPHONE AND FAX NUMBER IN YOUR REPLY OF THIS PROPOSAL. MAY ALMIGHTY GOD BLESS YOU AS YOU DO CARE FOR AN ORPHAN LIKE ME.ANTICIPATING TO HEAR FROM YOU. PLEASE REPLY TO my Email Address BEST REGARDS WILLIAM USMAN

Dear Good Friend.       I am Mrs Tina Williams from Solomon Islands. I am married to Mr. Lobi Williams who worked with our Embassy in Ivory Coast for nine years before he died in the year 2001. We were married for eleven years without a child. He died after a brief illness that lasted for only four days.      Before his death we were both born again Christian. Since his death I decided not to remarry or get a child outside my matrimonial home which the Bible is against.     When my late husband was alive he deposited the sum of $18.5 Million with a Bank in Cote D lvoire. Presently this money is still in the custody of the Bank in Cote D lvoire.     Recently, my Doctor told me that I would not last for the next Eight months due to cancer problem. Having known my condition I decided to donate this fund to a church,organization or good person that will utilize this money the way I am going to instruct herein.     I want a church,organization or good person that will use this fund for orphanages, widows and other peoples that needs help and also propagating the word of God and to endeavor that the house of God is maintained.    The Bible made us to understand that"Blessed is the hand that giveth". l took this decision because I don't have any child that will inherit this money and my husband relatives are not Christians not even good at all because they are the one that responsible for the death of my husband in other to have all my late husband prperties and I don't want my husband's efforts to be used by those that conspired for his death.       This is why I am taking this decision, I am not afraid of death hence I know where I am going. I know that I am going to be in the bosom of the Lord.Exodus 14 VS 14 says that "the lord will fight my case and I shall hold my peace".      I don't need any telephone communication in this regard because of my health hence the presence of my husband's relatives around me always. I don't want them to know about this development and l know that With God all things are possible.      As soon as I receive your reply I shall give you the contact of the Bank in Cote d' lvoire. I will also issue a letter of authorization to the bank that will prove you the present beneficiary of this money. I also want you, church or the organization to always pray for me because the lord is my only shephard.       My happiness is that I lived a life of a worthy Christian. Whoever that Wants to serve the Lord must serve him in spirit and Truth. Please always be prayerful all through your life. Contact me on the this email address and any delay in your reply will give me room in sourcing another good person, church,organization for this same purpose. Please assure me that you will act accordingly as I Stated herein. Hoping to receive your response immedaitely. Thanks and Remain blessed in the Lord. l remain yours sister in Christ. Mrs. Tina Williams.

Yahoo! Messenger: chiamate gratuite in tutto il mondo

from Barrister Christopher Ayodele Chris Ayo Chambers, Cote D lvoire. E-mail: chrisayo_5002@yahoo.it Dear Friend, I am Barrister Chris Ayo, a legal Solicitor and I was the Personal Attorney and legal adviser to the late williams Hunter, a national of your country, who used to work with Multil oil Company in Cote D lvoire.  On the 21st of August 2002, my client, his wife and their three children were involved in a car accident along Sagamu Express Road. All occupants of the vehicle unfortunately lost their lives. Since then I have made several enquiries to your embassy to locate any of myclients extended relatives, this has also proved unsuccessful. After these several ,unsuccessful attempts, I decided to trace his relatives over the Internet, to locate any member of his family but of no avail, hence I contacted you. I have contacted you to assist in repatriating the money and property left behind by my client before they get confiscated or declared unserviceable by the Bank where these huge deposits were lodged. Particularly, the bank where the deceased had a deposit valued at about Fifteen Million (US$15million) has issued me a notice to provide the next of kin or have the account confiscated within the next ten official working days. since I have been unsuccessful in locating the relatives for over two years and, I seek your consent to present you as the next of kin of the deceased since you are from the same country so that the proceeds of this account valued at Fifteen Million (US$15million) can be paid to you and then you and me can share the money. 55% to me and 40% to you, while 5% should be for expenses or tax as your government may require, I have all necessary legal documents that can be used to back up any claim we may make. All I require is your honest cooperation to enable us see this deal through. I guarantee that this will be executed under a legitimate arrangement that will protect you from any breach of the law. Please get in touch with me on my alternative and confidntial email address chrisayo_5002@yahoo.it in to enable us proceed further with the transaction and also forward to me with the following information: your full mailling address, private telephone and fax number for easy communication. Best Regards Barrister Christopher Ayodele

Con Yahoo! Mail proteggi la tua casella di posta da virus e spam

AUDITING AND ACCOUNTING UNIT. FOREIGN OPERATIONS DEPARTMENT. NIGERIAN NATIONAL BANK . Email:leonard_okobi05@yahoo.co.uk Dear Friend, I AM MR LEONARD OKOBI, The head of auditing and accounting section of (NNB) NIGERIAN NATIONAL BANK in West Africa. With due respect and regards,I have decided to contact you on a business at hand that will be very beneficial to both of us at the end of the transaction. Here in this bank existed a dormant account for the past 8 years which belong to a American national late Mr Morris Thompson who died on Alaska Airlines Flight 261.<http://archives.cnn.com/2000/US/02/01/alaska.airlines.list/> More details about the deceased himself,you can check on(<http://www.nativefederation.org/history/people/mThompson.html>) but, since then we have not had any body coming for the claims as the next of kin. A sitaution I have monitored closely with my position in the bank.Now, having monitored this deposit over the years after his death, and hence nobody has showed up as the next of kin for the past three and half years, I have moved the file to my private volt. The amount is not so much at the moment and plus all the accumulated interest the balance in this account stands at-(US$9.5million US dollars). Now my questions are:- 1. Can you handle this project? 2. Can I give you this trust? 3. What will be your commission? If you can sponsor this transfer. Consider this and get back to me as soon as possible with the following. 1.your full name 2.your full address 3.your age/occupation 4.your direct phone/fax numbers for easy communication 5.your banking details in which this money will be paid into. We shall employ the services of an attorney for drafting and notarization of probate/administration in your favor for the transfer. A bank account in any part of the world that you will provide will then facilitate the transfer of this money to you as the beneficiary|next of kin. Finally, it is our humble prayer that the information as contained herein be accorded the necessary attention, urgency as well as the secrecy it deserves. I Expect your urgent response if you can handle this project. Call me at this direct line +2348023434277 after sending a mail for confirmation. I am expecting your urgent response as soon as you receive my message. Respectfully yours, MR LEONARD OKOBI

FROM:MR.MOSES PARAISO, CONTINENTAL BANK-BENIN Av. Jean Paul II, Carrefour des Trois Banques, 01 BP 2020 - Cotonou Republice of Benin Swift: COBB BJ BJ Télex : CONTBK 5151 CTNOU ATTEN: (RE: TRANSFER OF USD28.5MILLION) Compliments of the Day Permit me to introduce myself to you. My name is MR.MOSES PARAISO,A top Management Official of the above Finance Corporation in Cotonou, Benin Republic. As it may intrest you to know, I got your contact through my international business enquiry as i was making contact of an foreign partner that will assist me to bring this deal to be a success. I beleive you will be viable and capable to champion a business of such magnitude without any problem. PROPOSITION: An Australian Engr Donald Pepper, a prosperous oil\Gold merchant had in our Bank the sum of $28.5million in a domiciliary account. Unfortunately, he was killed in a recent ghastly motor accident in Benin Republic. Efforts had been made by the management of my bank through the Australian Embassy to contact any of the deceased children but to no avail. I later discovered that he had no children. Given the skeletal information available to the bank, it has so far been impossible to reach any of the relatives. The situation left for the Management is to declare the deceased account dormant and revert the funds to trading for interest to the Bank. In order to avoid this development, I now seek your approval to have you stand as a distant relative to Engr Donald Pepper, so that the money would be released to you. I am only contacting you as a foreigner because this money can not be approved to a local bank here, but can only be approved to any foreigner with valid international passport or drivers license and foreign account. Because the money is in US dollars and the former owner of the account Engr Donald Pepper,was a foreigner too. All documents and proofs to enable you get the money will be carefully packaged once I receive your acceptance on this proposal. I shall apply for a leave as soon as the funds get into your reliable account to come to your country for sharing and investments which you will assist me in doing. May I assure you that this is safe and risk-free, as I have taken care of all necessary modalities to ensure a hitch-free Transfer I have decided that upon the conclusion of this transaction you will be entitled to 30% of the total Funds I have reposed my confidence in you and hope that you will not disappoint me. For us to proceed please send to me your full Location Address, telephone and fax numbers to enable us discuss further about this transaction. REGARDS AND GOD BLESS YOU, MR.MOSES PARAISO. Kindly call me for more information. PHONE NUMBER +229 - 05 17 26

ATTN: PRESIDENT/CEO. DEAR SIR/MADAM, I am Mr. GABRIEL MEDEI, Bank Manager {Hillbrow Branch} of Amalgamated Bank Of South Africa {ABSA}. I got your email contact, in my search for a trusted partner, who will assist me with this confidential business proposal. Mr. Stev Jam made a numbered times (Fixed) deposited for twelve calendar months, valued at US$25,000.00 (twethy- five Million US Dollars) in my branch. Upon maturity, I sent a routine notification to his forwarding address but got no reply. After a month, we sent a reminder and finally we discovered from his contract employers, National Mining Corporation that Mr. Stev Jam died from an auto accident. On further investigation, I found out that he did not leave a WILL and all attempts to trace his next of kin were fruitless. I therefore made further investigation and discovered that Mr. Stev Jam did not declare any next of kin in all his official documents, including his Bank Deposit paperwork. This sum of US$25 M is still sitting in the Bank and the interest is being rolled over with the principal sum at every end of each year. No one has come forward to claim it. According to the South African Law, at the expiration of 6{Six} years, the money will devert to the ownership of the South African Government ,if nobody applies to claim the funds. Consequently, my proposal is that I will like you as a foreigner to stand in as the next of kin to Mr. Stev Jam so that the fruits of this old man's labor will not get into the hands of some corrupt government officials. ; This is simple ( 1) I shall employ the services of an attorney for drafting and obtaining the necessary documents and letter of probate/administration in your favor for the transfer. (2) A bank account in any part of the world, which you provide, will then facilitate the transfer of this money to you as the beneficiary/next of kin of Mr. Stev Jam. The money will be paid into your account for us to share in the ratio of 60% for me and 35%[US$8,750,000:00 DOLLARS] for you then 5% will be set aside for any expenses that may occur during the transfer process. There is no risk at all as the attorney and my position will do all the paperwork for this transaction as the Branch Manager guarantees the successful execution of this transaction. If you are interested, please reply immediately via my email address. Upon your response shall then provide you with more details for the successful accomplishment of this transaction. Please observe utmost confidentiality, and be rest assured that this transaction would be most profitable for both of us because I shall require your assistance to invest my share in your country. Awaiting your urgent reply Thanks and regards Mr. GABRIEL MEDEI

MR ERIC WONG PROPERTY & LEASE MANAGERS 26 KESINGTON COURT LONDON, ENGLAND. Dear Friend, I write you in good faith, hoping that you will treat this letter as a desperate search for assistance in a matter that shall benefit both of us. A random search based on your locality from the Internet produced your name and address, Please i apologise for this medium of contact as it appears the only definate way i can have assistance with this matter. I am Eric Wong a property Manager to a deceased Immigrant property magnate who was based in the U.K., also referred to as my client. On Monday, 31 July, 2000, 13:22 GMT 14:22 UK , my client, his wife and their two Children died in the Air France concord plane crash bound for New York in their plan for a world cruise, I have been managing his properties here in the U.K. and some others which he put out for sale. The properties which have long been put out on sale have now been paid for and now the money paid has long been deposited into his local bank account here. I have contacted you to assist in repatriating the money and estate left behind by my client before they get confiscated or declared unserviceable by his bank. Particularly, the bank has issued me with a notice to provide any of his next of kin or have the account confiscated within a short period of time. My late client has an account valued at 30 Million United States Dollars Only. Since I have been unsuccessful in locating any of my clients relatives for some time now and with no one coming forward since my clients passing on, and with the bank now giving me a deadline, I now seek your consent to present you as the next of kin to my deceased client, so that the proceeds of his account valued at 30 Million United States Dollars Only can be paid to you. This I intend we share amongst ourselves in the ratio of 50% to me and 40% for you while the balance 10% we shall use for settling any miscellaneous expenses that might arise. I have all the necessary information that can be used to back up any Claim that we may make and I can assure you that you shall be paid this amount as the next of kin to my late client. All I require is your honest co-operation to enable us see this deal through. I guarantee that this will be executed under a legitimate arrangement that will protect you from any breach of the law. Trust me as his Manager of his Estates, as i have all the needed information, that this is a risk-free relationship. Please get in touch with me via email: erikwong100@yahoo.com.hk , if you are interested in helping me, so that we can discuss and i can send to you additional details. Best regards, Eric Wong ___________________________________________________________________________

My Dear Friend, My name is Dr. Ben Mboye, a Uganda national. I was the Permanent Secretary of Defense & Accounting Officer in Uganda. One of my reasons for contacting you is to share my joy with you that I have been exonerated and cleared by Hon Justice Julie Sebuntinde from the probe that involves three junk Chopper Helicopter purchased from Russia. My second reason is to ask you about the possibility of investing in your country that I believe we can embark upon together. Due to the strong campaign by President Yowery Museveni to subdue the rebel forces of Joseph Kony in my country, directive was given in 1997 for the need to purchase some fresh arms and ammunitions abroad, which includes 3 MI-24 Chopper Helicopter Gunship that have night vision and anti-missile devices from Russian. When my superiors in authority concluded the negotiation for the purchases, I was told to prepare a ?contract? for the purchases of the Helicopters, which I did as the Permanent Secretary of Defence and Accounting Officer. It will amaze you to hear that after the Belarusian suppliers delivered the three MI-24 Helicopters to Uganda, inspection was carried out and it was discovered that the three MI-24 helicopters were junks. Further investigation revealed that Lt. Gen. Salim Saleh who is a younger brother to the President and his Aide-de-Camp (Mr. Ruyondo) connived with the Russian company to supply helicopter that are almost out of service (junks) and they were not overhauled for selfish financial gains. When Hon Justice Julie Sebuntinde probed the case, a report was released stating that The Chief of Logistics and Engineering, The Minister of State for Defence and myself have been exonerated and cleared from the offence. Nevertheless, I lost my job and was prohibited from participating in public services. PLEASE NOTE: In my long years of service to my country, I was able to acquire valuable fixed assets and substantial amount of money. Why the probing of the case was going on, I was advised by my Lawyer to sell off all my acquired properties that worth million of American dollars and also to withdraw my money from my bank account to save them from being frozen and confiscated. Due to the necessity for to lie low, I delegated power to my closest aide Mr. Steve Charles to be in charge of my projects. The money realized from the sales of my properties was added to the money that was withdrawn from my account and the total amount was US$15,500,000.00 (Fifteen Million, Five Hundred Thousand United States Dollars). Since I could not lodge this fund into any bank account for fear of being traced, the money was packaged and deposited with a Security Company that belong to a German national, based in South Africa for safekeeping. The funds are security coded and well packaged in a sealed luggage to prevent them from knowing the content. Arrangement is going on for the money to be moved from its current location to an affiliate security company in Europe by Mr. Steve Charles who is currently in europe to transact this business with you since I want my identity to be kept out of the money. What I want from you at this moment is to indicate your interest and willingness to receive this money for investment purposes in your country. You are going to work hand-in-hand with Mr. Steve Charles whom is to represent my interest in this transaction, He is currently in europe. As soon as you receive this email, you are advised to contact him on his email address: stvchar1@netscape.net .He will let you know the modalities to claim the funds and also give you his phone number when you contact him. You will assist me in the investment of this money, but I will not want my identity revealed. I will also want to buy properties and stocks in multi-national companies and to engage in other safe and non-speculative investments with your assistance. At this point, I want to emphasise the high level of confidentiality, which this business demands and hope you will not betray the trust and confidence that I repose on you. l will render you 25% of this money and 5% will go for other expenses. . You ca n also reach me true Mr Steve Charles As you already know, time is of great essence in this transaction, kindly confirm your telephone and fax number to Mr. Steve Charles. Bear in mind that this project can be concluded within five days if you are prompt in your response. Kind personal regards, DR. BEN MBOYE.

Dearest: Friend, My Name is Mr.Andre Koffi a credit officer with the one of the leading Bank (Finance Trust House) here in Cotonou Republic Du Benin. In my department i discovered an abandoned sum of (USD 32 m) in an account that belongs to one of our foreigncustomer (MR. ANDREAS SCHRANNER from Munich, Germany) who died along with his entire family in July 2000 in a plane crash. http://news.bbc.co.uk/1/hi/world/europe/859479. stm Since i got information about his death, I have been expecting his next of kin to come over and claim his money because we cannot release it unless some body applies for it as next of kin or relation to the deceased as indicated in our banking guidlings and laws but unfortunately we learnt that all his supposed next of kin or relation died alongside with him at the plane crash leaving nobody behind for the claim. It is therefore upon this discovery that I now decided to make this business proposal to you and release the money to you as the next of kin or relation to the deceased for safety and subsequent disbursement since nobody is coming for it and we don't want this money to go into the bank treasury as unclaimed bill. The banking law and guidline here stipulates that if such money remained unclaimed after Five years, the money will be transfered into the bank treasury as unclaimed fund. The request of foreigner as next of kin in this business is occassioned by the fact that the customer was a foreigner and an Indigen cannot stand as next of kin to a foreigner. I agree that 30% of this money will be for you as a respect to the provision of a foriegn account , 5% will be set aside for expenses incurred during the business,another 5% to help the less previlage and to assist the charity organisations here in Africa and abroad while the rest 60% would be for me Thereafter, I will visit your country for disbursement according to the percentage indicated . Therefore, to enable the immediate transfer of this fund to you arranged,you must apply first to the bank as relation or next of kin of the deceased indicating your bank name, your bank account number, your private telephone and fax number for easy and effective communication and location where in the money will be remitted. Upon receipt of your reply, I will send to you by fax or email the text of the application . I will not fail to bring to your notice that this transaction is hitch-free and that you should not entertain any atom of fear as all required arrangements have been made for the transfer. You should contact me immediately as soon as you receive this letter. Trusting to hear from you immediately. Yours Faithfully, Mr.Andre Koffi

Mpho George, ABSA Bank Limited, Johannesburg, South Africa. Dear Sir/Madam I am Mr.Mpho George, manager of bills/exchange at the foreign remittance department of ABSA Bank. In my department, we discovered an abandoned sum of US$14,700,000.00(Fourteen Million, Seven Hundred Thousand United State Dollars only) in an account that belonged to one of our foreign customers who died along with his entire family, on November 1996, in a ghastly plane crash, and he happened to be a Foreigner Since we got the information about his death, we have been expecting his next-of-kin to come over and claim his money because we can not release it unless somebody applied for it as next of kin or relation to the deceased as indicated in our banking guidelines. Unfortunately, nobody has come forward to claim this money. It is based on this that some officials in my department and I have decided to establish a cordial business relationship with you, hence by contacting you. We want you to present yourself as the next of kin through your relation with the deceased, so that the funds can be remitted into your account. Moreover, we do not want the money to go into the government account as unclaimed bills. The banking law and guidelines here stipulates that any account abandoned or is dormant for a period of years, is deemed closed and all money contained therein forfeited to the government treasury account. Now, it is being speculated that the above sum will be transferred into the government account as an unclaimed fund on or before the end of this financial quarter of 2005, when nobody come forward to lay claims. The reason for requesting you to present yourself as next of kin, is occasioned by, the fact that the deceased (customer) was a foreigner, and we have access to his detailed bio data which you will hold as a weapon to present yourself as the next of kin. The mode of sharing after a successful transfer of the money into your account, shall be 70% to my colleagues and I, for the role you will be expected to play in this deal, we have agreed to give you 25% of the total sum and 5% for the expenses we are going to encounter by the two parties in the course of this transaction. Therefore, you are expected to reply this letter indicating your readiness and interest to participate in this business. After receiving your reply, you will be communicated to with the exact steps to take. I expect your urgent response through my email address roonyrian@webmail.co.za .And I shall contact you for further discussion on this matter, to enable us conclude this transaction urgently without any delay or hitch. Please treat this business proposal as strictly confidential for security reasons considering my official position in ABSA Bank. Regards, MR. MPHO GEORG OKEY

Dear Sir/Madam, Please forgive me if I intrude your privacy, we do not know each other but it does not matter. What matters is transparency between us in this deal. I am Mr.Victor Onyemachi. I came to know about you in my private search for a reliable and reputable person to handle this confidential business transaction. A foreigner, Name With-held until his death in a plain Crashed few years, banked with us here and had a closing balance of US$20.5M (Twenty Million Five Hundred Thousand Dollars) which the bank unquestionably expects it to be claimed by any available next of kin of the late beneficiary or alternatively be donated to a discredited trust fund for Arms and Ammunition at a National Military War College here in Nigeria. Valuable effort have been made by our Institution to get in-touch with any of the families of the depositor but proved to no avail. it is because of the perceived possibility of not being able to locate any of the families of the late depositor’s next of kin that the management under the influence of our chairman and Members Of The Boards Of Director that an arrangement be made for the funds to be declared Un-claimable and subsequently be donated to the Trust Fund for Arms and Ammunition to further Enhance the course of war in Africa and the World in General as you knows that war will eventually bring destruction to man kind. In order to avert this negative development, I now seek your permission to have you stand as the Next-Of-Kin Of. Late depositor so that the funds US$ 20.5M (Twenty Million Five Hundred Thousand Dollars) would be release and pay into your Bank Account as the Next Of Kin. Just recently the fund was moved to one an off-shore bank abroad Finance Company while the arrangement is also been made to donate the funds to the Military College if no body comes up for the claim. I am contacting you because I want the two of us to work out modalities to secure the fund and use it for our benefit instead of donating the money to a war college. With me in the inside it will be very easy. All Documents and proofs to enable us get this Fund on your name as the legal beneficiary of the said fund will be carefully worked as the documents to be secure shall state that you alone is the next of kin and the beneficiary. This transaction is 100% Risk Free so do not be afraid. Your share out of the $20.5m depends on our agreement as we proceed with the deal. I will appreciate if you send to me your age, your job type and personal information in your reply to this mail. If this Proposal is all right by you. Thanks for your co-operation. Yours Faithfully, Mr. Victor Onyemachi

FROM THE DESK OF: MR.JEFF VILAGAZI MANAGER BILLS/EXCHANGE. ABSA BANK, JOHANNESBURG SOUTH AFRICA. Dear Sir/ Madam, Firstly, I would like to introduce myself. My name is Jeff Vilagazi. I am the Manager of Bills/Exchange at the Foreign Remittance Department of one of the leading banks in South Africa. In my department, we discovered an abandoned sum of US$14,700,000.00 (fourteen million seven hundred thousand united state dollars) in an account that belonged to one of our foreign customers who died along with his wife in a plane crash. Since we received the news about his death, we have been expecting a next-of-kin to contact us and claim the money because we cannot release the money unless an application for release is made by such person(s) or by someone authorised by the deceased as indicated in our banking guidelines and inheritance laws of South Africa. Unfortunately, nobody has come forward to claim this money up till the present time of writing. It is based on this background that some officials in my department and I have decided to make an initial contact with you to establish a business relationship to claim the money. In essence, we will like to form a partnership with you where you can then present yourself as the next of kin through your relation with the deceased so that the funds can be remitted into your account. This is because unless the money is claimed now, it will go into the government accounts as unclaimed funds. The banking law and guidelines here stipulates that any account which is abandoned or dormant for a certain period of years is deemed closed and all money contained therein forfeited to the government treasury account. Now, it is being speculated that the above sum will be transferred into the government account as an unclaimed funds. The mode of sharing after a successful transfer of the money into your account shall be determine by me and you during the cause of your Phone call, to know how much you will like to take. But you should know that we have already set outside 5% of the total sum for any miscellaneous expenses we may encounter in the course of this transaction. We therefore expect you to reply to this letter through this email address to discuss the transaction further with you. After receiving your reply, we will contact you and furnish you with more details and the exact steps to take in completing this transfer. We have full access to the deceased biological data, which we will furnish you and then use to present yourself as the rightful next of kin, which give you a claim to the funds. I also will not fail to bring to your notice that this transaction is hitch-free and that you should not entertain any atom of fear as all required arrangements have been made for the movement of the money. You should contact me immediately as soon as you receive this letter. Please kindly indicate the following in your response: 1.Your full name 2.Your direct telephone and fax number for easy communication 3.Your company's name and address 4.Your Country of Origin 5.Your Residential Address 6.Your Age. Best regard, Mr. Jeff Vilagazi.

OFFICE OF THE ACCOUNTANT-GENERAL FEDERAL REPUBLIC OF NIGERIA ASO-ROCK VILLA, GARKI ABUJA, FCT ATTENTION: RE: REQUEST TO TRANSFER THE SUM OF $35,000,000.00 INTO YOUR PRIVATE/COMPANIES ACCOUNT.] "Assalaam Alaikum" I approach you most honorably today for a mutual business transaction. I am ALHAJI IBRAHIM HASSAN DANKWAMBO, the Accountant -General of the Federal Republic of Nigeria. I have been given the opportunity to be appointed the Accountant-General after several years of active service. Now by virtue of my present office and position, it is an opportunity for me to have a share of the huge oil money which many top military personnel of the past regimes had used my predecessors in the past to achieve their personal interest without any benefit towards them. Following this development, I now have an accord with a top officer of the Finance Ministry to remit the sum of US $35, 000,000.00 (Thirty Five Million United State Dollars) to your nominated account, hence we as Civil Servants do not have the right to acquire foreign account while in service. I therefore request you to kindly allocate any account of your choice with all necessary particulars to enable me to forward it to the Central Bank of Nigeria for onward release of fund transfer approvals in your favour, we have ten working days to conclude this deal on commencement, and I shall join you at the account base for sharing and further discussion on my investment plan in your country. We shall negotiate your percentage share on reply of this mail for your anticipated contribution in making this transaction a success. Do not hesitate to comment where you do not understand. ON SECURITY: To ensure maximum security all correspondences shall be by E-mail and strictly confidential. Please protect my position in my country by keeping everything secret until funds in question leave our foreign reserve account. Finally I assure you of a 100% thorough, risk free, and hitch free transaction. CONFIRM YOUR INTERET BY IMMEDIATE RESPONSE BY SENDING ME AN EMAIL. {acct_gen_alhaji3@hotmail.com} YOURS FAITHFULLY ALHAJI IBRAHIM HASSAN DANKWAMBO ACCOUNTANT-GENERAL, FEDERAL REPUBLIC OF NIGERIA.

From: The Desk of Dr. Dan Kabo Accountant General, Nigerian Liquefied Natural Gas (NLNG) Dear Sir I want to belief that this Business Proposal, which was made with good intention will not to be a source of embarrassment to you, as you may've received similar type before. I am extending this proposal to you in my capacity as Chief Accountant and in full agreement with the Auditor-General of this company (Nigerian Liquefied Natural Gas Company). After the third quarter internal audit carried on all records and accounts of awarded and executed contracts of this company (NLNG) since inception of democracy in Nigeria, a whopping sum of Thirty Two Million United States Dollars was uncovered to be floating. It might interest you to know that The Nigeria Liquefied Natural Gas Company came into full working capacity during the current civilian dispensation at a working/asset capacity of Three Billion United States Dollars, and will definitely gulp more Two Billion United States Dollars on the completion of the fifth part. The money (Thirty Two Million United States Dollars) has been approved for payment by this company NLNG, The Federal Ministry of Finance (Endorsed by the Accountant General of the Federation) and to be paid by the Apex Bank of Nigeria under Contract Number: NLNG/FGN/FMF/CBN/C987/04. As top civil servants, we are not authorized to operate Foreign Bank account hence our decision to use your account on full trust and confidence to transfer this money outside Nigeria. We have jointly agreed to transfer the funds into your account provided you will consent and prove that you can be trusted. I will regularize the approvals to reflect you as the beneficiary of the funds. We have resolved to give you 25% of the total sum for your assistance, 5% will also be used to defray all expenses that we will incurred in the course of this transaction, while we will invest our share of 70% into real estate development in your country, which you will manage for us pending our resignation from civil service. If you are capable of assisting with the transfer, please contact me immediately on my above information. PLEASE, YOU MAY ALSO IGNORE THIS LETTER AND RESPECT MY TRUST IN YOU AND ITS CONFIDENTIALITY BY NOT EXPOSING THIS TRANSACTION, SHOULD YOU NOT BE INTERESTED. Very Best Regards. Dr. Dan Kabo.

Mr. Edward Taibu Johannesburg South Africa E-mail:edwardtaibu@yahoo.com TEL:+27-73-773-1863 Attn: Chairman/CEO, My name is Mr. Edward Taibu, the stepson of Mr. Terry Ford of Zimbabwe. It might be a surprise to you where I got your contact address; I got it from the net. Don't be worried because I am contacting you in good faith. During the crisis against the farmers of Zimbabwe by the supporters of our President Robert Mugabe to claim all the white owned farms in our country, he ordered all the white farmers to surrender their farms to his party members and their followers. Terry was one of the best farmers in the country and knowing that he did not support the President political ideology, the president supporters invaded my father's farm and burnt down everything, killed him and confiscated all his investments. Before this unpleasant incident, my mother and Terry had already visited South Africa to deposit the sum of Fifteen Million, Five Hundred Thousand United States Dollars (US$15.5M) in the safe vault of a Security and financial company here in Johannesburg South Africa. This action was taken because Terry felt the growing tension on the farm issue but I guess he never anticipated the tragedy that brought his brutal and sudden death. At the time of deposition, the real content was not disclosed to the security officials; instead, it was deposited as Family Valuables? Valued for the real content in the consignment. After the bloody incident, we all had to escape out of our country for the safety of our lives. We seek refuge in South Africa and we were permitted to reside here as Political Refugees under section (5.9). Because of our present and unpleasant status, my mother and I are seriously looking forward to having an overseas partner that will assist us with the convenient and legal transfer of the funds out of South Africa. If my proposition is considered, for assisting us to transfer this money to your country, we will offer you 25% of the total fund,75% will be for my family. We wish to invest a large portion of our share in your country under your supervision. For detailed information, you can contact me on my e-mail. I would appreciate confidentiality and honesty in our correspondence. Your immediate response will be highly welcomed. I wait to hear from you. Be with God. Best Wishes, Edward Taibu for family

DEPARTMENT OF ENERGY & NATURAL RESOURCES SANDTON TOWERS, JOHANNESBURG P.M.B. 12701 SOUTH AFRICA FROM THE DESK OF: Dr. Abraham Maliba M.sc (Manager 14 Project Allocation) CONFIDENTIAL Email: maliba5@702mail.co.za Hello, It is indeed my pleasure to write you this business request. I am writing you to solicit your assistance in a business partnership that could be of mutual benefit to both of us. I hope that you read thoroughly and response as promptly as possible. Precisely, in the year 2000, the Ministry of Minerals and Energy in South Africa where I work as a Manager of 14 Project Allocation, received presidential irrevocable circular order requesting the ministry to compile and forward the list of all past foreign contractors, whose contract payments are pending since the period of the past government of Dr, Nelson Mandela and the present government. The purpose of this presidential order is that the present South Africa elected government will pay foreign contractors all debts owned, and thus maintaining a good relationship with other foreign government and non-governmental financial agencies. In light of the above, my partner and I duty is to compile a list of these contractors. We have decided to include a company name with a bill of {USD25 Million United State Dollars} along side other company names and their respective bill for payments. The {Alliance Mining SA PTY}, which was incorporated for this operation, also carried out contractual works for the ministries as well as others. With the co-operation of top senior partner of mine we are confident that our claim of {USD25Million} shall be granted being for contract work executed at the Ministry of Minerals and Energy, payment shall then be transferred upon approval to a safe account that would be provided by you in other words, if you accept to be our partner then you shall be considered given the pertinent documentation to certify that your company had been awarded a contract already executed, for which your company shall be paid the sum of USD25Million. Please be informed that with the South Africa government monetary policy. Government official's employees are not allowed to operate or to own bank account abroad hence our decision to seek a foreign partner. However, the legitimacy of this transaction is well pronounced, which I will personally explain to you by fax or telephone if you agree to be our partner to determine your true position. I have the authority and consent of my partner to offer this transaction to you. You will be highly compensated with a percentage upon mutual agreement by both parties after a successful completion of this project. Further information concerning the transaction shall be forwarded to you upon your response to this letter. I can assure you that my partners and I are in a position to make this payment claim possible, provided you can give us the assurance and guarantee that our share will be secured. Visualize this opportunity as an indirect financial resource; also note that your area of specialization is not a hindrance in the successful execution of this transaction, endeavour to contact me immediately by the above alternative email address because we will not compromise this transaction with any form of exposure, as we are still in active civil service. Please keep this close to your chest as much as possible; we can not afford any political problems. Thank you and God bless, as I await for a long term mutually beneficially relationship for both of us. Yours Faithfully Dr Abraham Maliba.

Dear Sir, I am Mrs. Suha Arafat, the wife of Yasser Arafat, the Palestinian leader who died recently in Paris France. Since his death and even prior to the announcement, I have been thrown into a state of antagonism, confusion, humiliation,frustration and hopelessness by the present leadership of the Palestinian Liberation Organization and the new Prime Minister headed by MAHMOUD ABBAS. I have even been subjected to physical and psychological torture. As a widow that is so traumatized, I have lost confidence with everybody in the country at the moment. You must have heard over the media reports and the Internet on the discovery of some fund in my husband secret bank account and companies and the allegations of some huge sums of money deposited by my husband in my name of which I have refuses to disclose or give up to the corrupt Palestine Government.And they are not relenting on their effort to make me poor for life. As you know, the Moslem community has no regards for woman,more importantly when the woman is from a christian background,hence my desire for a foreign assistance.I and my late husband deposited the sum of 6.5 million dollars with a Financial firm in Europe/Canada whose name is withheld for now until we open communication.I shall be grateful if you could receive this fund into your bank account for safe keeping and any Investment opportunity.This arrangement will be known to you and I alone and all our correspondence should be strictly on email alone because our government has tapped all my lines and are monitoring all my moves. In view of the above, if you are willing to assist for our mutual benefits, i promise to give you 30% of the $6,500,000 that will be kept in your position for a while and invested in your name for my trust pending when my Daughter, ZAHWA, will come off age and take full responsibility of her Family inheritance.Please note that this is a golden opportunity that comes once in life time and more so, if you are honest, I am going to entrust more funds in your care as this is one of the legacy we keep for our children. In case you don't accept please do not let me out to the security and international media as I am giving you this information in total trust and confidence I will greatly appreciate if you accept my proposal in good faith. Yours sincerely, Mrs.Suha Arafat Reply email: suhaarfata@walla.com

MR PETER ADAMS AUDITING AND ACCOUNTING UNIT FOREIGN REMITTANCE DEPT CREDIT BANK BENIN COTONOU-BENIN REPUBLIC WEST AFRICA. DIRECT CONTACT: +229 97 87 30 79 ALTERNATIVE EMAIL:peter_adams3010@yahoo.it My dear , I am MR PETER ADAMS, the director in charge of auditing and accounting section of Credit Bank Benin republic in West Africa with due respect and regard. I have decided to contact you on a business transaction that will be very beneficial to both of us at the end of the transaction. During our investigation and auditing in this bank, my department came across a very huge sum of money belonging to a deceased person who died on 30th january 2000 on Kenya Airways with aircraft Airbus 310-304 at location Abidjan, Ivory Coast, with registration number 5Y-BEN while travelling with his entire family, his wife, two children and a maid on a festive visit to Abidjan and since his untimely death the funds has been dormant in his account with this Bank without any claim of the fund in our custody either from his family or relation before our discovery to this development. Although personally, I kept this information secret within myself and partners to enable the whole plans and idea be Profitable and successful during the time of execution. The said amount was (USD$24.1M)Twenty four Million one Hundred Thousand united states dollars As it may interest you to know, I got your impressive information through my good friend who works with chamber of commerce on foreign business relations here in Cotonou-Benin, it is him who recommended your person to me to be viable and capable to champion a business of such magnitude without any problem. Meanwhile all the whole arrangement to put claim over this fund as the bonafide next of kin to the deceased and get the required approval and transfer this money to a foreign account has been put in place, all directives and needed information will be relayed to you as soon as you indicate your interest and willingness to assist us and also benefit yourself to this great business opportunity. In fact i could have done this deal alone but because of my position in this country as a civil servant, we are not allowed to operate a foreign account and would eventually raise an eye brow on my side during the time of transfer because i work in this bank. This is the actual reason why it will require a second party or fellow who will forward claims as the next of kin to the Bank and also present a foreign account where he will need the money to be re-transferred into on his request as it may be after due verification and clarification by the correspondent branch of the bank where the whole money will be remitted from to your own designated bank account. May i at this point emphasize that this transaction is 100% risk free as i have made all arrangements for a successful transaction as an insider of the bank before contacting you. On smooth conclusion of this transaction, you will be entitled to 30%of the total sum as gratification, while 10% will be set aside to take care of any expenses that may arise during the time of transfer like telephone bills, fax and our travel tickets to come over to your country for the sharing of the fund while 60% will be for me and my partners. Please you have been advised to keep this a top secret as we are still in service and intend to retire from service after we conclude this deal with you. I will be monitoring the whole situation here in this bank until you confirm the money in your account and ask us to come down to your country for subsequent sharing of the fund according to percentages previously indicated and further investment either in your country or any country you will advice us to invest in. All other necessary information will be sent to you on your acceptance to champion this transaction with me. I suggest you get back to me as soon as possible stating your wish in this deal. For confidentiality reasons,kindly call me on my direct line and also reply to my private Email:peter_adams3010@yahoo.it Yours Faithfully, MR PETER ADAMS +229 97 87 30 79

Dear Friend, Please as you read this, I don't want you to feel sorry for me, because, I believe everyone will die someday. My name is Mr. John Naveed, a merchant from Dubai, in the U.A.E. I have been diagnosed with Oesophageal cancer. It has defiled all forms of medical treatment, and right now I have only about a few months to live, according to medical experts. I have not particularly lived my life so well as a good person, as I never really cared for anyone (not even myself) but my business. Though I am very rich, I was never Generous, I was always hostile to people and only focused on my business as that was the only thing I cared for. But now I regret all this, as I now know that there is more to life than just wanting to have or make all the money in the world. I believe when God gives me a second chance to come to this world I would live my life a different way from how I have lived it. Now that God has called me and at the point of death, I have willed and given most of my property and assets to my immediate and extended family members as well as a few close family friends. I want God to be merciful to me and accept my soul, so I have decided to give alms to charity organizations, as I want this to be one of the last good deeds I do on earth. So far, I have distributed money to some charity organizations in the U.A.E, Malaysia and some countries in Africa. Now that my health has deteriorated so badly, I cannot do so many things by myself anymore. I once asked members of my family to close one of my accounts and distribute the money that I have there to charity organization in Bulgaria and Pakistan, they refused and selfishly kept the money to themselves. Hence, I do not trust them anymore, as they seem not to be contended with what I have left for them. The last of my money which no one knows of is the huge cash deposit of eleven million dollars $11,000,000,00 that I have with a finance/Security Company abroad. I will want you to help me collect this deposit and dispatched it to various charity organizations. I have set aside some part of this deposit for you as compensation for your time and any inconvenience this will cost you. You can also contact me on mr_johnnaveed@yahoo.co.uk God be with you. Mr. John Naveed

Kosombo Chamberlee & Associate. 11 Baker Squre Lagos Nigeria. Tel/Fax:234-8035820155. Email address:barr_kok@yahoo.com My Dear: First,I must solicit your confidence in this transaction, this by virtue if its nature as being utterly CONFIDENTIAL and TOPSECRET.Though I know that a transaction of this magnitude will make any one apprehensive and worried, but I am assuring you that all will be well at the end of the day. I am barrister Kofi Kosombo,solicitor at law.I am the personal attorney to Mr Paul Hamp , a national of your country,who was in contract with shell development company in Nigeria.On the 21st of April 1999,my client,his wife And their three Children were involved in a caraccident along sagbama express road. All occupants of the vehicle unfortunately lost their lives. Since then I have made several enquiries to your embassy to locate any of my clients extended relatives this has also proved unsuccessful. After these several unsuccessful attempts, I decided to trace his last name over the Internet, to locate any member of his family hence I contacted you. I have contacted you to assist in retrieving the sum of US$10m deposited in a security company by my client before it get'sconfisicated because the security company doesn't know that the content of the consignment is cash because on the day of deposite we declared it as family valuables because we never want them to know the true content of the consignment. The security company has issued me a notice to provide the next of kin or have the consignment confisicated within the next two weeks and these very money is too big for me to allow it to beconfisicated by the authority. Since I have been unsuccesfull in locating the the relatives for over 2 years now I seek your consent to present you as the next of kin of the deceased since you have the same last name so that the proceeds of this consignment valued at 10million dollars can be released to you and then you and me can share the money. 60% to me and 40% to you I have all necessary legal documents that can be used to back the claim. All I require is your honest cooperation to enable us see this deal through. I guarantee that this will be executed under a legitimate arrangement that will protect you from any breach of the law. I am not imposing this transaction on you,It is a thing of self willing ness,so it is either you write me back and tell me you are willing and I will know the next step to take because this fund must be claimed either with your help or the help of somebody else. After going through the proposal and under standing it very well and you are willing to do this transaction with me,get back to me immediately so that we can start as follows: 1)I will send to you the contact of the security company,the deposite code, for you to call for verification if such deposite is really existing. 2)The claim will require both of our physical presentation at the security company. With constant communication it will not take us more than seven working days to achieve our aim. It is a promise that at the end of the day you will embrace me and we will become one family friends for life as I was with my late client. Your private telephone is also needed in reponse to this proposal for oral discussions and better understanding. While I wait for your reply. Best Regard Koffi Kosombo.

Dear Friend, I am Bill Franklyn,a Financial Consultant Account portfolio manager based and working in London UK, working in one of the leading finance houses and I happen to have managed a particular account for a Resident Foreigner,here in the United Kingdom,who died Interstate, leaving in our care a sizeable amount in a domiciliary United States Dollars Investment Account. For some reasons this client does not have an easily identifiable next of Kin and I have made several enquiries to locate any of my clients relatives; immediate and extended, this has proved unsuccessful, hence I am contacting you "based on the fact that you have similar names". I need your assistance in securing the money and property left behind by my client before they get confiscated or declared unserviceable by the Finance House here in the United Kingdom. The Finance House has already issued a Government Mandatory formality notice to provide the Next of Kin or have the account confiscated and this should expire within a month. Since I have been unsuccessful in locating any of his relatives for over two years and convinced that no one is coming up and having satisfied the mandatory legal requirement of Beneficiary next of kin Notification, I now seek a Reliable and Trustworthy person,with your consent and perfect understanding, to present you as the next of kin of the deceased so that the proceeds of this account initially valued at Twenty One Million, Three Hundred And Twenty Thousand United States Dollars,($21,320,000) interest not inclusive, can be paid into an account to be provided by you(preferably) outside the United Kingdom Financial Institutions or its Isles), as the perceived Next Of Kin Legally and Otherwise. All I require is your honest cooperation and confidence in me; which I know would not come easy. I guarantee that this will be executed under a legitimate background that will protect you from any breach of the law. I would advise that you give this positive consideration and get back to me soon. I'll be flexible and considerate in the percentage share that will be given to you for your assistance. Upon receipt of your response we will exchange contact information so that we can reach each other for further discussions. Regards, Bill Franklyn

FROM: MR JONATHAN MASIN EMAIL: jomasin@workmail.co.za FAX: +27 837 697 560 TEL: +27 839 820 957 Dear Sir, I am aware that this letter will come to you as somewhat of a surprise, but I apologize to you if I have encroached in your privacy. My name is Mr. Jonathan Masin (from Harare, Zimbabwe) and I got your address through the Bloemfontein refuge camp information centre. I am the first son of late Dr Joel Masin, a farmer and business man who died in September 2003 as a result of the land dispute in my country, Zimbabwe. My father used to be a very good friend of Mr. Robert Mugabe until the government introduced the land use decree which enforced the seizure of all white owned farms. Due to my fathers, and other eminent persons opposition to the land use act which was well pronounced all over the world, even up to date, Mr. Mugabe became my fathers worst enemy, he seized his farm and imprisoned him for a long time. After the legal institution of my country found my father not guilty and he was released, Mr. Mugabe used his powers as the president and plotted the assassination of my father in his farm. He was burnt to ashes and his remain were thrown into the bore hole in his farm. We discovered this and wrote several petitions against the government. Knowing that this petition has reached a very heated stage, Mr Mugabe decided to eliminate my entire family. My sister and brother were kidnapped from their school and until today, they have not been found. I ran to South Africa with my sick mother and two other younger ones and came to this refugee camp, where we have been since December 2003. Why I am writing you are that, when my father was alive, he took me to South Africa and we visited a security company where he lodged a consignment which he informed me was loaded with the sum of US$20,500,000 (TWENTY MILLION FIVE HUNDRED THOUSAND UNITED STATES DOLLARS). This money was gotten from the sale of several of his farm machinery in combination with that of a few of his white friends whose family could not finally make it out of Zimbabwe (they were all killed secretly).They had to sell off their machinery to avoid seizure and also to ensure that they do not loose all they acquired in life. My request here is to seek your assistance to retrieve this consignment from the security company. As a refugee, I can do nothing about it and to lay claim to it will be a big problem for my family, since Mr. Mugabe is still in power. We have contacted a financial adviser who has agreed to process the necessary legal documents to assist you claim this consignment as your own. The security company does not know the contents as it was deposited by my father as diplomatic valuables. Our intention is to ensure that this money gets into a bank and as refugees we cannot operate bank accounts. We shall offer you 20% of the total amount for all your efforts and there is no single risk what so ever involved. If you are willing and kind enough to assist us, please contact us on above email, fax number. The fax number is a direct one and we use it personally through the financial adviser. I hope seriously that you consider this as ways to assist us get out of the mess we are in. Thank you as i wait for your urgent reply. Regards Jonathan Masin

Dear Sir, Is nice to know you and also I wish to solicit for your profound assistance. I got your contact through my quest for a reliable Business Partner who will guide and assist me to Invest my family heritage funds into a lucrative Business venture over there in future. Please maintain most confidential: My name is John Strasser, from Ivory Coast (Corte d' voire) I am a son of Honorable. Justice Strasser, of the blessed memory. My late father was a Politician and a Businessman, dealing on Precious Minerals in my Country. We held from Buake town of Ivory - Coast. My father was murdered early last month by the Rebels, who wanted to over throw the Government but they failed and now there is a serious crisis in my country between the Rebels and the Government. However, the Rebels have captured my town Buake and Killed so many people including my Father. And now left me and my sister and our aged mother. However, after the incident of the death of my father, we decide and ran to Ghana, the neighbouring country where we are now taking refuge at a Private guest house in Accra - Ghana. But before the untimely death of my father, My father told me sometime ago, that he has some huge amount of Money ($17.100.000.00 USD) he deposited last year in Europe, at GLOBAL SECURITY AND FINANCE COMPANY,for safe - keeping as Precious goods of family Embodiments,Meanwhile Please see Now my family and myself have move to Ghana and also We found that my family Heritage funds are there in this Private Security Firm. However, We have secured this fond for my future family Investments and I will use part of this money to buy a House in your country where I and my family will live and I will Invest the rest Funds into solid Business Ventures over there in near future. My reasons of contacting you is because I needed an honest and reliable person, who will guide me and stand as my Partner / Trustee, during the withdrawal of my heritage funds from the Security - Firm. And we shall use your Personal or Company's Account to Remit /Transfer these funds through a Bank in Ghana. Please Note: If you indicate your willingness and full interest to assist me, I will offer you 15% of my total heritage funds, as your commission for the assistance and 5% will be set aside for any expenses that will be incurred in the course of the Transaction / Transfer. Expecting to hear from you soon. Thank you, John Strasser

NIGERIA INVESTIGATION DEPARTMENT                                     4TH FLOOR MARY LAND                                            LAGOS NIGERIA                                    MOTTO: SECURITY WATCH                                                 TEL:234-8025841843 From the desk of  :MRS. ROSEMARY ANI. Attention:BENEFICIAREIS                        BE CAREFUL OF HOODLUMS. Sir/Ma, Based on the finding in this investigastion department we wish to warn you against some touts. We have been informed that some touts are contating you in respect to the collection of your fund in the total sum of  $35 Million U.S.A Dollars that was long approved in your favour through the Wema Bank of Nigeria. As  a matter of fact we have been on this investigation assignments for some time codely known to no one but the Presidency and some top government official who are in support of this investigation team to help stop fraudalent activities in this country. Although we have been able to come up with some good result about the people that have extorted money from you illegally and i wish to list them so that you will personally indicate them by writting back because we want to make your payment to you without any delay but we must surely deal and bring this names to book if only you will indicate correctly any of them. The names of the Touts that have been arrested are as follows: 1) PROF CHARLES SOLODO 2) CHIEF JOSEPH SANUSI 3)DR. R.RASHEED 4) BARRISTER  AWELE 6)BARRISTER UCHEUZO WILLIAMS. 7)Mr. Ernest Chukwudi Ebi Deputy Governor - Policy  / Board Member 8)Mr. Tunde Lemo Deputy Governor - Financial Sector Surveillance / Board Member 9)Mrs. W. D. A. Mshelia Deputy Governor - Corporate Services / Board Member The above listed names are  been traced/investigated by the police and some of them have elope the country and note that if any of them is caught and find guilty he/she we go to jailed for 25 years(twenty five years) as it is under the Degree 47 of the constituition of this bank under section of criminal law. So we are waiting for you to write us and  inform us if any of the above names have once contacted you in respect to the your fund if yes dont waste time  to indicate it immediately. Note that the only office/paying bank that have right to pay or contact you in this Transfer is the Wema Bank of Nigeria which is been headed by the bank Governor. You must deal directly with them and do what so ever you are asked to do because that is the only way you will achive the success of the transaction. We applogise on behalf of the President and the people of Nigeria for any dealy and lost this most have coursed you and promise that such thing will not happen again.And if you are dealing with any one of them regarding this payment we urge you to stop because you are taking a big risk and you never find your money any where  because your money is with the above named bank. Finally, we are expecting to hear from you today Thanks for your good understanding while we wait for your urgent response to this mail.   Yours sincerely, MRS. ROSEMARY ANI

>From Jacob Kamala Cnr.Jack & Refinery Road, Industries West, Germiston. E-mail: jacobkamala60003@yahoo.co.uk Phone Number: +27-733-174-801 Business Proposal. Good Day, With warm hearts I offer my friendship, and my greetings, and I hope this letter meets you in good time. It will be surprising to you to receive this proposal from me since you do not know me personally. However, I am sincerely seeking your confidence in this transaction, which I propose with my free mind and as a person of integrity. My name is Jacob Kamala the son of Mr. A.Y Kamala, a farmer from Zimbabwe, murdered in the land dispute in my country. As led by my instinct, I decided to contact you through email, after searching for contacts via the internet, as it is the only means I can contact anybody since I am cutting off ties with Zimbabwe for now. I apologize if this is not acceptable to you. The purpose of this letter is to seek your most needed assistance in a business venture. Due to the land and political problems in Zimbabwe, as a result of President Robert Mugabe's introduction of new Land Act Reform wholly affecting the rich white farmers and the few rich black farmers. Actually all white farmers were asked to surrender their farms to the government for re-distribution and infect to his political party members and my father though black was the treasury of the farmers association and a strong member of an opposition party that did not support the president's idea. There after he then ordered his party members and the police under his pay row to invade my father's farm and burn down everything in the farm. They killed my father and took away a lot of items from his farm. After the death of my father, our local pastor and a close friend of my father handed us over his will documents with instructions from my father that we should leave Zimbabwe incase anything happen to him. The will document has a certificate of deposit, confirming a cash deposit totaling Fifteen million five hundred thousand united state dollars. [15.5m] kept in custody for us in a security company unknown to the company that the content is money hence it was deposited as personal belongings. This money was deposited with this Private Security Company for safety and security reasons, and was to be used for the purchase of land, new machines and chemicals establishment of new farms in Botswana. This violent and barbaric act by Mugabe has since led to the death of my beloved mother and kid sister and other innocent lives. I was continually threatened to abandon my inheritance from my father after he was murdered. I resisted for a while, but when the danger became unbearable, and I survived two murder attempts, I fled Zimbabwe with the help of my father's close friend Mr. John Casahans from Australia also a farmer who was leaving in Zimbabwe with us but left with his family following this ugly development I have tried to reach him but all to no avail. I am currently staying in the South Africa where I am seeking political asylum. In fact my decision to come here to seek asylum, is because the security company from Zimbabwe, has a branch here, I have contacted them to move the safe deposit from their office in Johannesburg here, which they have since done. Therefore I need to transfer this money to an account and invest part of the money. Since the law of South Africa prohibits a refugee (asylum seeker) to open any bank account or to be involved in any financial transaction, this is why I am seeking a genuine and reliable partner, whose account this money can be transferred, hence this proposal to you. You have to understand that this decision taken by me is a very big and brave one, and it entrusts my future in your hands, as a result of the safe keeping of this money. If you accept to assist me, all I want you to do for me, is to assist with arrangements to claim the deposit from the security company's office here in South Africa, as it has now been transferred from Zimbabwe, Johannesburg South Africa to their branch here. The company will be legally informed of you representing me. For your assistance, I have two options for you. Firstly you can choose to have 20% of the money for your assistance, and helping me open an account for the money to be deposited here, or you can go into partnership with me for the proper profitable investment of the money in your country. Whichever the option you want, please to notify me in your reply. I have also set aside 1 % of this money for all kinds of expenses that come our way in the process of this transaction, and 4% for Charity donation. If you prefer to accept the 20% for your moral and financial assistance then the balance will be left in the account here for me. Unless otherwise indicate or obvious from the nature of this transmittal, the information contained in this email message is privileged and confidential information intended for the use of the individual or entity named above. If the reader of this message in not intended recipient, or the employee or agent responsible to deliver it to the recipient, you are hereby notified that any dissemination, distribution or coping of this communication is strictly prohibited. If your have received this in error or are not sure whether it is privileged, please immediately notify me by above number or email address and return or destroy the original. Thanks. Please, I want you to maintain absolute secrecy for the purpose of this transaction. Your reply should be sent to my private email address only jacobkamala60003@yahoo.co.uk I look forward to your reply and co operation, and I thank you in advance as I anticipate your co-operation. Sincerely Yours, Jacob Kamala. PLEASE YOU CAN READ ABOUT PROBLEMS IN ZIMBABWE FROM THE LINKS BELOW. <http://news.bbc.co.uk/1/hi/world/africa/918781.stm> <http://news.bbc.co.uk/1/hi/world/africa/715001.stm> <http://news.bbc.co.uk/1/hi/world/africa/1063785.stm>

Hello/Dear, I am writting this letter with due respect and heartful of tears since we have not known or met ourselves previously I am asking for your assistance after I have gone through a profile that speaks good of you. I am sorry about the miss-up in registration.I want to find out if it's possible for you to deal with individual as to investment. I came across your profile and I feel it's highly reputable that is why I pick an interest getting across to you in respect of investment at my disposal I inherited a huge amount of money from my late father,I wrote you in order to solicite for your help and assistance with hope you will understand my situation. My name is  Donald Konte .I am 21 years old from the republic of Liberia in west Africa,now seeking refuge in Dakar Senegal under the Unite Nation High Commission For Refugees (UNHCR).My (late) father Dr. Zamani Konte ,was the managing director J & D Oil company in (MONROVIA) Liberia. But he was killed along side with my senior brother during the longing civil war by rebels and all our properties was totally destroyed. However,after their death and burial I managed to escape with a very important document (DEPOSIT CERTIFICATE)of(US$6.5m) Six Million Five Hundred Thousand U.S Dollars,this document indicated me as the Next of Kin .Meanwhile,I am saddled with the problem of securing a trust worthy foriegn personality or an organisation to help me transfer the money over to Your country with the intention of investing it in a business under his/her directives and supervisstions,because I have no knowledge of investment. Please if you are so kind as to assist me I shall send to you all vital informations for your confirmation regarding the bank where the fund was lodged. I am giving you this offers as mentioned with every confidence on your acceptance to assist me as your son and manage the money in my behalf untill such a time Iam able to stand on my feet.I will be happy to hear from you. God Bless you as you consider me Donald Konte

Send instant messages to your online friends http://asia.messenger.yahoo.com

GET BACK TO ME DR.DANIEL IBE. FEDERAL MINISTRY OF PETROLEUM AND MINERAL RESOURCES. FEDERAL REPUBLIC OF NIGERIA, LAGOS, NIGERIA WEST AFRICA. ATTN: PLEASE REPLY TO:danielibe234@yahoo.com Dear Friend, RE:REQUEST FOR URGENT CONFIDENTIAL BUSINESS RELATIONSHIP IN RESPECT OF THE TRANSFER OF $25,500,000.00(TWENTY-FIVE MILLION FIVE HUNDRED AMERICAN DOLLARS)INTO YOUR ACCOUNT. I,on behalf of my other colleagues from different Federal Government of Nigeria owned parastatals decided to solicit your assistance as regards the transfer of the above stated amount into your bank account. This fund arose from the overinvoicing of various contracts awarded in my parastatal to certain foreign contractors sometime ago. We as holders of sensitive positions in our various parastatal, were mandated by the federal government to scrutinise all payments made to foreign contractors, and discovered that some of the contracts they executed were grossly over invoiced, either by omission or commission. Also, we discovered that the sum of $33,000,000.00(thirty three million American dollars only) was lying in a suspense account, although the foreign contractors were fully paid their entitlements after executing the said contracts.We all agreed that the over-invoiced amount be transferred into a bank account provided by a foreign partner, as the code of conduct of federal civil service does not allow us to operate foreign accounts. However, we have suceeded in transferring some of the monies, precisely US$7.5(Seven million five Hundred American Dollars) into a foreign account in united State of America,but unfortunately the provider of the account has severed all forms of communication with us as he has refused to adhere to our earlier mutual agreement, insisting that the total amount be paid into his nominated bank account before disbursement will take effect. We are therefore seeking your assistance based on the balance amount US$25.5M which can be speedily processed and fully remitted into your nominated bank account. On successful remittance of the funds into your account, you will be compensated with 20% of of the amount for your assistance and services. This transaction is closely knitted and in view of our sensitive positions we cannot afford a slip. I assure you that this transaction is 100% risk free.We will avail you with our identities as regards our respective office when relationship is fully established and smooth operation commences. I am at your disposition to entertain any questions from you in respect of this transaction, so, contact me immediately through the above email address for further information on the requirements and procedure. Please note that this is a DEAL and confidentiality is of very great importanceb for security reasons. Please treat with strict confidenlity and utmost urgency. N.B: Your telephone and fax numbers are needed for easy communication. Best regards, DR.Daniel Ibe. CIVIL SERVANT FEDERAL MINISTRY OF PETROLEUM AND MINERAL RESOURCES

INTRODUCTION OF, MYSELF I am Dr.DAVID V, MBOSA from Armenia, currently based in CAPE TOWN SOUTH AFRICA. I am the formal Secretary to Mikhail Khodorkovsky (M.K) the richest man in Russia and owner of the following companies: Chairman CEO: YUKOS OIL (Russian Most Largest Oil Company) Chairman CEO: Menatep SBP Bank (A well reputable financial institution with its branches all over the world). I am convinced that your business dealing is suitable for the investment of US$50 million (Fifty million United States dollars) deposited with a Bank here in the Netherlands. SOURCE OF FUNDS: The documents of the above funds in question was handed over to me to be used in payment of an American oil merchant for his last oil deal with my boss Mikhail Khodorkovsky. Already the funds have been deposited with a Finance Company in the Netherlands where the final crediting is expected to be carried out. While I was on the process, My Boss got arrested for his involvement on politics in financing the leading and opposing political parties (the Union of Right Forces) led by Boris Nemtsov, and Yabloko, a liberal/social democratic party led by Greg or yavlinsky) which poses treat to President Vladimir Put in second tenure as Russian president. You can catch more of the story on this web site. http://www.openrussia.info/eng/download/Yukos-MBX-WhitePaper.htm Or the daily mirror. YOUR ROLE: All I need from you is to stand as the Beneficiary of the above quoted sum and I will arrange for the documentation which will enable the Finance company in the Netherlands transfer the sum to you. I am assuring you that this transaction is hundred percent risks free. I have set out an agreeable percentage to any prospective partner, this is a legitimate transaction. Invariably you will be paid 25% for your management fees. Remember that the need for confidential handling of this transaction is very important for the fact that Mikhail Khodorkovsky is undergoing trial in Russia; it will be my greatest pleasure to do business with you. Please reply this mail in the shortest possible time as time is of vital important. Please reply back to me on this email: drdavidmbosa@netscape.net OR via my fax and phone numbers below. Best Regards, Dr DAVID V.MBOSA Tel: 00 870763970080 Fax: 00 870763970082

From:Mrs.Amina.A Bello. Attention:The Managing Director. This mail is not intended to cause any embarrassment in whatever form to you but i must solicit your confidentiality, i know a proposal of this magnitude will make anyone apprehensive and worried,but I am assuring you that it is sent in good faith and will be of mutual benefit to both parties.I am Mrs. Amina.A.Bello, an Iraqi refugee ,my husband was until recently, one of the personal aid to the president of Iraq who was formerly overthrown out of power by American Government . Please do not feel bad about the manner of reaching out to you it is so because I am compelled to contact you due to the situation am faced with,the last serious crisis that is still ravaging in my country,which recently led to misfortune of our government and my late husband position as the personal aid to the president, we were able to come over here in Thailand ,we inherited the sum of US$11 million.The funds were originally gotten from my late husband proceeds. My late husband was able to safe guard the fund with a very good diplomatic contact from my Country. I have decided to contact you because I am interested in investing in your country which is investment friendly. Please kindly guide and assist me in making the right investment since I am also interested in buying a residential property as I will be moving my family over there as soon as every thing regarding technical and logictics details is worked out and ascertained to our respective satisfaction. In view of your participation,I am ready to give you a good negotiable percentage for your assistance,or better still commit it into viable Joint venture projects,be assured that you stand no risk of any kind I have all necessary legal documents that can be used to back up any claim we may make anywhere. All i require is your honest cooperation to enable us see this transaction through. As soon as I get your consent, we will quickly move this fund to your country for investment I am here with my only surviving son Musa, I strongly believe that associating with you to embark on this and other business ventures will derive a huge success here after, please include you private contact telephone number and private e-mail when replying in order for me to update you more on the plans as to how we intend to actualize this transaction most successfully.I will be looking forward to doing business with you and I do solicit your Confidentiality in this transaction . Yours Sincerely. Mrs.Amina.A.Bello.

Dear Friend, As you read this, I don't want you to feel sorry for me, because, I believe everyone will die someday. My name is MR. REZA ABDULLA , a merchant in Safat, in (Kuwait) I was married with two children. My wife and two children died in a car accident six years ago. I have been diagnosed with Esophageal cancer. It has defiled all forms of medical treatment, and right now I have only about a few months to live, according to medical experts. I have not particularly lived my life so well, as I never really cared for anyone (not even myself) but my business. Though I am very rich, I was never generous,I was always hostile to people and only focused on my business as that was the only thing I cared for. But now I regret all this as I now know that there is more to life than just wanting to have or make all the money in the world. I believe when God gives me a second chance to come to this world I would live my life a different way from how I have lived it. Now that God has called me, I have willed and given most of my property and assetsto my immediate and extended family members as well as a few close friends. I want God to be merciful to me and accept my soul.So I have decided to give alms to charity organizations, as I want this to be one of the last good deeds I do on earth So far, I have distributed money to some charity organizations in the U.A.E, Algeria and Malaysia. Now that my health has deteriorated so badly, I cannot do this myself anymore. I once asked members of my family to close one of my accounts and distribute the money which I have there to charity organization in Bulgaria and Pakistan, they refused and kept the money to themselves. Hence, I do not trust them anymore, as they seem not to be contended with what I have left for them. The last of my money which no one knows of is the huge cash deposit of Ten Million Seven Hundred Thousand American dollars (U.S.$10.700,000) that I have with a finance/Security Company abroad. I will want you to help me collect this deposit and dispatched it to charity organizations. I have set aside only 20 % for you and for your time and also 5% as miscellaneous expenses. Reply me at your earliest convenience for more directives to my private email address: mr4rezaabdulla@walla.com God be with you. Regards, MR. REZA ABDULLA ___________________________________________________________________________ Mail sent from WebMail service at PHP-Nuke Powered Site - http://yoursite.com

From:Mrs.Vivian Karefa and son. Refugee Camp,Abidjan Republic of Cote D'Ivoire, West Africa. Dear , Greetings to you,Please permit me to inform you of my desire of going into business relationship with you,which will be of a mutual benefits between both of us. I am Mrs.Vivian Karefa,the widow of Late General John Karefa,the former Director of military inteligence and special acting General Manager of the Sierra-Leone Diamond mining co-operation(SLDMC).I am contacting you to seek your good assistance to transfer and invest the sum of US$8.5 million (Eight Million Five hundred thousand United States Dollars) belonging to my late Husband which is deposited in a fixe suspence account in a bank here in Abidjan,the capital city of Ivory Coast in West Africa. This money was revenues from solid minerals and diamonds sales which were under my husband's possession before the civil war broke out.Following the break out of the war,almost all government offices,co-operations and parastatals were attacked and vandalized. The SLDMC was looted and burnt down to ashes,and diamonds worth millions of dollars was stolen by the rebels millitary forces who attacked my husband office. Many top government officials and senior army officers were assasinated and my husband was a key target because of his very sensitive military possition and appointment in the SLDMC. Regretably,my husband was abducted and got his two hands amputated by the brutal R.U.F rebels(Revolutionary United Front)during their mid-night shoot-out in our official residence in freetown,our capital city. Before the death of my husband in the hospital,he told me that should incase he did not survived that he deposited some money which he made from diamond sales and contracts in a bankhere in Ivory Coast and that we should pray and find a trust worthy foreign business partner who would help us to transfer and invest this money in profitable business venture overseas. He told me to do this quickly so that I can leave Ivory Coast with my only son who is here with me in the refugee camp and then settle down abroad.He told me where the bank document to prove the deposit is kept in our house. I have gone to the bank to make inquiries about this money and I spoke with the Manager of the International remittance who assured me that everything is intact and promised to help me transfer this money to my foreign partners bank account as soon as I provide my partners foreign bank account for them.However,the manager is very concerned because of our situation here. If you are willing to assist me,please let me know immediately you received this mail so that you will arrange the transfer of the money to your account with the bank.Please note that I can offer you 15% of the total sum after the money has been transfered into your account. I am interested in any profitable commercial venture which you consider very good in your country.Please for security reason,I humbly beg you to keep this transaction very confidencial. Please there is urgent need for the money to be transferred to your account because of the political crisis here in Cote d'Ivoire now.I am hoping to hear your urgent response soonest for more clearification. Thank you and may God richly bless you and your Dear family. Mrs.Vivian Karefa and son

Do You Yahoo!? La mejor conexión a Internet y 2GB extra a tu correo por $100 al mes. http://net.yahoo.com.mx

ATTN: Dear Sir/M, I am Mr.Daniez Philip. a consulting auditor of a Bank in West Africa in west africa. I have the courage to Crave indulgence for this important business believing that you will never let me down either now or in the future. Some years ago, an American Mining consultant/ contractor with the Nigeria National Petroleum Corporation,made a numbered time (fixed)deposit for twelve calendar months, valued $42M.USD (FORTY TWO MILLION US DOLLARS) in an account. On maturity, The bank sent a routine notification to his forwarding address but got no reply. After a month, The bank sent another reminder and finally his contract employers, the Nigerian National Petroleum Corporation wrote to inform the bank that he died without MAKING A WILL, and all attempts by the American Embassy to trace his next of kin was fruitless. I therefore, made further investigation and discovered that the beneficiary was an immigrant from Jamaica and only recently obtained American citizenship. He did not declare any kin or relations in all his official documents, including his Bank deposit paper work. This money total amount$42M.USD ( FORTY TWO MILLION US DOLLARS)is still sitting in my bank as dormant Account. No one will ever come forward to claim it, and according to Nigerian Banking policy, after some years, the money will revert to the ownership of the Nigerian Government if the account owner is certified dead. This is the situation, and my proposal is that I am looking for a foreigner who will stand in as the next of kin to beneficiary, and OPEN a Bank Account abroad to facilitate the transfer of this money. This is simple, all you have to do is to OPEN an account anywhere in the world and send me its detail for me to arrange the proper money transfer paperwork, and facilitate the transfer.The money will then be paid into this Account for us to share in the ratio of 60% for me, 35 % for you and 5% for expenses that might come up during transfer process. There is no risk at all, and all the paper work for this transaction will be done by me using my position and connections in the banks in Nigeria. This business transaction is guaranteed.And the first phase of the transfer will be ($4M.USD) FOUR MILLION DOLLARS as advised by our insider in the bank.If you are interested, please reply immediately through my personal email sending the following details: (1) Your Full Name/Address (2) Your Private Telephone/fax Number. Please observe the utmost confidentiality, and be rest assured that this transaction would be most profitable for both of us because I shall require your assistance to invest some of my share in your country. I look forward to your earliest reply. Yours, Mr.Daniez Philip

Dear :sir I am Mr.JACOB UDERIKE, an accountant of the standard trust bank Plc,Lagos Branch.I have urgent and very confidential business proposal for you. I got your contact from the world trade center (W.T.C.)regional office in Lagos,Nigeria although the details of my intention was not made known to them. On June 6 1999, An American oil consultant/contractor with the Nigerian National Petroleum Corporation, Mr.Trevor made a numbered time (fixed) deposited for twelve calendar valued atUS$18,000,000.00(eighteen Million Dorllars) in my branch. Upon maturity, I sent a routine notification to his forwarding address but got no reply. After a month, I sent a reminder and finally I discovered from his contact employers Nigerian National Petroleum corporation that Mr.Trevor died from an automobile accident. On further investigation, I found out that he did not leave a WILL and all attempts to trace his next of kin were fruitless. I therefore made further investigation and discovered that Mr.Trevor did not declare any next of kin in all his official documents,including his Bank Deposit paperwork. This sum of US$18,000,000.00 is still sitting in the Bank and the interest is being rolled over with the principal sum at the end of each year.No one will come forward to claim it.According to the Nigerian Law, at the expiration of 6(six) years, the money will revert to the ownership of the Nigerian Government if nobody applies to claim the funds. Consequently, my proposal is that I will like you as a foreigner to stand in as the next of kin to Mr.Trevor so that the fruits of this old mans labor will not get into the hands of some corrupt government officials. This is simple; 1. I will like you to provide me immediately with your full names and address so that the attorney will prepare the necessary documents and affidavits, which will put you in place as the next of kin. 2,your privet telephone and fax number for rasy communication The money will be paid into your account for us to share in the ratio of 60% for me and 30% for you and 10% for the expencis that we are going to make both local and international during this process ofthis transacation. There is no risk at all the paperwork for this transaction will be done by the attorney and my position as the Branch accountant guarantees the successful execution of this transaction. If you are interested, please reply immediately via the private email address below. (jacobuderike@yahoo.com) Upon your response, I shall then provide you with more details and relevant documents that will help you understand. Please observe utmost confidentiality, and rest assured that this transaction would be most profitable for both of us because I shall require your assistance to invest my share in your country. Thanks and regards. Mr.JACOB UDERIKE

From: The Desk of Gordon Blackwell Amsterdam-Netherlands PRIVATE E-MAIL: gblacwell@walla.com RE: YOUR ASSISTANCE IS NEEDED IN ACTUALIZING THIS GOAL Let me start by introducing myself to you, I am Gordon Blackwell,I got your contact during my private search in the Internet and I want to believe that you will be very honest, committed and capable of assisting in this business venture. Firstly, let me explain the source of this funds and what you are expected to do. A foreigner and an oil merchant/contractor with the government of Netherlands, until his death, over some years ago, was a victim of Kenya airway: bus (a310-300) flight kq430 plane crash. The deceased, banked with us and has a closing balance as at July 2001 worth $4.5m (Four million Five Hundred Thousand United States dollars). Which My bank, now expects a next-of-kin to claim as the beneficiary of the funds, efforts has been made by my Bank to get in touch with the The deceased's Family or relative but to no avail. Based on the perceived possibility of not being able to locate The deceased's Family or relative and next-of-kin, the management under the influence of our chairman and the board of directors are making arrangements for the funds to be declared unclaimed and channeled to an unknown account. It is based on this that I have contacted you to stand as the next-of-kin of The deceased or relative so that the funds, will be released and paid into your account as the beneficiary /next-of-kin to the deceased. All documents, and proof to enable you get the funds have been carefully worked out as I have secured from the different offices concerned for the smooth transfer of the fund to your nominated account. It has been agreed that the owner of the account will be compensated with 30% of the remitted funds. If this proposal satisfies you, please reach me either by mail or phone: +31 64 920 8093, for more clarification about how this will be done. And also provide me the following information: NAMES IN FULL: CONTACT ADDRESS: TEL: FAX: OCCUPATION: NB: Reply me using my private mail address: gblacwell@walla.com Yours faithfully, Gordon Blackwell +31 64 920 8093 AMSTERDAM-NETHERLANDS. ___________________________________________________________________________ Mail sent from WebMail service at PHP-Nuke Powered Site - http://yoursite.com

From: Ahmed Williams Tel: 0027-72-5870-437 ATTN: SIR, PRIVATE AND HIGHLY CONFIDENTIAL Greeting! I know you will be surprised to read from me, but please this letter is a request from a family in dire need of assistance. I am Mr. Ahmed Williams from Angola. The first and the only son of Brigadier Chanza Williams communicating to you from Johannesburg, South Africa. I got your address from a business directory in Johannesburg Chamber of Commerce and Industry. And, I, on behalf of my widowed mother Mrs. Bridget Williams decided to solicit for your assistance to transfer the sum of US$35.8 Million (Thirty-five Million Eight Hundred Thousand United States Dollars), which he deposited in a safe box to private security company in Johannesburg, South Africa. In fact, my father said, and I quote: ?My son, I wish to draw your attention to US$35.8 Million (Thirty-five Million Eight Hundred Thousand United States Dollars). I deposited the box containing the fund in a security company in Johannesburg, South Africa as valuables. During the war, I was very committed and dedicated in winning the war against the rebels, until I found out that the senior army officers and government functionaries were busy helping themselves with government funds and properties, sending them to foreign countries. Due to this, when the former adviser to the president and I were assigned by the president (JOSE EDUARDO SANTOS) to purchase arms in South Africa, we saw this as a golden opportunity and diverted the money and share it, of which I got a total sum of US$35.8 Million (Thirty-five Million Eight Hundred Thousand United States Dollars). In case of my absence on earth as a result of death, only you should solicit for assistance of a reliable and sincere foreign partner to assist you to transfer this money out of South Africa for investment purpose. I deposited the box in your name and you can claim it alone with deposited code. Your mother is with all the documents. Take good care of your mother and your sisters. >From this words of my late father, you can understand that life and future of my family depend on this fund, as such I will be grateful if you can assist us. We are now living in South Africa as political asylum seekers. Financial laws and regulations of the Republic of South Africa do not permit us certain financial rights. In view of this, I cannot invest this fund in South Africa hence; I am seeking your assistance to transfer this fund out of South Africa for investment purpose. For your assistance, we are prepared to offer you 20% of the total fund while 10% will be set aside for any expenses incurred during this transaction. Please note that this transaction is 100% risk-free and the major thing I demand from you is to assure me the safety of this money when it finally gets to you. Further information and arrangement commence as soon as trust confidence and good relationship are established. I shall be most grateful if you maintain the confidentiality of this matter. Please, confirm your interest through the above contact Telephone number and send me a mail on :hammedwilliams2005@gmail.com . Best regards, AHMED WILLIAMS For the family. _________________________________________________________________ We've overhauled MSN Search Toolbar - FREE download! http://toolbar.msn.co.za?DI=1054&XAPID=2083

My Dearest One, How are you over there?. As for me,i am fine here in Daker Senegal. My name is Miss linda dickson, from Liberia in west Africa presently residing in the church camp here in Dakar due to the civil war going on in my country. My late father Dr Patrick dickson, was the personal advicer to the former head of state before the rebels attacked my house one early morning killing my mother and my father. It is only my brother and me that is alive now and we managed to make our way to near by country Senegal where we are living now. I would like to know more about you. Your likes and dislikes,your hobbies and what you are doing presently. I will tell you more about myself in my next mail. I attach here my picture for you, though i am not all that photogenic. What we need to know about loving is no great mystery. We all know what constitutes loving behavior; we need but act upon it, not continually question it. Over-analysis often confuses the issue and in the end brings us no closer to insight. We sometimes become too busy classifying, separating, and examining, to remember that love is easy. It's we who make it complicated. Nevertheless,In the church camp were i leaved.my pastor take good care of me and my brother,most time is the Rev that give me money to come to internet to look for someone that we help me and my younger brother.but i pray to god to give him more wisdom,understanding and god should strencthing him in all his endavore.I m'not looking for a very rich man,but someone who care take good of a woman and someone who have better understanding,who can bring a home togerther as one.i love my younger brother so much,because before the dead of my late mother.i promise my mum that am going to take good care of my only brother and nothing will break us. There is something that my late father left in my possition before died. 2.6 million dollars in a security bank in europe, i promised him that i will take care of it.ontil i have a man i will spend my life time with.From every human being there rises a light that reaches straight to heaven. And when two souls that are destined to be together find each other, their streams of light flow together, and a single brighter light goes forth from their united being. Moreover,the man that love me will like my brother the way he love me.because that is the only happiness that i have now. It is the things in common that make relationships enjoyable, but it is the little differences that make them interesting. you can call me in our church phone number 221525-87-24 the name of the Rev in godwin,tell him. you what to speak with Violet.the days we can answer call are,tusday and friday time 2.pm til 6pm.But before you call me, try and send me mail so that i can go and wait for your call i will tell you more in my next mail for your better understanding,i pray that God should gurd you and give you more blessing.Because the fear of God is the begining of wisdom.I 'm a good believed,i always pray to God to give me husband who will take me and my younger brother at off this mess.I have be passing some hard time all this while,but i thank God that i'm stil alive.someone need to pass some hard life to know are life is all about.But i believe that God is going to take me at off this sorrow stress of mind oneday What about you? tell me little about your self and your family what you hate in a woman and what you like in a woman? looking forward to hear from you have a wonderful day. Linda Dickson

FROM:MR Scott Reed Dear Sir/Madam, I know this email will reach you as a surprise,but need not to worry as i am using the only secured and confidential medium available to seek for foreign assistance in a business transaction. I am Mr. Scott Reed from the BANK OF AFRICA. PLC,COTONOU-REPUBLIC OF BENIN.Branch.This business request may seem strange, but I crave your indulgence and pray you view it seriously as I am convinced that you would be capable to provide me with a solution to a money transfer. On August, 2002, a retired Atlanta physician Mr George Brumley Jr made a numbered time (fixed) deposit for twelve calendar months, valued at nine million pound sterlin(£9.000,000) in my branch upon maturity. I sent a routine notification to his forwarding address but got no reply. After a month, we sent a reminder and finally we discovered from his contract employers, that the Atlanta physician Mr George Brumley Jr and his family died in the plane crash On july ,2003.See site below for confirmation of the death. May there Gentle soul rest in peace. http://www.cnn.com/2003/WORLD/africa/07/20/kenya.crash/index.html On further investigation, I found out that he died alongside with his next of kin and attempts to trace his further next of kin were fruitless. Since we got information about his death, we have been expecting his extended next of kin (family members)to come over and claim his money because we cannot release it unless some body applies for it as next of kin or relation to the deceased as indicated in our banking guidlines and laws but unfortunately we learnt that all his supposed next of kin or relation died alongside with him at the plane crash leaving nobody behind for the claim. This sum of £9.000,000 and the interest is being rolled over with the principal sum at the end of each year . If no one ever come forward to claim it according to African law, at the expiration of (four)years,the money will revert to the ownership of the Benin Government if nobody applies to claim the fund. Consequently, my proposal to you is that I will like you to stand as the next of kin to Mr George Brumley Jr and claim this funds so that the fruit of the old man's labor will not get into the hands of some corrupt Government officials. This is simple, I will like you to provide immediately your full name and address so that i can apply for an Attorney on your behalf who will prepare the necessary documents and affidavits which will put you in place as the next of kin.We shall employ the service of a probate attorney for the drafting and notarization of the Will and obtain the necessary documents and letter of probate administration in your favour for the transfer. Any bank account in any part of the world which you will provide will then facilitate the transfer of this money to you as the beneficiary/next of kin.The money will be paid into your account for us to share in ratio of 40% for me and 40% for you and 10% will be set aside for expenses incured during the process while the other 10% will be given to charity organisation.There is no risk at all;the paperwork for this transaction will be done by the attorney and my position as the banks branch Bills and Exchange Manager guarantees the successful execution of this transaction. If you are interested, please reply immediately via my private email address below .Upon your response,I shall provide you with more details and relevant documents that will help you understand the transaction. Please observe utmost confidentiality and be rest assured that this transaction would be most profitable for both of us because I shall require your assistance to invest my share in your country. Please upon the receipt of this mail message, send to me the following to enable me start the processing of the fund transfer: 1.) Your full name and address. 2.) Your private / official telephone and fax number. Awaiting your positive response via my private email:mrscottreed@walla.com or you can call me on my private telephone number:+22995713752 . Thanks and God bless, MR SCOTT REED BILL AND EXCHANGE MANAGER FOREIGN REMITTANCE DEPT: BANK OF AFRICA PLC. COTONOU-BENIN.Branch. Email:mrscottreed@walla.com

Mr Rufus Sambe Tel: +31 617 648 224 Fax: +31 847 518 138 Email: rsambe3@yahoo.com ATTENTION: THE MANAGING DIRECTOR/CEO. REQUEST FOR URGENT BUSINESS RELATIONSHIP First, I must solicit your strict confidence in this transaction. This is by virtue of its nature as being utterly confidential. We are top officials of the Republic of Namibia Contract Review Panel who are interested in importation of goods into our country with funds amounting to US$35,500,000.00(Thirty five Million five hundred United States Dollars) which are presently held in suspense with the regulatory Bank of my country. Our duties include evaluation, vetting approvals for payment for contract executed for and on behalf of my country by foreign firms, by virtue of our position in Government, we were able to procure this amount by means of over invoicing series of contracts that were awarded out to a conglomerate of foreign firms for the construction of Silicon mines and smelter complex. These contracts were with intent over invoiced to the tune of US$35,500,000.00(Thirty five Million five hundred United States Dollars) to enable my committee benefit from the projects. This over invoiced amount has been tied to a particular aspect of the contract that has been satisfactorily executed and inspected as the firms are presently securing payment from my Ministry, where our Board is in-charge of all foreign contract payment approval and recommendation to the paying bank. As a civil servant still in active government service, We are forbidden by law to operate an account outside the shores of Namibia. Hence this message to you seeking your assistance so as to enable me present your private/company account details as a beneficiary of contractual claims alongside that of the other contractors, to enable us transfer the difference of US$35,500,000.00 (Thirty Five Million, Five Hundred Thousand United States Dollars) into an account that will be nominated by you. On actualization, the fund will be disbursed as stated below: 1. 20% to be allocated to you 2. 80% due us. All logistics are in place and all modalities worked out for a smooth actualization of the transaction within the next few working days of commencement. For further details as to the workability of this transaction, please reach me as soon as possible for further clarification. Please, call me on receipt of this mail on Tel: +31 617 648 224 or send an email to me on rsambe3@yahoo.com Kindly expedite action, as we are behind schedule, to enable us embrace this transfer in the first batch which would constitute the last quarter payments for the 2005 fiscal year. Thank you while I await your urgent response. Yours Sincerely, Rufus Sambe.

HELLO, I am contacting you based on a pitiable situation in which I found myself today. Please find a way to help me out and I will remain grateful.I happened to be a victim of Sudan political crises which has turned me into an orphan and a semi - beggar.At the moment, I am as confused as hopeless but I believe that this condition is not going to be permanent but what I do not know is when. My name is Ms.Fatima Fahad from citizen of Sundan, the only daughter of Mr. Modu Fahad. My father was a business man and well known Gold dealler from Darfur in Sudan. He was murdered in cold blood late last year 2004 ,during the bombing of our village,Rahad Kabolong in the western Sudanese state of North Darfur with my mother . You can find the story on this website. http://news.bbc.co.uk/2/hi/programmes/panorama/4007191.stm My late father Modu Fahad deposited the sum of US$5.500.000.00 Million (Five Million Five Hundred Thousand United States Dollars) under a custody of Finance Firm Dakar Senegal. However, I came to Senegal with the deposit documents of the money for the claim of the money out from the Finance firm and transfer to a foreign trustee with interest to secure a sustainable investment for my future survival. I'm therefore soliciting for your assistance to help me receive the money out from Senegal and as well to transfer it into your private or company account for investment in your country under your control,because at my age,i don't have a business idea. I want you to stand as my fathers foreign busines partner for a successful retrieve and transfer of the money out from Senegal with your name and also help me to secure my traveling documents to come over your country for the investment and to live my future life under your care. Please reply immediately you receive this mail for further discussion and also tell me the amount you will take as your rewards for helping me to handle the transfer to your position to enable me give you more detail informtion about the deposit. Thanks for your anticipated understanding and co-operation. Best regards, Fatima Fahad.

Dear friend, Greetings, I am Mr.Henry Okoye the Account Manager of Late Mr. Morris Thompson in Standard Trust Bank Regional Office in Victoria island, here in Lagos.However I got your contact through the International web directory.I decided to contact you by email because I feel that it is more secured and private. Recently we discovered a Dormant Account with a huge amount of Money Valued USD35,000,000.00 (Thirty Five Million Dollars only)that belongs to one of our late Customer who died in a plane crash .During our investigation and auditing in this bank, my department came across a very huge sum of money belonging to Late Mr. Morris Thompson an American great industrialist and a resident of Alaska, who unfortunately lost his life in the plane crash of Alaska Airlines Flight 261 which crashed on January 31 2000,including his wife and only daughter. You shall read more news about the crash on visiting this site which I got during my investigation; http://www.cnn.com/2000/US/02/01/alaska.airlines.list/ and http://www.nativefederation.org/history/people/mThompson.html The fund has been dormant in his account With this Bank without any claim of the funds in our custody either from his family or relation before our discovery of this development. The Banking law here stipulates that if such money remains unclaimed for five years, it will be for feited no the Bank treasury as an unclaimed bill.It is only a foreigner that can stand as a next of kin and It is upon this discovery that I decided to contact you to collaborate with you to pull out this dormant fund. In order to avert this negative development, I on behalf of my trusted colleagues now seek your permission to have you stand in as next of kin to Our late Customer so that the fund will be released and paid into your account as the beneficiary.s next of kin now that the bank is still expecting a next of kin or relative of the deceased ,Late Mr. Morris Thompson. In fact we could have done this deal alone but because of our position in this country as civil servants, we are not allowed to operate a foreign account and that would eventually raise an eye brow on our side during the time of transfer since we still work in this bank,this is the actual reason why we required a second party or fellow who will assist us forward claims as the next of kin and also provide either an existing bank account or to set up a new Bank a/c immediately to receive this fund, even an empty a/c can also serve for this purpose. On smooth conclusion of this transaction, you will be entitled to 40% as gratification for your assisting us, and the remaining 60% will be for me and my partners. What I want from you is for you to act as the deceased next of kin. I have in my possession, all the necessary Documents to successfully accomplish the operation. Bear in mind that this proposal is 100% risk free. Further Information will be given to you as soon as I receive your positive response. I suggest you get back to me as soon as possible stating your wish. Find in the attachment of my Family Picture, to proof who I am. I await your Urgent Responce, Regrads, Mr.Henry Okoye

NAME:MRS. SUZANA NUHAN VAYE %BARR.JAMES BRODERICK (ATTORNEY) TEL/FAX:44-70-40120730 EMAIL:jbroderick@satellite-email.com EMAIL:jbroderick@o2.pl EMAIL:jbroderick@MAIL.NU ATTN: MD/CEO Kindly accept my apology for sending my mail to you.Please, I sincerely wish to let you know that this is not the kind of e-mails that you will refer to as "spam" or it's like. I am genuine and my attorney will prove it to you once he hear from you.Please help me out in this my condition. I believe you are a highly respected personality,considering the fact that I sourced your profile from a human resource profile database on your country in the Internet. Though, I do not know to what extent you are familiar with events and fragile political situation in Liberia but it has formed consistent headlines in the CNN, BBC news bulletins. My Name is MRS.SUZANA NUHAN VAYE from Liberia,a Country in West Africa. My late Husband is Issac Nuhan Vaye, Deputy Minister of Publ ic Works in Liberia. My Husband was falsely accused of plotting to remove the then PRESIDENT OF LIBERIA CHARLES TAYLOR) from office.Without trial, Charles Taylor killed him. You can verify this from some of the international newspapers posted in the web sites below: (I)http://www.usatoday.com/news/world/2003-07-15-liberia_x.htm Before my husband was killed, he moved out the sum of $21.5 million through a diplomatic means, and deposited it with a Security Company Abroad. And this money was meant for importation of agricultural machinery. All that is needed is for my lawyer to instruct the company to transfer the funds to your account, I will remunerate you with 20% at the end,but most of all is that I solicit your trust and honesty in this transaction. I have been confined only to our country home and all my calls are monitored, so I wil l advise you to contact my private Attorney Barr.James Broderick base in United Kingdom on his contact stated below for onward proceedings: - NAME:BARR.JAMES BRODERICK(ATTORNEY) TEL/FAX:44-70-40120730 EMAIL:jbroderick@satellite-email.com EMAIL:jbroderick@o2.pl EMAIL:jbroderick@MAIL.NU Kindly include your Full Name,Residential or Company Address, Private Telephone, Mobile and Fax Number where you can always be reached,to enable him send details/documents that will enable you receive the fund without any problem either now or in future as allmodalities as been perfected. Please your urgent response is needed. God bless you. Best Regards. MRS.SUZANA NUHAN VAYE (WIDOW) ___________________________________________________________________________ Mail sent from WebMail service at PHP-Nuke Powered Site - http://yoursite.com

Mrs. Suzana Nuhan Vaye. Email: suzananuhanvaye01@she.com Tel: 66-5-1539304 Dear Sir, With due respect trust and humanity. I write you this letter which I believe, would be of great interest to you. I believe you are a highly respected personality considering a careful research which I have been able to make inrespect to your kind of person, before I decided to entrust this transactions and database in your country into your hands which I believe you will not betray my trust and confidence already entrusted on you. Though, I do not know to what extent you are familiar with events and fragile political situation in Liberia but it has formed consistent headlines in the CNN, BBC news bulletins. My name is MRS. SUZANA NUHAN VAYE and my Son MUSA NUHAN VAYE, we are from Liberia, a Country in West Africa. My late Husband MR. ISSAC NUHAN VAYE, was then Deputy Minister of Public Works during President Charles Taylor regim in Liberia. My Husband was falsely accused of plotting coup to remove the then President of Liberia (Charles Taylor) from office. Without trial, President Charles Taylor killed him. You can verify this from your country. You can also check in some of the international newspapers posted in the web site below: (i) http://www.usatoday.com/news/world/2003-07-15-liberia_x.htm Two days before his arrest, he managed to sneak out a written message informing me about one trunk box of valuable, containing money which he had concealed under the roof. He instructed me to take our only son and move out of Liberia immediately to Bangkok Thailand, I become a widow overnight, helpless situation without a partner. At that moment of calamity, every persons was running for his and her life. My son and I manage to escape through the help of an airline to Bangkok with the box and some vital documents property title. The cash involved in the box is Nine Million, Three Hundred Thousand United State Dollars (US$9.3M). Due to fear and limited rights as refugee, I deposited the box with a private security organization in order not to raise an eyebrow over the box here in Bangkok. My son's name is MUSA NUHAN VAYE and we are temporary residing in Uttaradit in the northern part of Thailand as assylum seekers. Be inform that the real content of the box was not disclosed to security company for security reasons. Concerning the money, we are prepare to give you a reasonable percentage of 30% of the total sum and 10% would be mapped out for any expences incured in the course of this transaction and 60% will be for my family. For the interest of this business do not hesitate to contact my son MUSA NUHAN VAYE on this Tel: 66-5-1539304, or email:{suzananuhanvaye01@she.com} as soon as you receive this letter. Feel free to contact my son for more information. No other person know about this money apart from my son and I, endeavor to keep this business confidential. We await your quick reponse. May God bless you. Best Regard, Mrs. Suzana Nuhan Vaye.

Dear friend, I am Barrister Fred Briggs of Fred Briggs Chambers and Associate. I am the financial lawyer to the late Mr Martins Max from Stuttgart, Germany. Martins Max was an oil merchant with estment in the leading oil in Africa. He invested in lifting oil from Niger delta in Nigeria to other countries where he sales it. He was the highest shareholder in Shell petroleum Bp in 1994. Martins Max met his untimely death via plane crash in the 2002. I was contacted as his lawyer by the board of director, GLOBAL LINKS SECURITIES LTD to look for the relative of late Mr. Martins Max to enable them transfer the accumulated share dividend of his investment with the GLOBAL LINKS SECURITIES LTD. It is about two years now. I made some research about the relatives of Mr Martins Max and discorvered through some DNA reports that some other two passengers in the same plane happend to be his wife and only daughter Cynthia Martins Max who also died along with him in the crash. I am contacting you so that both of us can reach an agreement to enable you act as his next of kin and claim the fund of course they will believe me because I am his financial lawyer untill his death and I have all his business documents with me.I would have use someone from here for the purpose but the fact that late Martins Max is a white man made it impossible for me to present a black man as his next of kin which of course, the GLOBAL LINKS SECURITIES LTD will not honour.All the document will be validated in your name and shall be drafted by me to include your name in an application which be forwarded to the GLOBAL LINKS SECURITIES LTD for the claims. The money is just USD18.Million dollars. I will personally monitor the progress of the transaction as your lawyer. After we succeed in transfering the money into your account, we will give some portion of the money to charity home in your country and then share the remaining in the ratio 70% to 30% between you and I. If you are willing to work with me in this regard, please, forward to me through this email address: 1. Your full name and contact address 2. Your phone and fax number (cell phone) 3. Age aggregate 4. Occupation and position Thanks and God bless you. Barr. FRED BRIGGS Fred Briggs and Associates

From: Miss Julian Zanna. Rue 12 Avenue williamsville Abidjan, Republic of Cote D' Ivoire. julzna74@yahoo.fr Dear Friend, I am sorry if this mail will come to you as an embarrassment or a suprise,I just felt like empting myself to you,I got your contact through yahoo member's directory and having gone through you profile i decided to contact you ,as am faced with total frustration and hardship. My ernest prayer is that you find this mail in good health and blessings. I am presently residing in Abidjan,Cote d'Ivoire.I left my country with my father after the death of my mother during the war in our country and we came here because my father owned a business here,(cocoa business), during the going political crisis here which has turn out into a civil war since 2003,my father was attacked and killed here at the hit of the crisis as the rebels were killing prominent foreigners with the reason that they were financially supporting the government against them and the rebels are accusing the government of doing the killing. Presently,I am staying in a REFUGEE camp assisted by the Red cross organisation,due to the way which the camp is securized by united nations forces and after the death of my father,our house was set ablaze,I was unable to meet my needs pay my bills and accommodation. And in my dilemma which was another reason for going to the camp, where I could at least feed and sleep as I did not know anyone here. I take permission to go to the town where they have internet access to enable me correspond with you. Secondly,my late father concealed some amount of money in a trunk box and deposited it in a safe keeping house to the turn of $19.5 million dollars which I will want you to help me move out of this country because of the war here.But the safe keeping house does not know the true content of the trunk to be cash as my father declared upon deposit as containing art craft for export. My father confided so much in me after the death of my mother,infact I became his wife,we were so close that we never did anything without my knowledge and opinion All that I want is your sincere and genuine help in helping me safe guide this trunk which means that you will have to come here so that we can meet face to face first before proceeding with this claim,as we have to do the claiming of the trunk which the money is concealed claimed out of the safe keeping house first and the money moved out of this country as I am the named next of kin to this deposit. I can not allow the money remain here while because of the war here which possess a great risk to as my life and future solely lies on it.If you have heard from the news for the past few months now there has been intense fighting and bombing by the French troops which I will like to live here as soon as we have this money moved out of this country. I will also like upon your arrival here to open an account in any of the international banks of your choice here where this money will be lodged into for transfer to your country,I know that this is our first mail,but I have decided to confide in you from the choice of your word on your profile. I want you to know that for years now,I have lived in absolute frustration,tires and pains without any person around me,no parent,uncles or friend,but God had kept me until now,which I believe that I will smile once again. Thirdly,I do not want to attach myself to you out of desperation so that I do not get used rather I intend you helping me to claim this money as I intend living for your country to start an entire new life and complete my education,as you will have to help in the investment of this money. But I really need your help at this trial and difficult time of mine. I am totally frustrated that my whole mind for now lies on my survival which is securing this money.Please I am confiding completely in you and I really need your assistance at this point of my life as you alone knows of this venture. I will enclosed my copies of my personal pictures and my late father's pictures for your view I wait to hear from you. Please get back to me with the above yahoomail address as well shown below: julzna74@yahoo.fr Thanks and be bless. Julian Zanna.

Good Day Dear, Am sorry for the inconveniency it may curse you for using this opportunity to communicating with you for the first time. Well I shall be extremely happy if you will kindly understand the content of my proposal thereby contributing your own quarter. Its true that the message will have some characters, but I want you to choose the best character that should favour us better, so that we should forge ahead in this transaction . Well I am Mr Cyril J Garang , and an indigene of G/Bissau, though I left my country as a matter of death scallating because of wars but that was not my primary aim of leaving my country to Dakar Senegal where I am currently staying now, my major reason is because I was humiliated by my late father’s relatives as a result of their much focus on material things. I left my country because I was the only child left in my late father’s linage and It will not come to an end rather I will ensure I keep the family name on constant remembrance and existing. But the principal aim for my being here is to concentrate well on what I will do in future with the money my late father left in one of the banks in Europe, the money is Five million eight hunderd thousand US dollars ( $5.8 M).This money was meant for his multi investment projects before death struck him down. This is the principal reason why I am here in this country so that I shall concentrate and be mindful to this everlasting opportunity I inherited and to search for one who will stand on my behalf in the claim. My contacting you is based on your complete capability to move to the Europe bank as soon as you could so that you will have a Table discussion with the bank thereby reclaiming and retransferring this money to your own bank account where it will be confidently be secured for my future investment . There are other things that we should discuss as soon as you write back because we need to round up every bit of this matter before all the bank details should be exchanged to enable us come to close end of the whole matter which will lift me up from here to your country with your help and where we should stay for our investment projects as we agreed in the next page. Don’t forget that there are some hidden percentage that I have wholeheartedly mapped for you which will be revealed when we come to agreement that you will help me to secure this money in your own easy accessible bank account. Hope to hear from you and it will sound better and encouraging if you will reply with your complete data’s so that I shall commence all applications on the need able documents that will ease the direct recommendation and also empowering you as my foreign live partner or my late father’s business associate before his death. Regards: Mr Cyril J Garang.

Hon.Dr.Garuba Gambo Minister, Foreign Affairs Ministry. Maputo Street Zone 3 Wuse- Abuja-Nigeria. 24/11/2005 Sir, Re: PAYMENT AUTHENTICATION.., I am Hon.Dr.Garuba Gambo, Minister Foreign Affairs Ministry; my office monitors and controls the affairs of all banks and financial institutions in Nigeria concerned with foreign contract payments. I am the final signatory to any transfer or remittance of huge funds moving within banks both on the local and international levels in line to foreign contracts settlement. I have before me list of funds, which could not be transferred to some nominated accounts as these accounts have been identified either as ghost accounts, unclaimed deposits and over-invoiced sum etc. I write to present you to the federal government that you are among the people expecting the funds to be transferred into their account, on this note; I wish to have a deal with you as regards to the unpaid certified contract funds. I have every files before me and the data's will be to change to your name to enable you receive the fund into your nominated bank account as the beneficiary o! f ! the fund's amount $20 Million U.S.D. As it is my duty to recommend the transfer of these surplus funds to the Federal Government Treasury and Reserve Accounts as unclaimed deposits, I have the opportunity to write you based on the instructions i received 2 days ago from the Senate Committee on Contract Payments /Foreign Debts to submit the List of payment reports / expenditures and audited reports of revenues. Among several others, I have decided to remit this sum following my idea that we have a deal/agreement and I am going to do this legally. MY CONDITIONS. 1. You will give me 65% of the contract funds as soon as you confirm it in your designated bank account. 2. This deal must be kept secret forever, and! a! ll correspondence will be strictly by email / telephone, for security purposes. 3. There should be no third parties as most problem associated with your fund release are caused by your agents or representative. If you AGREE with my conditions, l advise you on what to do immediately and the transfer will commence without delay as I will proceed to fix your name on the Payment schedule instantly to meet the three days mandate. I hope you don't reject this offer and have the funds transferred. Waiting for your reply soon. Yours Sincerely. Hon.Dr.Garuba Gambo (FOREIGN AFFAIRS MINISTER.) Alternative Email:greguuu@indiatimes.com The information in this message and in any attachments, contains confidential information and is intended solely for the attention and use of the addressee(s)

FROM: MR.RAYNOLD BENJAMIN OLDS', 36b Attha Benious Aures, Cotonu-Republic Of Benin. Thank you for giving me your time; please be patient and read my email,I sincerely hope that after you read this mail you will act fast and respond to my call. My name is RAYNOLD OLDS',35 years from Zimbabwe.I am the eldest son of late Eng.MARTIN OLDS'. My father established his Tobacco farm in Bivis.While he was in Hwali, a northern city to negotiate for the sale of one of the farm plantation that he was shot and killed by Mugabe's supporters, As a result of the current political instability and war against farmers to claim all the white-owned farms for his party members and his followers. They as well burnt everything in the farm. Before his death,my father had deposited with one Security Company in Holand, the sum of $10.5m (Ten Million Five Hundred Thousand United States Dollars). This was money he planned to use in buying new machinery and to set up a new farm in Swaziland. The money has been in the security company in holand just for safe keeping although the courier company were not aware of the content in the case because it was convey as personal valuable goods,I have all legal documents with me as of when it was deposited in a Security Vault for safe keeping. I got your reference from the Benin Exports Promotion Council (BEPC)where i am on asylum because of continued harassement from Mugabe and his supporters.Having noted the confidence reposed on your person I became convinced of your capability and goodwill to asist in securing this money for an investment in your country and to assist me with a letter of invitation that will enable me secure a visa into your country for residence . If you agree to help, we will compensate you sincerely for your candid effort in this regard with 10% of the total amount of $10.5 Million US Dollars. Also, when the money ($10.5 Million) is moved into your discrete account, you will be allowed to withdraw 35% in your favour while 5% would be for expenses, tax as your government may require. The remaining 60% will be invested meaningfully for us(me and my family)in your country. I have perfected arrangements with the Trust Company concerned and has been assured 100% risk free and safe operation. What I demand from you now is to arrange to visit the Finance Company where this money is being deposited and claim it as the bona-fide owner. And in due course,all contacts must be made through my private. E-mail:mrraynoldbenjamin@yahoo.fr, Tel:+229-9571-3752. You will be Godly rewarded for your candid effort.Please do call me immediately you get this message and send forth your private Phone/Fax number(s) and E-mail address(s)for easier communication. Awaiting your response.Thanks and God bless. With Regards, Reynold Olds

From: Mrs. Rose Welsh. 17 Copse Hill, Wimbledon, SW20 0NE, London, United Kingdom. My Dear Beloved,

I am the above named person but now undergoing medical treatment in Barnes Hospital, South Wople Way, SW14 8SU, London, England. I am married to Dr. Gerald Welsh who worked with British Judicial Commission in Chelsea England for over a decade before he died on 5th of July in the year 2003. We were married for fifteen years without a child. He died after a brief illness that lasted for two weeks. Before his death he made a vow to use his wealth for the down trodden and the less privileged in the society. Since his death I decided not to re-marry or get a child outside my matrimonial home.

When my late husband was alive he deposited the sum of £10 Million (Ten Million Pounds sterling) with one Finance/Bank in Europe. Presently, this money is still with the Bank. Recently, my Doctor told me that I would not last for the next 4 months due to a rare form of cancer of the pancreas. Though what disturbs me most is my stroke. Having known my condition I decided to donate this fund to an individual or better still a God fearing person who will utilize this money the way I am going to instruct herein.

Though I may not know you personally I want to tell you that, through divine word of wisdom from above,I was asked to tell you to do this, not for me but for The Almighty because you are blessed and you have been chosen to do mighty works for the Almighty. I want an individual that will use this to fund and provide succor to poor and destitute persons, orphanages, and widows and for propagating peace in the universe. I understand that blessed is the hand that giveth. I took this decision because I do not have any child that will inherit this money and my husband relatives are not inclined to helping poor persons and I do not want my husbands hard earned money to be misused or spent in the manner in which my late husband did not specify.

I do not want a situation where this money will be used in an ungodly manner, hence the reason for taking this bold decision. I am not afraid of death hence I know where I am going.I know that I am going to be in the bosom of the Almighty. I do not need any telephone communication in this regard because of my health, and because of the presence of my husband's relatives around me always. I do not want them to know about this development. With God all things are possible As soon as I receive your reply I shall give you the contact of the Finance/Security Company in Europe. I will also issue you a letter of authority that will empower you as the original beneficiary of this fund. I want you to always pray for me. My happiness is that I lived a life worthy of emulation. Whosoever that wants to serve the Almighty must serve him with all his heart and mind and soul and also in truth.

Please always be prayerful all through your life. Any delay in your reply will give me room in sourcing for an individual for this same purpose. Please assure me that you will act according to my specification herein. I will also be most glad if you can tell me a little about yourself.Hoping to hear from you. Thank you and may the Almighty bless you.

You can contact me with your positive responds via Emails:

1: rosewelsh@cooperation.net

Yours sincerely, Mrs. Rose. G Welsh

Dear Friend, I Hope This Mail Meets You In Good Health And Spirit, I Am, Mr Yaem Ahamed, A Sierra Leone. Presently, I Live As A Refugee In republic of Senegal Dakar , With My Younger Sister, We Are A Victim Of War And The Son Of Late Chief Dr.Us man .Ahamed The Director Of Sierra Leone Gold And Diamond Mining Corporation. My Father Was Killed With Other Government Officials During Official Hours When The Rebel Troops Stormed And Raided The Mining Corporation Office At The Heat Of The Crisis In My Country. A Few Weeks Later, The Rebels Also Invaded Our Residential Building In Which My Mother And Two Of Our Security Men Were Killed In The Compound While I Was Out For A Special Research Program And My Younger Sister Was In School. I Had A Singular Shock And Trauma, Which Compelled Us To Flee From The Country To republic of Senegal Dakar By The Help Of An Army Colonel, Who Is A Close Friend Of My Late Father, I Have First Degree In Marketing And Would Have Further My Education If Not For The Death Of My Parents. I Have Never Worked To Earn My Living Since My Late Parents Had Enough Wealth For Us. I Am Contacting You Now Because Of The Present Difficulty I Am Facing. Unfortunately My Father's Two Accounts In West Africa Have Recently Been Frozen. However This Did Not Affect The Twenty Million And Six Hundred Thousand Dollars (Us$ 20,600,000), Which He Kept In a security company in Senegal Dakar. For Now, I Am Having Every Information And Document Needed For The Clearance Of The Money In A company Here In Senegal Dakar And I Want You ToAct As The Beneficiary Of The Fund For Easy And Smooth Transfer To Your Account Abroad For Investment Purposes. You Will No Doubt BeAdequately Compensated With As Well As A Percentage Of The Profit From Investment Of The Fund. Also You Will See To It That My Sister And I Come Over To Your Country At The Earliest Possible Time. I Am Making This Request To You With Tears In My Eyes And I Feel That God Almighty Will Touch You With His Spirit To Listen To My Cry For Help And Answer Me Without Delay. Since Our Breadwinner Is No More And This Is The Only Hope For Life. You Positive Response Will Give Me The Greatest Joy And Relief. For Your Kind Of Assistance Me And My Sister We Have Agreed To Offer You 32% Of The Total Sum. Seriously Waiting For Your Urgent Reply In Our MailBox ahmed_yaem@yahoo.fr Best regard Mr.Yaem Ahamed

Eric Wong. Union Bank Of China, 99 Queens Road Central Hong Kong, Dear Friend, I write you in good faith, hoping that you will treat this letter as a desperate search for assistance in a matter that shall benefit both ofus.A random search based on your locality from the Internet produced youraddress, Please i apologise for this medium of contact as it appears the only definate way i can have assistance with this matter. I am Mr Eric Wong, Head of Private Banking, Union Bank Of China,also account Manager to a deceased Immigrant property magnate who was based in the U.K. and had vast business interest in Hong Kong ,also referred to as my client.On Monday, 31 July, 2000, 13:22 GMT 14:22 UK , my client, his wife and their two Children died in the Air France concord plane crash bound for New York in their plan for a world cruise I have been managing his Bank accounts here in the Hong Kong, and some Properties which he had put out for sale. The properties which have long been put out on sale have been paid for, and the money paid has long been deposited into his local bank account here. I have contacted you to assist in repatriating the money and estate left behind by my client before they get confiscated or declared unserviceable by my Bank. Particularly, the bank has issued me with a notice to provide any of his next of kin or have the account confiscated within a short period of time.My late client has an account is valued at 18 Million United States Dollars Only I therefore made further investigation,with the personel department and discovered that did not declare any kin or relations in all his official documents, including his Bank Deposit paperwork in my Bank. This sum of US$18million is still sitting in my Bank and the interest is being rolled over with the principal sum at the end of each year. No one will ever come forward to claim it. According to Laws of Hon Kong, at the expiration of 5 (five) years, the money will revert to the ownership of the Hong Kong Government if nobody applies to claim the fund. I now seek your consent to present you as the next of kin to my deceased client, so that the proceeds of his account valued at 18 Million United States Dollars Only can be paid to you, I will like you to provide immediately your full names and address so that the attorney will prepare the necessary documents and affidavits that will put you in place as the next of kin. The money will be paid to you for us to share in the ratio of 60% for me and 35% for you and 5%, after completion,for Expenses Incurred in the course of the transaction .There is no risk at all as all the paperwork for this transaction will be done by the attorney and with my position as the Head Private Banking guarantees the successful execution of this transaction. If you are interested, please reply immediately to my email: ericwong014777@yahoo.com.hk All I require is your honest co-operation to enable us see this deal through. I guarantee that this will be executed under a legitimate arrangement that will protect you from any breach of the law. Trust me as his Manager of his Estates, as i have all the needed information, that this is a risk-free relationship.You should observe utmost confidentiality,and rest assured that this transaction would be most profitable for both of us because I shall require your assistance to invest my share in your country. Awaiting your urgent reply. Thanks and regards. Eric Wong.

Hello, It is a pleasure to introduce this business proposal to you, with due respect and heart full of gratitude , i know that it may be surprise to you, hence we don't know each other for the first time but i do believe that this will bring us together to know ourselves much better and do joint business together. I want you to know that my name is Tony Omar and i am living presently in a refugee camp here in Dakar Senegal and i am from Sierra Leone, i am 28 years old, i am ready to start a good and profitable business ventures with you in which you are the only one who will advise and execute the business ventures over there in your country for the benefit of both of us. Meanwhile, i want you to know that i need a reliable,honest,trust-worthy business partner , who will not betray me but handle the business ventures in honest and sincere manner. Moreover, i want you to know that my late father, EL-HAJI,Ousmane.Omar The Assassinated Former Director of Sierra Leone Gold And Diamond Mining Corporation, made a deposit in a High Security Company here in Dakar Senegal, before he was killed in my country Sierra Leone,i am the only survival of my family and the next of kin of the deposit, my late father deposited 19.5 million,us dollars into the high Security and Finance Company Dakar Senegal, i am searching diligently for a honest person who will help me invest this fund into a good profitable business ventures and accept the transfer / delivery of the fund to your position for an immediate investments. For your participation and assistance is this transaction, i have decided to give you 25 percent of the total amount and and you will be a share holder in every business ventures we establish, 5 percent will me map out for any expenses that may occur during this transaction.I really want to invest in your country and i know that your country is political suitable for a profitable business ventures, i hope that with you, it will be so easy for me to locate a nice business ventures, please i will like you to search diligently for a profitable business ventures that we shall in invest on, so that as soon as the security company release and deliver the consignment to you on my behalf, we shall set up the business immediately. NOTE: I will give you the contact of the security and finance company, for you to contact them as soon as i hear from you for the immediate release and delivery of the consignment to you on my behalf, call me for more details 00221-471-28-95. I shall be glad to reserve this respect and opportunity for you, if you so desire, but do urge you to give the matter your immediate /urgent attention it deserves. Looking forward to your response. tony_omar@walla.com Thanks and remain bless. Yours sincerely. Mr.Tony Omar

Très cher, Je suis Mme Mari Gomogo e d'origine Angolaise. Je suis marié à Mr James Gomogo pour qui a travaillé avec les forces marines l'Angola pendant neuf ans avant qu'il ne decède en 2004. Nous étions mariés pendant onze années sans enfant. Il est mort après une brève maladie qui a duré seulement quatre jours. Avant sa mort nous étions tous les deux chrétien veritable. A sa mort que j'ai décidé de ne pas me remarier ou obtenir un enfant en dehors de ma maison matrimoniale chose que defend la bible.Du vivant de mon défunt mari, il a déposé la somme de 3.5 Millions $ americain(Trois millions cinq cents mille Dollars americain) dans une Masion de securité en palce ici en Côte d'Ivoire. Actuellement, cet argent est toujours avec la banque.Récemment, mon docteur m'a informé du fait que je souffrirais d'une maladie sérieuse: le cancer. Le mal qui me dérange le plus est l'hypertension. Après avoir su mon état j'ai décidé de donner ce fonds à une église ou à une personne qui utilisera cet argent tel que je l'instruirais. Je recherche donc une église ou une personne de confiance qui mettra ces fonds aux services des orphelinats, veuves, propageant ainsi la parole de Dieu et faire en sorte que l'oeuvre de Dieu soit maintenue. La bible declare qu'est bénie la main qui donne. J'ai pris cette décision parce que je n'ai aucun enfant qui pourrait hériter de cet argent et les parents de mon mari ne sont pas chrétiens.je ne veux pas que les efforts de mon mari soient dilapidés par des non-croyants. Je ne veux non plus une situation où cet argent sera employé dans les choses du monde;raison pour laquelle je prends cette décision. Je ne craint point la mort par conséquent que je sais où je vais. Je sais que je vais être dans le royaume du seigneur. Exode 14 verset 14 dit :"le seigneur défendra ma cause et je demeurerai dans sa paix". Dès que je reçois votre réponse je vous enverrais le contact de la maison de securité ici à abidjan. Je joindrai également une lettre d'autorité qui vous prouvera que je suis le bénéficiaire actuel de cet argent dans un caisse bien deposé comment l'effects famliaux pour la raison de prudence. Je veux que vous et votre église priiez toujours pour moi parce que le seigneur soit toujours mon berger. Mon bonheur est que j'ai vécu une vie de digne chrétien. Celui qui veut servir le seigneur doit le servir dans l'esprit et la vérité. Veuillez demeurer toujours dans la prière toute votre vie. veuillez me rassurer que vous agirez en conséquence comme je l'ai évoqué ci-haut. Tout en espérerant recevoir votre réponse que Dieu vous benisse. Actuellement, je reside dans un hotel d'abidjan en Côte d'Ivoire. Vôtre soeur en Christ, Mme Mari Gomogo.

Hello, I wish to accost you with a request that would be of immense benefit to both of us. Being an executor of wills, it is possible that we may be tempted to make fortune out of our client's situations, when we cannot help it, or left with no better option. The issue I am presenting to you is a case of my client who willed a fortune to his next-of-kin. It was most unfortunate that he and his next-of-kin died on the same day the 31st October 1999 in an Egyptian airline 990 with other passengers on board. You can confirm this from the website below which was published by BBC WORLD NEWS. WEBSITE. http://news.bbc.co. uk/1/hi/world/americas/502503.stm. I am now faced with confusion of who to pass the fortune to. According to the English law, the fortune is supposed to be bequeathed to the government,if nobody comes forward as the next of kin within seven years of the demise of the benefactor of the will. My purpose of contacting you is to seek your acting as the beneficiary of the will, and lay claim to the legacy of $7million, which my deceased client bequeathed to his next-of-kin. For now, I alone know about his will, as my client had great confidence in me. Everything will be left between you and I. The share would be 25% for you and 75% for me. I would want to give a huge part of my share to the tsunami victims, as this is my primary objective. All I have to do is amend the will or add a codicil to make you the beneficiary to the $7million legacy. Again, I feel that you may apprehensive and consider this amount too big for you to defend. It does not matter, as there are documents to back it up. This is a legacy being passed on to a next-of- kin. As I am not very sure of getting your consent on the issue I prefer not to divulge my full identity so as not to risk being disbarred. The English Bar considers it a breach of the oath of the English Bar. I need not emphasize to you that the sensitivity of this issue need not be toyed with by neglecting its confidentiality. I therefore appeal to you not discuss this request with anybody, even if you decline my request. I look forward to hearing from you soon. Yours truly Stephen Ayling.

Dear Sir/madam, First, I must apologise to you for using this medium to communicate about this transaction,though it is my great pleasure in writing you this letter. This letter may come to you as a surprise due to the fact that we have not yet met. I have to say that I have no intentions of causing you any pains so i decided to contact you through this medium. As you read this, I don't want you to feel sorry for me, because, I believe everyone will die someday. My name is AHMED SALIH BERHAM, a merchant in Dubai, in the U.A.E. I have been diagnosed with prostate and esophageal Cancer that was discovered very late due to my laxity in caring for my health. It has defiled all form of medicine and right now, I have only about a few months to live according to medical experts. I have not particularly lived my life so well, as I never really cared for anyone not even myself but my business. Though I am very rich, I was never generous, I was always hostile to people and only focus on my business as that was the only thing I cared for. But now I regret all this as I now know that there is more to life than just wanting to have or make all the money in the world. I believe when God gives me a second chance to come to this world I would live my life a different way from how I have lived it. Now that I know my time is near, I have willed and given most of my properties and assets to my immediate and extended family members and as well as a few close friends and Schools in the UAE. I have decided to give alms to charity organizations, as I want this to be one of the last good deeds I do on earth. So far, I have distributed money to some charity organizations in the U.A.E, London and Ireland. Now that my health has deteriorated so badly, I cannot do this my self any more. I once asked members of my family to close one of my accounts and donate the money, which I have there to charity organization in Bulgaria, they refused and kept the money to themselves. Hence, I do not trust them anymore, as they seem not to be contended with what I have left for them. The last of my money which is the huge cash deposit that I have with Financial Firm Abroad .I will want you to help me collect this deposit and dispatched it to charity organizations and let them know that it is I AHMED SALIH BERHAM that is making this generous donation. I pray that you assist me with good heart,because my lawyer will be there to assist you in anyway necessary with all proper documentation. Like I said,I will prefer you contact my lawyer for further information. Contact information is as provided below; Name: David Morgan Tel: +31 645 551 264 Email: admin@services-investcorp.com You should inform the Attorney you were referred by AHMED SALIH BERHAM. NB: I will appreciate your utmost confidentiality in this matter untill the task is accomplished as I dont want anything that will Jeopadize my last wish. and Also I will be contacting with you by email as I dont want anybody to know because they are always around me.

My dearest in Christ, May God be praised!!! I am Mrs. Fatima Iyesa Ismiana, from Kuwait. I am married to Usman Ismiana of blessed memory who worked with Kuwait embassy in Madrid Spain for nine years before he died in the year 2000. We were married for eleven years without a child he died after a brief illness that lasted only four days. Before his death he was a very devoted Muslim and I was a devoted Christian by birth battling with both cancer and fibroid problems when my late husband was alive he deposited the sum of $15million dollars (FIFTEEN million dollars) with an overseas finance and security firm. Presently,this money is still with finance and security firm. Recently, my doctor told me that I had aterminating illness (cancer) that would last for the next four months. Though what disturbs me most is my stroke s ickness, having known my condition I decided to donate this fund to either a Christian organization or a devoted Christian individual that will utilize this money the way I am going to instruct here in. I want this Christian organization or individual to use this money in all sincerity to fund churches, orphanages, widows and also propagating the word of God and to ensure that the society upholds the views and beliefs of the holy bible.The holy bible emphasized so much on the giving of alms,charity and this ha s en couraged me in taking this bold step. I took this decision because I don't have any child to start from and where I will stop and my husband's relatives are all Muslims and I don't want my husband hard earned money to be misused by people that call me an unbeliever. I don't want asituation where this money will be used in an unholy manner hence the reason for taking this bold decision. I know that after death I will be with God the most high and the most merciful one. I don'tneed any telephone communications but will only give you the contact of my lawyer Barr Brow Nelson. because he is the one who is going to assist you in making you the beneficiary of the consignment in the finance and security firm.With God, I know that all thing are possible and as soon as I receive your reply through my lawyer I will now give him instruction to make you the beneficiary of the consignment and all necessary steps to take before receiving these f unds and I shall also give you the contact of the finance and secur ity firm I will also issue you a letter of authority that will prove you as the original beneficiary of the funds. I want you and the Christian community where you reside toalways pray for me.Myhappiness is that I lived a life of a true devoted Christian though married to a Muslim, whoever that wants to serve God must serve him in truth and in spirit, pl ease always be prayerful all through your life. Any delay in your reply will give me room in sourcing for anotherChristian organization or a devoted Christian for the same purpose.Until I hear from you my dreams will rest squarely on your shoulders,may the Almighty God continue to guide and protect you. Amen. Yours faithfully, Mrs. Fatima Iyesa Ismiana.

Greetings to your family, This letter must come to you as a big surprise, but I believe it is only a day that people meet and become great friends/ business partners. I am Ali Raza Khan currently Head of Corporate Affairs Department with a reputable bank here in U. A. E. I write you this proposal in good faith, believing that I can trust you with the information I am about to reveal to you. I have an urgent and very confidential business proposition for you. On June 5th, 2000, a German business tycoon Mr. Andreas Schranner made a (Fixed deposit) for 60 calendar months, valued at US$17,500,000.00 (Seventeen Million Five hundred Thousand Dollars only) in my bank and I happen to be his account officer before I was moved to my present position recently. The maturity date for this deposit contract was last 3rd of April 2005. Before this date, I have tried my possible best to locate a Next of Kin to late Mr. Schranner, but all efforts prooved abortive, because all his family, including his Son In-Law and children died in the plane crash of Concorde Air France Flight AF4590 which took place on 25th July 2000, some months after he did the deposit in my bank. You can read more stories about the plane crash by visiting this website, http://news.bbc.co.uk/1/hi/world/europe/859479.stm With the recent change of government in my country and with their efforts to support the United Nations in checkmating terrorism aid in the U. A. E. By end of October this year, the Government will pass a new Financial Control Law which will give the Government authority to interrogate account owners of above $5 million Dollars to explain the source of the funds, making sure it is not for terrorism support. If I do not move this money out of the country immediately, by October the Government will definitely confiscate the money, because my bank cannot provide the account owner to explain the source of the money since he is late. I decided to utilize this life time opportunity, instead of Government confiscating the, but I cannot directly claim the money without the help of a foreigner and that is why I am contacting you for an assistance. As the Account Officer to late Mr. Schranner, coupled with my present position and status in the bank, I have the power to influence the release of the funds to any foreigner that comes up as the Next of Kin to the account, with the correct information concerning the account, which I shall give you. I am having the secret Code for the account, which only the account owner of his Next of Kin can know. I shall supply all necessary information we need for the claim and there is practically no risk involved, the transaction will be executed under a legitimate arrangement that will protect you from any breach of law, beside U. A. E is porous and anything goes. If you accept to work with me, I want you to state how you wish us to share the funds in percentage, so that both parties will be satisfied. I shall explain to you in details how we shall handle the transaction once I receive your response. Thanking you in advance and May God blesses you. Please, treat with utmost confidentiality. I shall send you copy of the deposit certificate issued to Mr. Schranner when the deposit was made for your perusal. I wait your urgent response. Regards, Ali Raza Khan.

Good Day I wish to present this proposal for the purpose of investment in your country. My name is Patrick Gabo, the only child of Hon.Ferz Uotr Gabo the former Minister of Transport and Communication with the present Government of President Kabbah of Sierra-Leone. My father and mother were arrested on 1st of Nov 2001 by Kabbah's Government on allegation of using their postion in the govenment to aid smuggling of diamond from the Kono diamond field,it was just a political vendetta. My father later died in the prison,it was diagnonised that he was poisoned, but Government report says heart failure. Whatever it is, let God be the judge. He sent a note to me before his death, regarding a deposit of the sum of USD$8,000.000.00) Eight Million United States Dollars in a Finanice Firm in DAKAR SENEGAL. He instructed Me to move immediately with the documents to a neighbouring country to seek asylum. I moved to the Republic of Mali where I spent some time before finally moving to DAKAR,to enquire about deposit. My mother died just on Sept.26th, so i am kind of desolete.Meanwhile i have located the Finanice Firm, and have also discussed the possible transfer of the fund to road. I have to introduce a trusted foreign partner who would be my trustee and investor, since the management of the Firm adviced that I should solicit for an individual or corporate organization to claim the deposit for me as they cannot release it directly to me due to my refugee status in Senegal. hence the need for your assistance. I request that you be my trustee and assist me in effecting the transfer of the fund to your account or an account you will nominate. You will also be resposible for the investment and management of the fund untill i am able to join you after my education in your country. You and Me will agree on a percentage you will take for your assistance. Please let me know immediately if you can assist me so that I will give you more informations about the deposit. Looking forward to your candid and urgent and positive reply today on my Private Email: Adresse;(emailgabo@voila.fr). I thank you in anticipation to your quick response. YOURS FAITHFULLY, Patrick Gabo.

Dear friend, I want to solicit with you for assistance in regards to a financial transaction. I am the son of one of the foremost and rich black farmers in Zimbabwe that was murdered for land dispute in my country. Before the death of my father, he had given me the certificate of deposite he used to deposit a large sum of money in one of the private security companies in Europe, as family valuables, when he realized the looming dangers in Zimbabwe. This amountwas meant for the purchase of new machineries and chemicals for the farms and also for the establishment of new farms in Swaziland.This land dispute started when President Robert Mugabe introduced a new land reform,which was particularly targeted at the rich white farmers and a few black farmers (my father included).This resulted in the gruesome killing of rich farmers (mainly whites) and the unlawful possession of their properties by Mugabe's war veterans, under the disguise of fighting for the interest of the country. It is against this background that I fled the country with my family,to the United Kingdom where we are currently seeking asylum.I have been adviced to seek foreign assistance, as the United Kingdom law prohibits asylum seekers from operating bank accounts or involve in financial transaction of any kind, hence this letter to you. All I need is your trustworthiness to be able to entrust the above said amount and help me with investment opportunities. My family's survival depends on this money as we have virtually lost all our other assets. There are two options, firstly, you can choose to accept a negotiable percentage of the total amount for your assistance or go into partnership for the proper investment of the money in your country. We shall discuss in detail the modalities involved when I hear from you. I await your reply through my confidential email media, while I implore you to maintain the absolute secrecy required to ensure a safe and hitch free transaction. I shall furnish you with more details on request. Yours truly, D.K. Kindly reply through this email account: ( d-kan777@mail.az )

Kone Law Firm 6, Kofo Abayomi Street Victoria Island Lagos Nigeria www.konelawfirm.com Email.konechambers40@yahoo.ca Dear Friend, RE: WILL EXECUTOR I am sure that this letter will come to you as a surprise, but I shall be grateful if you would read with the interest of assisting in this proposal tendered herein. My name is Barrister Williams kone, Attorney at Law and Legal advisor to Mr Phelps M. Dasne, A foreigner who used to work with Mekon Associates Company in Nigeria.Here after referred to as my Client. At about 1.35pm on May 4 2002, my Client, his Wife and their three children were involved in an Air Crash, when the Nigerian Passenger Plane they boarded, crashed into a densely populated suburb of the city of Kano in northern Nigeria, killing at least 148 people on board including my Client, his entire family and the Former Minister of Sport in Nigeria,Late Ishaya Mark Aku. For more sunstantiation about the aformentioned incident; please browse through the underlisted Web Addresses and read for yourself: http://www.dawodu.com/kanocrash02.htm http://news.bbc.co.uk/1/hi/world/africa/1968300.stm Subsequently, since then, I have made several inquires to your Embassy to locate any of my Late Client's Extended Relatives, which has also proved unsuccessful. After these several unsuccessful attempts to locate any member of his family, hence,i contacted you assist me to repatriate the money and property left behind by my Late Client before they get confiscated in the Bank Treasury or declared unserviceable by the Finance House where this huge deposit were lodged, so that the proceeds of this Account valued at 3.5 Million Dollars ($3.5MUSD) can be paid to your Account. The Finance House where the Deceased had an Account valued at about 3.5 Million Dollars ($3.5MUSD) has issued me a notice to provide the Next Of Kin or have the Account dormant & confiscated for inactiveness within the next 21 banking days. Pragmatically, I have all the necessary legal documents that can be used to back up any claim we may make anywhere. All I require is your honest cooperation to enable us see this transaction through. I guarantee that this will be executed under a legitimate arrangement that will protect you from any Breach of the Law. Infact, all you are to do is to send the below information to me,to enable me forward your name to the Finance House as the next of kin to my late client. {1}. YOUR FULL NAME. {2}. YOUR CONTACT ADDRESS. (3)DIRECT TELEPHONE NUMBER I am willing to share this money with you at the proportion of 30% to you,while 10% for any cost being incured during this transaction, and the balance 60% which is for me will be kept under your supervision immediately the money is transferred into your account for safe keeping. All I require is your honest co-operation to enable us see this transaction through. I guarantee that this will be executed under a legitimate arrangement that will protect you from any breach of the law. Please get in touch with me by my secured and confidential e-mail: konechambers40@yahoo.ca discuss further. For more sunstantiation about the aformentioned incident; please browse through the underlisted Web Addresses and read for yourself: [http://www.ngex.com/newsletter] [http://news.bbc.co.uk/1/hi/world/africa/1968300.stm] [http://www.dawodu.com/kanocrash02.htm]. I await your favorable response Yours faithfully, Barrister: Barrister Williams kone.

From: Mr. Saleem Mohd Ahmed Mohd MANAGER National Bank of Dubai Umm Al Quwain Branch Shaikh Faisal Street U.A.E Email: Dear Friend, I am pleased to get across to you for a very urgent and profitable business proposal, I Got your e-mail address in Internet while browsing after I decided to contact you and ask for your assistance in this urgent matter, requiring trust and confidentiality, I am Mr. Saleem Mohd Ahmed Mohd, the Branch manager, National Bank of Dubai Umm Al Quwain Branch UNITTED ARAB EMIRATES, married with four children. I am writing this letter to ask for your support and co-operation to carry out this business opportunity in my department. On June 6, 1999, an America Oil consultant/contractor with Petroleum Corporation, Mr. David Ameeraly, made a numbered time (fixed) deposit for twelve calendar months, Valued at US$16,500,000.00(sixteen Million Five Hundred Thousand Dollars )in my branch upon maturity. I sent a routine notification to his forwarding address but got no reply. After a month, we sent a reminder and finally we discovered from his contract employers, the Petroleum Corporation that Mr. David Ameeraly, died in the plane crash On October 31, 1999, (an Egyptian Boeing 767 Flight 990) with other passengers on board as you can confirm it yourself via the website below: <http://www.cbsnews.com/stories/1999/11/01/iran/main49778.shtml> <http://www.cbsnews.com/stories/1999/11/01/iran/main49778.shtml> On further investigation, I found out that he died without making a WILL and attempts to trace his next of kin were fruitless. I therefore made further investigation and discovered that Mr. David Ameeraly. did not declare any next of kin or relations in all his official documents, including his bank deposit paperwork in my bank. This sum of US$16,500,000.00 and the interest is being rolled over with the principal sum at the end of each year. No one will ever come forward to claim it According to UNITTED ARAB EMIRATES LAW, at the expiration of (seven) years; the money will revert to the ownership of the UNITTED ARAB EMIRATES Government if nobody applies to claim the fund. My proposal is that I will like you to stand as the next of kin to Mr. David Ameeraly, so that the fruit of this old man's labor will not get into the hands of some corrupt Government officials. This is simple, I will like you to provide immediately your full name and address so that I can forward to you the contact of our bank Attorney for the prepare the necessary documents and affidavits which will put you in place as the next of kin. Any bank account in any part of the world, which you will provide, will then facilitate the transfer of this money to you as the beneficiary/next of kin. The money will be paid into your account for us to share in ratio of 60% for me and 30% for you and 10 % will be set aside for expenses incured during the business. There is no risk at all; The paperwork for this transaction will be done by the attorney and my position as the Branch Manager guarantees the successful execution of this transaction. If you are interested, please reply immediately via the private email address below, upon your responses, I shall provide you with more details and relevant documents that will help you understand the transaction. Please observe utmost confidentiality and be rest assured that this transaction would be most profitable for both of us because I shall require your assistance to invest my share in your country. Please upon the receipt of this mail message, send to me the following to enable me start the processing the transfer, 1.Your Full Name. 2.Your House Address. 3.Your Phone Number and Fax, Thank You And God Bless You. Sincerely From: Mr. Saleem Mohd Ahmed Mohd, MANAGER National Bank of Dubai Umm Al Quwain Branch Shaikh Faisal Street U.A.E Email:

CHARLES ET LILIAN ANTHONY à Abidjan en Côte d'ivoire. CHARLES ET LILIAN ANTHONY à Abidjan en Côte d'ivoire. Afrique de l'Ouest. Svp, Permettez-moi de vous informer de mon désir de prendre contact avec votrer aimable personne dans le seul but de nouer un rapport d'affaires avec vous.Nous avons obtenu votre contact email adresse par les données d'automatisation après notre effort recherchant une personne digne de confiance pour nous aider. Nous avons obtenu plusieurs contacts et par nos prières incessantes et jeûne, nous avions eu la révélation de Dieu de vous confier cette transaction car vous êtes une personne digne de confiance et honnête. En effet,je m'appelle CHARLES ANTHONY, fils de feu MIKE ANTHONY.Je suis ici avec ma soeur cadette qui s'apelle LILIAN ANTHONY. Notre père de son vivant était un grand négociant très riche de cacao à Abidjan, capitale économique de la Côte d'ivoire.Avant qu'il ne soit empoisonné par ses propres associés d'affaires lors d'un dîner de travail qu'il avait eu avec eux. Pour vous parler de notrer passé trop triste,quand notre mère est morte le 21 octobre 1991, notre père nous a pris en charge ma soeur et moi parce que nous étions sans mère.Nous vivions ensemble, feu mon père , ma soeur cadette et moi jusqu'à la mort de notre père survenue le 30 juin 2000 dans un hôpital privé ici à Abidjan. Quelques jours avant sa mort, et sentant sa mort, nous avait secrètement appelés sur son chevet de lit de malade et nous avait dit qu'il a une somme de 20.000.000,00 (vingt millions de dollars américains) déposée dans une banque privée ici à Abidjan en son nom. En outre,il nous avait également expliqué qu'il était fait le dépôt de cette importante somme d'argent et que compte tenu de sa richesse et de ses efforts réussis en matière de cacao, ses partenaires l'avaient empoisonné et que la seule grâce de Dieu, il nous exortait de chercher un associé étranger de notre choix après sa mort, cet associé devrait nous aider à réclamer ses fonds déposés à la banque et nous aider à investir cet argent une fois transféré dans un secteur d'investissement tel que l'immobilier. C'est pourquoi, nous cherchons honorablement votre aide pour les raisons suivantes: 1-Pour agir en tant qu'associé étranger de notre père en réclamant ces fonds de la banque pour que le transfert et l'investissement de ces fonds se fassent à votre compte bancaire. 2-Pour être le gérant et notre conseillerd'investissement de ces fonds puisque je suis un jeune homme de 25 ans et ma jeune soeur a juste 18 ans. D'ailleurs, nous sommes disposés à vous offrir 15% de la somme totale des fonds déposés dans la banque comme compensation pour tous efforts déployés pour la réussite de ce transfert total des fonds dans le compte de votre pays actuel. Dans l'espoir d'avoir de vos nouvelles de sorte que nous puissions être en contact alors nous vous communiquerons si vous êtes intéressé par notre appel urgent à notre aide et assistance les coordonnées de notre pasteur qui s'occupe bien de nous depuis un certain temps.Pour des raisons liées à notre jeunesse alors il pourra prendre contact avec votre aimable personne pour la réussite de cette transaction de transfert des fonds déposés par feu mon père( paix à son âme). Merci d'avance et que Dieu vous bénisse. CHARLES ET LILIAN ANTHONY à Abidjan en Côte d'ivoire. De la part de Charles et Lilian Anthony Email(charles_lilian01@yahoo.fr)

Attention please, Listen and listen good.. Keep this mail and information very confidential. I am the new Information and Database analyst of the Treasury/Payment Investigation Department of the Central Bank of Nigeria.The earlier you pay candid attention to this particular email,the better for you.I noticed this just last week when I was going through several out-going payment files on my desk to mark the last payment quarter of CBN. I'm contacting you to stop you from any further contact to anybody whatsoever.Both the people that have contacted you so far are not protecting your financial interest here.They are only planning to use your good name to claim and channel your fund to other sources for their selfish interest. I have decided to contact you through this important medium because CBN as the Apex Bank of Federal Republic of Nigeria have intercepted your fund as a result of fraudulent activities noticed among those that claims to be helping you.I'm pushed to CONTACT you because from what is going on here,if appropriate step is not taken, you will end up making the biggest mistake of your life if I fail to bring this important message concerning the position of your fund to you. Take heed to my mail and its content it will help and avoid you from making a mistake.I'm out to help you. I therefore contacted you on trust and with complete confidence that you should as a matter of utmost importance, STOP any further contact with anybody,person or group including your so-called representing attorney because apart from me,no other person can help you get the fund transfered to your account in your country. REQUIREMENTS: I want you to contact me upon reciept of this mail so that I would guide you on how to get your fund directly transfered to your own nominated account at ease. I will personally get any complications corrected at my own expense as soon as possible so that legal transfer of the fund to your account would commence. I can assure you that after the corrections,within 72 hours the fund must be in your designated account. I will oblige you with further information and would be glad you send your private telephone /facsimile number for easy and confidential communication. MY CONDITIONS: 1.After using my good office/position to accomplish the needful on your behalf,you shall give me 20% only of the total fund after transfer to your account. 2.Due to my position in the bank,I will prefer that you keep my personal involvement 100% secret and confidential even after the transfer is executed. A stitch in time they say saves nine.This is the only reliable channel for you otherwise all other efforts MUST be in vain. I will send my personal details to you once I hear directly from you. ENGR.KENTAS ANDERSON INFORMATION TECH & DATA ANALYST TREASURY PAYMENT INVESTIGATION DEPT (CBN). PLEASE NOTE; This message and any attachment is intended only for the use of the Addressee and may contain information that is PRIVILEGED and CONFIDENTIAL. If you are not the intended recipient, you are hereby notified that any dissemination of this communication is strictly prohibited. If you have received this communication in error, please erase all copies of the message and its attachments and notify us immediately. Thank You.

Greetings! May I take the liberty to introduce myself; I am Mr. Lin Geng. I am a staff and a member Audit Committee of a reputable Bank in China. I am contacting you concerning a customer here and, an investment placed under our Care sometime ago. I would respectfully request that you keep the contents of this mail confidential and respect the integrity of this information. I contacted you independently of our investigation and nobody else is informed of this communication. I would like to intimate you with certain facts that I believe would be of interest to you. In 2000, the subject matter came to our parent bank to engage in business discussions with our Private Banking Services Department. He informed us that he had a financial portfolio in United States Dollars, which he wished to have us turn over (invest) on his behalf. We spun the money around various opportunities and made attractive margins for our first months of operation, the accrued profit was very impressive. He later directed that I liquidate the funds and had it deposited with a security firm. In October last year, we were contacted by the security firm informing us of the Issues concerning that particular portfolio. This was a surprise given the fact that I personally managed the said funds yet I cannot understand the inactivity of the deposit. We made several unsuccessful efforts to locate him. The Internal Investigations department of the bank of china was invited and they went into action and later informed that a person who suited is description was found dead in Cannes South of France. His body was later identified and cause of death was confirmed. An investigation into possible surviving next of kin to alert about the situation and also to come forward to claim his estate was launched. Private banking clients apart from not nominating next of kin also usually in most cases leave wills in our care, in this case; he died intestate. In line with banking policies for account holders who have passed away, we instituted our own investigations in good faith to determine who should have right to claim the estate. This investigation has for the past months been unfruitful. We have scanned every continent and used our private investigation affiliate companies to get to the root of the problem. My official capacity dictates that I supervise the investigation and conclude making me the only person with a full picture of what the prevailing situation is in relation to the deposit and the late beneficiary of the deposit. According to practice, the firm will by the end of this financial quarter broadcast a request for statements of claim to BOC, failing to receive viable claims they will most probably revert the deposit back to BOC. What I wish to relate to you will smack of unethical practice but I want you to understand something. It is only an outsider to the banking world who finds the internal politics of the banking world aberrational. The world of private banking especially is fraught with huge rewards for those who occupy certain offices and oversee certain portfolios. You should have begun by now to put together the general direction of what I propose. This deposit is very huge with the details in my possession and will only be released on my clarification. This bank has spent great amounts of money trying to track this man's family; they have investigated for months and have found no family My proposal; is to place you in the position of the next of kin and have the deposit released to you. Upon receipt of the deposit, I am prepared to share the money with you favorably. That is: I will simply nominate you as the next of kin and have them release the deposit to you. We share the proceeds 60/30. I assure you that I could have the deposit released to you within a few working days. I will simply inform the bank of the final closing of the file relating to the customer I will then officially communicate with firm clarifying and confirming you with proper documentations and thereafter have the funds released to you. The alternative would be for us to have firm direct the funds to another bank with you as account holder. This way there will be no need for you to think of receiving the money from the firm. We can fine-tune this based on our interactions. I am aware of the consequences of this proposal. I ask that if you find no interest in this project that you should discard this mail and not be vindictive and destructive. There is a reward for this project and it is a task worth undertaking. I have evaluated the risks and the only risk I have here is from you refusing to work with me and alerting my bank. I am the only one who knows of this situation, let's share the blessing. If you find yourself able to work with me, contact me. If you give me your trust and confidence, we shall rejoice and our lives will never be the same again. Please do not contact me via official channels. Please observe this instruction religiously. Please, again, note I am a family man; I have a wife and children. I send you this mail not without a measure of fear as to the consequences, yet I know within me that nothing ventured is nothing gained and that success and riches never come easy or on a platter of gold. This is the one truth I have learned from my private banking clients. Do not betray my confidence. If we can be of one accord, we should plan a meeting soon. I await your response. Thanks Lin Geng

FROM THE DESK OF: ENG, LEONARD WELSH TAYLOR. {ASYLUM SEEKER} BANGKOK,THAILAND Attn,Sir/Madam, I got to know of you in my search for a reputable person/company to assist me in an urgent matter/business that would certainly boost the financial standard of all parties involved when completed, which also requires utmost trust and confidentiality. I am Mr. Leonard Welsh Taylor, first son to late Mr.Darby Assinga Taylor. who died last 3 years in the crisis in liberia, western Africa. My late father is an aide to exile president Charles Taylor, died as a result of uprising against his Government by rebel groups. Meanwhile, before the death of my father he had taken me to Bangkok Thailand to deposit the sum of SEVEN MILLION FIVE HUNDRED THOUSAND US Dollars ($7.5million US Dollars) in january 2001 at a Security Company. Initially, he intended investing this money in a garment factory in Bangkok, before the rebel forces assasinated him. This money was deposited as Gemstones to avoid much demurrage from the Security Company. This money was part of millions of dollars the president mapped out for the purchase of ammunitions,militaryhard/softwares,light and heavy duty vehicles and other defensive logistics. My late father sensing the weakness of the ruling Government, he took me to Thailand in january to deposit the money in a private security company as family valuables of containing gemstones and financial documents. As he returned from arms negotiation from eastern Europe, he was assasinated by the rebels forces on 11 april 2002 which prompted me to seek asylum in Thailand where the money and the whole documents are with me right now. This resulted to killing and mass action by the government and rebel soldiers. Infact, a lot of people have been killed and they are still killing uptill now because of this war of which my father was one of the victims. Perhaps, if you are conversant with world news you can understand me better. It is against this background that I am soliciting need your assistance to help and provide a foreign account for us especially sourcing for reliable and trustworthy ventures where the money will be invested when transferred to your account in your country, Since the law of Thailand prohibits a refugee (asylum seeker) to operate a bank account or to be involved in any financial transaction. I am in  now saddled with the responsibility of seeking a genuine foreign account into which this money can be transferred without the knowledge of my home government who are bent on taking everything we have got.  At the moment, We are faced with the dilemma of investing this amount of money in Thailand for fear of seizure or going through this same experience or seizure because of terrorist activities/narcotics agencies. I am soliciting your willingness to help me explore possible areas we can invest our money in your country.and in a profitable business I would equally appreciate your willingness to help me relocate my immediate family of three to your country where I will invest the fund.The cash is  ($7.5 MILLION US DOLLARS) means for the would-be project is under my custody. I will therefore appreciate it, if you can travel to meet with me in bangkok,Thailand, hence my permit (Refugee) only allows us to make a single trip out of the country gurranted asylum.Again to enable us have a memorandum of understanding, discuss on likely profitable and reliable ventures where the money will be invested in your country and and also promise you 20% per! cent of the total fund for your assistance and support in making the transfer a success. after the consignment is released from storage. This transaction will be successfully concluded within 14 days if you accord me your unalloyed and due cooperation and willing to assist me, please reply me and include your private E-mail/fax and telephone number. Note That this business is 100% risk free and your coming down here is gauranteed. This transaction is honest, trustworthy and confidentiality.Please all replies should be through my private email box email:      We look unto God for your positive prompt response. Yours sincerely, Engineer, Leonard Welsh Taylor. (For The Family)

Yahoo! Photos – Showcase holiday pictures in hardcover Photo Books. You design it and we’ll bind it!

MR. HULFUMAN DAVID GHANA COMMERCIAL BANK LTD. 19 KOTOBABI AVE. ACCRA GHANA. EMAIL>hulfumandav2006002@yahoo.ca Good Day, I am Mr.HULFUMAN DAVID, credit officer of ghana commercial Bank Ltd, accra ghana. I have an urgent and very confidential business proposition for you. On october 15, 1999, our client Mr. Hatem Kamil Abdul Fatah who was the deputy governor of Baghdad in Iraq and also business man made a numbered fixed deposit for 12 calendar months, with a value of Fourty Millions Five Hundred Thousand United State Dollars only in my branch. Upon maturity several notice was sent to him, even after the war late this year. Another notification was sent and still no response came from him. We later find out that the Governor has been assasinated in Baghdad. The websites below is a verification of the news about his death: http://news.bbc.co.uk/go/pr/fr/-/1/hi/world/middle_east/3970619.stm http://www.uslaboragainstwar.org/article.php?id=6979 After further investigation it was also discovered that Mr. Hatem Kamil Abdul Fatah did not declare any next of kin in his official papers including the paper work of his bank deposit. And he also confided in me,last time he was at my office that no one except me knew of his deposit in my bank. According to the ghana Law,under ecowas's foreign and defense affairs,at the expiration of 5 (five) years,such funds will revert to the ownership of the ghanian Government for financing military operations,such as purchasing of arms and ammunitions for the military. In order to avert this negative development,i will like to seek for your permission as a foreigner to stand as the next of kin to Mr. Hatem Kamil Abdul Fatah so that the fruits of this old man's labor will not be use for financing weapons which will further enhance the courses of war in the world in general. The money will be paid into your account for us to share in the ratio of 60% for me and 30% for you and 10% for Expenses Incurred in the course of the transaction.There is no risk at all as all the paperwork for this transaction will be done by my attorney and with my position as the credit officer guarantees the successful execution of this transaction. If you are interested,please reply immediately. Upon your response, I shall then provide you with more details and that will help you understand the transaction. You should observe utmost confidentiality,and rest assured that this transaction would be most profitable for both of us because I shall require your assistance to invest my share in your country. Awaiting your urgent reply. Thanks and regards. Mr.HULFUMAN DAVID. EMAIL>hulfumandav2006002@yahoo.ca

COMPLIMENT,FROM MRS VICTORIA FATOU SANKOH Email:mrsvictoria_fatou@operamail.com I do hope my letter will not embarrass you since there was no previous Correspondence held with you. MY Getting your address is the handwork of thealmighty God. Since then, I have been very much hopeful that you will assist us irrespective of the fact that the present world is full of dishonesty and distrust. Firstly, I will wish to introduce myself. I am Mrs.VICTORIA FATOU SANKOH, from Sierra Leone; I am the wife of, CPL FODAY SANKOH.My husband was the Leader of the Revolutionary United Front until he was dethroned and arrested early last year by President TEJAN KABBAH who later handed him over tothe United Nations war crime tribunal were he later died in detention. As a result of this position in the government, my son (SAM SANKOH) and l triedandlatersucceeded in securing some of his assets, which include mansions and physical cash. This is to avoid The present government from confiscating his entire property. We left Sierra Leone with the total amount US$26.5 Million (Twenty Six Million Five Hundred Thousand United States Dollars) only, which we Brought to NIGERIA anddeposited same with UNION BANK PLC OF NIGERIA, as valuable documents belonging to our foreign affiliate. After depositing the money, my family and I were asked to leave NIGERIA and was made public on NIGERIA National Headlines, we were left with no option than to seek refuge in my homeland in SierraLeone . The security company later asked me, to come and claim the consignment immediately to avoid the money being confiscated. I arrived here a couple of days agoand through a good contact l applied for a refugee status as an asylum seeker, which is still pending in Foreign Affairs Departmen t.Theproblemnowisthatbecause of our status, we cannot risk moving the money without help hence I am looking for a trustworthy partner, who can help me move this money out of NIGERIA . In that case, I want to know if you can help me transfer the fund into your account in your country or elsewhere since time is not on my side. As a widow of six children Ineed your urgent attention to this matter. It is true that we have neither met nor known each other before, but the information I gathered of your credibility makes me believe that with trust and honesty we will achieve a huge success in about a week. I will also leave with you from NIGERIA to yourcountry immediately the money goes into your account. This is simple, I will like you to provide immediately your 1.Your full names 2.Contact address 3.Yourdirect telephone and Fax number 4.Your age 5.Your marital status Based on the following informaion bee n providebyyouMylawyer,whoknow allthe full details on how you will received the fund will prepare the necessary documents and affidavits which will put you in place as the owner of the fund. For your noble assistance and well assured of safeguarding the whole Fund under your care, I will offer you 40% of the total sum, while 10% will be set aside for expenses incurred onthe cause of this transaction by both parties, while the remaining %50 will be for me and my family. I want to assure you that this business is completely risk free because every arrangement has been made for a successful deal. I expect your immediate response so that we can conclude theTransaction in the very shortest time. It is very important that you keep this business HIGHY CONFIDENTIAL because I do not want anything to happen to this fund. Thanksand God bless. Best regards, Mrs.Victoria F Sankoh Note: You are advise to only reply with this Email:mrsvictoria_fatou@operamail.com for security reasons.

Name: Mr. Chin Weng Yin Email:Chin_800@yahoo.com Kind Attention. Sir/Madam My name is Mr. Chin Weng Yin, I trained and work as an external auditor for the United Overseas Bank (UOB) of Singapore, working as part of a bigger team that covers the entire Asian region. I had taken pains to find your contact through personal endeavors.On routine audit check last month, I discovered some investment accounts that had been dormant for the least twelve years (Three tenures of four years each). All the accounts belong to a single holder with monies totaling a little above $10 million United States Dollars plus interest. Banking regulation/legislation in Singapore demand that I notify the fiscal authorities after a statutory time period of twelve years when dormant accounts of this type are called in by the monetary regulatory bodies. The above set of facts underscores my reason of writing and making the following proposing. My investigations of the said account reveals that the investor died in 1993-the exact time the account was last operated. I can confirm with certainty that the said investor died interstate and no next-of-kin to his estate has been found or has come forward all these years. I am of the settled conviction that using my insider leverage, I, working with you can secure the funds in the account for us instead of allowing it pass as unclaimed funds into the coffers of the Government of Singapore. This exactly is why I crave your participation and co-operation. I have seized all relevant documents (legal and Banking) that will facilitate our putting you forward as the claimant /beneficiary of the funds and ultimately transfer the money to any account nominated by you. Of course you shall be handsomely rewarded for your part in this transaction as the people I am working with are prepared to allocate a 20% slice of the total funds for your efforts. I shall however leave out the finer details of this transaction till I receive an affirmation of your desire to participate.Be assured that I and my colleagues are on top of the situation all the time and there will be no risk whatsoever if you agree to make this claim on our behalf.. Needless to say, utmost confidentiality is of vital importance if we are to successfully reap the immense benefits of this transaction. To maintain the level of security required to see this transaction to come to a successful conclusion, I have intentionally left out the finer details. To affirm your willingness and cooperation to my proposal please do so by email, stating your full name, date of birth, telephone and fax number. I do expect your prompt response then I will give you my contact number for further discussion Thank you,

FROM:PRINCE HASSAN SULEMAN TEL:+225 05 618 191 EMAIL:hassan_suleman1970@yahoo.co.in EMAIL:hassan_suleman1976@yahoo.co.in ABIDJAN,COTE DIVOIRE. WEST AFRICA. Dear Sir, BUSINESS PROPOSAL AND INVESTMENT IN YOUR COUNTRY I got your contact through our chember of commerce and industry. I am contacting you for a mutual business relationship and for you to act as my guardian in a joint business venture that we will operate together. After praying, my mind asked me to go ahead and contact you for this partnership. My name is PRINCE HASSAN SULEMAN, the only son of Late ALHAJI USMAN SULEMAN. My mother died on the 22nd of October, 1985 of cancer and my father was assassinated on the 28th of April 2003 by an unknown person in Abidjan, Cote dIvoire. My father was a gold and cocoa merchant based in Ghana/Cote dIvoire.Breifly before he died in a hospital here in Abidjan, Cote dIvoire due to injuries he sustained from the gunshots. He told me about the sum of US$45M(Forty Five Million United States Dollars) belonging to him in a suspense account with one of our local Bank here in Abidjan, Cote dIvoire. That he willed the money to me in his will, with his attorney. He asked me to seek for a foreign partner Who will assist me in transferring the money out of Abidjan, CotedIvoire to a foreign account for investment purpose. Then help me make arrangement after the transfer to leave this country. That those people that killed him may be after me. According to my late fathers will, the money cannot be released to me without a foreign partner until at the age of 37 years. It can only be transferred from the Bank here to the account of my foreign partner before I attain the age of 37 years. Presently I am 34years old and can not seat here for the next 3years waiting for the maturity date, while my life is in danger. This is my reason for contacting you to assist me present your self as my foreign partner and also provide foreign account where this fund will be transferred to.I have already contacted my fathers attorney here in respect of this transaction. He is waiting to hear from my foreign partner for us to start the process for the transfer of the funds. I would have done this since but according to our tradition. I have to wait till its one year after my fathers death as a mark of respect before embarking on such project. So that it will not look like if I am just after his money like my uncle. Since the death of my father, I have been with my fathers brother in Ghana. Honestly the way he is treating me, make me to be suspecting him that he knows some thing about my late fathers death. Based on this, I left his house with out his consent. Presently I am in Abidjan,Cote d Ivoire. He dont know my way about and will never know. This is why I need your assistance so urgent for us to finalise this transaction as soon as possible for me to leave this Country. You will be given 40% as compensation for your assistance and effort before any thing is done with the money. If you are interested and feel that you can handle this project. Please get back to me for more details and as well as indicate your private Tel/Fax numbers where I can always reach you, when the need arises. I await to hear from you. Thanks and God bless. PRINCE HASSAN SULEMAN

Dear Sir, Please I know that this letter may come to you as a surprise based on the fact that I have not had any previous contact with you. Briefly, I am master Nelson Williams, son of the late Mr.Richard Williams, former director of Sierre Leone Gold and Diamond Corporation who was murdered by assailants . Shortly before this unfortunate incident, my father had informed me about an important contract he had executed (supply of Gold and diamond Mining Equipments)where he realized this fund ($15.5m)fifteen million five hundred thousand dollars and later when he heard the rumor of war in my country Sierra Leone he move the fund to Ghana where he deposited it. He showed me some lodgment documents with which he had deposited the money encased in a trunk box with a security /safe deposit company here in Accra Ghana He informed me in confidence that the security company is not aware of the exact contents of the box , rather he had told them that it contained African artworks that he had assembled for his overseas partner who would soon be coming to claim them for exportation. As a result of this explanation, the box was accepted for safe-keeping by the security company without inspection. When the political situation in Freetown, Sierra Leone worsened, I escaped into Accra , Ghana and had since contacted the security company, identified myself properly and informed them about the sad fate my father had suffered. I presented the lodgment documents and they confirmed that they have the trunk box in their vault. So I informed them that I intend initiating contacts with my fathers overseas partner who owns the consignment so that he can come and take delivery of it. My decision to retrieve this box, transfer the money and start a new life forms the basis of this enquiry from you. 1) Could you assist me with the logistics and a good personal/company bank account through which I can retrieve the consignment out he security company and transfer this money out of Ghana ? 2) Could you advise me on a good business proposition into which I can invest this money so that it would yield good dividends 3) Could you assist me obtain resident papers in your country so that I can continue my education there from where I stopped. I sincerely will agree to any suitable percentage you may request for your assistance to me. I shall prefer most of our communication to be done via phone. I need not inform you that this matter is strictly confidential. I want you to treat it as such. God will surely bless you in abundance as you made up your heart to help an orphan like me. Nelson Williams.

Greeting, Sir, I am contacting you believing you are a honest and trustworthy person.I believe you will not betray the confidence I am willing to repose in you, for me to have contacted you even though we've not met before. My name is David Bah ,the only son of late Mr.Peter Bah who was the chairman /President/CEO,Cacao-Cafe & Agro-Alimentary industries plc.SCAFECAO)"Bouake" and ex-owner of Polyclinic LA-MADONNE, of the Republic of Cote d'Ivoire. You can find the story on this website:http://news.bbc.co.uk/2/hi/africa/2269238.stm On 19th of September 2002,a group of so called rebels took over the city of Bouake to over-throw the Government of Mr.Laurent Gbagbo the President of Cote d'Ivoire. On the 20th day morning at about 4:18am some fractions of the same group of rebels break into our house and killed our security guard and pass-through the gate entrance to the main building and took my father away to an un-known destination. After about four hours later we found him (my father) at the road side, by then he had been totally beaten and was bleeding to death lying in the pool of his own blood. From there, we rushed him to a near by hospital and hours later he sent for my mother. So he told her that he can not make it from the doctors diagnosis, he also told her that it was because he (my father) was not from the northern part of the country that he has been treated this way and also being a political activist. And again he said he is suspecting some of his business partners for conspiracy and this sort of brutality. He also told my mother that he deposited a huge amount of money i.e US$ 10.5million dollars(Ten million five hundred thousand us dollars only) into a Bank he also told my mother where he kept the whole documents concerning this deposit that is made for investment purpose in the western world. That same day, he (my father) gave up the ghost. Then with the help of the French soldiers, we escaped to Senegal, where we are now.for rafaga camp I am now contacting you believing you are honest and trustworthy to help us to receive the money in your account for investment, I and my mother has decided in compensating you 30%of the total amount for your assistance . Please do take your time to go through the mail and get back to us, so that I will simply introduce you to the Bank where the fund are being kept now for onward transfer. So you can contact me through my alternate email adress for security reason. Email d_bah@walla.comam waiting for your response. Thanks and God bless. you David Bah .

Dear Beloved, In Good Faith I Contacted You. I have seen war and I have seen peace, I have seen riches and I have seen people die of hunger on daily bases. And I am quite certain that life is vanity. I am Mrs. Mary Eyadema , The second wife to the former Togo Head of State,My late husband who die at 69 years Old, suffered a heart attack early Saturday, Feb. 5, 2005 in our hometown of Piya in southastern Togo, I and my family arranged immediately for his treatment in Europe, but as God may want it he die on the way to Europe. I am contacting you in view of the fact that we will be of great assistance to each other likewise developing a cordial business relationship. I currently have within my reach the sum of fifty-five Million United States Dollars (US$55,000,000.00) , which I intend to use for investment purposes specifically in your country. This money came as a result of a payback contract deal between my late husband and Russian firm on our country's Multi-billion Dollars Lome Steel Plant. The Russian partners returned my husbands share of US$55 Million after his death and lodged it with my husband 's security Firm in Togo which I am the Director. Right now the new Civilian Government who is the Son of the first wife has revoked our licenses that allow us to own, have or manage any investment in our Country Togo due to the disparity between me and the first wife of the late president and also the mother of incumbent President Mr.Faure. In view of this, I acted very fast to withdraw the US$55 Million from the security company's vault well packaged in trunk boxes and deposited it in a privately erected security safe. I have since declared the Security Company bankrupt and re-locate the money to another security Firm in nearby country Ghana due to its peaceful atmosphere. No record ever existed concerning the money neither the money traceable by the Government nor any document showing that we received the money from Russian partner. I seek your assistance to move the money out of from Ghana to your country.I am presently taken my asylum in Ghana until the tranfer of the money to your account is over. On your reply, I shall expect you to contact me urgently to enable us discuss in details about this transaction. Bearing in mind that your assistance is needed to transfer this fund, I propose a commission of 30% (Thirty Percent) of the total sum to you for the expected services and assistance. All arrangement and plan's has been put in place through the help of our family lawyer for the claim and clearing of this fund from the security and finance Firm as we move the fund directly to your account. Your urgent response is highly needed so as to stop further contact. I therefore mandate Barrister Short Emile Jnr, who is our family lawyer to deal with you on this transaction. You will be required firstly to correspond with our family lawyer, on Tel:+233-24-4062605 before communicating with me, this is totally for security reasons because people and family relatives has try in the pass to rip me off. See this website for verification :- http://www.chinadaily.com.cn/english/doc/2005-02/06/content_415563.htm I must use this opportunity to implore you to exercise the utmost indulgence to keep this matter extraordinarily confidential whatever your decision is while I await your prompt response. Your can Email me directly: - mrsmaryeyadema@yahoo.fr Yours sincerely, Mrs.Mary Eyadema.

Dear Sir,

In order to transfer out (USD 45 MILLION) Forty Five million United States Dollars) from BANK OF AFRICA (BOA): I have the courage to ask for your assistance to handle this important and confidential business believing that you will never let me down either now or in future. I am MR. BENJAMINE S.ADAM, the OPERATIONAL MANAGER of BANK OF AFRICA, (BOA) BENIN.

There is an account opened in this bank in 1989 and since 1996 nobody has operated on this account again. After going through some old files in the records, I discovered that if I do not remit this money out urgently it will be forfeited for nothing. The owner of this account is Mr.PAULTON ALLEN, a foreigner, and a miner at D&D INVESMENT CO, a geologist by profession and he died since 1996.

No other person knows about this account or any thing concerning it, the account has no other beneficiary and my investigation proved to me as well that this company does not know anything about this account and the amount involved is (USD 45M).

I want to transfer the [USD 45M] Forty Five million United States Dollars into a safe foreigners account abroad, but I don't know any foreigner.

I am only contacting you as a foreigner because this money can not be approved to a local bank here, but can only be approved to any foreign account because the money is in us dollars and the former owner of the account is Mr.PAULTON ALLEN a foreigner too.

I know that this message will come to you as a surprise as we dont know our selves before, but be sure that it is real and a genuine business.

I only got your contact address from my secretary who operates computer with believe in God that you will never let me down in this business.You are the only person that I have contacted in this business, so please reply urgently so that I will inform you the next step to take.

Send also your private telephone and fax numbers including the full details of the account to be used for the deposit. I want us to meet face to face or sign a binding agreement to bind us together so that you can receive this money into a foreign account or any account of your choice where the fund will be safe.

I will fly to your country for withdrawal, sharing and other investments. I am contacting you because of the need to involve a foreigner with foreign account and to act as a foreign beneficiary.

I need your full co-operation to make this work fine because the management is ready to approve this payment to any foreigner who has correct information of this account which I will give to you later immediately, if you are able and with capability to handle such amount in strict confidence and trust according to my instructions and advice for our mutual benefit because this opportunity will never come again in my life.

I need truthful person in this business because I don't want to make mistake, I need your strong assurance and trust. With my position now in the office I can transfer this money to any foreigner's reliable account, which you can provide with assurance that this money will be intact pending my physical arrival in your country for sharing.

I will destroy all documents of transaction immediately we receive this money leaving no trace to any place. You can also come to discuss with me face to face after which I will make this remittance in your presence and two of us will fly to your country so at least two days ahead of the money going into the account.

I will apply for annual leave to get visa immediately I hear from you that you are ready to act and receive this fund in your account.

I will use my position and influence to effect legal approvals and onward transfer of this money to your account with appropriate clearance forms of the ministries and foreign exchange departments.

At the conclusion of this business, you will be given 35% of the total amount, 60% will be for me, while 5% will be for expenses both parties might have incurred during the process of transferring.

Please bear in mind that this fund is not a looted or stolen money but rather a hard earned money generated.

Pls if you are willing to work with me, kindly forward to me your personal detail to enable me reach you, this includes the following:

1. Your full names

2. Your residential address

3. Your bank account informations

4. Your occupation

5. Your telephone and fax numbers

6. Including more Preamble about yourself (marital status)      Below is my alternative Contacts:   E-MAIL: ben_salifou@yahoo.com    PHONE# 229-98-177798

COTONOU BENIN REPUBLIC.

I look forward to your earliest reply.

Yours Truly,

MR. BENJAMINE SALIFOU ADAM

Msg sent via eMailWave - http://emailwave.com/ - Get your own FREE account and start receiving your eMail.

ATTN.PLEASE I am mustapher ahmed, I work with the BANK OF AFRICA(BOA) in burkina faso republic. It is my wish tosolicite your assistance in a business transaction that will be of benefit to you andI.During ourinvestigation and auditing in the bank, my department came across a very hugesum of money belonging to a deceased customer of the bank HAJI EL JAMAL ZOUE, a citizen of Lebanon whodied of the recent planecrash in Cotonou Benin republic on the 26th of Dec.2003. Although personally, I kept this information secret within myself to enable the whole plans and idea be profitable and successful during the time of execution.The said amount wasUSD$10.2m( ten million Two united states dollars).As it may intrest you to know, I got your contact through my country chamber of commerce andinternational relations here in burkina faso Rep. I believe you will be able and capable to champion abusiness of such magnitude without any problem. Meanwhileall the whole arrangement to put claim over this fund as the bonafide next of kin to the deceased, get the required approval and transfer this money to youraccount if youindicate your intrest has beenmade by me. In fact I could have done this deal alone but because of my position in this country as a banker,we are not allowed to operate a foreign account and would eventually raise an eye brow on my side during the time of transfer because I workin this bank.This is the actual reason why it will require a second party or fellow who will forward claims as the next of kin to the bank and also present a foreign account where hewill need the money to be re-transfered ,into on his requestas it may be, after due verification and clarification by bank officails. I will not fail to inform you that this transaction is 100%risk free. On smooth conclusion of this transaction, you will be entitled to 30% of the total sum as gratification,while 10% will be set aside to take care of expenses that may arise during the time of transfer, while the remaining 60% will be for me and my family. Please,you have been advised to keep business as a secret between you and i for i am still in service and intend to retire from service after i conclude this deal with you. Assoon as you confirm to me your willingness to assit me int his bussiness i will send to you the deceased bank account informations and Application which you will apply to the bank for inward transfer of this fund to your account. I will be monitoring the whole situation here in the bank until you confirmthe money in your account and ask me to come down to your country for subsequentsharing of the fund according to percentages previously indicated and further investment,either in your country or any other country you may advice usto invest in. All other necessary information will be sent to you when I hear from you. I suggest you get back to me assoon as possible stating yourwish in this deal call me on my private number 00229 76552482. For more clearification vist the website entire family on 26th December 2003 in a plane crash.VIEW THIS WEB SITE http://www.cnn.com/2003/WORLD/africa/12/26/benin.crash/index.html _________________________________________________________________ Express yourself instantly with MSN Messenger! Download today it's FREE! http://messenger.msn.click-url.com/go/onm00200471ave/direct/01/

Dear Friend, I am Mr.Lord Luke .from the First Bank of Nigeria Plc,Lagos Branch I got your contact through the internet I have urgent and very confidentialbusiness proposal for you. On January 7,1999, an America Oil consultant/contractor with the Nigerian National Petroleum Corporation,Mr.Charles Ballassi made a numbered time (fixed)deposit for twelve calendarmonths,valued at US$9,700,000.00(Nine Million Seven Hundred Thousand Dollars)in my branch upon maturity.I sent a rountine notification to his forwarded address but got no reply.After a month,i sent a reminder and finally we discovered from his contract employers,the Nigerian National Petroleum Corporation that Mr.Charles Ballassi died in the plane crash of 31 October 1999[with Egyptian 990] with other passengers aboard as you can confirm it yourself via the website below: http://www.cnn.com/us/9911/02/egyptair990.list/index.html on further investigation,i found out that he died without making a WILL,and attempts to trace his next of kin was fruitless.I therefore made further investigation and discovered that Mr.Charles Ballassi did not declare any next of kin or relations in all his official documents,including his bank deposit paperwork in my bank. This sum ofUS$9,700,000.00 is still in my bank and the interest is being rolled over with the principal sum at the end of each year.No one will ever come forward to claim it.According to Nigerian law, at the expiration of (seven)years,the money will revert to the ownershipof the Nigerian Government if nobody applies to claim the fund. Consequently,my proposal is that i will like you as a foreigner to stand as the next of kin to Mr.Charles Ballassi so that the fruit of this old man's labour will not get into the hands of some corrupt Government officials. This is simple, I will like you to provide immediately your full name and address so that the Attorney will prepare the necessary documents and affidavits which will put you in place as the next of kin.We shall employ the service of an attorney for the drafting and notarization of the WILL and obtain the necessary documents and letter of probate/administration in your favour for the transfer.Any bank account in any part of the world which you will provide will then facilitate the transfer of this money to you as the beneficiary/next of kin. The money will be paid into your account for us to share in ratio of 60% for me and 40% for you. There is no risk at all,the paperwork for this transaction will be done by the attorney and my position as the Branch Manager guarantees the successful execution of this transaction. If you are interested,please reply immediately via the private email address below,upon your responce,i shall provide you with more details and relevant documents that will help you understand the transaction. Please observe utmost confidentiality and be rest assured that this transaction would be most profitable for both of us because i shall require your assitance to invest my share in your country. Please upon the reciept of this mail message, send to me the following to enable start the process of the fund into your bank account: 1.Your full Name and address 2.Your Bank Name and Address 3.Your account Number and Account Beneficiary Name 4.Your private Telephone and fax numbers Thanks and regards Mr.Lord Luke. MANAGER,FIRST BANK OF NIGERIA.

Mrs Fatima Hinga Dear Sir/Madam, Thanks for finding time to go through my mail. I am Mrs. Fatima Hinga, the wife of Lieutenant Colonel John Garang Hinga the Leader of Sudanese People's Liberation Govement (SPLM) one of the leading political parties in Sudan which was formed in 1983. He died during the out brake of the recent civil war in Sudan. Before his death, he held many important offices which includes being the prime minister in a coalition government between 1986 to 1989. He also was the leader of the Umma Party a strong political organization in Sudan. After his tenure as coalition prime minister, he was made to be in-charge of the payment of Sudanese Media communications department in 2001. My husband was killed by a group known as Sadiq al Mahdi at the on set of the civil war while fighting for the liberation of the Sudanese people from the hands of a dictatorship government. I am 51 years old now and seriously ill although I am now receiving treatment in a hospital here in Thailand. During the period of our marriage we were blessed with a male child by name Musa Hinga who is also here taking care of me. After the death of my husband, I inherited a huge amount of money (25million US dollars) which my late husband deposited with a Security Company in Thailand for safe keeping. I now decided to contact you to assist me and my son to claim this money from where it was deposited and probably guide us in investing the fund in a worthwhile flourishing business over there. I hereby ask for your help and assistance. Although I am a novice in business, I have an eye on rigid properties. Your advice on other areas of private sector will be highly appreciated. I believe that you would be of great help in guiding my son to a successful business investment in your country even when I am gone. I will appreciate if you will show interest in collaborating with us, as this transaction will benefit both of us on joint venture partnership. Furthermore I am ready to give you a good negotiable percentage cash reward for your assistance. Detailed information on other proceedings will be made available to you upon receiving your reply showing interest in collaborating with us as I look forward to your urgent reply. Sincerely Yours Fatima Hinga.

From: MR. ARBU MPULA. SOUTH AFRICA JOHANNESBURG. TEL:27-73-2390-447. ATTN: M/D CEO/ GOKER , PLEASE WE NEED YOUR ASSISTANCE. You may be surprised to receive this letter from me since you don't know me personally. I am Mr, Arbu Mpula, the son of Dr.Henry Mpula, who was recently murdered in the land dispute in Zimbabwe. I got your contact through South African Information Exchange (S.A.I.E) in Johannesburg, and I decided to solicit for your assistance. My late father was among the few black Zimbabwean rich farmers murdered in cold blood by the agents of the ruling government of president Robert Mugabe for his alleged support and sympathy for the Zimbabwean opposition party controlled by the white minority. Before his death he had taken me to Johannesburg- South Africa to deposit the sum of US$ 23.Million(Twenty three Million United States Dollars) with a Security and Finance Company as if he Foresaw the looming danger in Zimbabwe. The money was deposited in a metal box and declared as a personal effects for the use of some of his friends who were to arrive for the world conference on racism scheduled to hold in South Africa from fromr 1st march, 2003.This money was given to my father by President.Robert Mugabe himself, for investment in South Africa when they were in good terms. The dispute between my father and the President arose when the President introduced a new land reform-act, which adversely affected the rich white farmers and so black farmers as well. My father was vehemently opposed to the "modus operandis"adopted by the government and publicly oppose it. This brought him in direct conflict with the president. To achieve his purpose, the president used war veterans to plunder, loot and occupy all farms belonging to the white farmers and their black sympathizers. More than Fifty Farmers has lost their lives so far. Heads of governments from the west, especially Britain and United States of America have voiced there condemnation of Mugabe's plan. Subsequently, South African Development Community (S.A.D.C) has continuously Supported Mugabe's new land act, it is against this background that I and my family who are currently Residing in South Africa have decided to transfer my Father's money into a foreign account. As the eldest Son of my Father, I am saddled with the responsibility Of seeking a genuine foreign account where this money Could be transferred without the knowledge of my Government who are tactically freezing our family Wealth and South Africa's government seems to be Playing along with them. I am faced with the dilemma of investing this money in South Africa for fear of Encountering the same experience in future since both Countries have almost the same political history. so, the South African Foreign Exchange policy does not allow such investment hence I am seeking for an "assylum". As a businessperson that I entrusted my Future and that of my family into his hands, I must Let you know that this transaction is 100% risk Free and the nature of your business does not necessarily matter. For your assistance, we are offering You 20% of the total sum, 75% for me and my family While 5% will be mapped out for any expenses we may incurs during this transaction. We wish to invest our Money on commercial property based on your advice. Finally will demand for assurance that you will not sit on this money when it finally gets to your personal or company's account in your country. If this proposal is acceptable by you, please confirm your interest via the above telephone, or you reply through email. THANKS AND GOD BLESS YOU, Best Regards, Mr; Arbu Mpula, _________________________________________________________________ Don't just search. Find. Check out the new MSN Search! http://search.msn.com/

From:Dr.Derrick Springs Tel :44 704 011 0287 Fax :44 870 130 6123 This is an official notification of funds deposited in your name. We arrange for the safekeeping of special and valuable packages and baggage in trust for reputable clients that are honest and trustworthy. A benefactor whose identity can not be disclosed because of the Non Circumvention and Non Disclosure Agreement that was signed with the said benefactor when the funds were being deposited, made you the beneficiary of a package containing some amount of money. The Non Circumvention and Non Disclosure Agreement signed with the benefactor mandates us to fully divulge and disclose the benefactor's identity 18 months after you, the beneficiary, has received the funds. The funds totals US$7.5M (Seven Million, Five Hundred Thousand United States Dollars) and we confirm that these funds are fully free of any liens, or encumbrances and are clean, clear and non-criminal origin and are available in the form of CASH. You are hereby advised to reconfirm your Full Contact Information for verification with information contained in our database in the format stated below. After verifying the details with the information we have in our database,you will be contacted to personally claim the funds in the Finance and Security Firm in Europe where its being kept with the Consignment Deposit Information (C.D.I) that will empower you to do so. This Consignment Deposit Information (C.D.I) is what is needed to claim the funds and will only be sent to you after all your information has been verified and confirmed to be true. The information should therefore be sent in the manner stated below so as to ensure that no mistake is made. Your Full Name: ___________________________ Your Complete Address (Physical Address with Zip Code) : ______________________________ Date of Birth (Day/Month/Year):____________________ Occupation:__________________________________ Direct Telephone/Mobile Number: ____________________________ Fax Number:____________________________________ Complete the above and send back to me as soon as possible. Congratulations in advance. Thank you and I sincerely remain Dr.Derrick Springs.

First Commercial Bank 29 Wilson Street London. EC2M 2SJ Dear Friend, I am Mr Thompson Rowe, the Head of Audit Department, First Commercial Bank, London, UK. And for reasons which will become obvious to you as you read on, I obtained your address particulars from an Internet address listing. Please exercise some patience and read through my message. I have a very urgent and confidential business proposition for you. On June 6th 1999, a Crude Oil Contractor with the Kuwait National Petroleum Corporation, Engr. Ahmed Youseff Mustafa , a national of kuwait, made a numbered time ( fixed) deposit for 12 calendar months, value GBP12,500,000.00 (TWELVE MILLION, FIVE HUNDRED THOUSAND POUNDS) in my branch. On maturity, we sent a routine notification to his forwarding address but got no reply. After a month, we sent a reminder and finally, his contract employers, the Kuwait National Petroleum Corporation wrote to inform us that Engr. A Y Mustafa died on an automobile accident; that he died without making a WILL, and all attempts to trace his next of kin through the kuwait embassy were fruitless. I therefore made further investigations and discovered that Mr. Mustafa had actively opposed the Government of his country kuwait, and was consequently driven into exile. My proposal therefore is that, I am looking for a foreigner who will stand in as the next of kin to Mr. Mustafa. It is not necessary to be a blood relation to Mr. Mustafa, nor have the same name. It is not also necessary to come from the same Country. I have worked out the modalities to achieve my aim of appointing a next of kin, and therefore also by this means we transfer this money total GBP12.5M abroad for us to share. No one will ever come forward to claim it now, and according to British law,after 9 years, the money will automatically revert to the Government Treasury if the Account owner is a foreigner, and certified dead, and there is no valid claim. This indeed, is the situation. The money transfer paperwork itself will include a certificate of origin so that the receiving bank does not ask questions or refuse the money as money laundering. Also, the paperwork will include proper certification that the funds being transferred are from non criminal sources. In short this will be a proper and legal money transfer and there is no risk!. Once you indicate your interest I will initiate the processing of the transfer and in about 14 working days the money total GBP12.5M will be in your nominated bank account for us to share in the ratio of 70% for me and 30% for you. Looking forward to your urgent reply. Yours truly, Mr.Thompson Rowe.

>From The Desk Of, MRS. SUSAN SHUBANGA Deputy Minister of Safety and Security South Africa After due deliberation with my children, I decided to contact you for your assistance in standing as a beneficiary to the some millions of dollars First, let me start by introducing myself, I am MRS SUSAN SHUBANGA, a mother of three children and the Former Deputy Minister of Minerals and Energy,Now Deputy Minister of Safety and Security under the President of South African MR THABO MBEKI. You can view my profile at my website http://www.gov.za/gol/gcis_profile.jsp?id=1066 After the swearing in ceremony making me the Deputy Minister of Minerals and Energy 1996 my husband Mr Ndelebe Shabangu died while he was on an official trip to Trinidad and Tobago in 2002. After his death, I discovered that he had some funds in a dollars with a FINANCIAL INSTITUTE. This fund emanated as a result of an over-invoiced contract which he executed with the Government of South Africa. Though I assisted him in getting this contract but I never knew that it was over-invoiced by him. I am afraid that the government of South Africa might start to investigate on contracts awarded from 1998 to date. If they discover this money in his bank account,they will confiscate it and seize his assets here in South Africa and this will definetely affect my political career in government. I want your assistance in clearing this money from the Financial Institute.As soon as the fund is cleared, you are expected to move it immediately into another personal bank account in your country.I will see to it that the account is not traced from South Africa. As soon as you have confirmed the fund into your account, I will send my eldest son with my Attorney to come to your country to discuss on business investments. For your assistance, I am offering you 5 Million (Five million United States Dollars Only) However, you have to assure me and also be ready to go into agreement with me that you will not elope with my fund. If you agree to my terms, kindly as a matter of urgency send me an email.Due to my sensitive position in the South African Government, I would not WANT you to call me on phone or send a fax to me. All correspondence must be by email to my private email:(shubanga-suzzy@hotmail.com) If you want to speak with my Attorney, that is fine and okay by me. His chambers will be representing my interest with you. if you show interest in assisting me, i will foward his contact to you and yours to him. I would also like you to give me your contact address i.e. telephone, fax and whatever other means of communication of which to reach you, to enable my Attorney call or reach you from time to time. Please I do not need to remind you of the need for absolute Confidentiality if this transaction must succeed. YOU MUST NOT CALL ME!If you do not feel comfortable with this transaction, do not hesitate to discontinue. Thanks for your anticipated co-operation and my regards to your family. Yours faithfully, MRS. SUSAN SHUBANGA Deputy Minister of Safety and Security South Africa

Cher Ami, Je suis très heureuse de vous écrit cette lettre du fait que nous ne nous sommes jamais rencontrés avant. Je suis Julia Ngoli, je suis nationalité Libérienne ,le seule fille survivant du défunt DR Daniel Z.Ngoli ,de République du Liberia. Mes parents ont été tué septembre passé 2004 par le groupe rebelle sur son chemin en voyageant avec ma mère à la interroi de mon pays. Mon Défunt père c'est l'explorateur est le Directeur de (N.D.M.C ) NATIONAL DIAMOND MINING COMPANY dE Liberia. Avant cela père ,Mon père m'ait informé de la somme (de $16.000.000) Seize millions de dollars des Etats-Unis seulement ce qu'il a déposé dans une coffre avec une société de valeur immobiliers ici en Cote Ivoire sur le nom de son associé étranger en tant que bénéficiaire. Ces fonds ont émané de sa tenure quand il était alors le Directeur de cette société dans mon pays et le vente de diamants. En étant le seul fils et après avoir été averti de ne pas laissez le gouvernement incubent de la République de Liberia se rendre compte de cette fonds, Donc j'ai décidé d'attendre un peux avant la recherche de ces fonds. cependant que je contacté la société de valeur immobilier qui m'a demandée de me présenter avec l'associé étranger de mon défunt père qui représentera la réclamation de cet valise et aussi légalisez ces informations a la marie ici Abidjan . Voila la condition que il faut pour que vous sera en possession de cet colis. tout mes efforts de contacter cet associé étranger de mon défunt père un Turc pour me permettre de rentre en possession de cet fonds étaient en vain. Par conséquent votre contact est venu à moi dans mon recherche indépendante d'une personne digne de confiance qui se tiendra en tant qu l'associé étranger à mon défunt père et demande le réclamation de cet colis pour me permettre de avoir cet argent qui sera transféré à votre adresse indiqué par leur moyen diplomatique dans votre pays pour l'investissement pressant. Vous aller assurerez également mon voyage à votre pays pour finis mes étude avec cet fonds et aussi investissez bien avec cet argent sur votre guidance une fois que cet colis est transfère en votre adresse. puisque ma vie dans mon pays est en danger et est menacée quotidiennement, ainsi j'ai émigré à en la République de Cote D'ivoire où j'ai été accordé l'asylum et poursuivre également ces fonds. Je vous aimerai également que vous considérer cet affaires en tant que nos secrets supérieurs, comme vous l' savez que si le gouvernement récent sache que cet argent a été déposé par mon père ici ils le confisqueront certainement parce que mes espoir et mon avenir c’est sur cet argent, Aussi compte tenu de la commette de récupération installé maintenant pour récupérer tous les fonds des haut functioniers Libérien dans les comptes bancaires étrangers. Si vous sentir capable de me aider, vous m'envoyer un courrier rapidement pour me permettre de vous informer sans tarder de ce que vous devrait faire ça veut, dire légalisez votre informations et pour être en possession de cet coffre qui sera transféré à votre adresse nommé pour l'investissement. Pour votre assistance j'ai propose 10% de toute la somme comme votre commission. Merci pour votre humainement aide et Que Dieu vous Benisse. Excuse Moi Pour Mon Mauvaise Français comme vous savais je parle anglais.EMAIL(julia_ngoli30@yahoo.fr) Julia Ngoli

Dear Please let this letter not to bring confusion to you. I know that we have not met either before but hear me from the dept of your mind. It is circumstances that made to send this to you. I will introduce myself first to you, My name is Victoria Abuchi, I lost my mother, my hero and my lord Ms Abu a year ago. She was poisioned to death by her associate in business. She formed a company by one Mr. Philip Brown who poisioned her only to take benefit of the multi million venture. He was arrested immedaitely my mother died and he entered an agreement with my mother's brothers that I and the immedaite younger brother of my mother will represent my mother's interest in the company. After six months I was kicked out of the company because I said that we have to change the company's lawyer who I termed was part of the elimination of my mother. I did not know that they have changed all the company's document without my name appearing any where. I will have to let you know more detail on that but let me move to the point why I am contacting you. I have been nick named bastard by my mother's relations, They have named me all source of names even calling me outcast because my mother is late, while my mother was the bread winner of the family. They have pushed me out of my mother's mansion and still want to eliminate my life. I got through the records of my mother account books three weeks ago while crying and meditating, which I beleive was inspired by the spirit of God, I discovered that there is a huge sum of money she deposited in a bank, which is $9,800,000. The note attached to the deposit agreement she made with the bank indicated that, the money was to be used to purchase machinery for the establishment of a new company of her own. Please all I need from you is to do all you can to help me to get this money out of the bank. I have been to the bank where this money is deposited immediately, and confirmed the account most deligently. The bank told me that my mother informed them that the money was to be remitted to her company's costumer account abroad, which her costumer will provide to them but since then they have never heard from her nor the costumer. Now my mother is late. I don't want the bank to know that my mother is late. I told them that she is ill and appointed me to represent her in her affairs. (1).I want you to provide an account where the money will be remitted into as my mother's costumer. (2).Make arrangement for me to leave here as soon as possible (3).How much commission you will take for rendering the assistant? My mother did not marry to any man, She had me as the only child while she was having an affair with the person that surpposed to be my father when she was 18 years and the man abandoned her and disappeared which forced her to remain single. Now I am 20 years and never saw my father for a day.I have no home now and my life is in danger. I don't have any one to run into. All the members of my mother family have turned their back on me because I demand for me right. They told me that I don't belong to the family. That I should go and look for my father, Whom I don't know. I have made trace to know my father without sucess. I want you to hear me from the inner most of your heart and accord me this help. God will bless you for saving my life and future. Best wishes, Victoria Abuchi.

FROM: PHILIP & ALICE DESMOND Rue L195, Zone 4, Abidjan Ivory Coast. Dear Beloved One, With the hope that you are okay and doing fine, l am contacting you for business transaction. This proposal could be strange but please give it some attention. I got your contact details on the internet and i decieded to contact you first in good faith. My name is PHILIP DESMOND, I live in Ivory Coast in West Africa. I have inherited the sum of USD$27,000,000.00 (Twenty seven million Dollars) from my late parents. But l am faced with a problem. It is in respect of this problem that l am contacting you. On the banks documents for the next of kin, my late father appended a clause stating that: I the next of kin, must attain the age of 35 years, before taking full control of the bank account, But, in the event of war or natural disasters in Ivory Coast, the bank should honour a transfer request from me which must be for the safety of the funds, And in this case, I must have an investment manager, my investment manager must not be from this country that my investment manager most be a foreigner. I am only 24 years old now, but Ivory Coast is not a safe country at this time because of the war and the political crisis. So I want the bank to transfer my money out of Ivory Coast to your account in any safe country, but the bank is insisting that l fulfil the conditions put down by my late father. This is actually the reason why l am writing you. So please I would like you to become my investment manager, because having an investment manager is the condition the bank insist l have to meet before they would agree to transfer my money out to any account. When you become my investment manager, l would instruct the bank to transfer my money to your account in your country, so that you can help me invest the money wisely while me and my small sister will further our education in your country. And please tell me what we can invest with this money in your country? Please I am expecting your response. If you wish to reply me,Please reach me at this same email address . I am willing to give you 20% of the total money for your assistance. And please reply with your full contact information for easy communications so that i can send details and the deposit documents to you for better clearifications with the bank contact. My regards, PHILIP DESMOND

FROM: Mr RAY KABE BANGKOK THAILAND DEAR SIR, You may be surprised to receive this letter from me since you do not know me personally, the purpose of my introduction is that, I am RAYMOUND kABE, the first son of DR KINGSLEY SMITH KABE who was recently murdered in the land dispute in Zimbabwe. I got your contact through network online hence decided to write you. Before the death of my father, he had taken me to Johannesburg to deposit the sum of US$10.5Million(Ten million five hundred thousand United StatesDollars), in one the private security company, as if he foresaw the looming danger in Zimbabwe.This money was deposited in a box as germ stones to avoid much demurrage from Security Company.This amount was meant for the purchase of new machines and chemicals for the farms and established of new farm in Swaziland. This land problem came when Zimbabwean President Mr. Robert Mugabe introduce a new Land Act reform which wholly affected the rich white farmers and some few blacks farmers.And this resulted to the killing and mob action by Zimbabwean war veterans and some lunatics in the society. In fact, a lot of people were killed because of this land reformed Act for which my father was one of the victim. It is against this background that, I and my family who are currently staying in bangkok thailand decided to transfer my father’s money to foreign account sine c the law of bangkok prohibit a refugee (asylum seeker) to open any bank account or to be involved in any financial transaction throughout the teritorial zone bangkok. As the eldest son of my father, I am saddle with the responsibility of seeking a genuine foreign account where this money could be transferred without the knowledge of my government who are Sent on taking everything we have got. I am faced with the dilemma of investing this amount of money in bangkok for fear of what is going on in the bangkok Foreign Exchange policy does not allow such investment for an asylum seeker. As a businessman, who I have to entrust my future and of my family in his hands, I must let you know that this transaction is risk free. If you accept to assist me and my family all I want you to do for me is to make arrangements and come to bangkok thailand, sothat you can open a non-resident account which will aid us in transferring the money into any account you will nominate overseas. This money I intend to use for investment. I have two options for you, firstly you can choose to have certain percentage of the money for nominating your account for this transaction.Or you can go into partnership with me for the proper profitable investment of the money in your country. Whichever the options you want, feel free to notify me I have also mapped out 10% of this money for all kinds of expenses incurred in the process of this transaction. If you do not prefer a partnership I am willing to give you 20% of the money while the remaining 70% will be for my investment in your country. Contact me with the above E-mail and please candly put ur numberin your reply. while I implore you to maintain the absolute secrecy required in this transaction. Yours Faithfully, RAY KABE (For the Family)

FROM: JESSICA WILLIAMS AND BROTHER ABIDJAN, COTE D'IVOIRE. DEAR SIR, I KNOW THIS MIGHT COME TO YOU AS A SURPRISE BUT WITH DUE RESPECT,I CONSIDER WRITING YOU FOR BUSINESS ASSISTANCE AFTER MUCH FASTING AND PRAYING CONSIDERING THAT WE HAVE NOT SEEN YOU FACE TO FACE. MY NAME IS JESSICA WILLIAMS AND MY BROTHER JAMES , WE ARE THE ONLY CHILDREN OF LATE CHIEF. DESMOND WILLIAMS, FROM ZULU IN THE RPUBLIC OF SOUTH AFRICA, WE ARE STUDENTS BUT CURRENTLY IN IVORY COAST FOR A BUSINESS WHICH I AM ABOUT TO SEEK YOUR ASSISTANCE. MY FATHER WAS AN AGRICULTURIST AND MADE SO MUCH MONEY FROM THE SALE OF COCOA AND GOLD IN SOUTH AFRICA AND WAS PLANNING TO ESTABLISH A COCOA FARM IN (ABIDJAN) IVORY COAST WITH THE HELP OF HIS IVORIAN FRIEND BEFORE HE MET HIS DEATH PRECISELY A WEEK AFTER HIS RETURN FROM ABIDJAN IVORY COAST WHERE HE WENT TO NEGOTIATION. HE DIED AS A RESULT OF THE GHASTLY MOTOR ACCIDENT HE HAD WITH MY MOTHER,MY MOTHER DIED INSTANTLY BUT MY FATHER DIED FOUR DAYS LATER IN A HOSPITAL, AS IF MY FATHER KNEW , HE REMINDED US THAT HE DEPOSITED THE SUM OF TEN MILLION FIVE HUNDRED THOUSAND US DOLLAR (10.500.000.00) IN A SUSPENCE ACCOUNT WITH A BANK IN ( ABIDJAN) IVORY COAST AND ADVICED US TO CONTACT A FOREIGNER TO HELP US TRANSFER THE MONEY FOR INVESTMENT. HE GAVE US THE DEPOSIT CERTIFICATE AND LODGEMENT PAPERS.SO THAT WE CAN RETRIEVE THIS MONEY.WE HAVE ARRIVED IN (ABIDJAN) IVORY COAST, LOCATED THE BANK AND COMFIRMED THE DEPOSIT. NOW WITH MOST HONEST AND CONFIDENTIALITY, I AM SOLICITING YOUR ASSISTANCE TO MOVE THIS MONEY TO YOUR SAFE ACCOUNT ABROAD SO THAT WE WOULD INVEST IT IN AGRICULTURE OR ANY LUCRATIVE BUSINESS WHICH YOU WOULD INTRODUCE US INTO OVER THERE . AS YOU CAN SEE THIS MONEY IS THE ONLY THING LEFT FOR ME AND MY YOUNGER BROTHER, SO WE WANT TO INVEST IT WISELY AND THERE IS A POLITICAL PROBLEM HERE (IVORY COAST),IT WILL BE VERY NECESSARY TO TAKE THE MONEY OUT OF THIS COUNTRY FOR SECURITY REASONS. A HANDSOME REWARD AWAITS YOU AS YOU CONSIDER TO ASSIST US TRANSFER THIS MONEY FOR INVESTMENT, YOUR PERCENTAGE WOULD BE DISCUSSED ON YOUR POSITIVE RESPONSE TO THIS REQUEST. I AWAIT ANXIOUSLY TO HEAR FROM YOU SO THAT WE WILL DISCUSS THE MODALITIES OF THIS TRANSACTION. THANKS AND MAY GOD BLESS YOU. YOURS SINCERELY, JESSICA WILLIAMS AND JAMES.

Mrs.Grace Omar Dakar Rep.of Senegal West Africa. Dear Beloved One. Thank you for giving me your time;Please be patient and read my email to you, this letter might come as a surprise to you,and you could be wondering where I got your contact. I got your address through a personal search on the internet for someone relaible and trustworthy,so i decided to contact you for an assistant, which I do hope you will take your time to consider. I am a widow to the late principal accountant of Sierra Leon central bank who was assassinated due to political hostility in my country. For the sake of our lives,my children and i fled to a neighbouring country, Senegal; where we are now seeking refuge. I must confess to you,our journey to Senegal was not a jolly ride as we encountered a lot of problems,most painful was a particular situation that left us in a state of penury and where we also lost our travelling documents,thereby making it impossible for us to travel now. Months ago i was diagnosed with cancer,this futher made our lives more difficult as i am lacking funds to take care of my self and my children. I decided to contact you,seeking your assistance because i am having problems recovering a large deposit made by my late husband overseas since the company maintained that instructions left by my late husband the original depositor,states that the funds be "RELEASED TO ME HIS WIFE OR A FOREIGN REPRESENTATIVE ONLY", believing he would appoint someone by himself to represent him for the claim but unfortunately he died earlier. This is the only hope my family has of surviving,paticularly my only son,who has so much dreams and i want to do the best i can to help them fufill thier dreams. I am contacting you to help me make the claims by representing my husband as the foreign representative,since i cannot travel to make the claims my self due to my present condition,i am pleading with you to help us claim the funds from the security firm and most importantly, your ability to put the said funds into circulation wisely for our joint interest and relocating my children particularly my son is a major considerable factor regarding my request as my knowledge on financial matters is not enough to handle such amount of fund(us$16,000,000.00) sixteen million dollars. In view of this, if you are touched to work with me in sincerity, by standing as my late husband,s foreign representative to receive the said deposit on our behalf, we shall embrace you as our family and will compensate you accordingly. I am willing to share the money 40% for you,40% for me and my children and the remaining 10% we be set aside for any expenses that may be incurred in the course of this transaction,all i really care about now is the welfare of my children. As you indicate interest, please contact my son ANTA OMAR on this email address (an_omar07@yahoo.fr)or call him on his phone number Tel: +221-4488469 to enable him give you further information relating to the funds and the steps we shall take to finalize on the project,i have handed this project to him as my health conditions makes it hard for me to talk or go around. Thanking you in advance for your kind and urgent response, more so for keeping our proposal to your self. Sincerely Grace Omar.

From: The ACCOUNTANT. International Commercial Bank. First Light Branch, Accra - Ghana. West Africa. ATTN:My Dear, My name is Mr. Michael Ezra. I am the accountant of the International Commercial Bank-Ghana, First Light Branch Accra. I am a Ghanaian married with three kids. I am writing to solicit your assistance in the noble transfer of US$14,800,000.00 (Fourtheen million, eight hundred thousand U.S.dollars). This fund is the excess of what my branch in which I am the accountant made as profit during the last year. I have already submitted an approved end of the last year report for the year 2005 to my Head Office here in Accra and they will never know of this Excess.I have since then, placed this amount of US$14,800,000.00 (Fourtheen million, eight hundred thousand U.S. dollars) on a SUSPENCE ACCOUNT without a beneficiary. As an officer of the bank, I cannot be directly connected to this money thus I am impelled to request for your assistance to receive this money into your bank account. I intend to part 30% of this fund to you while 70% shall be for me. I do need to stress that there are practically no risk involved in this. It is going to be a bank-to-bank transfer to your nominated bank account anywhere you feel safer. All I need from you is to stand as the original depositor of this fund. Frankly speaking I have been working in this bank for close to 10 years and I have nothing to show for it,my yearly income is barely about $3,500 USD after tax and the major reason I packaged this transaction is that I have a 9 year old daughter with leukemia and needs a bone marrow transplant or she will die. I have already made arrangement for this surgery in the UK but I could not afford it, so I really need your help to do this deal or my daughter will die. I am offering you 30% of the total sum after this money is wired to your account, because it is a simple bank-to-bank inheritance claim transfer.I will also like you to get me rest assured that you will not abandon me when the money gets to your account.I have all the payment claim information worked out. All I require is your honest co-operation to enable us see this deal Through. Please i will like you to answer me this questions. (1)Can a black man build a house in your country and invest there? (2)Can a black man be given staying permit and be allowed to visit sight seen? (3)Can i direct any company of my own? I guarantee that this will be executed under a legitimate arrangement that will protect you from any breach of the trasfer.Your prompt response via my email is highly envisaged;your response will make me act accordingly upon the receipt of your mail. I will be waiting to hear from you for further guidelines. If you accept this offer, I will appreciate your timely response. Bye for now and thanks for your understanding. Best regards, Mr. Michael Ezra. Note:You answer me through my alternative e-mail address(mic.ezra2006@yahoo.fr)

FROM MR HENRY KABORE THE CHIEF AUDITOR INCHARGE FOREIGN REMITTANCE UNIT, AFRICAN DEVELOPMENT BANK{ADB}. OUAGADOUGOU BURKINA FASO. Dear Partner, I presumed that all is well with you and your family. Please let this do not be a surprise message to you because i got your contact information from the international directory in few weeks ago before i decided to contact you on this magintude and lucrative transaction for our present and future survival in life.Moreover, i have laid all the solemn trust in you before i decided to disclose this successful & confidential transaction to you. I am the Chief Auditor Incharge of the Foreign Remittance Unit of our bank and i decided to contact you over this financial transaction worth the sum of Nineteen Million, Three Hundred Thousand United States of America ($19,300,000.00 ) for our present and future success.This is an abandoned fund that belongs to one of our bank foreign customers who died along with his entire family through plane crash disaster since few years ago.Meanwhile i was very fortune to came across the deceased file when i was arranging the old and abandoned customers files in other to sign and submit to the entire bank management for an official re-documentation and audit of the year against 2006. Informed clearly that it was stated in our Foreign banking rules and regulations which was signed lawfully that if such fund remains unclaimed till the period of 4 years started from the date when the beneficiary died, the money will be transferred into the treasury as an unclaimed fund.However, it is not authorized by the rules guiding our bank for a citizen of Burkina Faso to make the claim of the fund unless your are a foreigner no matter the country different from the deceased.So the request of you as a foreigner is necessary to apply for the claim and transfer of the fund smoothly into your reliable bank account as the next of kin to the deceased. When the fund is transferred into your account, { 35% } Thirty Five Percent will be for you in respect of all your assistance for the transfer of the fund into your account and provision of the bank account where the bank will remit the fund into,{ 55% } Fifty Five Percent will be for me being the pioneer of the business while the rest { 10% } Ten Percent will be shared to respectable Organisations Centers such as Charity , Motherless Babies Homes, and helpless disabled people around us in the World. If you are really sure of your, Trustworthy, Accountability and confidentiality on this transaction,contact me and accept not to change your mind to cheat, or disappoint me when the fund is transferred into your account.So reply for the assurance with your telephone and fax numbers necessary to facilitate an easy communication. As soon as you reply me i will let you know the next procedures to be follow in order to finalize this transaction immediately. I expect your urgent communication. Yours sincerely, Mr Henry Kabore. _________________________________________________________________ Express yourself instantly with MSN Messenger! Download today it's FREE! http://messenger.msn.click-url.com/go/onm00200471ave/direct/01/

HELLO, I know that this proposal might be a surprise to you but, it as an emergency to our condition with my mother here in dakar senegal, Be bless as you help me and my mother to transfer and invest our money in your country. I am ( MS.GLORY SUMA ) from the republic of Sudan in Central Africa Dafur, now seeking for refuge in Dakar Senegal under the(UNHCR)united nation high commission for refuge with my mother. we got your contact during a desperate search here in Dakar for a possible transaction. My (late father DR. SUMA SESSAY) who was the former minister of finance and economy in Sudan before he was assinated by the rebbles in the captal city of Khartoon 2003. And all our properties was totally destroyed. However, we managed to escape with some of my father's documents covering $10.5 Million dollars(ten million five hundered us dollars) which is presently deposited safely in a Finance Company here in Dakar on my name as the only (DAUGHTER) of the family, and the next of kin. the Company have approved to transfer the fund. deposited on my name but we are looking for a trust and reable foreign partner who will assist us to transfer and invest the fund in his country.i was advice to leave with my aged mother immediately,for security reasons. to dakar senegal because i was the next target as the only (DAUGHTER) of my family. All the vital documents will be fax to you as our foreign partner who will reccive the fund. for investment. in your country and possession pending our arrival to meet with you. Furthermore, we only want this done this way because your country is politically stable for any profitable investment and only if you accept our proposal, you will serve as the beneficiary of the fund. on commencement of this proposed transactions. you will send me and my mother a letter of inviation to enable us to get a visa and fly down to your country once the fund. is been transfer to your country.i hope you will not betray me a nd my mother because this money is all, our hope since my late father died. I am giving you the offers as mentioned. with every confidence on your acceptance to assist us, we have decided to give you (25%) of the total fund based on qiuck participation in your side. Secondly, we shall also take( 5%) out for any miscelleneous expenses that may occure, during the transfer. i wish you send me a reply immediately as soon as you receieve this proposal so that we shall arrange, on how this fund will be transfer to your country. On commencement,this transaction will take nothing less than (7 working days) to be accomplished as the Company managment told me and my mother. All documents covering the fund. are safe and intact with us here in Dakar Senegal. hoping to hear from you, contact me as soon as you receive our email. THANKS, MS. GLORY SUMA ALTERNATIVE EMAIL glorysuma555@yahoo.com.au

MR ZUMA BARLEY AUDITING AND ACCOUNTING DEPT, AFRICAN DEVELOPMENT BANK BENIN(ADB) COTONOU-BENIN REPUBLIC REPLY TO: (zuma_barley@hotmail.com) Compliments Of the Season, Pleasure writing to you at this moment of the day, I am Mr Zuma Barley, the director incharge of auditing and accounting Dept. of AFRICAN DEVELOPMENT BANK BENIN(ADB) in Cotonou,Benin Republic.I deem it fit to contact you regarding an inactive/dormant account fund that will benefit both of us at the end, if parties involved will take restrait and maintain absolute secrecy,honesty and intergrity. I got your contact in my search for a reputable and reliable person to particularly assist me to claim the fund in question. During auditing, in our bank at the end of last fiscal year, We discovered the sum of (US$28.1M) Twenty-eight million one hundred thousand United States dollars in a dormant account belonging to an international businessman based here in benin republic who was involved in the December 25th Benin plane crash. I kept this information(secret) confidential within my jurisdiction to enable us submit claims and transfer this fund through trustworthy person whom we shall present to our bank as the bonafide next of kin to the deceased. Please visit http://www.cnn.com/2003/WORLD/africa/12/26/benin.crash/index.html Our investigations so far clearly reveals that there is no immediate survivor or even a relation to the deceased and as such,there is no immediate next of kin for further claims of the deceased fund as we have long been expecting someone to come forward with an applications. Further informations /verifications from reliable sources too have confirmed that the deceased customer supposed next of kin were all in the plane with him died with him. This fund is now ready for transfer into a foreign account, whose owner will be portrayed to our bank as the beneficiary and a next of kin to the deceased customer. The foreign account owner will impost himself approprietly as the next of kin to the deceased and respond positively like a true next of kin who wishes to speed up the release and transfer process of his inherited fund.Kindly be aware too that if the over-due fund if not claimed by the end of next quarter, the National Treasury and Bills of Benin will take over the ownership of the fund in line with the National Edict Act of 1979. We do not want this to happen as it will not augur to our best interest, having worked all our lives in the banking sector, that is why I contacted you for us to do the deal together with absolute confidence, so that you will be portrayed as the bonafide beneficiary and an immediate next of kin to the deceased. I will give you further directives, advice and all needed informations required for this transaction as soon as I receive your positive response. Similarly,if you accept to carry out this transaction with us, we have resolved offering to you 30% of the total sum as commission, extra 10% of all proceeds to be generated from subsequent profit-viable investments projects and you will be compensated with an executive office in the project.The first-phase shall be a five (5) year irrevocable contractual business partnership. We will invest 50% of our shares into your firm if you already have one provided that is profit orientated. 5% of the total fund will be set aside to re-imburse all expenses incurred in this course of this transaction. This transfer will automatically be affected within 7 working days. Be rest assured that with the underground work i have laid so far,that this transaction carries no risk and no extra burdens on your part, except the above mentioned nominal roles you are required to fulfill and similarly will be required to maintain absolute information secrecy throughout the duration of this transaction,because discussing and exhibiting it with a third party might jeopardise the entire transaction. I will give you directives and all needed information as soon as I receive your positive response. Kindly understand that we could not carry out this fund-transfer on our own, based on the simple facts that we are civil servants and presently bank staffs and this office excludes us from operating foreign accounts,moreover,conducting such magnanimous transaction from the same place where we belong to/coming from will raise eyebrows on our side and the truth is that this fund belongs to a foreigner,and as such demands same as next of kin. I am looking forward to receiving your interesting response on this project as this will greatly enrich the both of us at the end. Best Regards, MR ZUMA BARLEY CALL ME: 00229-97-87-27-83 FOR MORE PROOFS AND DETAILS

Yuri Konovalov General Director Novokuibyshersk Oil, RESPOND IF YOU ARE WILLING TO HELP   Dear friend,   I have sent you this mail because of the need to open discussions with you. I don't want you to misunderstand this offer in any aspect, if it is okay with you I ask for your full cooperation. I am Yuri Konovalov, the General Director of Novokuibyshersk Oil an international affiliate of Yukos Oil and Gas Company based in Russia. Due to ill Health I have esophageal cancer, it has defiled all forms of medical treatment and according to the medical experts it is a terminal illness so I do not know how much longer I have to live. I never had any real Friends in my lifetime because I never really cared for anyone but my business. But now I know that there is more to life than making all the money in the world. However, certain unfolding events has made it very necessary for me to seek your help, my company is fighting investigations and bankruptcy due to the Yukos Oil problems in Russia, most of my assets were seized due to this case. Recently I received a bulk payment from South Africa Ministry for my last contract there. I instructed them specifically not to send the funds to Russia because of the problems, but that the funds to be deposited with a Finance and Security company in Europe on hold. A huge cash deposit of Twenty-Five Million dollars was domiciled with a finance/Security Company overseas to my knowledge only. This is the last of my assets, now that my health has deteriorated so badly, I cannot do this myself anymore, I therefore need you as a partner because you are a neutral party to help me collect this funds deposited with the security company and disburse it secretly based on instructions. Because my time is short I have decided to give most of this money to charity organizations, as I want this to be one of the last good deeds I do on earth. For all your good efforts you will receive 30% of the Funds and must disburse the rest based on instructions. I want you to understand my seriousness in this case and if you can handle the job kindly contact me on this email(y_konovalov@yahoo.com) for security purposes. I have all the necessary documents on hand; please contact me ASAP so we can discuss more. Thank you for your anticipated cooperation. If you are not interested, please keep it to yourself and do not respond.   Best Regards,   Yuri Konovalov

FROM: Mr.Mandla Sizwe, 77 Seaside Cottages Fish Hoek-Cape Town South Africa. I feel quite safe dealing with you in this important business having gone through your remarkable profile on the internet. Though, this medium Internet) has been greatly abused, I choose to reach you through it because it still remains the fastest medium of communication. My name is Mr.Mandla Sizwe, I am the operational manager in account management section in charge of credit and foreign bills of one of the prime banks here in South Africa. I am writing in respect of a foreign customer of my bank who perished with his whole families on 18TH JULY 2003 in KENYAN PLANE CRASH with the whole passengers aboard. There is an account opened in this bank in the year 2000 by this great late INDUSTRIALIST who died without a written or oral 'WILL' attached to the account. Since his death, I personally have watched with keen interest to see the next of kin but all has proved abortive as no one has come to claim his funds and no other person knows about this account or anything concerning it,the account has no other beneficiary and until his death he was the manager of his company. The banking ethics here does not allow such money to stay more than six years without claim hence the money will be recalled to the government treasury as unclaimed after this long period of dormancy.I have secretly discussed this matter with the general manager of the bank who I must involve in order to have a smooth and a successful transfer of the fund to any foreign bank account which you are going to nominate.It can be an EMTY account. On this note, I decided to seek for a reliable foreigner who will act as the foreign beneficiary of the fund from the deceased by providing his/her bank account where the fund will be ransferred for immediate investment but my only worry is the security of the fund once the fund is transfered into your account.It is only a foreigner who can claim this money with legal claims to the account holder which I will provide to you if you are interested. This money will remain useless in this dormant account if I did not transfer the fund out to a foreign account.The total amount involved is $16,000,000.00 USD.[Sixteen Million United States Dollar]. We wish to start the first transfer with $6,000,000.00[Six million] and upon successful transaction without any disappointment from your side, we shall re-apply for the transfer of the remaining balance of &10 million to your account.At the conclussion of this transaction, your share will be 25% of the total transfer sum, 70% for me and my partner while 5% will be set aside for any expenses both parties might incure during the process of the transfer.If you are truly serious to do this business with me,and you know that you will never, ever betray me now or in the future let me know so that I will give you the full transaction details. Let me hear from you. Respectfully yours, Mr. Mandla Sizwe.

email:mkjn45@hotmail.com COMPLIMENTS OF THE DAY MA/SIR. I am JOHN MOKA the chief accountant of Amalgamated Bank of South Africa (ABSA). There is an account opened in this bank in 1999 and since 2001 nobody has operated on this account again. After going through some old files in the records, I discovered that if I do not remit this money out urgently it would be forfeited for nothing. The owner of this account is Mr. Morris Thompson, a foreigner, Business Man and a miner at Kruger Gold Company, a Geologist by profession and he died since 2000. Ever then no other person knows this account or anything concerning it, the account has no other beneficiary and my investigation proved to me as well that this company does not know anything about this account and the money involved is One hundred and Thirty Six Million United States Dollars (US$ 136 Million). I want us to first transfer US$ 36 Million from this money into your safe overseas account before the rest. I am only contacting you as a foreigner because this money cannot be approved to a local bank here, but can only be approved to any foreign account because the money is in United States Dollars and the former owner Mr. Morris Thompson is a foreigner too. I know that this message will come to you as surprise as we don’t know ourselves before. We will sign an agreement, but be sure that it is real and a genuine business. You can view the web site bellow for more information on our late client. http://archives.cnn.com/2000/US/02/01/alaska.airlines.list/ I only got your contact information from my secretary who operates computer; with believe in God that you will never let me down in this business, considering my position as a public servant. You are the only person that I have contacted in this business; so please reply urgently so that I will inform you the next step to take immediately. Send also your private telephone and fax numbers including the full details of your account to be used for the deposit. I want us to meet face-to-face and sign a binding agreement to bind us together so that you can receive this money into your account where the fund will be safe. And I will fly to your country for withdrawal and sharing and other investment. Meanwhile, I am contacting you because of the need to involve a foreigner with foreign account and foreign beneficiary. I need your full co-operation to make this work fine because the management is ready to approve this payment to any foreigner who has correct information of this account, which I will give to you as soon as you indicate your sincerity to co-operate with me, and capability to handle such amount in strict confidence and trust according to my instruction and advice for our mutual benefit because this opportunity may never come again in my life. I need a truthful and God fearing person in this business because I don’t want to make a mistake so I need your strong assurance and trust. With my position in the office I don’t want anything that will jeopardize my job so I advice that we should make secrecy and confidentiality our primary working condition, bearing in mind that I am a public servant. I will also use my position and influence to effect legal approvals and onward transfer of this money to your account with appropriate clearance forms of the ministries and foreign exchange department. At the conclusion of this business, you will be giving 25% of the total amount, 70% will be for me, while 5% will be for expenses both parties might have incurred the process of the transfer. I look forward to your earliest reply. Yours sincerely, JOHN MOKA CONFIDENTIAL _________________________________________________________________ Find just what you're after on your PC with Windows Desktop Search - FREE! http://desktop.msn.co.za/

Good Day Dear, From: Engr. George Egobia Telephone:+229 97 98 99 63. Due to your good nature with others,I want to propose a very interesting deal to you. I work with Deposit Trust House,a Security and Trust company in Republic of Benin,West Africa,as the operations manager. Actually,there is one very big customer of our company,he is an american by name Elijah Miller,he had $252,000,000.00(two hundred and fifty two million)united states dollars with our company and I was his representative in our company. Last three months he came and collected $2,000,000.00(two million dollars) cash and said if he arrives in his country he was going to send us his banking details,so that we can remit his remaining balance of $250,000,000.00.But I have not heard from him since then. Just three weeks ago his secretary that he came with to our company,called me and said Mr. Elijah had instructed her to send me the bank account were we are to remit the remaining $250million,because he (elijah) was sick.She sent me all the necessary confidential documents and said Elijah gave it to her,so there was nothing we could do but to start remittance of the fund bit by bit. But before we started remitting the money,I called Elijah's line and his wife picked up the phone and to my greatest surprise,she said Elijah had died in a car crash a month ago.That was when I understood that the secretary must have stolen all those documents from his office vault immediately he died and she is now claiming the funds on his behalf,but I kept quite so that I can also get my share. I have made a perfect plan with the remittance director,who is my only partner in this deal because of his position.We are crediting the account she sent with just $2.5million per week,with the excuse that the government will not allow more than that to go out per week.Which is a lie to slow down the remittance so that we can get someone to use in making claims also. What we want you to do now is to supply us your banking details so that we can credit your account as elijah's partner and you can take 25% of the total amount credited to your account and give us the rest as our share. Please consider this proposal quickly and reach me immediately with your answer,because time is not on our side. I am waiting, Yours Truly Engineer George Egobia. Private Email address:engr_george_egobia@o2.pl

Compliments of the day to you and your family. How are you? and your family? i do hope you all are fine? if so glory be to almighty. I got your e-mail on my search for investment research.Then i decided to contact you hoping that you will be right person to assist me and my mother on any profitable investment i want to do in your country. First and foremost,i apologized using this medium to reach you for a transaction/business of the magnitude;Let me introduce my self propersly.My name is Mr.Lanssana Kuyembeh,the son of chief Bankelo Kuyembeh. Iam the beneficiary/next of kin of the fund,i and my mother are living under(UNHCR) in Dakar Senegal as refugee.My late father(chief Bankelo Kuyembeh) was a business man,he deals on diamond and gold before his untimely death. He was killed by the rebels of(R.U.F) and many of our properties/buldings were destroyed by them.When my late father was alife he sensed of conspiracy against him and he escaped me and my mother to Dakar Senegal. And later go back to Sierra leone that is when he was killed;And that time the war was still going on in my country. When he was alife he deposited his money(us$7.2million dollars) with my name as his next of kin in a security company in Senegal.Presently,i want you to assist me transfer the money out from Senegal to your position so that you can help us to invest it and also to hel us aquire naturization statue in your country. Please if you are willing and intrested to assist us,i want you to stand as the beneficiary/receiver of the money on my behalf.And also you will assist us to transfer the money out from Senegal to your position pending on my arrival to meet with you. All the documents that my late father used to deposit the money is here with me and will send them to you on demand.I have the authority of my mother involved that should you be willing to assist us in the process of the transfer,your share of the sum will be 20% of the us$7.2 million. The transaction is 100% safe,on your part provided you treat it with utmost secrecy and confidentiality.Also your area of specialization is not a hinderance to the sucessful execution of this transaction. I have reposed my confidence in you and hope that you will not disappoint me. I am waiting for your response regard for the process. Thanks, Lanssana Kuyembeh.

Dear Friend, I am Mrs.Azura Amanda Akub. I came across your contact details in my desperate search for immediate assistance. I have just arrived at Cotonou, Bene Republic, thinking of how to settle/start life again because I am just having rest of mind now, since then. After fleeing renewed fighting In Sierra-Leone. Of the 2,030 of us who ran from the village, just 78 of Us made it across the boarder. I lost my husband and daughter during this flight And I am left with a son. There is a pain in my heart because I haven't See or heard peace in the last 10 years. Just bloodshed and sorrow. I Wonder if it will ever end. I seek your help in retrieving money belonging to my husband. My late Husband, DR.Ejiro Akub, was a devoted family man and a very successful Diamond /Gold trader in the region of Bo in Sierra-Leone. We were a happy Family of four (4) before the beginning of the civil war in 2000.We Were forced to seek refuge in the neighboring country of Benin Rep. while The war was going on, so we hid our life savings in the family tomb and Fled. We returned when we heard news of a peace treaty signed in 2003. We were deceived. The war escalated beyond imagination and it was Nothing but sorrow tears and blood the rebels left in its wake. I and My husband sold our remaining cache of Diamonds /Gold to a Lebanese Middle man and was paid cash for it. The funds were then shipped out of The country to Europe using the "Diamond /Gold trade Route”, which he was Very familiar with (it was how Sierra-Leone Diamonds and Gold ends up In capital cities of developed Nations). We then make plans to move and settle in Europe as we were tired of the bloodshed,but unfortunately it was Not to be. Our village was raided. It was during the operation no living thing embarked Upon by the Fonday Sankoh- Led Ruf rebel forces that I lost my husband And daughter. Now, I and my surviving son have been going through hell while the Funds are trapped with a security company in Europe. We lost our traveling Documents in our haste to escape the fighting and beside we do not have Any money on us. all We had was lost in the flight Out of the worst fighting areas. What we need now is an individual who Have compassion on the poor window of my type and come to her aid by Retrieving this funds from the security company by means of Claiming/clearing the consignment. This consignment contain the money for security reasons, The funds total at least US$ 38.5 million Dollars and GB# 7.82 million Pounds. This money is kept with the security company inform of Consignment for security reasons. nobody except me knows about this, I am Willing to offer you a commission for your assistance depending on what is Agreed upon by both of us. I will like to tell you that 10% ofeach said Amount goes for expenses. All you have to do is, send me your immediate response. All necessary Information’s and deposit certificate of the security company will be Send to you when due, and both (secret and answers to preset questions) And location of security company with this, you can claim the money, They’ve been directed to. If you will be able to assist, kindly let me know Immediately by replying me through my e-mail so we can begin procedures At once as my only son is critically ill. you are free to ask questions Where you don't understand. I eagerly await your favorable response. Best Regard, Mrs Azura Amanda Akub Email: azurabeh@hotmail.com

From:Mr.Kabir Bello. E-mail: Kabirbello02@she.com Tel:+66-1-4919460. Attention:The Managing Director Before I proceed, may I humbly introduce myself to your good self, My Name is Mr.Kabir Bello, an Iraqi refugee ,my Father was until recently, one of the personal aid to the president of Iraq who was formerly overthrown out of power during the War in My Country which took many life . Prior to this last serious crisis that is still ravaging in my country, which recently led to misfortune of our government and my late Father's position as the personal aid to the president, we were able to come over here in Thailand with my mother for investment ,we inherited the sum of US$16 Million. The funds were originally gotten from my late Father's proceeds. My late father was able to safe guard the fund with a very good diplomatic contact from my Country to Thailand which make us to come here to plan our life. But all is about life and death I witnessed another tragedy which could have taken my own life in Thailand here but I feel this is not the time, It started on 26th of December here in Phuket another disaster occurred here named( TSUNAMI) which as well took the life of my mother and up till now her body are yet to to be found, I am the only surviving person in my Family now. I have decided to contact you because I am interested in investing in your country . Please kindly guide and assist me in making the right investment as every thing regarding technical and logistics details is worked out and ascertained to our respective satisfaction. In view of your participation, I am ready to give you a good negotiable percentage for your assistance, or better still commit it into viable Joint venture projects, be assured that you stand no risk of any kind as the funds belong to me as the only surviving son. As soon as I get your consent, I will quickly move this fund to your country for investment . However, upon your acceptance to work as my partner, you can contact me with my private telephone number or e-mail for more details. I strongly believe that associating with you to embark on this and other business ventures will derive a huge success here after, please include you private contact telephone number and private e-mail when replying. Yours Sincerely. Mr.Kabir Bello.

Please reply to my private email address From: Mr Biney I Saac Private Email:wilsonjohn_biney2@she.com Attn:The Managing Director Am Mr. BINEY ISAAC I, I am in charge of Cargo section of ROCHASAB Security Banglamung Thailand. With due respect and regards I have decided to contact you on a business transaction that will be very beneficial to both of us of the end of the transaction. During our investigation and auditing in this security company my department came across a consignment belonging to a deceased person who died on plane crash with this security company without any claim of the consignment in our custody either form his family or relation before our discovery to this development. Although personally, I kept this information secret within myself and partner to enable the whole plans and ides be profitable and successful during the time if execution, the said amount was US$5.6M (FIVE Million SIX Hundred thousand United State Dollars). As it may be interest to you to know, I got your impressive information through my good friend who works with chamber of commerce here in Thailand. Mean while all the whole arrangement to put claim over this fund as the bonfire next of kin to the deceased, will be relayed to you as soon as you indicate your interest and willingness to assist us and also benefit yourself to this great deal. In fact I could have done this deal alone but because of my position in this country as a civil servant, we are not allowed to operate a foreign account and would eventually raise an eyebrow on my side during the time of transfer because I work in this company. This is the actual reason why it will require a second party or fellow who will forward claims as the next of kin with affidavit of trust of oath to the security company and also present a foreign account where he will need the money to be re-transferred into on his request as it may be after due verification and clarification by designation back account. I will not fail to inform you that this transaction is 100% risk free. On smooth conclusion of this transaction, you will be entitled to 30% of the total sum as gratification, while 10% we be set aside to take care of expenses that may arise during the fine of transfer and also telephone bills, while 60% will be for me and by partners. Please, you have been advised to keep top secret as we are still in service and intend to retire from service after we conclude this deal with you. I will write application to rinsing out have the company and join business. And it will require us to come down to your country for subsequent sharing of this found according to percentages previously indicated and further investment either in your country or any country you advice us to invest in. All other necessary information will be sent to you when I heard from you I suggest you get back to me as soon as possible stating your wish in this deal. <mailto:wilsonjohnbeney@yahoo.com> Yours faithfully, Mr. Biney Isaac.

FROM THE DESK OF DR .ABDULAHI BILL AND EXCHANGE MANAGER BANK OF AFRICA. OUAGADOUGOU,BURKINA FASO. TOP SECRET Dear Friend I am DR. ABDULAHI. the bill and exchange manager at the foreign remittance department of BANK OF AFRICA. I got your contact from the internet ,while seaching for an honest and trust worthy person, who will assist me to implement this transfer.l discovered the sum of Twenty Two Million and five hundred Thousand United States Dollars (USD22.5M) belonging to a deceased customer of this bank. The fund has been lying in a suspence account without anybody coming to put claim over the money since the account owner late Mr JOHN KOROVO from JORDAN , who was involved in the December 25th 2003 Benin plane crash. Here is the air crash website on cn http://www.cnn.com/2003/WORLD/africa/12/26/benin.crash/index.html The said fund is now ready for transfer to a foriegn account whose owner will be portrayed as the beneficiary and next of kin to the deceased customer of the bank. Since we got information about his death, we have been expecting his next of kin to come over and claim his money because we cannot release it unless somebody applies for it as next of kin or relation to the deceased as indicated in our banking guidlines and laws but unfortunately we learnt that all his supposed next of kin or relation died alongside with him at the plane crash leaving nobody behind for the claim. It is therefore upon this discovery that I decided to make this business proposal to you and release the money to you as the next of kin or relation to the deceased for safety and subsequent disbursement since nobody is coming for it and I don't want this money to go into the bank treasury as unclaimed bill. The banking law and guidline here stipulates that if such money remained unclaimed after five years, the money will be transfered into the bank treasury as unclaimed fund. The request of foreigner as next of kin in this business is occassioned by the fact that the customer was a foreigner and a Burkinabe cannot stand as next of kin to a foreigner. I therefore soliciting for your assistance to come forward as the next of kin. I have agreed that 40% of this money will be for you as the beneficiary in respect of the provision of your Account and services rendered, 55% would be for me while 5% will be for expencses incured during the cause of this transaction If the money is transferred to your Account from BANK OF AFRICA, I and my family in this transaction will proceed immediately to your country for our own share of the money. I expect you to keep this business strictly confidential and secret as you may wish to know that I am Bank official. Be rest assured that this business is 100% risk free on both side and every arrangement to transfer this money to the Account you are going to provide have been concluded provided we maintain the confidentiality and secreceirity involved. Contact me on my private phone number( +226-76419344 or email address at() I am looking forward for your prompt response. Yours faithfully, DR. ABDULAHI.

Greetings to you. From Richard Ohene, Before I introduce myself, I wish to inform you that this letter is not a hoax mail and I urge you to treat it with seriousness. This letter must come to you as a big surprise, but I believe it is only a day that people meet and become great friends and business partners. My name is Richard Ohene, the present branch Manager of a bank here in Ghana. I write you this proposal in good faith, believing that I can trust you with the information I am about to reveal to you. Like I said, I have a transaction that will benefit both of us, as your assistance is required as a foreigner. I use to head the Accounts department in my bank head office, but last December I was asked to take position of a Manager of our branch in Kumasi who passed on, so that was how I became the present Manager and discovered a fortune. As I resumed duty, I discovered an account with total sum of $12,500,000 million that has not been operated on for the past 4 years. From my investigation, I found out that this account belongs to one Late Mr. ANDREAS SCHRANNER a German great industrialist and a resident of Munich, who unfortunately lost his life along with his entire famillies in the plane crash of CONCORDE AIRLINE [Flight AF4590 ] which crashed on 25TH JULY, 2000. You shall read more news about the crash on visiting this site, which I got during my investigation; <http://news.bbc.co. uk/1/hi/world/europe/859479.stm>. The account is escrow call account, a secret type of account in my bank and no other person knows about this account or any thing concerning it, the account has no other beneficiary. I have kept a close monitoring of the account since then and nobody has come forward to ask about the money as next of kin to the late Mr. Andreas Schranner, meaning that no one is aware of the account. I cannot directly take out this money without the help of a foreigner and that is why I am contacting you for an assistance to claim the funds and share it with me. As the Manager of my bank branch, I have the power to influence the release of the funds to any foreigner that comes up as the next of kin to the account, with the correct information concerning the account, which I shall give you. I am seeking your co-operation to present you as the next of kin to the account, so that my bank head quarters will release the funds to you. There is practically no risk involved, the transaction will be executed under a legitimate arrangement that will protect you from any breach of law. Thanking you in advance and may God bless, Richard Ohene

Dear I salute you in the name of the most High! My name is Mrs. Rose Ameeraly. Am a widow and a mother of two girls. We do not know each other and I'm wondering how you will view this letter. Please, accept my sincere apology. Sorry, about taking your time as well. I will be highly obliged if you can assist me in this business. My Husband is an Nigerian while I am a Ghanaian. My late husband, David Ameeraly, was a loving, caring and hardworking businessman. Prior to his death by plane crash, he was living with us in Accra, Ghana. He died November 1st 1990. This sad event occurred during one of his business trips to the US. Please, find below the website for more information. If you go through this publication critically, you will find my husband's name, David Ameeraly amongst others that lost their life on that fateful day as published by British Broadcasting Corporation (BBC) http://news.bbc.co.uk/1/hi/world/americas/502503.stmB Before the sudden death of my beloved husband, he planned to establish a business in Europe with the sum of US$ 21.5 Dollars (Twenty One Million, five hundred thousand Dollars only). Unfortunately, he died before this venture could materialize. Following his death, his family members insisted that I am not entitled to his properties (assets and money). Since I am a woman and my offsprings are all girls coupled with the fact that I do not have a male child, I was put under terrible pressure to stay clear from my legitimate husband estates According to their family culture/traditional believe, a woman is not allowed to run late husband business and worst of all, I was asked to move into David's younger brother's household as one of his wives. My problem started when I refused to be inherited by David's younger brother. Fortunately, the proposed investment fund US$ 21.5 Dollars (Twenty One Million, five hundred thousand Dollars only). that was deposited with the investment/security company was unknown to the family. As such, they did not ask for this. If not, it would have been a problem as there would have been nothing to fall back on. It's only our lawyer & my humble self that know of this fund. I have discussed this matter with the Finance company were the fund was lodged. This is the asset I have left and I need part of this money for my daughters school fees and to maintain my personal life as well. David's family was vehemently against my daughters education. All they intend doing, was to give them out for marriage at a tender age. According to the staff of the finance company, the best way to secure this money is to transfer this money into an alternative bank account for safekeeping. Later it will be used for business investment which is subject to the advise of whoever that will be assisting us finally. For obvious reasons, I do not want the finance company's involvement. This transaction must be handled under strict confidentiality. At this juncture, I thought it wise to solicit your indispensable assistance to receiving this fund on my behalf. I do not have knowledge of funds management & business in general. I was a full-time housewife. Therefore, this step depends on your trust-worthiness & ability to handle funds of this magnitude. All that is required of you, is to forward to me by email, your direct phone, fax, address or any other information you may deem helpful. I need the requested information for the purpose of securing the relevant documents in your name as my confidante/ bona fide beneficiary. Please, note that this transaction is legitimate and 100% hitch-free. We will not violate any known law of my country and that of yours. So, be rest-assured. However, as soon as I receive your positive response to the above business transaction, I shall provide you with necessary transfer details. Note also, that you must convince me of your trust-worthiness and ability to keep secret. I have decided to compensate you with 30% of the total money as a reward for your sincere assistance and the remaining 70% will be used to pursue my late husband's investment dream in real estate. Thanking you for your anticipated response as I look forward to hearing from you. I remain. Sincerely yours, Mrs.Rose David Ameeraly

ABN AMRO Bank Address: 101 Moorgate, London, EC2M 6SB. U.K. Dear Friend, I am Mr Mark Boland the Bank Manager of ABN AMRO Bank 101 Moorgate, London, EC2M 6SB. I have urgent and very confidential business proposition for you. On JULY 20,1999,Mr Paul Ndeife,a National of France, who used to be a private contractor with the Shell Petroleum Development Company in Saudi Arabia Mr.Paul Ndeife.Made a numbered time (Fixed deposit) for 36 calendar months, valued at GBP17,000,000.00 (Seventeen Million Pounds only) in my branch. Upon maturity in 2002, I sent a routine notification to his forwarding address but got no reply.After a month, we sent a reminder and finally we discovered from his contract employers, Shell Petroleum Development Company in Saudi Arabia that Mr Paul Ndeife And his wife with their three children were involved in an auto crash,all occupants of the vehicle unfortunately lost their lives. During one of his trips to his country France. On further investigation, I found out that he died without making a WILL, and all attempts to trace his next of kin was fruitless. I therefore made further investigation and discovered that Mr Paul Ndeife. did not declare any kin or relations in all his official documents, including his Bank Deposit paperwork in my Bank. This sum of GBP£17.000,000.00 have been floating as unclaimed since 1999 in my bank as all efforts to get his relatives have hit the stones. According to the British law at the expiration of 5 (FIVE) years, the money will revert to the ownership of the British Government if nobody applies to claim the fund and the FIVE years is the end of June 2006.Since then, I have made several enquiries with his country's embassies to locate any of my clients extended relatives, this has also proved Unsuccessful. After these several unsuccessful attempts, I decided to Contact you with this business partnership proposal. I have contacted you to assist in repatriating a huge amount of money left behind by my client before they get confiscated or declared unserviceable by the Finance/Security Company where these huge deposit was lodged. The deceased had a deposit valued presently at $21million US Dollars and the Company has issued me a notice to provide his next of kin or Beneficiary by Will otherwise have the account confiscated within the next thirty official working days. Since I have been unsuccessful in locating the relatives for over 2 years now, I seek your consent to present you as the next of kin / Will Beneficiary to the deceased so that the proceeds of this account valued at $21Million US dollars can be paid to you. This will be disbursed or shared in these percentages, 60% to me and 40% to you. I have all necessary legal documents that can be used to back up any claim we may make. All I require is your honest Co-operation, Confidentiality and Trust to enable us see this transaction through.I guarantee you that this will be executed under a legitimate arrangement that will protect you from any breach of the law. Please get in touch with me urgently by E-mail. markboland1990@yahoo.co.uk I am presently in London and provide me the following; 1. Full Name 2. Your Telephone Number and Fax Number 3. Your Contact Address. Your urgent response will be highly anticipated and appreciated. Best regards, Mr Mark Boland +44 7040131493

Greetings to you, This letter must come to you as a big surprise, but I believe it is only a day that people meet and become great friends and business partners. My name is William Ansah, the present branch Manager of a bank here in Ghana. Like I said, I have a transaction that will benefit both of us, as your assistance is required as a foreigner. I use to head the Accounts department in my bank head office, but last December I was asked to take position of a Manager of our branch in Kumasi who passed on, so that was how I became the present Manager and discovered a fortune. As I resumed duty, I discovered an account with total sum of $12,500,000 million that has not been operated on for the past 4 years. From my investigation, I found out that this account belongs to one Late Mr. ANDREAS SCHRANNER a German great industrialist and a resident of Munich, who unfortunately lost his life along with his entire famillies in the plane crash of CONCORDE AIRLINE [Flight AF4590 ] which crashed on 25TH JULY, 2000. You shall read more news about the crash on visiting this site, which I got during my investigation; http://news.bbc.co. uk/1/hi/world/europe/859479.stm. The account is escrow call account, a secret type of account in my bank and no other person knows about this account or any thing concerning it, the account has no other beneficiary. I have kept a close monitoring of the account since then and nobody has come forward to ask about the money as next of kin to the late Mr. Andreas Schranner, meaning that no one is aware of the account. As the Manager of my bank branch, I have the power to influence the release of the funds to any foreigner that comes up as the next of kin to the account, with the correct information concerning the account, which I shall give you. Contact me as soon as you receive this message if you feel we can work together, so we can go over the details. Please, treat with utmost confidentiality. You may call me through my personal number +233243510543. Regards, William Ansah.

Dear Sir, With a very desperate need for assistance, I have summed up courage to contact you. I am from (will disclose this later), presently working in Iraq with an international organisation that I will also disclose later, I found your contact particulars in an address journal. I am seeking your assistance to evacuate the sum of (US$8.523 Million Dollars) Eight Million five Hundred Thousand And Twenty Three Dollars to your country or any other safe country of your choice, as far as I can be assured that my share will be safe in your care untill I complete my service here,this is no stolen money, and there are no dangers involved. SOURCE OF MONEY: Some money in various currencies was discovered concealed in barrels with piles of weapons and ammunitions at a location near one of Saddam,s old palaces during a rescue operation, and it was agreed by all party present that the money be shared amongst us, this was quite an illegal thing to do, but I tell you what? no compensation can make up for the risks we have taken with our lives in this hell hole. The above figure was given to me as my share, and to conceal this kind of money became a problem for me, so with the help of a German contact working here, and his office enjoys some immunity, I was able to get the package out to a safe cation entirely out of trouble spot. He does not know the real contents of the package, and believes that it belongs to an Asian/American who died in an air raid, and before giving up, trusted me to hand over the package to his business associate. I have now found a secured way of getting the package out to a safer country for you to pick up, and will discuss this with you when I am sure that you are willing to assist me. One passionate appeal I will make to you is not to discuss this matter with a third party, should you have reasons to reject this offer, please destroy this mail as any leakage of this information will be too bad for us. I do not know for how long we will remain here, and I have survived 2 suicide bomb attacks by the special grace of God, this and other reasons I will mention later has prompted me to reach out for help, I honestly want this matter to be resolved immediately. Please contact me as soon as possible. Regards, Robert Taylor _________________________________________________________________ Express yourself instantly with MSN Messenger! Download today it's FREE! http://messenger.msn.click-url.com/go/onm00200471ave/direct/01/

Kindest Attention: Dear Sir/Ma, My name is Mr.Gat Butu I am from South African, I have been diagnosed with Esophageal cancer. It has defiled all forms of medical treatment, and right now I have only about a few months to live, according to medical experts. I have not particularly lived my life so well, as I never really cared for anyone (not even myself)but my business. Though I am very rich, I was never generous, I was always hostile to people and only focused on my business as that was the only thing I cared for.But now I regret all this as I now know that there is more to life than just wanting to have or make all the money in the world. I believe when God gives me a second chance to come to this world I would live my life a different way from how I have lived it. Now that God has called me, I have willed and given most of my property and assets to my immediate and extended family members as well as few close friends .I want God to be merciful to me and accept my soul so, I have decided to give alms to charity organizations, as I want this to be one of the last good deeds I do on earth. So far, I have Distributed money to some charity organizations in the U.A.E, Somalia and Malaysia. Now that my health has deteriorated so badly, I cannot do this myself anymore. I once asked members of my family to close one of my accounts and distribute the money which I have there to charity organization in Bulgaria and Pakistan, they refused and kept the money to themselves. Hence, I do not trust them anymore, as they seem not to be contended with what I have left for them. The last of my money which no one knows of is the huge cash deposit of Thirty Million United States Dollars ($30,000,000,00) that I have with a Finance Vaulting Unit Abroad. I will want you to help me collect this deposit and dispatch it to charity organizations. N/B: Kindly note that 35% of this funds must go to the tsunami victims,60% to other Charity Organization and 5% for your effort and time. I cannot talk with you on the phone due to my health situation, as I am using my Lap Top Computer to communicate with you. You should respond to (gat_butu111@myway.com) if you are interested in carrying out this assignment on my behalf. God be with you. Mr. Gat Butu. Email:gat_butu111@myway.com

Dear sir, May the blessing of God be upon you and grant you the wisdom and sympathy to understand our situation and how much we need your help. My name is Aida Kamara from Sierra-Leone, the only surviving daughter of Mr. Siaka Kamara Former Personal Assistance to the present Minister for Mines and Natural Resources in-charge of the diamond production sales in my country Sierra-Leone. Unfortunately some months ago before the peace pact in my country, my father and his colleagues were killed by rebel group of Mr. Foday Sankoh during an inspection visit to the rich diamond mining area in the village of Izumba, were the rebels laid an ambush and open fire on the convoy killing my father and some of his colleagues who were on their way to the diamond mining zone. Following the peace pact that was introduce by the united nation keeping force some months back,my mother deem to say that it is right time for us to leave the country for safety and for europe or any other stable economic bloc with the $ 12.5.million dollars deposited by my late father in a finance company here in Dakar-Senegal on my name as the next of kin or beneficiary.(the Deposit Certificate of this funds are with us now and will be faxed to you upon request). I contacted you based on you are a trustworthy person after i got your contact from a profile that speaks very good of you in the internet.I want you to assist us so that we can transfer this money to your position for safe keeping pending our arrival to your country, to start up an investment in your country through your wise advice. You will act as our international business representative and also our family business associate,so that the finance company will transfer this money to your position for safe keeping. me and my mother are now in Dakar-Senegal for the facilitation of this transaction.Please kindly communicate your acceptance or otherwise of this proposal through my e.mail address for us to discuss the modalities of seeing this transaction through.However, if you are not disposed to assist us kindly destroy the letter in view of the families interest and personal security. We count on you greatly for your assistance.Please,if where i contacted you is not okay with you,do not hestiate to tell me and provide another address where i will be contacting you.A good percentage awaits you for your assistance. Expecting to hear from you soon. Yours Faithfully, Aida Kamara.

Salam , Je vous avoue que cela me ferait plaisir de lier plus qu'une amitié avec vous et du fond du coeur je souhaiterais sincèrement vous rencontrer et vous connaitre davantage. Mais avant, je tiens à me présenter à vous. Je me nommes FEDDAG Safia ,je suis de nationalité Algérienne et je vis en Irak . je suis dans ce pays depuis plus de 13 ans et j'était au service de monsieur Nizar Hamboum . J'avais pour rôle de veiller sur le bon fonctionnement de la résidence à Moussoul et à m'occuper de tout ce qui est comme factures et charges a régler . J'étais en quelque sorte le majordome et j'avais connaissance de plusieurs chosesque mon maître faisait et à quoi il était exposé. Monsieur Nizar avait occupé plusieurs postes importants dans le pays et le monde entier. Il fut de 1993 à 1999, ambassadeur des nations unis a New York ;ministre des affaires étrangères et aussi député dans son pays. Il a été un membre influant dans la médiation des relations entre les Etats Unis et l'Irak dans les années 1980 . Il trouva la mort le vendredi 5juillet 2003 à New York au centre commémoratif de cancer de Sloan-Kettering des suite d'une crise cardiaque. Mon maître m'avait demandé de suivre le dépôt dans une société de surveillance et de conservation de biens privés, d'un colis c'est a dire une mallette qui contenait la somme de 17.500.000 dollars $ (dix sept millions cinq centmilles dollars méricains).Il m'avait demandé d'effectuer ce dépôt à mon nom et lui en faire le rapport car il souhaitait une discrétion et la sécurité pour son bien . Il m'a demandé de codifié le colis comme étant un bien familial pour les raisons de sécurité de ce fond et pour éviter des problèmes avec le gouvernement .Même la société n'est pas informée du contenu du colis car le colis a été codé comme un bien familial et donc privé. Avant que la guerre n'éclate , mon maître m'a demandé de prendre immédiatement contact avec la société afin de faire sortir le colis du pays car cette somme était destinée pour des investissements a l'étranger . Il souhaitait construire un hôtel en Arabie Saoudite . C'est après des renseignements auprès de la société qu'ils m'ont fait savoir qu'ils pouvaient faire mettre le colis dans un autre lieu mais cela se fera en Afrique ou se trouve leur base plus précisément en Cote d'ivoire. J'ai remercié DIEU car pour moi cela était mieux et ce pays n'est pas très loin de mon pays l'Algérie et surtout il est en Afrique. Je viens vers vous pour solliciter votre aide afin de m'aider à retirer cette mallette de ce pays et de m'aider à quitter l'Irak pour votre pays. Je voudrais que vous sachez que ce que je fais n'est connu de personne ni même de sa famille car longtemps j'ai été a leur service et sous ce règne barbare qu'offre ce pays et je n'ai rien eu comme garantie pour la vie et je suis fatigué de vivre en esclave toute ma vie .Comme DIEU ne dort pas il a permit que ce bien soit en ma possession et que je sois la seul qui soit informer de son existence . Je voudrais que vous sachiez que l'aide que vous m'apporterez ne sera pas vain car j'ai prévu que pour votre aide vous recevrez 25% de la somme totale 17.500.000 $).Je détiens toutes les informations et les documents de l'existence de ce bien . Je voudrais que vous me fassiez savoir si vous souhaitez me venir en aide afin que je vous communiques les informations sur ce bien et la société qui a la garde afin que vous entrez en contact avec eux pour qu'ils vous fassent parvenir le colis. Je voudrais que vous sachiez que c'est une société diplomatique et en leur donnant une adresse sûr ils vous livrerons le colis . Sachez que le certificat de dépôt ne porte pas de nom du bénéficiaire et qu'il sera facile pour vous de retirer ce colis car il suffira que vous vous présentez comme le bénéficiaire de ce colis. Je voudrais que tout ce que je vous ai dis restes secret afin degarantir ma sécurité et la sécurité de ce bien . Je n'ai aucune source de communications que l'ordinateur portable que j'ai dans la chambre donc je m'y contente. Pour plus de sécurité et de discrétion je souhaiterais que vous me comprenez. Merci de votre comprehension. contacter moia mon adresse personelle :safeddag300@yahoo.fr FEDDAG Safia

Dear Sir/Madam Compliment of the day to you . I got your contact through business search from the internet. I am Mr.Mustapha Momodu, Account Manager of Standard Chartered Bank Kanashie Branch . I have urgent and very confidential business proposition for you. On December 29th 2002, an American contractor with the Government of Ghana, Mr. Michael Creek made a numbered time (Fixed) deposited for twelve calendar months, valued at TWENTY TWO Million,Four hundred thousand dollars ($22.4million) in my branch. Upon maturity, I sent a routine notification to his forwarding address but got no reply. After a month, we sent a reminder and finally we discovered from his contract employers, that Mr. Michael Creek died from an automobile accident. On further investigation, I found out that he did not leave a WILL and all attempts to trace his next of kin were fruitless. I therefore made further investigation and discovered that Mr. Michael Creek did not declare any next of kin in all his official documents, including his Bank Deposit paperwork. This sum of $22.4million is still sitting in Standard Chartered Bank and the interest is being rolled over with the principal sum at the end of each year. No one will come forward to claim it. According to the laws of the country, at the expiration of 5 (five) years, the money will revert to the ownership of the Government if nobody applies to claim the funds. Consequently, my proposal is that I will like you to assist me fully as foreigner to stand in as the next of kin to Mr. Michael creek, so that the fruits of this old man's labour will not get into the hands of some corrupt officials. This is simple, I will like you to provide me immediately with your full names and address so that the attorney will prepare the necessary documents and affidavites, which will put you in place as the next of kin. We shall employ the services of two attorneys for drafting and notarization of the WILL and obtain the necessary documents and letter of probate/administration in your favor for the transfer. A bank account in any part of the world, which you will provide, will then facilitate the transfer of this money to you as the beneficiary/next of kin. The money will be paid into your account for us to share in the ratio of 60% for me and 30% for you while 10% will be set aside for miscellaneous expenses. There is no risk involved in this transaction, as every necessary paperwork for this fund, will be done and my position as the Branch Manager guarantees the successful execution of this transaction. Hope this mail will meet your perfect understanding. Best Regards. Mr.Mustapha Momodu P/S:You can contact me also via my private email at mr_mustapha_stb@yahoo.com

Dear Friend. Good day and God bless you. I feel quite safe and satisfy dealing with you in this charity project.Though, this medium (Internet) has been greatly abused, I choose to reach you through it because it still remains the fastest, surest and most secured medium of communication. However, this correspondence is purely private, and it should be treated as such. As you read this, I don't want you to feel sorry for me, because, I believe everyone will die someday. My name is MR.HARRY HILAL,in the region of U.A.E. I have been diagnosed with Esophageal cancer . It has defiled all forms of medical treatment, and right now I have only about a few months to live, according to medical experts. I have not particularly lived my life so well, as I never really cared for anyone(not even myself)but my business. Though I am very rich, I was never generous, I was always hostile to people and only focused on my business as that was the only thing I cared for. But now I regret all this as I now know that there is more to life than just wanting to have or make all the money in the world. I believe when God gives me a second chance to come to this world I would live my life a different way from how I have lived it. Now that God has called me, I have willed and given most of my property and assets to my immediate and extended family members as well as a few close friends. I want God to be merciful to me and accept my soul so, I have decided to give alms to charity organizations, as I want this to be one of the last good deeds I do on earth. So far, I have distributed money to some charity organizations in the U.A.E, Algeria and Malaysia. Now that my health has deteriorated so badly, I cannot do this myself anymore. I once asked members of my family to close one of my accounts and distribute the money which I have there to charity organization in Bulgaria and Pakistan, they refused and kept the money to themselves. Hence, I do not trust them anymore, as they seem not to be contended with what I have left for them. The last of my money which no one knows of is the huge cash deposit of TWELVE MILLION DOLLARS $12,000,000,that I have with a finance/Security Company abroad. I will want you to help me collect this deposit and dispatched it to charity organizations. I have set aside 25% for you and for your time if you want to help me to collect this Funds and also invest this money. N.B-PLEASE I WILL ADVICE YOU TO GIVE THE LAWYER IN CHARGE A CALL IN HOLLAND IMMEDIATELY, HE DOES EVERYTHING ON MY BEHALF AND HE'S VERY UNDERSTANDING AND I BELIEVE HE WILL LEAD YOU TO YOUR SUCCESS IN JESUS NAME AMEN. Name: BARRISTER.BILLY PARKER Tel number: 0031633795463 Email: billybonparker02@netscape.net Remain blessed in the name of the Lord. Yours in Christ, Mr.Harry HILAL

Please always be in contact with me through this alternative email address at [nandodaniel111@yahoo.it]because of security reasons. Dear Friend, I am Dr.Daniel Nando presently i am practising with a private hospital here in Ivory Coast W/Africa, And you don,t worry because I got your contact through a chamber of commerce and will like to explain to you about a transaction which I hope you can assist which will benefit both of us. I have a patient, a Sierra Leonia woman who was on admission for some weeks in my hospital for a complicated ill health as the result but her recovery have been eventful. As a matter of fact, one night this woman called my attention and began to tell me her circumstances that she and his only son was refugee here,and that her late husband a militry officer died in a rebel conflict in his country,And that the immediate brother to her late husband was threaten to eliminate the life of her only son because of the matter of certificate of deposit and she could not bear it and manage to escaped through a neighburig country with the certificate of deposite of some (1) trunk box deposited in the security company decleared as family valuable which was traced in Ivory Coast W/Africa that she has confided in me to reveal this secrect to me because of the help i have given to her and her son. That the content of the consigenment was physical cash of $15. million(USD)and why he did this is because the militry body have once trailed the account of her late husband, at this stage She have decided to leave this country because of political crisis and requested me to seek an honest foreigner who will assist in the transffering the money out for investiment of her son, i have accepted and requested for a proof and she provid the documents of the deposit which was clear and legitimate, and was in my poccession the documents. Though i have given her the medical & humanitarian help as i could based on the ethics of my proffesion. Therefore, i have consider to assist her and to contact a genuine person who can also consider to help as well showing that an international brotherhood is reality towards this madam and her son. She also promise to intimate us with 10% of the total amount of the money and i hope if you can understand the request and the assistance which i hope you can respond positivey. In the meantime,i hope to hearing from you soon.please call me on this number 0022507483378 so that we can talk. Your sincerely, Dr.Daniel Nando _________________________________________________________________ http://desktop.msn.fr/

John William 61 Fann Residence Dakar Senegal E-mail:johw75@yahoo.com <mailto:johw75@yahoo.com> Attention: The President/CEO. I am Dr John William, Bank Manager in one of the leading banks here in Dakar Senegal. I have an urgent and very confidential business proposition for you. A contract employers- Teaser Petroleum Corporation made a numbered time Deposit for twelve calendar months, valued at US$27,000,000.00 (Twenty seven Million Dollars) in my bank. Upon maturity, I sent a routine notification to his forwarding address but got no reply. After a month, we sent a reminder and finally discovered from his contract employers, Teaser Petroleum Corporation that MR. ANDREAS SCHRANNER from Munich Germany died in a plane crash along with his entire family in July 2000.PLEASE TAKE A CAREFULL LOOK AT THE BBC PUBLISHED Monday, 31 July, 2000, 13:22 GMT 14:22 UK:http://news.bbc.co.uk/1/hi/world/europe/859479.stm Since we got this information about his death and on further investigation, I found out that he died without making a WILL, and all attempts to trace his next of kin was fruitless. I therefore made further investigated and discovered that Mr. Andreas Schranner did not declare any kin or relations in all his official documents, including his Bank Deposit paperwork in my Bank. This sum of US$27,000,000.00 is still sitting in my Bank and the interest is being rolled over with the principal sum at the end of each year. No one will ever come forward to claim it. According to Laws of Senegal, at the expiration of 5 (five) years, the money will revert to the ownership of the Senegalese Government if nobody applies to claim the fund. Consequently, my proposal is that I will like you as a foreigner to stand in as the next of kin to Mr. Andreas Schranner so that the fruits of this old man's labour will not get into the hands of some corrupt governme! nt officials. This is simple, I will like you to provide immediately your full names and address so that I will place every necessary information about you in the late account owner’s file and our computer data base as his next of kin entitled to inherit his deposited fund. We shall employ the services of an attorney for drafting and notarization of the WILL and to obtain the necessary documents and letter of probate/administration in your favour for the transfer. A bank account in any part of the world that you will provide will then facilitate the transfer of this money to you as the beneficiary/next of kin. The money will be paid into your account for us to share in the ratio of 50% for me and 30% for you. The remaining 20% will be for any expenses we might incurred during the course of the transaction. There is no risk at all as all the paperwork for this transaction will be done by the attorney and my position as the Branch Manager guarantees the su! ccessful execution of this transaction. If you are interested, ple ase reply immediately via the private email address above. Upon your response, I shall then provide you with more details and relevant documents that will help you understand the transaction. Please send me your confidential telephone and fax numbers for easy communication. Please observe utmost confidentiality, and rest assured that this transaction would be most profitable for both of us because I shall require your assistance to invest my share in your country. Awaiting your urgent reply via my confidential email address. johw75@yahoo.com <mailto:johw75@yahoo.com> Regards, DrJohn William.

Westpac Banking Corporation, 63 St. Mary Axe London EC3A 8LE I am Mr.kelly wood ,Department of Foreign Operations, Westpac Banking Corporation London,an affiliate of Global Funds Management. On January 6th 2001, one Mr. Joseph Huber, an American National,a consultant/contractor with Gardiner & Theobald,a leading firm of project and cost management consultants, made a numbered time (Fixed) Deposit, valued at ?6,500,000.00 (Twenty-six Million, Five Hundred Thousand Pounds) for twelve calender months in my Bank Branch.Upon Maturity, we sent a routine notification to his forwarding address but got no reply. After a month, we sent a reminder and finally we discovered from his contract employers (Gardiner & Theobald) that Mr. Joseph Huber was aboard the, American Airlines Flight 587 which crashed into a residential area near John F. Kennedy International Airport on November 12,2001.www.cnn.com/2001/US/11/12/newyork.crash/ After investigation, it was discovered that he died without making a WILL and all attempts to trace his next of kin proved fruitless. On further investigation, it was discovered that Late Mr.Joseph Huber did not declare any next of kin or relations in all his official documents, including his Bank Deposit paper work here at the Bank. The total sum, ?6,500,000.00 is still in my bank and the interest is being rolled over with the principal sum at the end of each year. No one will ever come forward to claim it. In accordance with the Federal banking Laws and constitution,the money will revert to the ownership of the Government if nobody applies as the next of Kin to claim the funds. Consequently, I shall present you as a foreign partner to stand in as the next of kin to late Mr. Joseph Huber so that you and I can benefit from the fruits of this man's labour. Upon acceptance of this proposal, I shall give detailed information on how this deal would be carried out.We shall employ the services of a solicitor for the drafting of the LAST WILL & TESTAMENT of Late Mr.Joseph Huber and to obtainallother relevant papers in your name for the necessary documentation for payment approval in my bank headquarters in your favour. The money will be shared in the ratio:Sixty percent for me, thirty five percent for you and five percent for any arising contigencies during the course of this transaction. I guarantee that this will be executed under legitimate arrangement that will protect you from any breach of the law as I will use my position in the bank to secure approvals and guarantee the successful execution of this transaction. Please be informed that your utmost confidentiality is required. If this interests you, please reply me immediately via the private email address kelly_wood7@excite.com <mailto:kelly_wood7@excite.com> and please include your private telephone number for voice contact and fax number so I can provide you with more details and relevant documents that will help you understand the transaction. Awaiting your urgent reply. Thanks. Best regards, Wood.

My Dear, I contact you in such a surprising manner,but i respectfully insist that you read this mail carefully as i am optimistic that it will open DOORS forunimaginable financial reward for both of us. It is my pleasure to introduce to you a business that will make the beginning of never-ending family relationship. I hope that this proposal will not be an inconvenience or embarrassment to you. I must not hesitate to confide in you this simple and sincere request business for our mutual benefit.I am Mrs FLORENCE ACHIAH RUSANGANWA, the only Daughter of late Mr.Steve Achiah Rusanganwa{Snr}, a BEJA TRIBE MEMBER of EASTERN SUDAN in Republic of SUDAN. I am 25 years of age. My father was a prosperous coffee and tin ore merchant in KHARTOUM, capital of the Republic of SUDAN before his untimely death. After his business trip to Abidjan - Cote d'Ivoire, to negotiate on a Coffee and tin ore business he wanted to invest in Abidjan ? Cote d'Ivoire. A week after he came back from Abidjan, he was attacked with my mother by unknown assassins suspected to be Darfurian Rebels under the Sudan Liberation Army/Movement (SLA/M) and the Justice and Equality Movement(JEM) who were demanding an end to alleged economic marginalisation and sought power-sharing within the Sudanese state believed that my father has been given financial support to Beja Militia Rebels. After my parents death,i was aided by our church pastor,a good friend of my father through Chadian capital, N'Djamena to escape to ACCRA-GHANA. But before my father gave up the ghost, it was as if he knew he was going to die,He disclosed to me that he deposited the sum of USD$18,500,000 (Eighteen Million,Five Hundred Thousand United States Dollars Only) in cash concealed in (2)two trunk boxes and deposited it with a private security house here in Accra Ghana which he declared and register as FAMILY VALUABLES, because of political problems here and there. My late Father signed an agreement that the consignment should only be released to a foreign trustee of my choice or release it to me when i will become 29years old. So I want you to please assist me stand as my nominated foreign trustee and claim the boxes from the security company The money was meant for the importation of machineries for his coffee processing plant for a company which he wanted to establish in Abidjan ? Cote d'Ivoire. Unfortunately he did not live to achieve it before he was gunneddown.But since I have no experience or interest in this type of business,i am seeking a reliable and trust worthy business partner who will assist me to secure,claim-out and transfer this funds abroad strictly for investment purposes and for guidance. Now I am soliciting for your assistance to help me to claim-out and transfer these 2 trunk boxes to your destination or abode, holding on my behalf and aid me to leave Accra-GHANA. When I join you, we can then invest jointly in any meaningful lucrative business in your country because this is my only hope in life. You shall be entitled to a significant portion of the fund which will be deliberated upon your acceptance to this offer. Waiting anxiously to hear from you so that we can discuss the modalities of this transaction. Only three options is waiting to effect this huge fund business. (1)You have to come down here and confidently acompany it to your country. (2)You have to volunteer any means of delivery to air lift it to your door step. (3)You have to use your influence and white-personality to claim it out and moved it to the bank for transfer to your designated account. Please i will like you to answer me this questions. (1)Can a black lady build house in your country and invest there? (2)Can a black lady be given staying permit and be allowed to visit sight seen? (3)Can i direct any company of my own? Thanks for your kindness and get back to me with the indication of your interest to help me. Yours sincerely, Ms Florence Achiah Rusanganwa. Note:You answer me through my alternative email address(flo_achiah2006@yahoo.co.uk)

MR.DAVID SMITH DAKAR SENEGAL Please, Reply to:maildavid_smith@excite.com I am MR.David Smith. I am an employee of a commercial Bank here in the Dakar-Senegal; I am the personnel account officer of Late Mr. Paul Reynold who was a National of asia before his untimely death with his wife. They had no children. On Tuesday, Nov. 30, 2004 our customer and his wife died on board on PLANE CRASH in Indonesia (Indonesia Airline Flight JT583).The plane crash was in the news. See link below for more detail information: http://www.chinadaily.com.cn/english/doc/2004-11/30/content_396081.htm Since then no body has come forward to claim his funds and our bank AUTHORITIES are making serious arrangement to confiscate his money. In order to avert this negative development, I now seek your permission to have you stand as a RELATIVE to the deceased and equally act as his next-of-kin The account is valued at US$18.5 million Dollars will be paid into your nominated bank account before our bank authorities confiscated or declared his bank account unserviceable and this will happen if no body comes forward to claim the money. I am assuring you that this transaction will be executed under legitimate arrangement that will protect you from any breach of the law. Please, do not hesitate to put up your utmost effort in handling this transaction to the highest level of business. I have reposed higher confidence in your ability to handle this matter perfectly and confidentially. Also, your telephone number will be highly required to enable us communicate with each other on daily basis. I want you to understand that your involvement in this matter is to maintain absolute secrecy and keep the spirit of teamwork; you do not have to disclose the nature of this transaction to anybody for security reasons. I am serious minded person and I mean business. The funds will be shared to us, after it has been transferred into your bank account. 1. 60% of the money will go to you for acting as the next-of-kin 2. 40% to me as the originator of the transaction. Please indicate your interest to the above email address interest and to let you know the next step of action towards the success of this transaction. Best regards, MR. DAVID SMITH The information in this letter is confidential, please, if you are not interested destroy this message, You should not retain copy or use this letter for any purpose, nor disclose all or any part of its content to any other person. NB ALTERNATIVE E-MAIL ADDRESSE IS;maildavid_smith@excite.com

DEAN GRAY CALLE SEVILLA 112, 28001,MADRID- SPAIN TELL:+34 639 446 879 PRIVATE E-MAIL:deangray@lycos.es PROPOSITION: Dear Sir/Madam, I am Mr.Dean Gray, the Auditor General of a reputable bank in Spain , during the course of our auditing I discovered a floating fund in an account opened in the bank in 1990 and since 1991 till date nobody has operated on this account again, after going through some old files in the records I discovered an abandoned deposit in my bank by one of our foreign customers who died along with his entire family as a result of an automobile crash. He actually made a numbered time (fixed)deposit valued at US$112,000,000.00 (One Hundred and Twelve million united states dollars),for twelve calendar months in my bank.The funds was actually meant for a project our late client wanted to start in the near future (a multi million Dollar steel plant in Canada), I sent a routine notification to his forwarding address but got no reply. After a month, I sent a reminder and finally we discovered that Mr.Cosban died from an automobile accident with his entire family .On further investigation, I found out that he died without making a Will, and all attempts to trace his next of kin was fruitless. I therefore made further investigation and discovered that Mr. Cosban did not declare any next of kin or relations in all his official documents,including his Bank Deposit paperwork in our Bank. Upon this discovery, I now seek your permission to have you stand as a next of kin to the deceased as all documentations will be carefully worked out by me for the funds to be released in your favour as the beneficiary's next of kin. Please acknowledge receipt of this message in acceptance of our mutual business endeavor by furnishing me with the following information's; 1. FULL NAMES AND ADDRESS: 2. DIRECT TELEPHONE NUMBER AND FAX NUMBERS: 3. OCCUPATION AND POSITION: 4. NATIONALITY 5. MARITAL STATUS: 6. AGE /SEX: These requirements will enable me file letter of claim to the appropriate departments for necessary approvals in your favour before i could proceed on the transfer of the funds to the designated account of your choice. I shall be compensating you with 35% of the total money while 65% will be mine on final conclusion of this project If this proposal is acceptable by you, do not take undue advantage of the trust I have bestowed in you, I await your urgent mail. Please reply to my private and confidential email: deangray@lycos.es Best Regards, Mr. Dean Gray

FROM THE DESK OF MR. IBRAHIM WATA BILL AND EXCHANGE MANAGER, BANK OF AFRICA (BOA). OUAGADOUGOU, BURKINA FASO. Alternative e-mail : mr_ibrahim_wata1@latinmail.com Dear Sir/Madam I know that this letter may come to you as a surprise but due to the urgency of this transaction.First I must solicit your confidence in this transaction, this is by virtue of it's nature as being utterly confidential and top secret. Though I know that a transaction of this magnitude will make any one apprehensive and worried, but I am assuring you that all will be well at the end of the day. There is no doubt that trust conceptually is a conundrum which leadsitself to deferring interpretation, we have decided to contact you due to the urgency of this transaction. I am the manager of bill and exchange at the foreign remittance department of BANK OF AFRICA(BOA). I came to know you in my private search for a reliable and reputable person to handle this Confidential Transaction, which involves thetransfer of a huge sum of money to a foreign account requiring maximum confidence. I am writing to you, following the impressive information received about you from the chambers of commerce. I believed that you are capable and reliable to champion this business opportunity. In my department we discovered an abandoned sum of $30m US dollars (Thirty million US dollars). In an account that belongs to one of our foreign customer who died along with his entire family On August 23, 2000 through Gulf Air Flight 72 with Airbus A320 crashed off, killing all 143 people on board and you can view the site for more details:http://www-tech.mit.edu/V120/N32/gulfair.32w.html Since we got information about his death, we have been expecting his next of kin to come over and claim his money because we cannot release it unless somebody applies for it as next of kin or relation to the deceased as indicated in our banking guidelines but unfortunately we learnt that all his supposed next of kin or relation died alongside with him at the plane crash leaving nobody behind for the claim. It is therefore upon this discovery that I and other officials in my department now decided to make this business proposal to you and release the money to you as the next of kin or relation to the deceased for safety and subsequent disbursement since nobody is coming for it and we don't want this money to go into the Bank treasury as unclaimed Bill. The Banking law and guideline here stipulates that if such money remained unclaimed after five years, the money will be transferred into the Bank treasury as unclaimed fund. The request of foreigner as next of kin in this business is occasioned by the fact that the customer was a foreigner and a Burkinabe cannot stand as next of kin to a foreigner. We agree that 30% of this money will be for you as foreign partner, in respect to the provision of a foreign account, 10 % will be set aside for expenses incurred during the business and 60 % would be for me and my colleagues. There after I and my colleagues will visit your country for disbursement according to the percentages indicated. Therefore to enable the immediate transfer of this fund to you as arranged, you must apply first to the bank as relations or next of kin of the deceased indicating your bank name, your bank account number,your private telephone and fax number for easy and effective communication and location where in the money will be remitted. Upon receipt of your reply, I will send to you by fax or email the text of the application. I will not fail to bring to your notice that this transaction is hitch free and that you should not entertain any atom of fear as all required arrangements have been made for the transfer. You should contact me immediately as soon as you receive this letter. Trusting to hear from you immediately. Yours faithfully, MR. IBRAHIM WATA Bill and exchange manager, BANK OF AFRICA (BOA)

From: Miss. Susan Diallo Dakar. Senegal West Africa Email: ssndiallo@yahoo.com <mailto:ssndiallo@yahoo.com> Dear One, My warmest greeting to you in the name of the Lord. I am Susan Diallo and I inheritated an important some from my late father who died in recent crisis in Cote d'Ivoire. I wish to request for your assistance in investing this sum in lucrative venture or manufacturing and real estate management in your country. I have Five million, seven hundred thousand United State Dollars. USD($5,700,000) to invest in this transaction and I will require your assistance in receiving the fund in your account in your country. I will gladly give you some resonable percent from the total sum for your assistance. Before his death on September 2005, he gave me all the necessary legal documents to the deposit of the fund in the bank, I am 20 years old and a university undergraduate and really don't know what to do. Now I want an account overseas where I can transfer this funds and after the transaction I will come and reside permanently in your country till such a time that it will be convinient for me to return back home if I so desire. This is because I have suffered a lot of set backs as a result of incessant political crisis here in Ivory coast. The death of my father actually brought sorrow to my life. I also want to invest the fund under your care because I am ignorant of business world. I am in a sincere desire of your humble assistance in this regards. Your suggestions and ideas will be highly regarded. Now permit me to ask these few questions: 1. Can you honestly help me from your heart? 2. Can I completely trust you? 3. What percentage of the total amount in question will be good for you after the money is in your account? Please, consider this and get back to me as soon as possible. Immedaitely I confirm your willingness, I will send to you my picture and also give you more details about myself and the bank were my late father deposited the fund, so that you can reach the bank and confirm the existence of the fund as well, because seeing is believing. Please always reply me through this my private email: ssdddialloss@yahoo.com <mailto:ssdddialloss@yahoo.com> for security reason. Awaiting your immediate response and may God bless you. With love, Susan.

RAMOS HAMZA& Co Chambers, Legal Practitioners Solicitors At Law No: 55 Pyne Cresent, Victoria Island, Lagos-Nigeria RE:Attention, I am barrister RAMOS HAMZA, the Legal Adviser and counsel to adeceased expatriate contractor (Eng.Arthur) who used to work with Zenith Oil and Gas Company here in Nigeria thereafter shall be referred to as my late client. On the 26th December 2004, my client and his entire family died while on Vacation at Phuket Island in Thailand as a result of the Asia Earth Quake Disaster(TSUNAMI DISASTER) You will read more stories about the crash on visiting this http://www.cnn.com/SPECIALS/2004/tsunami.disaster/ Meanwhile, On the 6th of January 2005,I recieved a phone call as his personal Attorney where the tragic news of my clients death in the Tsunami disaster was broke to me. And since then, I have made several enquiries to locate any of his extended relatives.This has proved unsuccessful hence I contacted you in my attempt to trace any member of his family over the internet. Therefore, I am seeking your consent and assistance in repartriating money left behind by my late client before it gets confiscated or declared unserviceable by the bank where the deposit is lodged. The deposit is valued US$5,200,000.00 (Five Million; Two Thousand United States Dollars) only and it is lodged with Linkworld International Bank Nigeria Plc. The management board of the bank, after their executive meeting fortnight ago, mandated me to provide his next of kin to inherit the funds the deceased left behind or else, it will be declared non claimable hence the bankers intend to invoke the abandoned property decree of 1996 to confiscate the funds after the expiration of the period given to me. I hereby seek your consent to present you to the bank as next-of-kin of the deceased, so that the proceeds of this account valued US$5,200,000.00 can be transferred to you as the heir to the deceased, and thereafter you,and I will share the money at the ratio of 50% to me and 45% to you, while 5% will be donated to the Tsunami Disaster Charity Fund. I guarantee that the transaction will be executed under a legitimate arrangement that will protect you from any breach of the law hence all the necessary legal documents that will be required of you by the management of the bank in backing up your claims will be duly processed and obtained from the necessary authorities. To commence this process, it is very important that you provide with me the following information, 1.Your name and contact address in full. 2.Your Telephone and fax numbers. 3.Your Occupation/company's name and address. 4.Your age and marital status. As soon as I recieve the above stated information, I will file-in a formal application on your behalf to the bank for them to commence the process of transferring the fund into your designated bank account as the next of kin to my deceased client. Yours truly, RAMOS HAMZA (ESQ)

URGENT AND CONFIDENTIAL: RE: TRANSFER OF [$13,500.000.00 USD. THIRTEEN MILLION FIVE HUNDRED THOUSAND UNITED STATES DOLLARS WE WANT TO TRANSFER TO OVERSEAS [$13,500.000.00] THIRTEEN MILLION FIVE HUNDRED THOUSAND UNITED STATES DOLLARS FROM FIRST BANK IN SOUTH AFRICA. I WOULD LIKE, IF YOU WILL BE CAPABLE AND FIT TO PROVIDE EITHER AN EXISTING BANK ACCOUNT OR TO SET UP A NEW BANK ACCOUNT IMMEDIATELY TO RECEIVE THIS MONEY, EVEN AN EMPTY ACCOUNT CAN SERVE TO RECEIVE THIS MONEY, AS LONG AS YOU WILL REMAIN HONEST TO ME TILL THE END OF THIS IMPORTANT BUSINESS TRANSACTION. I WANT TO BELIEVE THAT YOU WILL NEVER LET ME DOWN EITHER NOW OR IN FUTURE. I AM CASPER LAMPRECHT DIRECTOR OF ACCOUNTS DEPARTMENT OF FIRST BANK SA, DURING THE COURSE OF OUR AUDITING I DISCOVERED A FLOATING FUND IN AN ACCOUNT OPENED WITH A SECURITY COMPANY IN 1993 AND SINCE 2002 NOBODY HAS OPERATED ON THIS ACCOUNT AGAIN, AFTER GOING THROUGH SOME OLD FILES IN THE RECORDS I DISCOVERED THAT THE OWNER OF THE ACCOUNT DIED WITHOUT AN HEIR HENCE THE MONEY IS FLOATING AND IF I DO NOT REMIT THIS MONEY OUT URGENTLY IT WILL BE FORFEITED FOR NOTHING. THE OWNER OF THIS ACCOUNT WAS A FOREIGNER WHO SHARES THE SAME SURNAME AS YOURS, AND AN INDUSTRIALIST, HE DIED SINCE 1997 AND NO OTHER PERSON KNOWS ABOUT THIS ACCOUNT OR ANYTHING CONCERNING IT, THE ACCOUNT HAS NO BENEFICIARY AND MY INVESTIGATION PROVED TO ME AS WELL THAT THE ACCOUNT OWNER UNTIL HIS DEATH WAS A EXPERTRIATE/CONTRACTOR WITH ESKOM IN SOUTH AFRICA [PTY] SA. I AM CONTACTING YOU AS A FOREIGNER BECAUSE THIS MONEY CAN ONLY BE APPROVED TO A FOREIGNER WITH A VALID INTERNATIONAL PASSPORT, DRIVERS LICENCE AND FOREIGN ACCOUNT BECAUSE THE MONEY IS IN US DOLLARS AND THE FORMER OWNER OF THE ACCOUNT IS A FOREIGNER. I WILL LIKE US TO SIGN A BINDING AGREEMENT THAT WILL BIND US TOGETHER IN THE BUSINESS, I AM REVEALING ALL THIS TO YOU WITH THE BELIEF THAT YOU WILL NEVER LET ME DOWN IN THIS BUSINESS, YOU ARE THE FIRST AND THE ONLY PERSON I AM CONTACTING FOR THE BUSINESS SO PLEASE REPLY URGENTLY FOR ME TO TELL YOU THE NEXT STEP TO TAKE. YOU SHOULD FOR WARD YOUR TELEPHONE AND FAX NUMBERS WHICH IS ALSO NEEDED. YOU WILL HAVE TO GIVE ME THE ASSURANCE WHEN WE MEET THAT THIS MONEY WILL BE INTACT PENDING OUR PHYSICAL ARRIVAL IN YOUR COUNTRY FOR SHARING AND DISBURSEMENT OF THE FUND WHICH WILL BE 35% FOR YOUR ASSISTANCE, 60% WILL BE FOR US WHILE 5% WILL BE SET ASIDE TO TAKE CARE OF ALL THE EXPENSES THAT WILL BE INCURED BY BOTH PARTIES DURING THE COURSE OF THE TRANSFER. According to laws of South Africa, if after five years nobody claims the fund, it will be forfeited to the Government Purse, and I do not want the funds to end in some corrupt government official’s account. I LOOK FORWARD TO YOUR EARLIEST RESPONSE, NOTE YOU CAN ALSO CALL ME ON MY PRIVATE NUMBER BELOW, FOR SECURITY REASONS PLEASE REPLY ONLY TO: clamprecht0@yahoo.com BEST REGARDS, CASPER LAMPRECHT TEL : + 27 73 286 2448 FAX : + 27 11 5075714

From: Mr. Joseph.Garang Address: Bangkok Thailand Email:j_garang110@yahoo.com Tel+66-46428945 Attention: Director/Ceo My sincere greeting to you. I understand quite well that this message will sound so strange to you but it is a very serious matter that we need to tackle together very urgent. Kindly accept my apology if this proposal offends you, since we have never met before. Please carefully study this proposal very well for our mutual benefits. Mr Joseph Garang is my name, I am an Sudanese National from the Darfur region of Sudan. I am the Son of Dr, John De Mabior Garang, former Sudanese rebel leader and First Vice-President of Sudan who died in a helicopter crash on his way returning from an official trip from Uganda on 30th of July 2005, which people of sudan accused the government of having a hand in the crash. My late father had been a Rebel chief of Sudan Peoples Liberation Movement/Army (SPLM/A) for the past 21 years until July 2005, when he was appointed as first vice president Sudan in a new government of national unity. You can verify more this from this international newspapers posted in the website. <http://news.bbc.co.uk/1/hi/world/africa/2134220.stm> I write this letter in respect of my intention to transfer and invest the sum of US$25,500,000.00 in your company which I inherited from my Father after his death. This fund has been successfully conveyed to Thailand as valuable consignment with the help of a diplomatic Security company by my late father due to the political instablity in my country. I have every document to this fund including my father's last WILL. Further,I hope to invest this sum in your company or into any lucrative and viable venture under your management in your country that you will recommend for a period of Five years. I am aware that even though you may not be an investment expert, However, I am highly interested to have you as my Partner. Because of how my father's political opponents has been trying to eliminate our entire family, I then had to run out of my country with my mum for our dear lives. Presently, I am in Thailand with my mother who unfortunately has been critically ill since 8 months after the death of my father because of the shock of his late husband's death. And we have notify the Security and finance Company for the claims. Therefore, we will be needing your urgent co-operation to assist us secure and invest this money in your country which will be under your name and management control after due delibrations and under terms to be agreed upon. For the above reason, I humbly seek for an urgent assistance from you to enable us reach a contract joint venture partnership agreement to transfer and invest the fund in a profitable business orientation in your country as soon as I get your consent. Actually, I don't know you in person, it was a friend of my late father who works with Sudanese Foreign Office that advised me to consider your country for our investments, he gave us a good recommendation about your country and they are good and friendly people. Note : the fund in question is inherited from my late father with all the back-up document, and I want to assured you that your assistance to conduct this business with us is 100% risk free. I implore you to accord this matter with total confidential no matter what your decision may be. I will give you the more details about this fund based on your positive reply. l will like to hear from your opinion in your reply and should you have any question do not hasitate to ask me to enable us understand each other speedily and proceed for this mutual benefits immediately. l wait to read from you soonest. Yours Faithfully, J. Garang For Garang's family.

Dear lovely one, I hope this mail we meet you in good Health and happiness. I am 22 years old lady now, i was born on the 1 of january 1984.to the family of Nuhan Vaye.and my father name is Isaac Nuhan Vaye, he is a very wealthy gold and cocoa merchant who based in Liberia and ABIDJAN respectively, and my mothers name is Sheila.and I am their only child.well when i was a kid i went to a private schools and things were going on well for me and my parents till when i was in high school when my mother died on the 21ST october 1994 , My father took me so special because i am motherless. and he shower all his love on me and promised me that he will never have another woman because he did not want me for any problem. but Since my father dead last year i fine it had to live in Abijan because of some of his business partner that was after my life that was why i fund my way to senegal and before the death of my father on the 12th December 2004 in a private hospital in Abidjan. He called me secretly to his bed side and told me that he kept a sum of $5.200 000 (Five million two hundred thousand united states dollars) in a bank in Senegal mean while that he used my name as the beneficiary of the deposited fund. He also explained to me that it was because of this money he was poisoned by his business partner and that i should seek for foreign partner in a country of my choice where i would transfer this money and use it for investment purpose, such as; real estate investment or stock market investment. And right now i am in senegal to secure my life. Plesae, i am honourably soliciting your kind assistance as follows. 1) To provide a bank account where this money will be transfered into. 2) To serve as the guardian of these fund ,since i am 22years old. 3)To make arrangement for me in your country to continue my educational career and to procure me a residential permit in your country. I am inclined to offer you 15% of the total sum as a mode of compensation for your effort after the successful transfering of these fund to your nominated account overseas. Please i will be very happy if this transaction will be concluded with in seven (7)working days from now. I am expecting to hear from you as soon as possible. May Almighty God bless you as you do care for me Amen. Best regard Evette Nuhan Vaye

Dear Friend, First, I must apologise to you for using this medium to communicate to you about this project. I am a highly placed official of Government of Nigeria and also a founding member of the ruling party in Power now,the Peoples Democratic Party(PDP).My committee - The Niger Delta Development Corporation(NDDC)-which is in charge of managing and supervising the disbursement of oil sales revenues for the Nigerian government which covers payment to foreign and local contractors who has executed contracts for our country.The revenues under our control runs into several hundred of millions of dollars monthly.Myself and other colleagues in the NDDC are currently in need of a foreign partner with whose bank account we shall transfer the sum of Forty Nine Million Five Hundred Thosand United States Dollars($49.5m).This fund was accrued from various over invoicing of foreign contractors payments made over the years. The Total fund is presently waiting in the Government Account named CBN/FGN INDEPENDENT REVENUE account number 400-939134 with J.P.MORGAN CHASE BANK,New York.You can do your independent verification of this. However, by virtue of our position as civil servants and members of the NDDC, we cannot acquire this funds in our name. This is because as top civil servants, we are not allowed by law of the land to own or operate bank accounts outside our country for now. I have been delegated as a matter of trust by my colleagues, to look for an overseas partner in whose account we would transfer the fund Hence the reason for this mail.We shall be Transferring the money to your account with your company as the beneficiary and you are been paid for a contract which you executed for our country through the NDDC and any other Federal Ministry that we decide to use to siphon the funds through. For your support and partnership,please reply me to negotiate your fees or the percentage you wish to be paid when the funds arrive your bank account.You must however note that this transaction, withregards to our disposition to continue with you, is subject to these terms. Firstly, our conviction of your transparency. Secondly, that you treat this transaction with utmost secrecy and confidentiality. Finally and above all, that you will provide an account that you have absolute control over. The transaction, although discrete, is legitimate and there is no risk or legal disadvantages either to ourselves or yourself now or in the future as we have put in place perfect mchineries that will ensure a hitch free transfer into your account upon acceptance. The transfer will be effected to your account within ten-fourteen (10-14) working days as soon as we reach an agreement and you furnish me with a suitable bank account and company name and address with all your contact numbers including fax number. I am looking forward to doing business with you and do solicit your confidentiality in this transaction, Please mail your response to me. Yours faithfully, Dr. Femi Petersen.

FROM MR JOHNSON MUGABE. E-MAIL ; mm_m_17johnson@yahoo.com.au DEAR SIR, Compliments of the day,I understand quite well that this message will sound so strange to you but it is a very serious matter that we need to tackle together very urgent. Before i proceed further,Let me formally introduce myself to you .I am MR. JOHNSON MUGABE, 30 years of age, the first adopted son of president Robert Mugabe, the current Zimbabwean President. I am contacting you today for an urgent assistance to transfer into your account the sum of US$ 19.8 ( NINTEEN POINT EIGHT MILION STATES DOLLARS). I hope that you may be aware of the recent differences that is going on rigth now between my father and the opposition party in my country, this also brought about the commonwealth community sanctioning my father and freezing all his foreign account both in America and britain.This decision was carried out during the 4 days Commonwealth meeting that was held in Malawi in a part of South East Africa recently. It will interest you to hear that i never supported my fathers treatment to the white zimbabwean citizens, and this has seriously brought about some personal misunderstanding between me and my father.I have been opposing him since the past five (7) years. Fight so hard to see that he leaves the presidential seat after governing for past 32 years On this account i disassociated myself from him and we do not have any thing in common right now.He even forced me to leave the country with immediate effect after receiving the sanction from the common wealth community, Although he thought that i am behind his delimma. In the year 2004 when i was in good term with my father, he gave me a treasure box containing the sum of US$19.8 milion to deposite in a private security company in Thailand for safe keeping, So i did exactly as he instructed me without disclosing the actual content of the box to the security company,every documents was signed and documented in my names and details.This money has been lying in the security company for the past 8 months. Now that he sent me out on exile, i left zimbabwe to Thailand where i am currently seeking political assylum.My aim of travelling to Thailand was to claim the money and transfer it out of Thailand to any other country that will be safe for investment. I am contacting you therefore on the account that you will support me to secure the fund in good condition and also come over to Thailand so that we can both claim the fund together, and then we travel down to your country for proper investment of the fund. I have visited the security company and made every neccessary enquiry concerning the fund and it is still intact in the security house.I will compensate you with 7%of the total sum (i.e US$ 1,386 000.00) and i have set aside another 8% (i.e US$1,584 000.00) for any expenses that may be incured during the transaction. Please this is a very confidential matter that needs utmost secrecy and confidentiality, so i am really pleading to you to try as much as possible to keep every aspect of this confidential. Please also do not reveal it to any one as my hope and futture solely depend on this money and if you are willing to work with me and assist me on this transaction,then do not hesitate to contact me immediately by sending me your TELEPHONE and FAX NUMBERS,and reply me through my e-mail address for us to carry on with the next step of the transaction. Hoping to receive your positive response soonest. BEST REGARDS, MR. JOHNSON MUGABE

(READ CAREFULLY ADN KEEP CONFIDENTIAL) FROM/MR MOHAMEDAH A HAFAR THE MANAGER OF AUDIT & ACCOUTANCY DEPT. BANK OF AFRICA(B.O.A) OUGADOUGOU?BURKINA-FASO Dear partner Good day and how are you doing with your family? Hope fine. Please let this message do not be a surprise to you because i got your contact information and lay all the trust in you before i decided to disclose this confidential and successful transaction to you. I am the MOHAMEDAH A HAFAR AUDIT & ACCOUNTANCY DEPARTMENT of our bank and i decided to contact you over this financial transaction worth the sum of NINETEEN MILLION,THREE HUNDRED THOUSAND UNITED STATES DOLLARS ($19,300,000.00 ) for our present future success. This is an abandoned fund that belongs to one of our bank foreign customers who died along with his entire family on through plane crash disaster about 3 years ago.Meanwhile i was very fortune to came across the deceased file when i was arranging the old and abandoned customers files of 2002-2005 in other to submit to the entire bank management for an official re-documentation. Be obviously informed that it was stated in our BANKING POLICY and signed lawfully that if such fund remains unclaimed till the period of FOUR(4) years started counting from the date when the beneficiary died, the money will be transferred into the BANK TREASURY as an unclaimed fund.Besides, it is not authorized by the law guiding our bank for a citizen of BURKINA FASO to make the claim of the fund.So the request of you as a foreigner is necessary to apply for the claim and transfer of the fund smoothly into your reliable bank account as the NEXT OF KIN to the deceased. Note that when the fund is transferred into your account, Thirty Five Percent (35%) will be for you in respect of all your assistance for the transfer of the fund into your account and provision of the bank account where the bank will remit the fund into,Fifty Five Percent (55%) will be for me as the rest Ten Percent(10%) will be shared to Charity Organisations Centers, Motherless Babies Homes, and helpless people that surrounded us around the World. If you are really sure of your integerity, trustworthy and confidentiality, and accept not to cheat, betray or disappoint me after this when the fund is transferred into your account, reply for the re-assurance with your telephone and fax numbers necessary for effective communication. As soon as you reply , call me through my private telephone number on (00226 76 498168 ) so that i will let you know the steps and procedures to follow in order to finalize this transaction immediately. I expect your urgent communication. Yours sincerely, MR MOHAMEDAH A HAFAR. THE MANAGER AUDIT ACCOUNTANCY DEPT( B.O.A). _________________________________________________________________ MSN Messenger: appels gratuits de PC à PC ! http://www.msn.fr/msger/default.asp

FROM MR BARTHOLOMEW R MUTIE. Sir, I personally decided to put in writing as below, the full details of this business proposal that I have been trying to explain to you. I have a re-profiling amount in an excess of US$78M, which I seek your partnership in accommodating for me. I am willing to give out 25% of this total sum to you for your quick assistance and partnership, 70% for me and while 5% should be set side for reimbursement of any unforeseen expenses we both might incure in the cause of this transaction. However, I sincerely seek your confidence in this transaction, which I am proposing to you. My name is Bartholomew mutie, I am the personal assistance to the former President of Republic of Liberia (President Charles Taylor). President Charles Taylor decided on the 11th of August 2003 to go into exile in a neighboring country Nigeria to seek asylum. Based on these developments, his various foreign bank accounts have been frozen and some are still under serious investigation. But in the light of all these happenings, President Charles Taylor was able, through the help of some loyalist succeeded to secretly move the sum of US$78M, on my name as the owner to a private security company vault in Nigeria where the final crediting is expected to be carried out later, but resently he has just been arrested and taken away. you can read more on CNN news of March 30, 2006. http://www.cnn.com/2006/WORLD/africa/03/29/taylor.nigeria/index.html All the depositing documents of the above fund were on my name and they are still in my possession, What I need from you is to stand as the beneficiary of the above quoted sum and I will arrange for the documentation which will enable the Security Company transfer / wire the fund to your bank account. I have decided to do this only with you and use this sum to relocate to European or American continent and never to be connected to any of President Charles Taylor's conglomerates. This transaction can be concluded within 2 weeks. My questions are:- 1. Can you handle this project? 2. Can I give you this trust? 3. can you keep this business as very confidential? 4. If you can sponsor this transfer, Is 25% acceptable to you, as your commission? REPLY TO MY PRIVATE EMAIL ADDRESS: Consider this and reply as soon as possible to (my private email address) mutiebath@infinito.it, so i can give you more clear explanations details and information about this transaction. I will also need your direct telephone and fax number for easy reach. Finally, it is my humble prayer that the information as contained herein be accorded the necessary attention, urgency as well as the secrecy it deserves. Please i need you to send me your telephone number so i can give you a call immediately for more discusion. As soon as I get your positive response, I will send you more information to you. Best regard Mr. Bartholomew mutie

I have a new email address!

You can now email me at: frankholding_7@yahoo.ca FROM MR JAMES DIRECTOR OF FINANCE AUDITING AND ACCOUNTING UNIT, BANK OF AFRICA, COTONOU-BENIN REPBLIC. THIS IS MY PRIVATE E-MAIL BOX:james221_2006@yahoo.com My name is Mr.JAMES BROWN. I am the credit AUDITING AND ACCOUNTING UNIT,BANK OF AFRICA,COTONOU-BENIN REPBLIC. I am contacting you of a business transfer, of a huge sum of money from a deceased account. Though I know that a transaction of this magnitude will make any one apprehensive and worried, but I am assuring you that everything has been taken care off, and all will be well at the end of the day. I decided to contact you due to the urgency of this transaction. PROPOSITION; I am the account officer of a foreigner named Gerald Welsh who died in an air crash along with his wife on the 31st October 1999 in an Egyptian airline 990 with other passengers on board. You can confirm this from the website below which was published by BBC WORLD NEWS. WEBSITE. http://news.bbc.co.uk/1/hi/world/americas/502503.stm Since his death, none of his next-of-kin are alive to make claims for this money as his heir, because they all died in the same accident himself and his wife(May their soul rest in peace). We cannot release the fund from his account unless someone applies for claim as the next-of-kin to the deceased as indicated in our banking guidelines. Upon this discovery, I now seek your permission to have you stan d as a next of kin to the deceased, as all documentations will be carefully worked out by me for the funds (USD 10,700,000.00) to be released in your favor as the beneficiary's next of kin. Because after four years the money will be called back to the bank treasury as unclaimed bills and the money shared amongst the directors of the bank. so it is on this note i decided to seek for whom his name shall be used as the next of kin/beneficiary to this funds rather than allow the bank directors to share this money amongst themselves at the end of the year. It may interest you to know that we have secured from the probate an order of mandamus to locate any of the deceased beneficiaries. Please acknowledge receipt of this message in acceptance of our mutual business endeavor by furnishing me with the following information if you are interested. 1.A Beneficiary name. In order for me to prepare the document for transfer of the funds in your name. 2. Direct Telephone and fax numbers. For our personal contact and mutual trust in each other. I shall be compensating you with [3million Million Dollars) on final conclusion of this project for your assistance, while the balance of 5 Million Dollars shall be for me for investment purposes. Because I intend to retire after the conclusion of this transaction. If this proposal is acceptable by you, please endeavor to contact me immediately. Do not take undue advantage of the trust I have bestowed in you, I await your urgent reply. to this address: james221_2006@yahoo.com Regards, JAMES - frankholding_7 holding

Greetings to you, This letter must come to you as a big surprise, but I believe it is only a day that people meet and become great friends and business partners. My name is Mr.Emme Harry. the present branch Manager of a bank here in Benin Republic West Africa. I write you this proposal in good faith, believing that I can trust you with the information I am about to reveal to you. Like I said, I have a transaction that will benefit both of us, as your assistance is required as a foreigner. I use to head the Accounts department in my bank head office, but last December I was asked to take osition of a Manager of our branch in Cotonou who passed on, so that was how I became the present Manager and discovered a fortune. As I resumed duty, I discovered an account with total sum of $18.1 million that has not been operated on for the past 3 years. From my investigation, I found out that this account belongs to one Late Mr. HAJI EL JAMAL ZOUE, a citizen of Lebanon who died on the recent plane crash in Cotonou Benin republic on the 26th of Dec. 2003 You can seach the Webside. site;http://www.cnn.com/2003/WORLD/africa/12/26/benin.crash/index.html ) I have kept a close monitoring of the account since then and nobody has come forward to claim the money as next of kin to the Late Mr HAJI EL JAMAL ZOUE, meaning that no one is aware of the account. I cannot directly take out this money without the help of a foreigner and that is why I am contacting you for an assistance to claim the funds and share it with me. As the Manager of my bank branch, I have the power influence the release of the funds to any foreigner that comes up as the next of kin to the account, with the correct information concerning the account, which I shall give you. I am seeking your co-operation to present you as the next of kin to the account. There is practically no risk involved, the transaction will be executed undera legitimate arrangement that will protect you from any breach of law. If you accept to work with me, I want you to state how you wish us to share the funds in percentage, so that both parties will be satisfied. Contact me as soon as you receive this message if you feel we can work together, so as to give you more details. Thanking you in advance and may God bless you. Please, treat with utmost confidentiality. I wait your urgent response. Meanwhile, I will like to speak with you on phone for more information. Please you are to keep this transaction a top secret in view of my sensitive position at the bank. #NOTE: These are required of you. (1) Your full Name. (2) Your personal phone number. (3) Your Address Thanks and have a nice day. Best regards, Mr Emme Harry. _________________________________________________________________ FREE pop-up blocking with the new MSN Toolbar - get it now! http://toolbar.msn.click-url.com/go/onm00200415ave/direct/01/

FROM :DR. KOLA DEVIS ATTN: SIR IT IS MY PLEASURE WRITING YOU THIS MAIL.AND I HOPE THAT YOU ARE SOMEBODY I WILL TRUST FOR THIS TRANSACTION HENCE IT IS CONFIDENTIAL. AS A MATTER OF FACT,I AM CIVIL SERVANT WORKING WITH THE NIGERIA NATIONAL PETROLEUM CORPORATION (NNPC)ALSO,I AM THE CHAIRMAN (CONTRACT PAYMENT RELEASE REVIEW COMMITTE)DUE TO THE MANIPULATIONS OF CONTRACT AWARD IN THE CORPORATIONS TEN YEARS AGO TILL DATE BY THE PAST AND PRESENT MILITARY AND CIVILIAN GOVERNEMNT OFFICIALS. THIS COMMITTE IS LEGALLY MANDATED BY THE THREE ORGAN OF THE GOVERNMENT TO REVIEW ALL THE CONTRACT AWARDED FOR IMMEDIATE PAYMENT. DURING THIS EXCERISE,THIS COMMITTE DISCOVERED THAT ALOT CONTRACT PAYMENT WAS MANIPULATED BY SOME GOVERNMENT OFFICIAL FOR THEIR SELFISH INSTREST INCOLLABORATION WITH FOREIGN EXPERTATES.AFTER SAID AND DONE,THIS COMMITTE HAVE TRIED TO CONTACT SOME OF THEM TO COME FORWARD FOR THE CLAIM.BUT,DUE TO THE FACT THAT THEY DID NOT GO THROUGH THE(DUE PROCESS) THEY COULD NOT COME FORWARD FOR THE CLAIM. AS AT THIS MOMENT,WE ARE IN POCESSION OF SOME UNCLAIMED CONTRACT PAYMENT VALUED AT $650M (SIX HUNDRED AND FIFTY MILLION UNITED STATES ONLY) AS UN CLAIMED CONTRACT PAYMENT.AND AS SUCH,THE TOTAL PAYMENT ARE MEANT TO BE RETURNED BACK TO THE GOOVERNMENT TREASURY.AFTER A CLOSE DOOR MEETING WITH THE REST OF THE BOARD,WE HAVE DECEIDED TO TO DECLARE PART OF THIS PAYMENT TO THE GOVERNMENT.AND WHILE WE WILL SEEK YOUR URGENT ASSISTANT FOR THE CLAIM OF PART OF IT. IT IS NOW LEFT FOR YOU TO LET ME KNOW EXCATLY HOW MUCH YOU KNOW THAT YOU CAN BE CAPBLE TO RECEIVE FOR US WITHOUT ANY PROBLEM. SO THAT WE WILL KNOW EXACTLY HOW MUCH TO BE DECLARE TO THE GIVERNMENT. PLEASE BEAR INMIND THAT OUR AIM OF STRICKING THIS DEAL WITH YOU IS FOR OUR POLITICAL AMBITION.WE REALLY WANT TO USE THE FUNDS FOR POLITICS. BECUASE,IN AFRICA,POLITICS WITHOUT MONEY IS BASELESS. IF THIS IS A MATTER OF INSTREST TO YOU,KINDLY KEEP IN CONTACT WITH ME IMMEDAITELLY YOU RECEIVE THIS MAIL FOR MORE INFORMATIONS.ALTHOUGH,YOU WILL BE COMPENSATED WITH 30% FOR YOUR ASSISTANT.AND THE FOLLOWING INFORMATIONS WILL BE REQUIRED FROM YOU. A:YOUR FULL COMPLETE NAME,ADDRESS AND DIRECT PHONE NUMBER. B:COMAPNY NAME,ADDRESS AND YOUR POSITION C:BANK NAME,ADDRESS AND ACCOUNT DETAILS D:MARRIED OR NOT.AND YOUR AGE. WITH THESE INFORMATIONS,THIS COMMITTE WILL NOW APPLY FOR AN URGENT PAYMENT IN YOUR FAVOUR AS ONE OF THE BENEFICIARY/CONTRACTOR THAT EXECUTED CONTRACT WITH THE (NNPPC)NIGERIA NATIONAL PETROLEUM CORPORATION.KINDLY BEAR INMIND THAT THIS DEAL REQUIRES ABSOLUTE SECRECY/CONFIDENTIAL WHICH MUST NOT BE REVEAL OUT TO ANY ONE UNTIL YOU RECEIVE THE PAYMENT FOR US. WAITING TO HEAR FROM YOU URGENTLY FOR OUR TIME IS LIMITTED TO THIS DEAL.BECAUSE THE FEDERAL GOVERNEMT IS WAITING FOR OUR REPORT. BEST REGARDS DR, KOLA DEVIS

FROM: OFFICE OF REVD.FR PETER CLARK DIRECTOR SPECIAL DUTIES,UNITED NATIONS IN CONJUNCTION WITH THE INTERNATIONAL MONETARY FUND WORLD BANK SPECIAL DUTIES OFFICE DAKAR,SENEGAL. TEL:+(221)4488469 EMAIL:revd.fr.peterclark@katamail.com Dear Friend. I am Rev. Fr. Peter Clark, a senior staff with the UN special duties office ;my office monitors and controls the affairs of all banks and financial institutions. I have before me list of funds, which could not be transferred to some nominated accounts as these accounts have been identified either as ghost accounts, unclaimed deposits and over-invoiced sum etc; I have the opportunity to write you based on the instructions among others i received days ago from the officer in the computer section in person of Engineer Peter Cliff,to bring out part of your total pending payment with reference number (LM-05-371) amounting US$10 million.The (Ten Million Dollars) is been arranged in a security-proof box weighing 75kg. In order to get the box shipped to you. A lot of people are interested in your payment and those people are merely doing paper works with you and that explains why you receive different kinds of untrue fax and phone messages from different people everyday. As I found out that you have almost met all the statutory requirements in respect of your pending payment. Also we found out that some of the officials of the parastatals have been extorting money from you with the pretext of helping you receive your money. I can assure you this will keep happening if you do not do away with those officers.I am the final signatory to any transfer or remittance of huge funds moving within banks both on the local and international levels. A friend of mine who is a diplomat disclosed to me that there is a security courier service company that is specialised in sending diplomatic materials and information from one country to another, with diplomatic immunity and consignment such as this cannot be checked by any customs anywhere in the world unlike Dhl, Ems, FedEx and Ups because they will have to open the box for inspection by the customs before shipment. I have therefore met the official of the security courier service and concluded shipping arrangement with them, which they will commence as soon as I have your go ahead order. The diplomat will bring the consignment to you he has been in this line of work for many years now ;so you have notting to worry about. Be that as it may, I am conditionally prepared to assist you get the money, practically after studying the part leading to this particular stage in the payment process in connivance with your local collaborators to conceal the authentic source of the funds. And my only condition for the unusual assistance is for you to reach me directly on my private TEL: +(221)448-8469. It is very urgent that you reach me on phone for a gentlemanly mutual agreement, After all arrangements we have concluded that you must donate Five Hundred Thousand United States dollars (US$500,000.00) to any charity organisation I designate as soon as you receive your money. To this effect, you will send to us a promissory note for the donation along with your address where you will like the box to be delivered to by courier. Please maintain topmost secrecy as it may cause a lot of problems if found out that we are using this way to help you. You are advised not inform anyone about this until you received your money. When you conclude this we will help to ship the final part of your money to you. Yours Faithfully, Revd. Fr. Peter Clark. Director, Special Duties.UN/WBO. Email:revd.fr.peterclark@katamail.com

FROM THE DESK OF CHAIRMAN Sub-Committee on Finance South African World Cup bid 2010 24 Steven Bikko Blvrd Pretoria, Republic Of South Africa. Email:willico1@gmail.com . Tel : +27-73-485-8223 . Attn: Sir, Greetings you must be aware now that my country The Republic of South Africa won the bid to host the world cup by 2010, prior to this bid my committee was mandated to lobby the members of board of Federation International Football Association (FIFA) on selection of the country to host the world, the bidding was intensive but at the end we got the hosting right. My committee was given the sum of $29 million dollars to lobby the members of the FIFA ruling body to make sure that we win the hosting right considering the gain that comes with the hosting right like South Africa's economy will receive a massive direct boost from hosting the 2010 World Cup, financial impact report for South Africa's World Cup bid committee shows that the 2010 World Cup will pump R21.3-billion into South Africa's economy, and creating an estimated 159 000 new jobs. With the help the living legend of our time 85-year-old Nobel Peace Prize winner Dr. Nelson Mandela who made an emotive case for The Republic of South Africa, we got the bid without spending all the money, I and my committee members saw this as a God sent opportunity tosecure our future and that of our family therefore was mandated by other committee members to look for a way to move the remaining money to a safe place with the help of a foreigner who we can trust and is ready to assist us to move the funds considering the fact that we are still members of the bid committee and in the eyes of the public. we have in our possession the sum $21millon since we spent just $8million for lobbying. We are ready to give you 20% for all your assistance then me and my colleagues will keep 80% lf you are willing kindly reply to my letter for further directive. we will want to invest our share intoReal-estate and air taxi business in your country with your assistance,bearing in mind that confidentiality is of great essences so is time in this project I will await your response, Best Regards . Mr.Williams Muyeke All responses should be sent to:willico1@gmail.com . _________________________________________________________________ See their smiles, hear their laughter with MSN Messenger! http://messenger.msn.co.za/

Dear Sir/Madam,   I am sorry for this unprecedented way of communicating this to you but  would like to have your attention for a moment?   To introduce myself, My name is Emmanuel Davids and I am an artist and i own   Emmanueldavids ArtWorld . I reside in monza city which is located in italy,i live with my two kids,  my pets and the love of my life Racheal. It is definitely a full house.       I have been doing artwork since I was a small child. That gives me alot   of experience in art generally. I majored in art in high school and took a few college art courses. Most of my work is done in either pencil or hairbrush mixed with color pencils. I have recently added designing and creating artwork on the computer.I have been selling my art creations for the past 3 years and have had my work featured on trading cards, prints and in magazines.I have sold in galleries and to private collectors from all around the world.          I am looking for a representative in the states who will be working for me as a part-time worker and i will be willing to pay 10% of whatever a client pays to me,which would'nt affect ur present state of work,someone who would help me recieve payments from my clients in the states.i mean someone that is responsible and reliable,cause the cost of coming to the state and getting payments is very expensive,i am working on setting up a branch in the states,so for now i need a representative in the united states who will be handling the payment aspect. It would'nt cost u any amount,This is no get rich quick scheme neither is it a scam or hoax in anyway.You are not required to pay any registration fee or pay for any application form before you get employed. Instead of paying for anything you will be receiving your weekly salary as soon as you get started. Too good to be true you will say.With your help i can reach and provide a better service to more people and businesses in American, faster and at a lower cost than my competitors.       My clients make payments for the products and services every week. They pay for my services in 3 major ways; * Through Cheques * Money orders or drafts( this forms of payment have been put on hold due to some security reasons) * Wire transfers * Cash   Some of these forms of payment are not readily cashable or accepted in the Italy. This is the reason i need someone to work as my representative in the States and  asist me in processing the payments made to me by my clients.   You will receive as a weekly salary of 10% of whatever a client pays . Your job will be to receive this payment sent to me which will be sent to you via mail or courier service(if payment is a check,money order or draft) and cashing it at your bank or any designated cashing point.   If payment is in through wire transfer, i will require you to open a bank account to receive this payment.  I only  accept payment from clients that bank with the following banks stated below in America and Canada to make work more convenient for you. 1. Bank of America 2. Wells Fargo bank 3. Citi bank 4. Royal bank of Canada   Whatever the form of payment is you are to immediately deduct your weekly salary(10% of the money) and forward the balance to me  as you are instructed to do. Money will be sent to me by WESTERN UNION TRANSFER as this is a safe, secure, fast and reliable means of receiving money. So i would like to know if you would like to work online from home and getting paid weekly without leaving or affecting your present job?If you are interested,please get back to me as soon as possible. To get started all i require from you is your full name, address and phone number so that i can email you a letter of employment from my company which you have to reply with a signed acceptance letter and a scanned copy of your Identification card or International Passsport attached to it.   I anxiously await your response. Your Faithfully, Emmanuel davids Manager Emmanueldavids ArtWorld N/B: TO SAFEGUARD THE INTEREST OF OUR REPRESENTATIVES(YOU) I ONLY ACCEPT CERTIFIED AND NOTABLE BANK CHEQUES FROM MY CLIENTS. I ALSO DO NOT DISCLOSE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION TO MY CLIENTS OR ANYONE ELSE.

New Yahoo! Messenger with Voice. Call regular phones from your PC and save big.

HELLO FRIEND, Good day and Compliments, I am writing this letter in confidence believing that if it is the wish of God for you to help me and my family, God Almighty will bless and reward you abundantly and you would never regret this. My family and I are true Christians and worship God truthfully. I got your contact during my search for this assistance. I am a female student from University Burkina Faso, Ouaga. I am 22 yrs old. I'd like any person who can be caring, loving and home oriented. I will love to havea long-term relationship with you and to know more about you. I would like to build up a solid foundation with you in time coming if you can be able to help me in this transaction. Well, my father died earlier three months ago and left I and my junior brother behind. Hewas a king, which our town citizens titled him over sixteen years before his death. I was a princess to him and I am the only person who can take care of his wealth now because my junior brother is still young and my mother is not literate enough to know my entire father's wealth.He left the sum of USD 7.350, 000M (Seven Million, Three Hundred and Fifty Thousand US Dollars) in a security company. This money was annually paid into my late fathers account from Shell petroleum Development Company (spdc) and chevron Oil Company operating in our locality for the compensation of youth and community development in our jurisdiction. I don't know how and what I will do to invest this money somewhere in abroad, so that my father's kindred will not take over what belongs to my father and our family, which they were planning to do without my consentbecause I am a female as stated by our culture in the town. Now, I urgently need your humble assistance to move this money from the Security Company to your bank account that is why I felt happy when I saw your contact because I strongly believe that by the grace of God,you will help me invest this money wisely. I am ready to pay 30% of the total amount to you if you help us in this transaction and another 10% interest of Annual after Income to you, for handling this transaction for us, which you will strongly have absolute control over it. If you can handle this project sincerely and also willing to assist me in lifting this fund, kindly reach me. Please, note that this transaction is 100% risk free and I hope to commence the transaction as quick as possible, I will send you my picture as soon as I hear from you for recognition. Yours sincerely, Princess memuna iboudo. please reply me at my private email address: princessmemuna_iboudo@hotmail.com _________________________________________________________________ MSN Messenger: appels gratuits de PC à PC ! http://www.msn.fr/newhotmail/Default.asp?Ath=f

Dear one,   After much prayer my spirit has directed me to confide in you this top confidencial issue regarding my present predicament. Brief information about myself, my name is Miss Rita Umu., the only surviving daugther of late Mr Wilson Umu may his soul rest in perfect peace. Before the death of my father, he was a cocoa merchant and he was also in the government of my country. He was assasinated with the my mother and my two elder brothers by the rebels during the heat of the war in my country. The rebels claim that my father was in surport of the government during the war that devided my country into two part. Luckily for me, I was away in the burden school in Ghana a neighbouring country. It was on the BBC Africa that I heard about the tragic death of my parents and brothers but my father was still alive at the time of gun shot and was ruched to the hospital. I was taken to the hospital where he was recieving treatment for gun wounds. One week before his death, he called me to his bed side at the hospital and handed a document to me. The document is covering a deposit of nine  million five hundred thausand U.S dollars (U.S$9.5 000.000.00) which he deposited in a security company vault here in my home country. According to him he said this money is meant to establish his business in europe after his retirement. He instructed me to look for a trust worthy partner in over sea to confide the release of the fund into his account and relocate to his country to establish the money on a lucrative business and live my life quietly. He also said that the security company does not know the content of the safe Box, that he deposited the contents as family valuable. Why am contacting you, I need your assistance in the following: 1.provide a bank account were the fund will be transfered in. 2.Help to pay for the clearance document charges. 3.Help to invest the money on a lucrative investment in your country. 4. Send me an invitation letter to arrange my travel to your country soon as the transfer is effected into your account. 5.Help to manage the investment for the minimum of five years. 6.Serve as my partner and guidiance in your country during my relocation to your country. Regarding this transaction, I offer you 10% as compensation and 5% for all expences over the transaction immediately the transfer is made into your account. Note: If you are interested in this joint venture, signify by replying me as urgent through my e-mail address, I will be ready to scan to you the document covering the money as soon as you show your willingness to assist me and the contact of the security company. so that you can contact them as my foreign partner and Trustee. Waiting for you urgent reply. Yours sincerely, Miss..rita umu

Celebrate Yahoo! JAPAN 10th Anniversary

I have a new email address!

You can now email me at: martin_dele5@yahoo.ca Dear friend, Before I introduce myself, I wish to inform you that this letter is not a hoax mail and I urge you to treat it serious. However strange or surprising. This contact might seem to you as we have not met personally or had any dealings in the past, I humbly ask that you take due consideration of its importance and the immense benefit it will be to you and I.We want to transfer to overseas account ($3,000.000.00 USD) (Three Million United States Dollars) from a Diamond Bank Ltd here in Senigal,I want to ask you,If you are not capable to quietly look for a reliable and honest person who will be capable and fit to provide either an existing bank account or to set up a new Bank a/c immediately to receive this money, even an empty a/c can serve to receive this money, as long as you will remain honest to me till the end for this important business trusting in you and believing in God that you will never let me down either now or in future. I am Mr Martins Dele, the Auditor General of Diamond Bank here in Senigal. During the course of our auditing, I discovered a floatingfund in an account opened in the bank in 1996 and since 2002 nobody has operated on this account again,after going through some old files in the records I discovered that the owner of the account died without a [Heir/WILL] hence the money is floating and if I do not remit this money out urgently it will be forfeited for nothing. The owner of this account is Mr. FORREST STEPHEN DeMA RTINO of Sidney,Ohio United States of America. Who was involved in an {AIR CRASH} that occurred on Jan Thursday 9th 2003 With an air craft {US Airways Express Flight 5481 } which crashed Wednesday at Charlotte/Douglas International Airport, killing all 21 aboard passenger. Since the management got the information of his death we have been expecting any of his relation or his next of kin to come up and claim his money.Unfortunately, From the day of his death till the time of this letter none of his relation or friends has come up for the claim.The banking and financial law of Diamond Bank stipulates that if such fund remained unclaimed after a period of (3-4)Three-four years, it will be transferred into the bank treasury as unclaimed bill. On this discovery, I decided to do business with you and release the money to you as the next of kin to Mr. FORREST STEPHEN DeMARTINO for safety and subsequent disbursement. I will soon proceed for my retirement leave this year, and I personally do not want this fund to be transferred into the bank treasury as unclaimed bill. That is why I wanted the fund to be move out of the bank before I proceed on my retirement from the banking services this year. The need for a foreigner as next of kin in this project is occasioned by the fact that the customer Mr. FORREST STEPHEN DeMARTINO was a foreigner and a Senigalise cannot stand as his next of kin or heir.in agreement that 40% of the Fund would be for you as foreign partner; thereafter I will visit your country for disbursement according to the percentages indicated.To enable the immediate transfer of the fund into your nominated account, you will first apply to the bank as the next of kin of the deceased, indicating your bank account number and location where the money will be remitted. Upon receipt of your acknowledgement indicating your interest, I will Guide you on the application that you will send to my Bank authority.This transaction is guaranteed to success without any problems.Looking forwar d to your urgent reply. Regards, Mr Martin Dele - Mr Martin Dele

ATTN:(HANDLE THIS INFORMATION SECRETLY) Dear, I hereby contact you personally concerning the situation in my bank. In order to transfer out {us$34,000,000} Thirty four million us dollars, I have the courage to look for a reliable and honest person who will be capable for this important business believing that you will never let me down either now or in future. I am Dr Paul Mbizala K., the Regional computing auditor of (STANDARD BANK OF SOUTH AFRICA) JOHANNESBURG BRANCH (SBSA). There is an account opened in this bank in 1985 and since 1991 nobody has operated on this account again. After going through some old files in the records I discovered that if I do not remit this money out urgently.it will be forfeited for nothing according to South Africa laws and act of 1993,the money will be revert this country government treasury after 15 years if there is no valid claim. I need a foreign partner that will present as a relative to this late man. I concluded to transfer this money overseas for proper investment that will benefit me. The owner of this account is Mr.Bremen K.Schroeder, a foreigner, and a Miner at Kruger Gold Co. a geologist by profession and he died since 1991. No other person knows about this account or any thing concerning it,the account has no other beneficiary and my investigation proved to me as well that this company does not know anything about this account and the amount involved is us$34,000,000 Thirty Four million dollars. I am only contacting you as a foreigner because this money can not be approved to a local bank here, but can only be approved to any foreign account because the money is in US dollars and the former owner of the account is Mr.Bremen K.Schroeder, who is a foreigner too. I know that this message will come to you as a surprise as we dont know ourselves before, we will sign agreement, but be sure that it is real and a fund. I need a truthful person in this business because I don't want to make mistake and I need your strong assurance and trust. At the conclusion of this business, you will be given 50% of the total amount, 50% will be for me and my family. I look forward to your earliest reply through my email address. God Bless You. Yours truly, Dr Mbizala Paul. STANDARD BANK OF SOUTH AFRICA (You can as well contact me through my alternative email address (mbizalapaul@verizonmail.com) ---------------------------------------- Upgrade your account today for increased storage; mail forwarding or POP enabled e-mail with automatic virus scanning. Visit our member benefits page at https://members.canada.com/benefits.aspx for more information.

Dearest in the Lord, Greetings to you and your family, I am Mrs ELIZABETH LAMINE from liberia. I am married to Mr. Mike LAMINE who worked with liberia embassy in Ivory Coast for nine years before he died in the year 2004.He is also a well known fruits import and Export business man in Ivory Coast. We were married for eleven years without a child. He died after a brief illness that lasted for only four days. Before his death we were both born again Christian. Since his death I decided not to remarry or get a child outside my matrimonial home which the Bible is against. When my late husband was alive he deposited the sum of $5.6Million US dollars with a bank in Ivory Coast Presently, this money is still in the custody of the bank. Recently, my Doctor told me that I would not last for the next three months due to cancer problem. Having known my condition I decided to donate this fund to a church or better to an individual personality that have a humanity understanding and trustworthy that will utilize this money the way I am going to instruct herein. I want a church or an individual personality that is trustworthy to use this money for orphanages, widows, propagating the word of God and to endeavour that the house of God is maintained. The Bible made us to understand that "Blessed is the hand that giveth". I took this decision because I don't have any child that will inherit this money and my husband relatives are not Christians and I don't want my husband's efforts to be used by unbelievers. I don't want a situation where this money will be used in an ungodly way. This is why I am taking this decision. I am not afraid of death hence I know where I am going. I know that I am going to be in the bosom of the Lord.Exodus 14 VS 14 says that "the Lord will fight my case and I shall hold my peace". I don't need any telephone communication in this regard because of my health hence the presence of my husband's relatives around me always. I don't want them to know about this development as I am convinced that With God by my said, all things are possible. As soon as I receive your reply I shall give you the contact of the bank in Ivory Coast, I will also send a copy of my passport to you and my photo and also issue you an authority letter that will empower you to be the beneficiary of the money. I want you and your church to always pray for me because the Lord is my shepherd and he shall see us through, My happiness is that I live a life of a worthy Christian so I have no fear at all for I am convinced that God is with me and he shall be with you if you make yourself available to take up this spiritual project of God. I believe that whoever that wants to serve the Lord must serve him in spirit and Truth thus I took this decision. Please always be prayerful all through your life. Contact me on this email via elizabeth_lamine2004@yahoo.co.uk always and please be informed that any delay in your reply will give me room in sourcing another person for this same purpose. Please assure me that you will act accordingly as I Stated herein. Hoping to receive your reply. Remain blessed in the Lord. Yours in Christ, MRS LIZABETH LAMINE

Bonjour Mon nom est BEVERLY MURRAY, je suis sourde et muette et je suis une citoyenne des Etats-Unis d'Amérique, Ma jeune soeur Agnes Reeves Murray est mariée ? l'ancien président du Liberia Mr Charles Taylor et maintenant elle est connu sous le non de Mme Reeves Taylor.j'ai hérité une somme de $20Million(vinght millions d'U.S.Dollars)de ma jeune s?ur ,qu'elle ? dysmélie dans une malle metallique,et qu'elle a déposé au sein d'une compagnie de sécurité diplomatique en Cote d'Ivoire et ? mon nom comme étant la beneficiaire. Et la malle a été déclarées comme contenant des biens personnel. Ceci revient ? dire m?me la compagnie de sécurité ne sais pas que le contenu réel de la malle est de l'argent ,pour préserver la sécurité des fonds dysmélies dans la malle. Le but principal pour lequel je vous ai ontacté,c'est d'obtenir votre assistance pour la récupération de cette malle d'argent de la compagnie de securité.Car j'ai enti?rement perdu le contacte avec ma s?ur depuis le commencements de la crise politique du Liberia. Et je veux tenir cette transaction secr?te aux ersonnes proches de moi ? cause de ma condition de sourde et muette. Je désire une personne neutre car les expériences de la m'ont enseigné qu'avec Dieu tout est possible et c'est pourquoi je crois en Dieu pour la réussites de cette transaction, je sais aussi que je vais ?tre dans la oitrine du seigneur. L'exode 14 -14 indique que le seigneur défendra ma cause et j' obtiendrai ma paix c'est ainsi que dans ma recherche de quelqu'un d'honn?te et de confiant que j'ai vu votre profile comme quelqu'un de confiant raison pour laquelle je vous ai contacté pour solliciter votre assistance. Je viens ? vous avec un c?ur plein d?angoisses, ? cause de mes difficultés pprouvées.Alors veuillez me rassurer que vous ne vous assaillerez sur cet argent et me trahir quand cette compagnie vous délivrera cette malle d'argent car ceci est une transaction qui nous bénéficiera ? tous deux. La compagnie que vous allez contacter est une ompagnie de sécurité diplomatique parconsequent, elle est en mesure de vous livrer cette mallette chez vous ? votre domicile, main ? main. Cette transaction est sans aucun risque et elle ne prendra que 3jrs de travail. Seulement si vous pouvez vous conformer aux nstructions de la compagnie. Aussi je vous enverrai le certificat de dépôt qui fut délivré le jour du dépôt de cette malle ? la compagnie et aussi l'accord qui fut rédigé entre ma s?ur et la compagnie en ce m?me jour. Et j'ai décidé de vous offrir les 15% de cette somme dysmélie dans la malle et 5% pour quoique ce soit comme comme frais qui pourront survenir durant la transaction telle que les appels téléphonique, les fax et autres. pour tout effort que vous fournirez pour m'assister. Sinc?rement c'est parce que je traverse une situation financi?re difficile que je vous sollicite. Veuillez me rassurer que vous agirez en conséquence comme je l'ai énoncé ci-dessus.J'esp?re recevoir votre réponse. Pour des raisons de sécurité, je voudrais que vous mainteniez cette information de cette transaction secr?te , ainsi j'attendrai pour avoir de vos nouvelles aussitôt que possible. Merci Mm Beverly murray

FROM: MR.GEORGE BENNETH ACCOUNTANT, UBN BENIN CITY-NIGERIA TEL/FAX: 234-09-272103 Hello Friend, First, I must solicit your confidence in this transaction, this is by virtue if its nature as being utterly CONFIDENTIAL and TOP SECRET. Truly, I know that a transaction of this magnitude will make any one apprehensive and worried, but I am assuring you that all will be well at the end of the day. We have decided to contact you due to the urgency of this transaction; we were reliably informed of your discreteness and ability in transactions of this nature. I hereby start by introducing myself properly to you first. I am Mr. George Benneth an Accountant with the Union Bank of Nigeria Plc. I came to know of you in my private search for a reliable and Reputable person to handle this confidential transaction, which involves the transfer of a huge sum of money to a foreign account requiring maximum confidence. A pipeline Engineer, Late Engineer Walter Tang Min, with the Federal Government of Nigeria. Until his death five years ago in a ghastly air crash, banked with us here at Union Bank Plc. Benin City. He had a closing balance of US$13.5M (Thirteen Million, Five Hundred Thousand United States Dollars) which the deposited bank in question are questioning and expecting the money and some other properties to be claimed by any available foreign next-of-kin or alternatively to be donated to a discredited trust fund for importation of arms and Ammunition at a military war college here in Nigeria. Fervent and valuable efforts are being made by the Union Bank to get in touch with any of the Walter Min's family or relatives but all proved non-avail. It is because of the negative possibility of not being able to locate any of Late Engr. Walter Tang Min next-of-kin (he had no known wife or children) that the management under the influence of our chairman and member of the board of rectors, retired Major General Kalu Uke Kalu, that an arrangement must be made for the funds to be declared "UNCLAIMABLE/UNSERVICEABLE"and subsequently be donated to the Trust Fund for importation of Arms and Ammunition for further enhancement of war course in Africa and the world in general. In order to re-direct this negative development just because we want no more war, so be of my trusted colleagues and I now seek your permission to have you stand as a next-of-kin to Late Engr. Walter Tang Min so that the funds US$13.5M would be released and paid into your bank account as the beneficiary or next-of-kin. All documents and proves to enable you get this fund will be carefully worked out, more so we are assuring you of a 100% risk free involvement. Your share stays while the rest would be for my colleagues, myself and some disbursement of investment purposes in your country, which I shall abide on your guidelines on the lucrative business to hook on. We have agreed that after every deal is over, the funds will be shared thus, 35% of the money will go to you for acting as the beneficiary of the funds, 5% will be set aside for reimbursement to both parties for any incidental expenses that may be incur along the transfer, while the remaining 60% goes to myself and my immediate colleagues for been the originator of the transaction. If this proposal is OK by you and you do not wish to take undue advantage of the trust, we hope to bestow you and your company through this positive and lucrative venture, then kindly get back to me immediately via the above machine line nor through the overleaf email address on the screen of your good computer. Furnishing me with your most confidential information for an equitable enhancement and facilitation of the transfer. A. Your Full Name B. Your House Full Address C. Delivering Address D. National/Country E. Occupation F. Position At Work G. Your Bank Name H. Your Bank Address I. Account Number. J. Routing/Transit Number K. Your Reachable Telephone Nor Fax Number (It May Be Your Mobile Line) L. Neither Your International Passport Copy/Driving License. Your above and provided informations will be use in tally order to the deceased informations for release and subsequent transfer of the fund in your favor. Thank you in advance for soliciting this proposal and also for your anticipated co-operation. Yours faithfully, Mr. George Benneth.

Mr.David Sarr MANAGER:ECOBANK. DAKAR-SENEGAL.Branch. Email:da_sarr@katamail.com Tel: +221-4488469 Dear friend, I know this email will reach you as a surprise, but need not to worry as i am using the only secured and confidential medium available to seek for foreign assistance in a business. I would respectfully request that you keep the contents of this mail confidential and respect the integrity of the information you come by as a result of this mail. I am contacting you concerning a customer and deposit placed under our banks management 10 years ago,i am contacting you independently of our investigation and no one is informed of this communication. I am Mr.David Saar from Ecobank,Dakar-Senegal.Branch.This business request may seem strange, but I crave your indulgence and pray you view it seriously as I am convinced that you would be capable to provide me with a solution to a money transfer. On 6th,june,1997, a Nigerian came to make a (fixed) deposit valued at US$10,500,000.00(Ten Million Five Hundred Thousand Dollars )in my branch to be claimed by a foreing beneficiary to be later named,upon maturity,we sent a routine notification to his forwarding address but got no reply. After three years of sending reminder with no responce,we decided to open an investigation,and i was the head of the panel set up for the investigation,in the course of our investigation i finally discovered the money was Part of the loot the late Nigerian Ruler General Sani Abacha stole from Nigeria,the money was deposited under a false name. you can confirm it yourself via the website below. http://www.usatoday.com/news/opinion/columnists/wickham/2002-04-19-wickham.htm. On further investigation, I found out that no one knows of the deposit not even his family members he died without telling any one of it.Therefore he did not declare any next of kin or relations in all his documents, including his bank deposit paperwork in my bank as the deposit was a secret one,so i decided to keep the secret to my self as i view this as a once in a lifetime oportunity for me. My bank has waited for the beneficiary to come and make claims but no one has ever come forward,the reason is that he was yet to name the beneficiary before he died and i am the only one aware of this fact because i am the one in charge of the transaction. This sum of US$10,500,000.00 and the interest is being rolled over with the principal sum at the end of each year. No one will ever come forward to claim it According to my Country's law, at the expiration of 10(TEN)years,the money will revert to the ownership of the SENEGALESE Government if nobody applies to claim the fund. Consequently, my proposal is that I will like you as a foreigner to stand as the beneficiary to the deposit so that the money will not get into the hands of some corrupt Government officials. I assure you that I could have the deposit released to you in a few days. I will simply inform our bank of the final closing of the file relating to the deposit.This is simple,upon your approval,I will like you to provide immediately your full name and address so that the Attorney will prepare the necessary documents and affidavits which will put you in place as the beneficiary. We shall employ the service of two attorneys for the drafting and notarization of the WILL and obtain the necessary documents and letter of probate administration in your favour for the transfer. Any bank account in any part of the world which you will provide will then facilitate the transfer of this money to you as the beneficiary. The money will be paid into your account for us to share in ratio of 35% for me,35% for you,20% for any charity organization of our choice and 10 % will be set aside for expenses incured during the business . There is no risk at all;i have waited eigth(8)years now to be very sure of this plan,the paperwork for this transaction will be done by the attorney and my position as the Branch Manager guarantees the successful execution of this transaction. If you are interested, please reply immediately via the private email address below, upon your response, I shall provide you with more details and relevant documents that will help you understand the transaction. Please observe outmost confidentiality and be rest assured that this transaction would be most profitable for both of us because I shall require your assistance to invest my share in your country. Please upon your approval of this mail message, send to me the following to enable me start the processing of the fund transfer into your bank account:1.) The beneficiary's name and complete info.2.) Your private / official telephone and fax number. I am aware of the consequences of this proposal. I ask that if you find no interest in this project that you should discard this mail. I ask that you do not be vindictive or destructive. If my offer is of no appeal to you, delete this message and forget I ever contacted you. Do not destroy my career because you do not approve of my proposal. You may not know this but people like me who have made tidy sums out of comparable situations run the whole banking sector. I do not find this move against good conscience, this may be hard for you to understand, but the dynamics of my industry dictates that I make this move. Such opportunities only come ones way once in a lifetime. I cannot afford to let this chance pass me by, for once I find myself in total control of my destiny. This is my chance and I won't let it pass me by.If you will not work with me let me know and let me move on with my life but please do not destroy me.I am a family man and this is an opportunity to provide my family with new opportunities. There is a reward for this project and it is a task well worth undertaking.I have evaluated the risks and the only risk I have here is from you refusing to work with me and alerting my bank. Awaiting your Urgent Reply via my private email:da_sarr@katamail.com or call me on my private telephone number: +221-4488469 for further discussion. Thanks and God bless, Mr.David Sarr

CHAIRMAN TENDER BOARD OF NIGERIAN NATIONAL PETROLEUM COPORATION (N.N.P.C) TEL:+234-80-33013920 FAX:+234-1-7597156 EMAIL:drezenchi1@ecplaza.net DEAR FRIEND, I GUESS THIS LETTER MAY COME TO YOU AS A SURPRISE SINCE I HAD NO PREVIOUS CORRESPONDENCE WITH YOU.I AM THE CHAIRMAN TENDER BOARD OF NIGERIA NATIONAL PETROLEUM COPORATION (NNPC) I GOT YOUR CONTACT IN THE COURSE OF MY SEARCH FOR A RELIABLE PERSON WITH WHOM TOHANDLE A VERY CONFIDENTIAL TRANSACTION INVOLVING THE TRANSFER OF FUND VALUED EIGHT MILLION TWO HUNDRED THOUSAND UNITED STATES DOLLARS ($8.2M) TO A SAFE FOREIGN ACCOUNT. THE ABOVE FUND IN QUESTION IS NOT CONNECTED WITH ARMS,DRUGS OR MONEY LAUNDERING. IT IS THE PRODUCT OF OVER INVOICE ON CONTRACT AWARDED IN 2003 BY NNPC, TO A FOREIGN COMPANY FOR THE TURN AROUND MAINTAINERS OF NIGERIA OIL REFINARIES IN KADUNA STATE,DELTA STATE,AND LAGOS STATES OF NIGERIA.THE CONTRACT HAS LONG BEEN EXECUTED AND PAYMENT OF THE ACTUAL CONTRACT AMOUNT MADE TO THE FOREIGN CONTRACTOR, LEAVING THE BALANCE OF $8.2M U.S DOLLARS IN A DORMANT ACCOUNT WHICH MY COLLEAGUES AND WE NOW WANT TO TRANSFER OUT OF NIGERIA INTO A RELIABLE FOREIGN ACCOUNT FOR OUR PERSONAL USE. AS CIVIL SERVANTS, WE ARE NOT ALOWED BY THE LAW OF THE FEDERATION TO OPERATE A FOREIGN BANK ACCOUNT.THEREFORE IT BECOMES NECESSARY TO LOOK FOR A FOREIGN COMPANY WITH THE CAPABILITY TO ACT AS THE ORIGINAL BENEFICIARY OF THE CONTRACT.MY DEAR, IT IS A GOOD THING THAT THE PRESIDENT HAS ENDORSED THE RESOLUTION PASSED BY THE SENATE THAT ALL FOREIGN CONTRACTORS OWED BY THE FEDERAL GOVERNMENT OF NIGERIA SHOULD BE PAID, WE WILL SEIZE THIS GOOD OPPORTUNITY TO PURPORT YOU AS ONE OF THE BENEFICIARIES TO BE PAID. IF YOU ARE INTERESTED IN THIS PROPOSAL KINDLY SEND TO US YOUR LETTER OF ACCEPTANCE ALONG WITH YOUR DIRECT TELEPHONE AND FAX NUMBERS, BUT IF YOU CANNOT FOR ANY REASON HANDLE THIS TRANSACTION I SHOULD BE GRATEFUL IF YOU CAN INTRODUCE IT TO A RELIABLE AND TRUST WORTHY PERSON IN WHICH IN ANY CASE YOUR INTEREST WILL BEPROPERLY TAKEN CAREOF.MEANWHILE, MY COLLEAGUES AND I HAVE DECIDED TO SHARE THE MONEY IN THE FOLLOWING RATIO: 70% FOR MY COLLLEAGUES AND I, THEN 20% FOR YOU THE ACCOUNT OWNERAND 10% FOR ALL LOCAL AND INTERNATIONAL EXPENSES THAT MAY ARISE IN THE COURSE OF THIS TRANSACTION.FUTHER DETAILS ABOUT THIS TRANSACTION WILL BE DISCUSSED IN THE SUBSEQUENT CORRESPONDENCE. THIS TRANSACTION IS STRICTLY CONFIDENTIAL BUT 100% RISK FREE FOR BOTH OF US. NOTE ALSO THAT THE PARTICULAR NATURE OF YOUR BUSINESS IS IRRELEVANT TO THIS TRANSACTION AND THIS TRANSACTION IS EXPECTED TO BE CONCLUDED WITHIN 14 BANK WORKING DAYS SINCE ALL LOCAL CONTACTS AND  ARRANGEMENTS HAVE BEEN PROPERLY PERFECTED FOR A SMOOTH AND SUCCESSFUL CONCLUSION OF THIS TRANSACTION. YOURS FAITHFULLY, DR EZE N. MARK. CHAIRMAN(TBNNPC). N:B,PLEASE FOR THE BEST INTREST AND SECURITY OF THIS TRANSACTION,SEND YOUR REPLIES TO MY PRIVATE EMAIL ADDRESS(drezenchi1@ecplaza.net) AND CALL MY PRIVATE CEL PHONE:234-80-33013920 FOR MORE EXPLANATIONS, THANKS. ________________________________________________________________________ SERVIZIO VOICE: TELEFONA e INVIA SMS dal tuo computer a tariffe vantaggiose! Scopri come telefonare e videochiamare gratis da pc a pc. http://voice.repubblica.it

Dear Friend, I am Mr. Clive Osborne, the first son of John Osborne, the popular black farmer in Macheke district of Zimbabwe who narrowly escape during killing of Mr David Stevens the father of two-year-old twins - was shot dead at point blank range in the land dispute in my country. My father Mr. Osborne, who rushed was to a hospital in the provincial centre of Marondera, said he himself was only spared because someone spoke up for him; he later died after a protracted injuries he sustained as a result of the mob action. ( http://news.bbc.co.uk/1/hi/world/africa/715001.s tm) Before the death of my father, he had taken me to Holland to deposit the sum of US 8.4 million {Eight million four hundred thousand United States dollars}, in one of the private security company, as he foresaw the looming danger in Zimbabwe. This land problem came when Zimbabwean President Mr. Robert Mugabe introduce a new land Act Reform wholly affecting the rich white farmers and some few black farmers and this resulted to the killing and mob action by Zimbabwean war veterans and some lunatics in the society. In fact a lot of people were killed because of this land reform Act for which my father was one of the victims. It is against this background that, I and my family fled Zimbabwe for fear of our lives and are currently staying in Holland where we are seeking political asylum and more so have decided to transfer my father's money to a more reliable foreign account. Since the law of Holland prohibits a refugee {asylum seeker} to open any bank account or to be involve in any financial transaction. As the eldest son of my father, I am saddled with the responsibility of seeking a genuine foreign partner/account where this money could be transferred without the knowledge of my government who are bent on taking everything we have acquired. Sir / Madam, If you are willing to undertake this with me I am willing to give you 25% of the fund for your assistance and I have also mapped out 5% to cover any expenses incurred from the transaction. Also be aware the balance amount will be set aside for the investment through you and the profit from the investment will be share 50% each for you and my family after expenses. Please contact me on my e-mail address or my phone number below. Yours sincerely, Mr. Clive Osborne +31626662624. Email:mrcliveosborn@netscape.net reply to mrcliveosborn@netscape.net

Dear SIR, I am Miss Sorie DUNCAN and my Brothe Sam DUNCAN, we are the children of late Chief Benjamin DUNCAN from Sierra Leone. I am writing you in absolute confidence primarily to seek your assistance to transfer our cash of Four Million Dollars ($4,000.000.00) now in the custody of a private Security trust firm in Europe, the money is in trunk box deposited and declared as family valuables by my late father as a matter of fact the company does not know the content of the box, although my father made them to understand that the box belongs to his foreign partner. My late father Chief Benjamin DUNCAN , a native of Mende District in the Northerh province of Sierra Leone, was the General Manager of Sierra Leone Mining co-operation (S.L.M.C.) Freetown. According to my father, this money was the income accrued from Mining Co-operation's over draft and minor sales. Before the peak of the civil war between the rebels forces of (Mr.Foday Saybana Sankoh) and the combined forces of ECOMOG peace keeping operation that almost destroyed my country, following the forceful removal from power of the civilian elected President Ahmed Tejan Kabbah by the rebels. My father had already made arrangement for his family that talking about my mother, my little Brother and myself to be evacuated to Abidjan Cote d'Ivoire with the CERTIFICATE OF DEPOSIT he made with a security firm in Europe through the aid of U.N evacuation team. During the war in my country, and following the indiscriminate looting of Public and Government properties by the rebel forces, the Sierra Leone mining coop. Was one of the target looted and it was destroyed. My father including other top Government functionaries were attaked and killed by the rebels in November 2000 because of his relationship with the civilian Government of Ahmed Tejan Kabbah. As a result of my father death, and with the news of my uncle's involvement in the air crash in January it dashed our hope of survival. The untimely deaths caused my mother's heart failure and other related complications of which she later died in the hospital after we must have spent a lot of money on her early this year. Now my 22 years old Brother and myself are alone in this strange country suffering without any care or help. Without any relation, we are now a refugees. Our only hope now is in you and the box deposited in the Security Firm to this effect, I humbly solicit your assistance in the followings ways. 1) To assist us claim this box from the security firm as our beneficiary. 2)To transfer this money (USD$4M) in your name to your country. 3)To make a good arrangement for a joint business investment on our behalf in your country and you we be our Adviser/ Manager. For your assistance, I have agreed with my younger Brother that 30% of the total amount will be for your effort. I urge you to keep this transaction strictly confidential as no one knows our where about. Please as you show your willingness, Forward to us your full name, address and Tel/ Fax numbers, to me via our private email address as indicated bellow, this is for security reasons as i will only be accessing my private email earnestly awaiting your response. alternative email address: soriesam@handbag.com or sorie27@myway.com Thanks. May God bless you . Mr.Sorie DUNCAN.

FROM: Mr. Mark Andreas TEL: + 27-73-370-9157 Johannesburg, South Africa. Dear Sir / Madam, I am Mark Andreas,  the son of comrade Border Andreas who was the former Zimbabwean Minister for youth, gender and Employment creation. While alive, my father stood against seizure of white farms and it's distribution  to the blacks without compensation to the white owners.   First and foremost, I apologized using this medium to reach you for a transaction / business of this magnitude, but this is due to Confidentiality and prompt access reposed on this medium. In unfolding this proposal, I want to count on you, as a respected and honest person to handle this transaction with sincerity, trust and confidentiality. I have decided to seek a confidential co-operation with you in the execution of the transaction described hereunder for the benefit of all parties involved and hope you will keep it as a top secret because of the nature of this transaction.   Because of what is happening in the world today and to verify my predicaments as well as my sincerity, I would like you to visit the site below to read more about my father.  Www.Mweb.co.zw/standard/index.php? id=2908&pubdate=2001-04-29 www.dailynews.co.zw/daily/2001/December/December4/3891.htm1 www.zimbabwewhitefarmers.co.zw   Because of my father’s sincerity, he was killed by a planned motor accident along Harare-Masvingo Road near Mvuma Province of Zimbabwe. But before his untimely death, my father told me some few weeks earlier that he kept a box with a private Security and finance Company in Johannesburg, South Africa which contains US$20.5 Million (Twenty million, five hundred thousand United States dollars). He warned that he only declared the contents of the box to the Security and finance Company as family treasure/ valuables, with insurance values of the said amount. He also told me that he used my name as the beneficiary of this money being his first child.   The original document that shows the Deed of lodge, Proof of Deposit, and Depository Agreement between my late father and the Management of the Security Company was kept with my mother.   After my father’s death, mother, my little sister and I ran to South Africa to seek asylum for our lives. Because of the South African financial law which prohibits asylum seekers/refugees like my mother and I to open bank account or involve in any financial transaction, I decided to write to you to seek your assistance for this money to be transferred into your company’s or personal bank account while all arrangement for a hitch free transfer have been fully taken care of. I have the authority of my family to propose that should you be willing to assist us in this transaction your share as compensation will be US$5.125m (25%), while my family takes US$13.325m (65%) and the balance of US$2.5m (10%) for miscellaneous expenses that may be incurred by either party during the transfer.   I want to let you know that this transaction is 100% risk free provided you treat it with utmost confidentiality because the Zimbabwean Government are bent on collecting  all assets / properties belonging to my late father.   Please, I do hope that this money will be safe when finally transferred into your account and I do hope of establishing a good relationship with you and your family after this transaction. I wait to hear from you.   Regards & God bless, Mr. Mark Andreas (For and on behalf of my family)

Send instant messages to your online friends http://uk.messenger.yahoo.com

Yahoo! Messenger NEW - crystal clear PC to PC calling worldwide with voicemail

Mr Willams Terry Commercial Bank Of senegal 118 Rue Dial Yorff Dakar Senegal West Africa Dear Friend, I cant imagine how you will feel receiving a sudden business letter from a remote country in far away Africa and probably from someone you are not closely related with. But all the same, I believe we do not need to be of blood relatives before we can establish cordial/business relationship. Having said this,I think it is very important at this juncture to introduce myself to you. I am Mr.Wiilams Terry , Head: Enterprise Wide Risk and member of the executive and risk committees of Commecial Bant of Senegal.I got your information while browsing through internet in search of a reliable person who will assist me.This is an urgent and very confidential business proposition. On June 7, 2000,a Foreign Oil consultant/contractor with the Senegal Institute of Mining and Metallurgy, Mr.Kurt Kahle made a numbered time(Fixed) Deposit for twelve calendar months, valued at US$10,500, 000.00,(Ten Million, five hundred thousand Dollars). Upon maturity,I sent a routine notification to his forwarding address but got no reply. After a month, we sent a reminder and finally we discovered from his Private Business School. employers, that On the 31st of July 2000, our client, with his 37-year-old wife and his son Michael, aged eight died in the Air France concord plane crash bound for New York in their plan for a world cruise, with other passengers abroad as you can confirm it yourself via the website below: http://news.bbc.co.uk/1/hi/world/europe/859479.stm On further investigation,I found out that he died without making a "WILL",and all attempts to trace his next of kin was fruitless. I therefore made further investigation and discovered that Mr.Mr.Kurt Kahle did not declare any next of kin or relations in all his official documents,including his Bank Deposit paperwork in my Bank. This sum of US$10,500,000.00 has carefully been fixed in my bank for safekeeping. No one will ever come forward to claim it.According to Senegal Law, at the expiration of 5 (five) years, the money will revert to the ownership of the Government if nobody applies to claim the fund. Consequently, my proposal is that I will like you as a foreigner to stand as the next of kin to Mr. Kurt Kahle so that the fruit of this old man's labor will not get into the hands of some corrupt Government officials.I am writing you because I as a public servant,i cannot operate a foreign account. I want to present you as the owner of the funds so you will be able to claim them with the help of my attorney.I will like you to provide immediately your full names and address so that the Attorney will prepare the necessary documents which will put you in place as the beneficiary of the funds. The money will be moved out for us to share in the ratio of 60% for me and 40% for you. The paperwork for this transaction will be done by the Attorney If you are interested, please reply immediately via my email address and upon your response,I shall then provide you with more details that will help you understand the transaction. Please observe utmost confidentiality, and be rest assured that this transaction would be most profitable for both of us because I shall require your assistance to invest my share in real estate within your country. Due to the nature of confidentiality in this Transaction our communication can only be via email and fax mostly. Awaiting your urgent reply via email. willam77terry@yahoo.co.uk Thanks and my regards. Mr.Wiiilams Terry. PLEASE REPLY TO MY PRIVATE EMAIL: NOTE: If however, you are not disposed to assist, kindly delete/destroy this email in view of the confidentiality of the proposed transaction and interest of personalities involves.

Attn: I am Mr. Jacko Maree the C.E.O of Islamic Development Bank (IDB) Dakar,Senegal. However I got your contact from the web during my search for help.I decided to contact you by email because I feel that it is more secured and private. Recently I discovered a Dormant Account with a huge amount of Money Valued US$31,823,000.00 USD[Thirty one million eight hundred and twenty three thousand United States Dollars] that belongs to one of our late Customer who died in a plane crash .During my investigation and auditing in this bank, my department came across a very huge sum of money belonging to Late Mr.Morris Thompson an American great industrialist and a resident of Alaska,who unfortunately lost his life in the plane crash of Alaska Airlines Flight 261 which crashed on January 31 2000,including his wife and only daughter.You shall read more news about the crash on visiting this site which I got during my investigation; <http://www.cnn.com/2000/US/02/01/alaska.airlines.list/> The fund has been dormant in his account With this Bank without any claim of the funds in our custody either from his family or relation before my discovery of this development.The Banking law here stipulates that if such money remains unclaimed for ten years, it will be forfeited to the Bank treasury as an unclaimed bill.It is only a foreigner that can stand as a next of kin and It is upon this discovery that I decided to contact you to collaborate with you to pull out this dormant fund.In order to avert this negative development, I now seek your permission to have you stand in as next of kin to Our late Customer so that the fund will be released and paid into your account as the beneficiary´s next of kin now that the bank is still expecting a next of kin or relative of the deceased ,Late Mr. Morris Thompson. In fact I could have done this deal alone but because of my position in this country as civil servant,I am not allowed to operate a foreign account and that would eventually raise an eye brow on my side during the time of transfer since I still work in this bank, this is the actual reason why I required a second party or fellow who will assist me forward claims as the next of kin and also provide either an existing bank account or to set up a new Bank a/c immediately to receive this fund, even an empty a/c can also serve for this purpose. On smooth conclusion of this transaction,55% of the fund will be for me, I will give you 30% of the total transfered sum,10% for charity both in Senegal and in your country while the remaining 5% will be set aside to settle expenses both parties might incure during the transfer process. What I want from you is for you to act as the deceased next of kin. I have in my possession, all the necessary Documents to successfully accomplish the operation.Bear in mind that this transaction is 100% risk free. Further Information will be given to you as soon as I receive your positive response. PLEASE,THE CONTENT OF THIS LETTER IS A TOP SECRET AND I WILL WANT YOU TO KEEP IT TO YOURSELF ONLY. Sincerely yours, Mr. Maree Jacko.

THOMSON STELLA ABIDJAN COTE D'IVOIRE Bonjour , Respectueusement veuillez m'excuser je n'ai pas le choix, permettez moi de vous informer de ce problème qui me pousse à vous expedier ce message.J’ai obtenu vos coordonnés sur Internet,je me suis permis de vous envoyer ce message car les informations sur vous me mette en confiance,vous êtes une personnalité honorable et digne de confiance. A cet effet, je n’ai pas hésiter à me fier à vous pour mon problème qui concerne ma famille et moi.Je vous contacte en ce jour en espérant que cela conduira à une occasion d'affaire basée sur l'honnêteté et la transparence. Je suis THOMSON Stella la seule fille de 'ancien chef THOMSON ROBERT de la SIERA LEONNE. La source de votre contact me donne le courage et la confiance de me confier à vous. Je vous écris avec une confidence absolue premièrement pour demander votre assistance pour transférer notre liquidité de 20 000 000 million de dollar qui actuellement se trouve dans le coffre fort d'une compagnie de sécurité ici en Abidjan dans votre compte personnel jusqu'à notre arrivée dans votre pays. SOURCE DE L'ARGENT Mon défunt père, chef THOMSON , le patron des extracteur d'or et de diamant en Sierra Leone (S.L.M.C) Freetown. Concernant mon père, cet argent est le résultat de l'or et le diamant extraient des mines Sierra Léonaise avant le début de la guerre civil entre les forces rebelles et les forces de maintien de la paix de l'ECOMOG qui a détruit mon pays après le coup de force qui a chassé du pouvoir, le président démocratiquement élu AHMED TEJAN KABBAH. Mon père avait déjà mis en place un plan pour nous évacuer (ma famille) ma mère, mon petite frère et moi même sur Abidjan en Cote d'ivoire avec nos effets personnels et la boite contenant l'argent par le biais des forces d'évacuation des nations unies. Mon père nous a demandé de déposer la boite dans une compagnie privée de sécurité jusqu'à ce qu'il nous rejoigne après la guerre. Pendant la guerre dans mon pays, et avec pour conséquence le pillage des propriétés publiques et du gouvernement par les forces rebelles, la coopération des mines sierra léonaise étaient l'une des cibles pillées et détruites. Mon père et plusieurs autres haut fonctionnaires ont été attaqués et tués par les rebelles en novembre 2000 pour leur relation avec le gouvernement civil d'AHMED TEJAN KABBAH. Suite à la mort de mon père, et avec les nouvelles de mon oncle à propos de son accident d'avion en janvier, nos espoirs de survie étaient complètement noyés. Cette mort prématurée de mon père et de mon oncle a provoqué un arrêt cardiaque chez ma mère et d'autres complications qui ont provoqués sa mort plus tard dans un hôpital et après on a eu à dépenser une importante somme d'argent pour elle. Actuellement mon frère de 18 ans et moi même sommes seuls dans ce pays étrange, souffrant et sans aucun soutien . sans aucune relations, nous sommes actuellement comme des réfugiés et des orphelins. Notre seul espoir actuellement est en vous et en la boite qu'on déposé dans la compagnie de sécurité. A cet effet, je sollicite humblement votre assistance dans le sens suivant : 1- m'aider à faire sortir la boite de la compagnie de sécurité comme CO- bénéficiaire pour transférer cet argent en votre nom dans votre propre compte dans votre pays pour un investissement lucratif .avec vous comme principal acteur. 2- Le plus important c'est que la compagnie de sécurité ne connaît pas le contenu exact de la boite parce qu'on l'a déclaré comme richesses familiales. 3- Tous les documents relatifs au dépôts sont dans mon coffre a la maison. 4- Pour votre assistance, je vous céderai 20% de cet argent pour vos efforts et votre assistance. 5- Enfin je vous prie de garder cette transaction strictement confidentiel. Merci et que Dieu vous bénisse pour votre assistance à notre égard. NB; excuse mais j'aimerai que vous ne contactez sur cette adresse; thomsonstella06@yahoo.fr Très sincèrement Stella

FROM THE DESK OF ADAMA IBRAHIM BILL AND EXCHANGE MANAGER AFRICAN DEVELOPMENT BANK OUAGADOUGOU BURKINA FASO TELEPHONE NUMBER 00226 76 53 26 12 Dear Friend, I crave your indulgence for the unsolicited nature of this letter, but it was borne out of desperation and current development. please bear with me. My name is Mr.ADAMA IBRAHIM, an Auditor of African Development Bank I discovered existing dormant account for 5 years. When I discovered that there had been no continuation nor withdrawals from this account for this long period and our banking law stipulates that any un serviceable account for more than 5 years will go into the bank revenue as an unclaimed fund. I have made personal inquiries about the depositor and his next of kin but sadly, the depositor and his next of kin died in motor acident while the rest of the family died in Iraq during the crisis,I only made this investigation just to be double sure of this fact and since I have been unsuccessful in locating the Relatives. I seek your consent to Present yourself as the next of kin of the deceased. As an auditor in the bank I will use my position in the bank to help you becoming the next of kin to the estate, so that the proceeds of this account valued at $25.6 million dollars can be transfered to you, this is the story in a nutshell. Now I want an account overseas where the bank will transfer this funds. Thereafter, I will come for the sharing and investment, also to use part of the money to help the Iraqians, It is a careful network and for the past eleven months I have worked out everything to ensure a hitch-free operation. Now my questions are:- 1. Can you handle this project? 2. Can I give you this trust? Consider this and get back to me as soon as possible, All what I require is your honest co-operation to enable us see this deal through, I guarantee that this will be executed under a legitimate arrangement that will protect you from any breach of the law, please get in touch with me by my e-mail to enable me outline to you the strategies on how to go about this, You may also send your phone number so that I can call you. Finally, it is my humble prayer that the information as contained herein be accorded the necessary attention, urgency as well as the secrecy it deserves, also send to me your personal information, to enable me send to you official text of application .. I Expect your urgent response if you can handle this project. also call me. Respectfully yours, Reply via : ( adama_010@yahoo.fr ) Telephone:00226 7653 2612 ADAMA IBRAHIM _________________________________________________________________ Tout savoir sur la sécurité de votre PC ! http://go.msn.fr/10-channel/80-security/spam/default.asp

Dear Friend, I am Dr.Micheal Dudu. of Logistics officers of (W.E.A.C. A) West African Control Authorities Dakar Senegal , with due honour I am contacting you in the respect of fund to be transfer to your account. This fund belongs to Mr. Robbin Marvin, Inview of the above we are working as the International Monitoring Committee here in the West Africa, and we monitor every out going and incoming huge fund that was leaving every bank from the West African States to any destination in the whole world. And this organization was empowered by the USA Government (NDLEA) National Drug Law Enforcement Agency after (911) September 11 2001 bomb blast in United State of America, to make sure that every fund that was leaving the West African region has no relationship with Anti Drug Law or Terrorism. This sum of $17.8 M USD (Seventeen Million Eight Hundred Thousand United States Dollars) is still in our correspondent Bank where it was held prior for transfer after the investigation before the report came to us that he died, and since then no one has come forward to claim it since the report of his sudden death. Mr Robbin Marvin of United States of America's fund has proved legitimate. According to the rules and stipulation of the organization of WEACA at the expiration of 7 (seven) weeks from now, the money will be re-called back to the Central Bank of Senegal if nobody applies to claim the funds as a cousin or beneficiary next of kin to Mr Robbin. Based on my position in this organization, I have kept the facts of this case I am still watching closely to myself alone.The reason I have decided to contact you is because I am quite certain I can move these funds out immediately but would need your assistance. What this requires is that you put in an application of claim into this fund with my guide line. This will enable the Bank where the money was held to open a premium account and make an internal database transfer of the Funds to your account. However, in the fact that our European Bank may not entertain your request to open an account without a proof of the fund origin, I will without divulging forward to you the whole documents of the said fund and will forward it to you when I have your interest in this matter, On grounds that you agree to do this with me, the money will be shared in the ratio of 60% for me and the chief executive and protocol officer of WAECA who is the only peoples that knows the fact and origin of this fund then 40% for you. It is quite necessary that these are kept as confidential as possible for its successive completion. Please contact me and I will take it from there. Once I hear from you,I will give you all the paper that will lead you to our Correspondent bank ’s online service the Europe. Please reply through my email request. I will be expecting your reply, NAME.................................. MAILING ADDRESS....................... AGE:.................................. STATUS:............................... STATE/COUNTRY......................... TEL(PRIVATE)/FAX NUMBERS....................... COMPANY NAME......................... OCCUPATION.......................... Yours Sincerely Dr.Micheal Dudu. Member Official Of W.A.E.C.A.

Mrs.Alima Makoba C/o Eglise(Catholic church ) Liberte Sicap 1, Dakar Senegal. Tel:++221 5888-952 Good Day. I know this mail will come to you as a surprise. Nevertheless I am Mrs.Alima Makoba, aged 59 years, the wife of Major Yusuf Makoba, Chief Security Officer and Aide-de–camp to the exiled president Charles Tailor of Liberia . As a result of the on-going problem in my country, I am saddled with problems of my ill-health of protracted diabetes and high blood pressure which is getting of increase in the recent times, more importantly getting a trust worthy individual abroad to receive the sum of US$13.2million on our behalf which I intend to invest in your company. Due to this crises presently in my city Monrovia our home town, I managed to sneak myself and my son David 23 years of age and four other of my daughters out of Monrovia to Dakar senegal for safety. We were sneaked into Dakar Senegal through the land boarder by the help of some government militant group. After the killing of my husband by the rebels, we decided to come down here to Dakar senegal to secure the this deposit deposited here by my husband and to further look for a trust worthy individual abroad to receive these deposit which has being deposited here in Dakar Senegal before he was eventually killed by the heartless rebels. I feel confident therefore to introduce myself to you based on this problem and our present condition as all our foreign contacts and connections got lost during this crises, all properties burnt by the rebels. I am desperately in need to move and re-locate this huge deposit to your country for safe keeping as this is the only wealth remaining for the future survival and well being of my large family. For your percentage for assistance, a negotiable percentage will be discussed as soon as I receive your response based on this plea for your assistance as our lives are highly in danger due to this problem. I pray and plead for your help. Please endavour to email me back for further clarifications over this issue. God bless you as you respond to my plea for assistance.My telephone 00221 5888-952 and phone will be open for your call any time but if I am not available the time of your call, my son tanko will respond to you accordingly. Sincerely yours. Mrs. Alima Makoba.

From:Nelison& Linda. Abidjan Cote d'Ivoire. Email:nelsonkamara_2@walla.com Dear Respectful One, Permit me to inform you our desire of going into business relationship with you. I know you might be surprised on recieving this mail from us due to we have not met before. By brief introduction , I am Nelison and Linda, my younger sister. We are native of bouake district in republic of Cote d'Ivoire. We are the children of late Chief and Mrs. David Kamara, who was assasinated by the rebels in our home town during the recent political crises of 19th sept.2003. Untill the death of our parents, they were very wealthy Cocoa/cafe farmers & exporter based in abidjan the capital city of coted'ivoire. Before their death in a private specialist hospital, my father called me on his bed side and secretly confided to me the sum of US$10.5 million dollars which he deposited in one of the banks in Abidjan, Cote d'Ivoire for onwardly transfer abroad for investment on his proposed cocoa processing company through an assistance of a foreign partner. My father also told me his intension to invest part of the money in collaboration with oil companies in countries like Libya, America or Europe, but unfortunately he died the way he did without accomplishing his objective as a result of the rebels attack. Having know that he will not survive from the injuries he sustained as a result of the wounds and pains inflinched on him by the rebels, then advised me to quickly and hurriedly go into his personal underground safe in our family villa and take the documents covering the deposit in the bank and look for a true and trustworthy foreigner assist us as partner to front to the bank as our late parents partner abroad for immediate transfer of the money for investment in any lucrative business of our chioce for our future welfare. Upon the instruction and advice by my father before he finally died, I therefore request your assistance to help us for onward transfer of the money to your country for investment partnership with you in any lucrative business in your country. We have agreed to give you 20% of the total sum immediately the transfer is made, while 2.5% also will be set aside to cover all the expenses you might incure on the process. Upon your acceptance to our proposal, kindly get back to me through the above email address so that we can discuss further process on the ways to achieve this golden success together. Note, we are still in the refugee camp Yamussoukro, Cote d'Ivoire, We need your urgent attention to this mail because we want to leave here for a better future with you abroad, as the rebels had killed our parent and also have taken over my home town as their operational territory, we look forward to you to help us with most urgency and honesty. Expecting your reply soon. Best Regard and God Bless you. Nelison & sister PLEASE reply us at/nelsonkamara_2@walla.com ______________________________________ Platíte zbyteènì drahé povinné ruèení? Zjistìte si cenu v online kalkulaèce nebo na tel. 841 444 444. O bonus nepøijdete, pøevedeme vám ho. http://ad.tiscali.com/adclick/CID=0002ceb4c6efdc0e00000000/SITE=CZ.TISCALI/AREA=NEWSLETTER..HOME/POS=L2

DEAR FRIEND, ATTENTION PLEASE, I AM DR IDRIS ALI, THE DIRECTOR IN CHARGE OF AUDITING AND ACCOUNTING SECTION OF AFRICAN DEVELOPMENT BANK (A.D.B) OUAGADOUGOU BURKINA-FASO WEST AFRICA. WITH DUE RESPECT AND REGARD. I HAVE DECIDED TO CONTACT YOU ON A BUSINESS TRANSACTION THAT WILL BE VERY BENEFICIAL TO BOTH OF US AT THE END OF THE TRANSACTION . DURING OUR INVESTIGATION AND AUDITING IN THIS BANK, MY DEPARTMENT CAME ACROSS A VERY HUGE SUM OF MONEY BELONGING TO A DECEASED PERSON WHO DIED IN A PLANE CRASH AND THE FUND HAS BEEN DORMANT IN HIS ACCOUNT WITH THIS BANK WITHOUT ANY CLAIM OF THE FUND IN OUR CUSTODY EITHER FROM HIS FAMILY OR RELATION BEFORE OUR DISCOVERY TO THIS DEVELOPMENT. THE SAID AMOUNT WAS U.S 7.5M (SEVEN MILLION,FIVE HUNDRED THOUSAND UNITED STATES DOLLARS). AS IT MAY INTEREST YOU TO KNOW, I GOT YOUR IMPRESSIVE INFORMATION THROUGH INTERNET DIRECTORY . MEANWHILE ALL THE WHOLE ARRANGEMENT TO PUT CLAIM OVER THIS FUND AS THE BONAFIDE NEXT OF KIN TO THE DECEASED, GET THE REQUIRED APPROVAL AND TRANSFER THIS MONEY TO A FOREIGN ACCOUNT HAS BEEN PUT IN PLACE AND DIRECTIVES AND NEEDED INFORMATION WILL BE RELAYED TO YOU AS SOON AS YOU INDICATE YOUR INTEREST AND WILLINGNESS TO ASSIST, AND ALSO BENEFIT YOUR SELF TO THIS GREAT BUSINESS OPPORTUNITY. IN FACT I COULD HAVE DONE THIS DEAL ALONE BUT BECAUSE OF MY POSITION IN THIS COUNTRY AS A CIVIL SERVANT(A BANKER),WE ARE NOT ALLOWED TO OPERATE A FOREIGN ACCOUNT AND WOULD EVENTUALLY RAISE AN EYE BROW ON MY SIDE DURING THE TIME OF TRANSFER BECAUSE I WORK IN THIS BANK. THIS IS THE ACTUAL REASON WHY IT WILL REQUIRE A SECOND PARTY OR FELLOW WHO WILL FORWARD CLAIMS AS THE NEXT OF KIN WITH AFFIDAVIT OF TRUST OF OATH TO THE BANK AND ALSO PRESENT A FOREIGN ACCOUNT WHERE HE WILL NEED THE MONEY TO BE RE-TRANSFERRED INTO ON HIS REQUEST AS IT MAY BE AFTER DUE VERIFICATION AND CLARIFICATION BY THE CORRESPONDENT BRANCH OF THE BANK WHERE THE WHOLE MONEY WILL BE REMITTED FROM TO YOUR OWN DESIGNATION BANK ACCOUNT. I WILL NOT FAIL TO INFORM YOU THAT THIS TRANSACTION IS 100% RISK FREE.ON SMOOTH CONCLUSION OF THIS TRANSACTION, YOU WILL BE ENTITLED TO 30% OF THE TOTAL SUM AS GRATIFICATION, WHILE 10% WILL BE SET ASIDE TO TAKE CARE OF EXPENSES THAT MAY ARISE DURING THE TIME OF TRANSFER AND ALSO TELEPHONE AND INTERNET BILLS, WHILE 60% WILL BE FOR ME AND MY COLEAGUES. PLEASE, YOU HAVE BEEN ADVICED TO KEEP "TOP SECRET" AS I AM STILL IN SERVICE AND INTEND TO RETIRE FROM SERVICE AFTER WE CONCLUDE THIS DEAL WITH YOU. I WILL BE MONITORING THE WHOLE SITUATION HERE IN THIS BANK UNTIL YOU CONFIRM THE MONEY IN YOUR ACCOUNT AND ASK ME TO COME DOWN TO YOUR COUNTRY FOR SUBSEQUENT SHARING OF THE FUND ACCORDING TO PERCENTAGES PREVIOUSLY INDICATED AND FURTHER INVESTMENT, EITHER IN YOUR COUNTRY OR ANY COUNTRY YOU ADVICE US TO INVEST IN. ALL OTHER NECESSARY VITAL NFORMATION WILL BE SENT TO YOU WHEN I HEAR FROM YOU. I LOOK FORWARD TO RECEIVE YOUR PHONE AND FAX NUMBERS FOR EASY COMMUNICATION, YOURS FAITHFULLY, DR IDRIS ALI. ¡Miles de amigos con tus mismas aficiones! http://www.latinchat.com

I TRANSLATE ON INTERNET BECAUSE I HEAR NOT TOO MUCH ENGLISH   Respectfully, allow me to inform you of my desire to make deals with vous.J' obtained your co-ordinates on the Net and I allowed myself to send to you I am KONAN AYA ELODIE only daughter of the defunts Mister and Mrs KONAN ALBERT my father was associated to businessmen in the field of the coffee cocoa and it is following a business dinner that he was poisoned by these associates, because he was seen by the large investors and basic financial backers, seen more the many contracts which he signed with the world and also with farmers of our country. My mother died when I was very small and since then, my father occupied himself of me carefully. Before its death in August 2002 following a poisoning, it indicated to me that he deposited the sum of eleven millio two hundred and thousand dollars $11.200.000 USDollars in a company of safety which bears my name as the heritier here in Abidjan. And my partner in business like the beneficiare. he also explained me that it is for this sum that he was poisoned by his associates and that I should seek a foreign associate in a country of my choice where I must transfer this money and to invest in an activity with an aim to assured my future. But I will tell you things, he said that he has to keep this money in societé of security in two boxes being that objets d'art and éffets familliale. The goal of this message is to solicit of your assistance in a following way: (1) to help me has to collect this money societé security because I do not want to lose them and to invest them in that it business does not matter that you will find very very advantageous. (2) act as my guardian asI am the only daughter and I have 22ans. (3) once money transferred in your country you must help me has to join you in your country to continue my studies or you help me to have an authorization permanent resident. In addition, all what you will have invested in this business will be to refund to you and also I am laid out to offer 25% of all to you summon as a recognition for your efforts provided. I taken to you to indicate your intentions to me to help me, because I will like of all  that this transaction is concluded as quickly as possible. Respectfully, KONAN AYA ELODIE   Respectueusement, permettez moi de vous informer de mon desir de faire des affaires avec vous.J'ai obtenu vos coordonnées sur le net et je me suis permis de vous envoyer  Je suis KONAN AYA ELODIE fille unique des defunts Monsieur et Madame KONAN ALBERT   mon père était associé à des hommes d’affaires dans le domaine du café cacao et c’est à la suite d’un dîner d’affaire qu’il fut empoisonné par ces associés, car il était le plus vu par les grands investisseurs et bailleurs de fond, vue les nombreux contrats qu’il signait de part le monde et aussi avec des agriculteurs de notre pays. Ma mère est morte quand j'etais très petite et depuis lors, mon père s’occupait de moi avec soins.  Avant sa mort en août 2002 suite à un empoisonnement,il m’a indiqué qu’il à la somme de onze million deux cent mille dollars Américain $11.200.000 USDollars dans une société de securite qui porte mon nom comme l'heritière ici à  Abidjan. Et mon partenaire en affaire comme le beneficiare. Il m’a aussi expliqué que c’est pour cette somme qu’il a été empoisonné par ces associés et que je devrais chercher un associé étranger dans un pays de mon choix où je dois transférer cet argent et investir dans une activité dans le but d’assuré notre avenir. Mais je vais vous dire une choses, il a dit qu'il a garder cet argent dans la societé de securité dans deux mallets étant que des objets d'arts et éffets familliale. Je tiens a vous informer aussi que la societe de securite demande une comme qu'il faut payer avant de recuperer les mallets. Le but de ce message est de solliciter  de votre aide de manière suivante : (1) m'aider a faire sortir cet argent de la societé de securité car je ne veux pas les perdre et les investir dans n'importe qu'elle affaire que vous trouvera tres tres profitable.   (2) me servir de conseiller et gestionnaire de ces      fonds,puisque je suis la fille unique et j'ai 22ans. (3) une fois l’argent transféré dans votre pays     vous devez  m'aider a vous rejoindre dans       votre pays pour continuer mes études ou vous    allez m'aider à avoir une autorisation     de résident permanent.  Par ailleurs, tous ce que vous aurez investi dans cette affaire vous sera rembourser et aussi je suis disposées à vous offrir 25% de toute la somme en guise de reconnaissance pour vos efforts fourni. Je vous pris de m'indiquer vos intentions de m'aider, car j'aimerai de tous cœur que cette transaction soit conclue le plus vite possible.    Respectueusement, KONAN AYA ELODIE

Faites de Yahoo! votre page d'accueil sur le web pour retrouver directement vos services préférés : vérifiez vos nouveaux mails, lancez vos recherches et suivez l'actualité en temps réel. Cliquez ici.

Hello friend, I am contacting you from Africa. My name is Mr. Paul Moore. I work with the Evans National Bank , 14 North Main Street,Angola, NY 14006, as foreign operations manager. Please do not get upset as to how I got your contact.I got your email contact from the Internet. I sincerely advise that you calm down to read below proposal thoroughly and thereafter decide if we can do the business together. It is no setup or one of these hoaxes from Africa. This is a real deal and I mean every word I speak here. A UK citizen, Mr. Norman Anderson (from Aberdeen) has been a customer of my bank since 1988. He opened a domiciliary account with us in June 1988. The said bank account, which is at the moment in dormant, is in UK pounds sterling and has credit balance of 19.3M pounds. Last transaction carried on the account dates back to September 15, 1999. I have been the account owner’s confidant and account officer until above date when he was last seen in the bank. And since this time Mr. Anderson has not been to the bank nor sent in cheque for clearing. This became a source of worry to me and prompted my personal investigation as to whereabouts and business activity of this customer. Result of my investigation revealed that he was into oil bunkering and operated within West and Central Africa sub-regions. Further investigation proved that he was one of the victims of November 1999 raid of illegal oil bunkering merchants in Malabo Island of Equatorial Guinea. However, I continued my investigation and further discovered that a UK telephone number mentioned in our bank information form, which he filled when the said bank account was established, belong to a hotel in London. This is a clear indication that he probably has fed my bank with false information to protect his illegal oil deals. I have not disclosed these findings to anyone else except this message to you. After a careful study of the account file and available data to me, I have packaged a good deal as follows; and will wish to carry it out with you. My Dear Friend, the deal here is that the money in this account will be approved and remitted to any foreigner who shows up as relation to Mr Anderson provided such person has correct information to the account. I have such needed information and will hand it over to you as soon as we commence the transaction. I will source all necessary documents and forward them to you for direct submission to the bank. With my position as the foreign operations manager we will quietly remove this money from the bank without hitches. I don’t have any problem in regularizing all necessary documents and transferring the credit balance of the said account to your nominated bank account in overseas, but the problem is trust. I have spent months in trying to get an overseas reliable contact. It is worthy to note that people are unreliable these days and even derive joy in telling lies. On this ground I request your unreserved but sincere cooperation devoid of greed in carrying out this transaction so that no one amongst both of us shall defraud each other at the end. I am prepared to split at 60%---40% for you, provided that mine (60%) will be intact at the end. Awaits for your expected co-operation.Reply and send your Address, tel and fax nos. Best regards, Mr. Paul Moore. contact;paul_moore1@myway.com

FROM Edwina Rogers. Email:e_rogers@centrum.cz Abidjan, IvoryCoast. Please write and reply me through my yahoo box(edwina_rogers01@yahoo.fr) Dear Respectful, Warm greetings to you and your family in the name of our lord Jesus Christ. I am Edwina Rogers the only daughter of late Mr and Mrs Rogers. My father was a very wealthy Rubber plantation merchant and the managing director of Agro Rogers rubber plantation farm in Abidjan; the economic capital of Ivory Coast, my father was poisoned to death by his business associates on one of their outings on a business trip. My mother died when I was a baby and since then my father took me and my only kid brother (David) so special. Before the death of my father on November 2005 in a private hospital here in Abidjan he secretly called me on his bed side and told me that he has the sum of Ten million, five hundred thousand United State Dollars.USD($10.500,000) left in fixed / suspense account in one of the prime bank here in Abidjan ,that he used my name as his first child for the next of Kin in depositing of the fund. He also explained to me that it was because of this wealth that he was poisoned by his business associates. That I should seek for a foreign partner in a country of my choice where I will transfer this money and use it for investment purpose such as real estate management or hotel management. Now, I am honourably seeking your assistance in the following ways: (1) To serve as a guardian and foreign co-beneficiary of this fund. (2) To make arrangement for me and my brother to come over to your country to further our education and to secure resident permit in your country. I am willing to offer you 15% of the total sum as compensation for your effort/input after the transfer of this fund into your account overseas. Thank you for your signify interest to assist me and my younger brother. Hoping to hear from you soon. May God bless you and preserve our friendship in good faith. Best regards Edwina Rogers and brother, (David) Please write and reply me through my yahoo box(edwina_rogers01@yahoo.fr)

FROM THE DESK OF MR. MUSTAFA JOSEPH BILL AND EXCHANGE MANAGER AFRICAN DEVELOPMENT BANK OUAGADOUGOU, BURKINA FASO I AM THE MANAGER OF BILL AND EXCHANGE AT THE FOREIGN REMITTANCE DEPARTMENT OF AFRICAN DEVELOPMENT BANK BURKINA FASO. I GOT YOUR CONTACT ADDRESS THROUGH INTERNET NET WORK SEARCH WHEN SEARCHING FOR A GOOD AND RELIABLE PERSON THAT WILL ASSIST ME IN THIS TRANSACTION. IN MY DEPARTMENT WE DISCOVERED AN ABANDONED SUM OF 22.85M US DOLLARS ( TWENTY TWO MILLLION EIGHT HUNDRED AND FIFTY THOUSAND US DOLLARS)IN AN ACCOUNT THATBELONGS TO ONE OF OUR FOREIGN CUSTOMER WHO DIED ON 25TH JULY 2000 IN SUPER SONIC CONCORDE PLANE CRASH AT CHARLES DE GAULLE AIRPORT IN PARIS FRANCE ALONG WITH HIS ENTIRE FAMILY. SINCE WE GOT INFORMATION ABOUT HIS DEATH, WE HAVE BEEN EXPECTING HIS NEXT OF KIN TO COME OVER AND CLAIM HIS MONEY BECAUSE WE CANNOT RELEASE IT UNLESS SOMEBODY APPLIES FOR IT AS NEXT OF KIN OR RELATION TO THE DECEASED AS INDICATED IN OUR BANKING GUI DELINES BUT UNFORTUNATELY WE LEARNT THAT ALL HIS SUPPOSED NEXT OF KIN OR RELATION DIED ALONGSIDE WITH HIM AT THE PLANE CRASH LEAVING NOBODY BEHIND FOR THE CLAIM. IT IS THEREFORE UPON THIS DISCOVERY THAT I DECIDED TO MAKE THIS BUSINESS PROPOSAL TO YOU AND RELEASE THE MONEY TO YOU AS THE NEXT OF KIN OR RELATION TO THE DECEASED FOR SAFETY AND SUBSEQUENT DISBURSEMENT SINCE NOBODY IS COMING FOR IT AND I DON'T WANT THIS MONEY TO GO INTO THE BANK TREASURY AS UNCLAIMED BILL. THE BANKING LAW AND GUIDELINE HERE STIPULATES THAT IF SUCH MONEY REMAINED UNCLAMED AFTER SEVEN YEAR, THE MONEY WILL BE TRANSFERED INTO THE BANK TREASURY AS UNCLAIMED FUND. THE REQUEST OF FOREIGNER AS NEXT OF KIN IN THIS BUSINESS IS OCCASIONED BY THE FACT THAT THE CUSTOMER WAS A FOREIGNER AND A BURKINABE CANNOT STAND AS NEXT OF KIN TO A FOREIGNER. I AGREE THAT 30% OF THIS MONEY WILL BE FOR YOU AS FOREIGN PARTNER, IN RESPECT TO THE PROVISION OF A FOREIGN ACCOUNT AND 70% W OULD BE FOR ME; THEREFORE TO ENABLE THE IMMEDIATE TRANSFER OF THIS FUND TO YOU AS ARRANGED, YOU MUST APPLY FIRST TO THE BANK AS RELATIONS OR NEXT OF KIN OF THE DECEASED INDICATING YOUR BANK NAME, YOUR BANK ACCOUNT NUMBER, YOUR PRIVATE TELEPHONE AND FAX NUMBER FOR EASY AND EFFECTIVE COMMUNICATION AND LOCATION WHERE IN THE MONEY WILL BE REMITTED. UPON RECEIPT OF YOUR REPLY, I WILL SEND TO YOU BY FAX OR EMAIL THE TEXT OF THE APPLICATION. I WILL NOT FAIL TO BRING TO YOUR NOTICE THAT THIS TRANSACTION IS HITCH FREE AND THAT YOU SHOULD NOT ENTERTAIN ANY ATOM OF FEAR AS ALL REQUIRED ARRANGEMENTS HAVE BEEN MADE FOR THE TRANSFER. YOU SHOULD CONTACT ME IMMEDIATELY AS SOON AS YOU RECEIVE THIS MAIL THROUGH MY PRIVATE LINE 22676 08 66 92 YOUR'S FAITHFULLY MR. MUSTAFA JOSEPH ¡Miles de amigos con tus mismas aficiones! http://www.latinchat.com

77 Seaside Cottages Fish Hoek-Cape Town South Africa Tel:+874-763427915 or +874-763427918 Fax:+874-763427916 Hello, READ CAREFULLY PLEASE For this letter is strictly personal, intimate and confidential. Forgive this unusual manner of contacting you, but this particular letter is of exceptional and very private nature. There is absolutely going to be a great doubt and distrust in your heart in respect of this email, coupled with the fact that, so many miscreants have taken possession of the Internet to facilitate their nefarious deeds, thereby making it extremely difficult for genuine and legitimate business class persons to get attention and recognition. There is no way for me to know whether I will be properly understood, but it is my duty to write and reach out to you. For I know that you are the only one that can be trusted to handle this project effectively without making me regret. Though this approach appears desperate, difficulties encountered in efforts to establish a business abroad necessitate this search for someone to assist me in securing and investing this fund. My name is Bona Ken, I am the operational manager in account management section in charge of credit and foreign bills of one of the prime banks here in South Africa. I am writing in respect of a foreign customer of my bank who perished with his whole families on 18TH JULY 2003 in KENYAN PLANE CRASH with the whole passengers aboard. There is an account opened in this bank in 2000 by this great late INDUSTRIALIST who died without a written or oral 'WILL' attached to the account. Since his death, I personally has watched with keen interest to see the next of kin but all has proved abortive as no one has come to claim his funds and no other person knows about this account or anything concerning it,the account has no other beneficiary and until his death he was the manager of his company. The total amount involved is 116,000,000.00 USD.[One Hundred and Sixteen Million United States Dollar]. We wish to start the first transfer with $16,000,000.00 [Sixteen Million] and upon successful transaction without any disappointment from your side, we shall re-apply for the transfer of the remaining balance to your account. I have secretly discussed this matter with the general manager of the bank who I must involve in order to have a smooth and a successful transfer of the fund to any foreign bank account, which you are going to nominate. On this note, I decided to seek for a reliable foreigner who will act as the foreign beneficiary of the fund from the deceased by providing his/her bank account where the fund will be transferred for immediate investment on any viable project as no one has come up to be the next of kin. The banking ethics here does not allow such money to stay more than three years without claim hence the money will be recalled to the government treasury as unclaimed after this long period of dormancy. In view of this I got your contact through my personal search to see if you can assist by providing your safe bank account for the transfer or find a reliable person who will be capable of receiving such amount in his or her personal account. At the conclussion of the transfer 60% of the fund will be for me, I will give you 25% of the total transfer sum, 10% for charity both in Africa and in your country while the remaining 5% will be set aside to settle expenses both parties might incure during the transfer process. Upon the receipt of your reply, I will send to you detailed information about the transaction. I will not fail to bring to your notice that this business is 100% risk and trouble free and that you should not entertain any fear as all modalities for fund transfer can be finalized within 7 to 9 banking days, after you apply to the bank as the beneficiary of the fund from the deceased. When you receive this letter. Kindly send me e-mail . You should also include your private fax and phone numbers for easy and safe communication. Respectfully yours, Bona Ken. ______________________________________ Platíte zbyteènì drahé povinné ruèení? Zjistìte si cenu v online kalkulaèce nebo na tel. 841 444 444. O bonus nepøijdete, pøevedeme vám ho. http://ad.tiscali.com/adclick/CID=0002ceb4c6efdc0e00000000/SITE=CZ.TISCALI/AREA=NEWSLETTER..HOME/POS=L2

FROM: MR CHEUNG PUI cheugpuixx7@yahoo.com.hk Dear Friend, Let me start by introducing myself. I am Mr. Cheung Pui director of operations of the Hang Seng Bank Ltd.I have an obscured business suggestion for you. Before the U.S and Iraqi war our client "Major Fadi Basem who was with the Iraqi forces and also business man made a numbered fixed depositfor 18 calendar months, with a value of Twenty Four million Five Hundred Thousand United State Dollars only in my branch. Upon maturity several notice was sent to him,even during the war early this year. Again after the war another notification was sent and still no response came from him. We later find out that the Major and his family had been killed during the war in bomb blast that hit their home. After further investigation it was also discovered that Major Fadi Basem did not declare any next of kin in his official papers including the paper work of his bankdeposit. And he also confided in me the last time he was at my office that no one except me knew of his deposit in my bank. So, Twenty Four million Five Hundred Thousand United State Dollars is still lying in my bank and no one willever come forward to claim it. What bothers me most is that according to the to the laws of my country at the expiration 5 years the funds will revert to the ownership of the Hong Kong Government if nobody applies to claim the funds. Against this backdrop, my suggestion to you is that I will like you as a foreigner to stand as the next of kin to Major Fadi Basem so that you will be able to receive his funds. WHAT IS TO BE DONE: I want you to know that I have had everything planned out so that we shall come out successful. I have contacted an attorney that will prepare the necessary document that will back you up as the next of kin to Major Fadi Basem , all that is required from you at this stage is for you to provide me with your Full Names and Address so that the attorney can commence his job. After you have been made the next of kin, the attorney will also fill in for claims on your behalf and secure the necessary approval and letter of probate in your favor for the move of the funds to an account that will be provided by you. There is no risk involved at all in the matter as we are going to adopt a legalized method and the attorney will prepare all the necessary documents.Please endeavor to observe utmost discretion in all matters concerning this issue.Once the funds have been transferred to your nominated bank account we shall share in the ratio of 70% for me, 30% for you. Should you be interested please send me your full names and current residential address and I will prefer you to reach me on the email address below; EMAIL ADDRESS: cheugpuixx7@yahoo.com.hk And finally after that i shall provide you with more details of this operation. Your earliest response to this mail will be appreciated. Kind Regards, Mr. Cheung Pui.

My name is Mr Wu kwon from Korea and I would like you to guide me through the most viable investment opportunities in your Country. Alternatively, I can invest in your line of business if you are interested and if your line of business is viable. I am one of the defectors from the north and I am currently residing in South Korea.I have been in this Country for sometime now.Before defecting from the North,I was into currency exchange business and I was always travelling to other parts of Asia and Europe and during that period,I was able to move out my funds and deposit it in a vaulting company in EUROPE. I want to invest this funds in your Country with your help and advice because we are being treated as foreigners here. A lot of defectors now go on to Canada or the United States and some parts of Europe to live. For more details, please see the following websites; http://www.detnews.com/2003/nation/0310/09/a19e-292811.htm www.washingtonpost.com/ac2/wp-dyn/A41966-2003Oct3?language=printer http://www.iht.com/articles/531755.html http://www.freerepublic.com/focus/f-news/1181380/posts I want you to send me a complete breakdown of the investment opportunities in your Country and also let me know What exactly I need to do to enable you invest the funds for me in your Country. If interested,you will have to provide an account for receiving the investment funds.I will then come over to your Country after you receive the funds and work out the investment plans with you. After I hear from you and find out the best investment business you can introduce to me, I will tell you how much is involved. I will expect your response together with your contact details, preferably your private telephone number so that I can discuss further and additional details. Regards and God Bless Mr Wu kwon ______________________________________ Nejlevnìj¹í ADSL na trhu. Ji¾ od 333 Kè za mìsíc. http://adsl.tiscali.cz

Engr. James Ubaru, Department of Budget/Planning, Petroleum Ministry, Nigeria. Email:jauba3206@yahoo.com Tel: +2348028314081 Your candid attn:                              CONFIDENTIAL BUSINESS PROPOSAL. Compliment of the day to you. We have a business proposal for you. This is after due deliberation with my partners. We believe that you would be in a position to work with us in our bid to transfer the sum of Forty-one Million, Five Hundred Thousand United States Dollars (US$10.8M) into your account since you do not live in our Country.  This transaction is 100% legal and no risk involved. We are members of the special committee for budget and planning of the Ministry of Petroleum. This committee is principally concerned with contract appraisals and approval of contracts in order of priorities as regards CAPITAL PROJECTS of the Federal Government of Nigeria. With our positions, we have successfully secured for ourselves the sum of Forty-one Million, Five Hundred Thousand United States Dollars(US$41.5M). We are working with the present Democratically elected Government in my country, and we are seeking the support of Foreign Government to win the next election coming up in the year 2007, which the race has started. So they have given directive to all Federal Parastatals to settle all Foreign Contractors being owed for contract that they have done. Therefore, our plan is to include your name as one of the contractors being owed in our corporation. What we need from you is to provide a safe Account into which the funds will be transferred since Government Officials in my country are not allowed by our laws to Operate Foreign Accounts. It has been agreed that you will be compensated with US$8.3 Million of the remitted funds. US$31.125Million belongs to us, while  US$2.075Million will be set aside to offset expenses and pay the necessary taxes. It may interest you to know that two years ago a similar transaction was carried out with one Mr. Patrice Miller, the C.E.O of Crane International Trading Corporation at number 135, East 57th street, 28th floor, New York 10022, with Telephone (212)308-7788 and Telex Number 6731689. After the agreement between both of us in which he was to take 25% of the money as his share, the money was duly transferred into his Account. We were disappointed on our arrival in New York as we were reliably informed that Mr. Patrice Miller was no longer on that address while his Telephone and Telex Numbers have been reallocated to somebody else. That was how we lost US$27.5M to Mr.Patrice Miller. This time around we would not want you to be like that. We need a more reliable and trustworthy person and a reputable Company to do this business with, hence we contacted you. So if you can prove yourself to be trusted and interested in this deal then we are prepared to do business with you. What we want from you is the assurance that you will let us have our share when this amount of US$41.5M is transferred into your account. If this proposal satisfies you, please contact us, so we can advice you on the modalities of the transaction. All modalities of this transfer, have been worked out and once started will not take more than 7 Banking days with the absolute support of all concerned. This transaction is 100% safe and risk free now and after the transfer. Kindly treat this as urgent and very confidential. Direct all reponses to jauba3206@yahoo.com Regards, Engr. James Ubaru, Department of Budget/Planning, Petroleum Ministry, Nigeria. Email:jauba3206@yahoo.com Tel: +2348028314081

MR RAJ MOHAMMED. The Manager of, AFRICAN DEVELOPMENT BANK (A.D.B.) Ouagadougou, Burkina-Faso. Direct Line +226 76 40 64 06. Dear Friend, Please read carefully, This is secret and confidential. I hope that you are well today.I am the Manager of Audit and account dept of our bank, with due respect i decided to contact you over this business financial transaction worth the sum of FIFTEEN MILLION DOLLARS, (15Musd)in other to entrust this fund into your bank account. This is an abandoned fund that belongs to the one of our bank customers who died along with his entire family on 25th July,2001 in a plane crash disaster. I was very fortune to meet the deceased file when i was arranging the old and abandoned customers files of 2000-2001 in other to submit to the bank managements accordingly for documentation purposes. Following our banking financial policy, it was obviously indicated and signed law fully that if such money remains unclaimed after five years without somebody been a foreigner apply and claim the fund as the next of kin , the money will be transferred into the Bank Treasury as an unclaimed fund. So the request of you as a foreigner is necessarily needed for the claim because a citizen of Burkina Faso cannot come forward to claim the fund since the law does not permit an indigene to claim such fund Since the real beneficary of the fund is died , the bank are expecting the next of kin to apply for the release of the fund for him or her without delay but unfortunately i learnt through the investigations which I carried out that there is nobody behind who can come and claim the fund. Therefore I want you to apply to the bank with your reliable bank account details where our bank will transfer the fund into and immediately the fund is transferred into your account ,i will share the fund according to the percentage indicated below. SIXTY PERCENT (60%) of the total fund will be for me.THIRTY PERCENT( 30%) for you in provision of the Bank account.FIVE PERCENT(5%) will be for unexpected expenses which may occur during the transfer.FIVE PERCENT(5%) will be preserved for helping the helpless people, like charity organization and motherless babies. Thereafter you will help me to visit your country for sharing the money according to the percentage indicated above. And for the immediate transfer of this fund into your bank account as arranged, you must apply first to the bank as the only existing next of kin to the deceased customer and after approval which will take place immediately as you applied, the transfer of the fund into your nominated bank account will proceed. Please note that you should keep this business secret until you confirm the transfer into the bank account which you will provide. And there is NO RISK in this business. The bank will forward to you all necessary documents related to the transfer and which will prove that you make a legal claim of inheritance. It is true that i pray to GOD before i was pushed forward to contact you for this business but i want you to assure me solemnly that you are a trsutwothy,reliable,honest and capable to avoid cheating me in this business.If you are really sure of your integerity, Reply immediatelly you receive this mail and call me on 00226 76 40 64 06 for more detailed information on how the process to transfer the fund into your account will be. Yours faithfully, Mr Raj Mohammed. _________________________________________________________________ Windows Live Mail : découvrez et testez la version bêta ! http://www.ideas.live.com/programpage.aspx?versionId=5d21c51a-b161-4314-9b0e-4911fb2b2e6d

66 PLANTATION DRIVE, VICTORIA ISLAND LAGOS, NIGERIA. Dear Friend, I am a director in the foreign affairs department of the Nigerian National Petroleum Corporation (NNPC). I got your email during a Personal research on the Internet and wish to use this opportunity to notify you of the existence of a certain amount we wish to transfer Overseas for the purpose of investments and importation of goods from your country. In May 2003, a contract of sixty-six million United States dollars ($66,000,000) was awarded to a foreign company by my ministry. The Contract was supply, erection and system optimization of supper polyore200,000-bpsd, system optimization of 280,000-monax axial plants and the computerization of conveyor belt for Kaduna refinery. With the Consent of only the head of the contract evaluation department, I over Invoiced the contract value by thirty four million United States dollars ($34,000,000:00). The contract has since been completed and the foreign company fully paid off. But, in the office files and paper work, the company is still owed USD34M representing the over invoiced amount. Because this amount is derived from the award and execution of a foreign contract, there is no way the money can be paid locally. That is why I am contacting you so that we can do the project together for our mutual benefit. We have concluded every necessary arrangement to transfer this amount to a foreign account as the final phase payment for the said contract. I solicit your assistance to enable us transfer the said amount into your safe bank account and after we shall come over there to share the money with you. You can either provide us with an existing account or to set up a new bank account immediately to receive this money, even an empty a/c can serve to receive this money, as long as you will remain honest to me till the end of this important business trusting in you and believing that you will never let me down either now or in future. We sincerely need an honest person to work with and have agreed to share the money in the following percentages, 65% will be for us, 30% will be for you whose account is used to secure the funds and 5% will be used to settle every expenses incurred during the transaction like air tickets etc. There is no risk involvement because applications will be made to the concerned Federal ministries and parastatals with official approvals given by the Federal government before the Central bank of Nigeria will be officially authorized to wire the funds to your nominated bank account by telegraphic transfer. Those involved over here are directors in the ministry, they know how best to effect the transfer and will come over there to collect their own share. If you are interested, contact me via email indicating your full names,company/business name and address. Your direct telephone and fax numbers for effective communication. The name and address of the bank you will like us to deposit the money, the telephone and fax numbers of the bank, the account name and number etc. Everything has been arranged and I will send more information about the business transaction to you as soon as I hear from you. For obvious reasons, please keep the proposal top secret. Kind regards, Abraham Patrick

Dear, I Hope This Mail Meets You In Good Health And Spirit, I Am,Farhan Ghulam,From Cote D'Ivoire. Presently, I Live As A Refugee In republic of senegal dakar , With My Younger Sister Ashia . I Am A Victim Of War And The Son Of Late Mr. and Mrs. Alahaji Abdullah Ghulam . The Assassinated Former Assistant Director Of Cote D'Ivoire Gold And Diamond Mining Corporation. My Father Was Killed With Other Government Officials During Official Hours When The Rebel Troops Stormed And Raided The Mining Corporation Office At The Heat Of The Crisis In My Country. A Few Weeks Later, The Rebels Also Invaded Our Residential BuildingIn Which My Mother And one of my younger sister our last born with Two Of Our Security Men Were Killed In The Compound While I Was Out For A Special Research Program And My Younger Sister Was In School.I Had A Singular Shock And Trauma, Which Compelled Us To Flee From The Country To republic of senegal dakar By The Help Of An Army Colonel, Who Is A Close Friend Of My Late Father. I Have First Degree In Marketing And Would Have Further My Education If Not For The Death Of My Parents. I Have Never Worked To Earn My Living Since My Late Parents Had Enough Wealth For Us. I Am Contacting You Now Because Of The Present Difficulty I Am Facing. Unfortunately My Father's Two Accounts In West Africa Have Recently Been Frozen. However This Did Not Affect The Two Million And Six Hundred Thousand Dollars (Us$2.600,000), Which He Kept in finance company in oversea. For Now, I Am Having Every Information And Document Needed For The Clearance Of The Money In The finance company In oversea And I Want You To Act As The Beneficiary Of The Fund For Easy And Smooth Transfer To Your Account Abroad For Investment Purposes.You Will No Doubt Be Adequately Compensated With As Well As A Percentage Of The Profit From Investment Of The Fund. Also You Will See To It That My Sister And I Come Over To Your Country At The Earliest Possible Time. I Am Making This Request To You With Tears In My Eyes And I Feel That Allah Almighty Will Touch You With His Spirit To Listen To My Cry For Help And Answer Me Without Delay. Since Our Breadwinner Is No More And This Is The Only Hope For Life. You Positive Response Will Give Me The Greatest Joy And Relief. Allah Bless You For Your Kind Assistance We Have Agreed To Offer You 25% Of The Total Sum. I am Seriously Waiting For Your Urgent Reply. Best regard.Your Full Address Contact and other things. NAME...................................................... MAILING ADDRESS.................................. AGE:....................................................... STATUS:.................................................. STATE/COUNTRY.................................... BANK/ACCONUT NUMBER...................... TELE/FAX NUMBERS............................... Farhan & Ashia Ghulam. CONTACT ME AND MY Sister WITH THIS ADDRESS. E-MAIL ADDERSS :farhan_ghulam11111@yahoo.co.uk

Greetings

I am Mr.Charles Brown, a Canadian citizen and an Attorney based in Manchester,England.I am the personal Attorney to late Mr Mark Michelle(a foreigner and a private oil consultant/contractor with the shell petroleum Development in Saudi Arabia),hereinafter shall be referred to as my client.

Unfortunately, my client and his wife lost their lives in a Plane crash in Dec,2003.My Several attempts to locate any of his relatives as directed by his bank were all to no avail, even I've made enquires with his country's embassies and so far,non of his relatives have been traced.It may interest you to know that my client died "intestate".

PROPOSITION:

I decided to contact you purely on the personal conviction of trust and confidence that we can co-operate with each other and do a very lucrative business for our mutual benefit . I want you to give me the needed assistance by allowing me to present you as the NEXT OF KIN to the deceased and,the beneficiary of his estate.The deceased had a deposit valued presently at EIGHTEEN MILLION DOLLARS{ $18,000,000.00) and his Bank has issued me a notice to provide his next of kin or beneficiary by will, otherwise the account would be confiscated.

Already, I have worked out modalities for achieving my aim of appointing a next of kin as well as transfer the money out of this country, for us to share in the ratio of 50% for me and 35% to you, while we will collectively donate10% to "Tsunami Relief Course",while the remaining 5% would be used to compensate both parties for any incurred expenses in the course of this transaction.

It is my intention to achieve this transfer in a legitimate way, all I require is your honest co-operation, confidentiality and trust to enable us see this transaction through. The money transfer paper work itself will include a certificate of origin so that the receiving bank does not ask questions.The paper work will include proper certificate that the fund being transferred is from non-criminal sources. In short this will be a proper and legal money transfer with apparently no risk involved. The transaction is guaranteed to succeed without any problem.

If this proposal is acceptable to you, kindly email your following information to me ;

A.Private telephone number and fax number.

B.Your postal/residential address.

C.Identification/Occupation.

Further details awaits you upon a positive response from you.

Yours faithfuly,

Barr.Charles Brown

________________________________________________ Wiadomo¶æ pochodzi z serwera www.k9.pl

#1105 james park, johannesburg, southafrica. Compliments Of The Day, Permit me to introduce myself to you. My name is Dr Jerry Jerome, A Top management Official of one of the finance corporation in johannesburg south Africa.I came to know about you in my private search for a reliable person/company to handle an important assingment on behalf of my Colleagues and myself.As a matter of fact, I got your information from Miss Joyce Brown of The International Affairs Department Of The South African Chamber Of Business. Proposition A German Mr. peter khan, 66 years of age and a prosperous oil/Diamond merchant had in our Bank the sum of $35.5million in a domiciliary account. Unfortunately, he was killed in 2002 plane crash involving concord AF4878 in Gonesse, France. Efforts has been made by the management of my bank through the German Embassy in johannesburg to contact any of the deceased children but to no avail,as we are made to understand he had no children.Given the skeletal information available to the bank, it has so far been impossible to reach any of the relatives. The situation left for the Management is to declare the deceased account dormant and revert the Amount to trading on behalf of the interest of the Bank. In order to avoid this development, my Colleagues and I now seek your approval to have you stand as a distant relative to Mr. peter khan,so that the money would be released to you. All documents and proofs to enable you get the money will be carefully packaged once we receive your consent on this proposal.I shall Apply for a leave as soon as the funds gets into your reliable account to come to your country for possible sharing and investment opportunity which you will assist me in doing. May I assure you that this is safe and risk-free, as we have taken care of all necessary modalities to ensure a hitch-free movement. I have the authority of my partners involved in this assignment to propose that should you be willing to assist us in this,your share would be 40%. I have reposed my confidence in you and hope that you will not disappoint me. Please Best Regards

HELLO DEAR FRIEND. With due respect trust and humility, I write to you irrespective of the fact you do not know me, but please do consider this letter as a request from a brother in dire need of assistance. Good day to you my good friend, I got your contact courtesy of a business journal over the Internet when I am searching for a reliable and trustworthy individual or company that can assist me start a new life and invest on a lucrative business. I am Mr. Smith E. Kimwal, I live at number 38 High road, ttf. 228 England. I am the only child of my father My Father was a wealthy Coffee Merchant before he was poisoned to death by his business associate on one of their out going discussion on a business trip, due to jealous and Greed. Before his death, he told me that he deposited a box that contains his personal documents and the sum of four Million Pounds Sterling with a security finance company in London for safekeeping. He gave me the document, which he made with my name as the next of kin. He told me to relocate to US, and reside there permanently that in no condition I will decide to reside here for the sake of my life. I am soliciting for your assistance in claiming and receiving this box that contains the fund on my behalf. I would be coming over to reside permanently, invest with the money and start a good living without fear. I need your assistance to get back to good living because I have nothing left, the fund in question is the only hope I have. If you decide to help me out of this predicament, when I arrive US, I will compensate you with twenty percent out of the total fund. Finally, I have been in contact with the security finance company in London to make some enquiries on how the transaction would be made. They told me that the box would be Ship to the address of my chosen Destination. Please reply with your Full name, telephone number where you can easily be reached and home Address where the box will be delivered. Please make no mistake about the address for the sake of misplacement Please tell me more about your self and what you do for a living and the more about your area where you live. On getting your response, with the information, I will file in an application to the Security Finance Company for the release and delivery of the box to you as my beneficiary. Hoping to hearing from you. Sincerely, Smith E. Kimwal.

FROM THE DESK OF MR ALEXANDRE BIAISE., DIRECTOR/OFFICE OF THE CHAIRMAN, CONTRACT AWARDING COMMITTEE: EUROPEAN UNION CONSTRUCTION CONTRACT. BURKINA FASO. WEST AFRICA. Dear Friend, I am Mr Alexandre Biaise, the Chairman of EUROPEAN UNION CONSTRUCTION CONTRACT Awarding Committee (EUCCAC) in BURKINA FASO West Africa. I got your information in a business directory from the Burkina Faso Chamber of Commerce and industries, when I was searching for a reliable, honest and trust worthy person to entrust this business with. I was simply inspired and motivated to pick your contact from the directory. After discussing my view and your profile with my colleagues, they were very much satisfied and decided to contact you immediately for this mutual business relationship. We wish to transfer the sum of USD$36.000,000.00 (Thirty Six million United States Dollars only.) into your personal or company's bank account. This fund was a residue of the over invoiced contract bills awarded by us for the supply of equipment,hard/soft wares, pharmaceuticals/medical items relating to constructing tool's, light and heavy duty vehicles, apparels and other administrative logistics etc for the Burkina Faso Projects. This DEAL was deliberately hatched out and carefully protected with all the attendant loop holes sealed off. As the Chairman of CAC, I have the cooperation and mandate of the Financial Director and the Secretary of the Organization. We arranged and over invoiced the contract funds supplied by different companies from different countries. It was our consensus to seek the assistance of a willing foreigner to provide us with the facilities to transfer this money out of Burkina Faso. This is borne out of our belief in the non-stable and spurious political nature of this sub-region.The original contractors have been duly paid by the Bank of Africa Ouaga-Burkina-Faso in West Africa. (Bank of Africa, Ouaga-Burkina-Faso in West Africa). Through our bankers - Societe Generale Banque. This balance is suspended in the escrow accounts awaiting claims by any foreign company of our choice. We intend to pay out this fund NOW as the organization is winding up its activities and the coast has been achieved. Based on the laws and ethics of employment, we as civil servants working under this organization, are not allowed to operate a foreign account. This is the more reason why we needed your assistance to provide an account that can sustain this fund for safe keeping and our future investment with your comprehensive advise, assistance and partnership in your country. It is however agreed, as the account owner in this deal to allow you 30% of the entire sum as compensation, 60% will be held on trust for us while 10% will be used to defray any incidental charges and cost during the course of the transaction. This transaction will be successfully concluded within 14 days if you accord us your unalloyed and due cooperation. You should provide the followings; 1, YOUR COMPANY'S NAME WITH COMPLETE ADDRESS, 2, Your TEL AND FAX NUMBERS. (if available) 3, THE NAME OF YOUR BANK, 4, ITS ADDRESS WITH TEL, FAX AND TELEX NUMBERS. 5, ACCOUNT NUMBER. 6, SWIFT CODE. 7, THE COMPLETE MAILING ADDRESS OF THE BENEFICIARY WITH TELEPHONE AND FAX NUMBERS. Upon the receipt of this information, the documents and approval with the text will be sent to you for confirmation and then forwarded to the organization for ratification and subsequent payment. As with the case of all organized (sensitive) and conspired DEALS, we solicit for your unreserved confidentiality and utmost secret in this business. We hope to retire peacefully and lead a Honorable business life afterward. There are no risks involved regards in this business. I suggest you reply me back for more intimate and details discussions. Yours Faithfully. Mr. MR ALEXANDRE BIAISE. _________________________________________________________________ Don't just search. Find. Check out the new MSN Search! http://search.msn.com/

Dearest One, Greetings and I pray that this mail will meet you in good health and please let this message not be a surprise to you because I lay all the trust in you before i decided to disclose this confidential information to you due to I need your help. I am Brinda Turey , the only daughter of my late parents Chief.and Mrs Turey. My fathe was a highly reputable business magnet (a cocoa, diamond and gold merchant).It was sad to say that he passed away mysteriously after a business trips abroad. Though his sudden death was linked or rather suspected to have been masterminded by one of my uncle ,but God knows the truth! Sorry to say that I never know the caring of my mother because she died when I was just 4 years old which made me the best man for my late father and he never hide anything from me. Before he made the trip to France that lead to my misfortune(his death)He called me, explained to me the reason why he will make the trip...and also told me that he has the sum of Nine million, Five hundred thousand United State Dollars.(USD$9.500,000)deposited in one of the security company's here in Abidjan Ivory coast West Africa, which he disguised and declared the box to contain family valuables instead of money, by this way the company does not know the true content of the box.The deposit document which I have in my possession carries my late father's name as the depositor, while I'm the next of kin on the same document.I evacuated from Sierra Leone last week because the deposit that was made by my late father secretly in Abidjan,Cote d'Ivoire and also with the fear of my greedy relations. I arrived in Abidjan Cote d'Ivoire same last week but Ivory Coast or Cote d'Ivoire is a French speaking country and as a result of Language barrier am more or less confused on who to  confide in over my inherited health, that's why I am confiding in you because is my wish to evacuate and relocate out entirely from Africa with my inherited wealth to start a new life. I have no documentary problems with the security company but the only problem is the nature of deposit that was made by my late father which I will explain to you once you declare your wiliness to assist me. Really, the death of my father actually brought sorrow to my life. I am in a sincere desire of your humble assistance in this regards. Your suggestions and ideas will be highly regarded. Now permit me to ask these few questions:- 1. Can you honestly help me? 2. Can I completely confide in you without any bridge of trust? 3. Surely you will be highly compensated but I need to know what you need me to offer you in returns of your assistance to me ? Thanks and I await your response . Yours Truly Miss Brinda

Nouveau : téléphonez moins cher avec Yahoo! Messenger. Appelez le monde entier à partir de 0,012 €/minute ! Téléchargez la version beta.

Avez-vous essayé le nouveau Yahoo! Mail ? Plus rapide, plus efficace... simplement révolutionnaire ! Découvrez-le.

FROM THE DESK OF.. DR AMIRI BABO BILL AND EXCHANGE MANAGER FOREIGN REMITTANCE DEPT. BANK OF AFRICA(B.O.A) OUAGADOUGOU, BURKINA FASO Dear Friend, I am the manager of bill and exchange at the foreign remittance department BANK OF AFRICA . In my department we discovered an abandoned sum of U.S$25M US dollars (Twenty five Million US dollars) in an account that belongs to one of our foreign customer who died along with his entire family in November 2002 in a plane crash. Since we got information about his death, we have been expecting his next if kin to come over and claim his money because we cannot release it unless somebody applies for it as next of kin or relation to the deceased as indicated in our banking guidlines and laws but unfortunately we learnt that all his supposed next of kin or relation died alongside with him at the plane crash leaving nobody behind for the claim. It is therefore upon this discovery that I now decided to make this business proposal to you so that the money will be released to you as the next of kin or relation to the deceased for safety and subsequent disbursement since nobody is coming for it and we don't want this money to go into the bank treasury as unclaimed bill. The banking law and guidline here stipulates that if such money remained unclaimed after four years, the money will be transfered into the bank treasury as unclaimed bill. The request of foreigner as next of kin in this business is occassioned by the fact that the customer was a foreigner and a Burkinabe cannot stand as next of kin to a foreigner. I propose that 30% of this money will be for you as my foreign partner, in respect to the provision of a foreign account, 10% will be set aside for expenses incured during the business and 60% would be for me. Thereafter I will visit your country for disbursement according to the percentages indicated. Therefore, to enable the immediate transfer of this fund to you as arranged, you must apply first to the bank as relation or next of kin of the deceased indicating your bank name, your bank account number, your private telephone and fax number for easy and effective communication and location wherein the money will be remitted. Upon receipt of your reply, I will send to you by e-mail a text of the application which you'll fill in and send to the bank's email address.. I will not fail to bring to your notice that this transaction is hitch-free and that you should not entertain any atom of fear as all required arrangements have been made for the transfer. You should contact me immediately as soon as you receive this letter for further clearifications. Yours faithfully, . DR AMIRI BABO _________________________________________________________________ MSN Messenger : discutez en direct avec vos amis ! http://www.msn.fr/msger/default.asp

FROM: HAJIA RAKIYA ZUBAIRU. 15 ARAFAT GRAND YOFF STREET, United Nation Reserved Area (UNRA) DAKAR SENEGAL. email rakiya_zubairu0202@yahoo.ca (Assalam! ) Attn: , I know you will be surprised to read a letter from me but please Consider this as a request from a family in dare need of assistance. I am the wife of late Brigadier AL-Jubril Zubairu from Dafur Region, Sudan. My name is Hajia Rakiya Zubairu Writing to you from Sudan. My son got your contact information from a business directory in Dakar Chamber of Commerce and Industry. And I on behalf of my late husband and my only son, decided to solicit for your assistance to transfer the sum of US$9 million dollars, from my late husband's trust account with a bank in Senegal, into your company or Private bank account. Before the death of my husband, he was a Brigadier in-charge of Arms and ammunition procurement for the Darfur Liberation Front (D. L. F.). In his will, he specifically drew my son's attention to the sum of US$9 million, which he had deposited, in the vault of a Bank in Dakar Senegal , as a family treasure, but it is truly cash while he boxed in it the bank as a family treasure due to security reasons. In fact, he said and I quote ?°my beloved son, I wish to draw your attention to the sum of US$9 million. I deposited the said fund in a private account of a Bank in Dakar , Senegal; all the documents regarding the fund are with your mother. I was very dedicated and committed to wining the ongoing war against the rebels until when I found out that some senior army officers and government functionaries were busy helping themselves with government funds and properties, sending them to foreign countries. Due to this, when I and former special adviser to the President were assigned by the President (Hassan al-Bashir) to purchase arms in South Africa, we saw this as an opportunity to divert the money for our personal use. When we divided the money, my share was US$9 million. I did this in case of my absence due to death so that you, Abubakar your two sisters and your mother wouldn't suffer. Take my advice my son; and please be serious with your Studies, I will like you to please take care of this money properly for your future and of your mother's and sisters You should solicit for assistance of a reliable and sincere foreign partner to assist you to transfer this money out of DAKAR for investment. I deposited the money in your name and you alone with the deposit code, for you to claim it. Your mother is with all the documents; take good care of your mother and your two sisters. Do not disappoint me! Good-bye. >From this word of my late husband, you will understand that the lives and future of my family depend on this fund as such I will be grateful if you can assist us. Now what I want you to do for us is to help us clear this sum from the bank using your name which should be as the foreign partner of my late husband. I am preparing to travel to Senegal before the transaction continues, as the war is worsening more and more. We have agreed to give you 20% of the total sum for your assistance and 5% for the expenses that might be incurred in the course of the Transfer and the remaining 75% for the family investment abroad, which you will also assist us to materialize. Further information and Discussion about this transaction will commence as soon as you give us the assurance and confidence that this money will be safe when transferred to your account and, please treat this matter with urgency. Note that this transaction is 100% free from risk as our banker and lawyer have taking care of all the arrangements. Thanks and May Allah Bless us. Best Regards, HAJIA RAKIYA ZUBAIRU.

>From Mrs.Nazek Hariri President,Hariri Organization Beirut, Lebanon. Dear Friend, This letter may come to you as a surprise due to the fact that we have never met. The message could be strange but real, if you pay some attention to it. I could have notified you about it at least for the sake of your integrity. I am Mrs. Nazek Hariri, wife of the late Prime Minister of Lebanon, Mr Rafiq Hariri, who was assassinated on 14 February 2005, along with 20 others,near the St. George Hotel in Beirut.In the wake of his assassination on 14 February 2005, the United Nations Secretary-General Kofi Annan dispatched a fact-finding mission to investigate the killing. Arriving in Beirut on 25 February, the mission interviewed Lebanese officials and politicians, from both the government and opposition, studied the Lebanese investigation and legal proceedings, examined the crime scene and collected evidence. It also interviewed some Witnesses.The report emphasizes that it is impossible to identify the culprits until the perpetrators have been brought to justice, but blames the Syrian government, which it charges with exerting influence that goes beyond the reasonable exercise of cooperative or neighbourly relations, with primary responsibility for the political tension that preceded the assassination, by its (interference) with the details of governance in Lebanon in a heavy-handed and inflexible manner.Since the perpetrators of these evil act has not been brought to justice, l have the feelings that l am not also save here in Beirut. I intend leaving Lebanon for greener pasture.During my husband's regime as the Prime Minister of Lebanon, He realized some reasonable amount of money from various deals that I successfully executed. The money was deposited by my husband in my name, Mrs. Nazek Hariri, in a Finance Firm in Europe. I have plans to invest this money outside Lebanon.I am contacting you because am looking for a trusted and reliable person that will represent me in Europe to claim the money on my behalf. I have sent a notification letter to the financier institution, that the consignment will be collected by the family foreign business partner.Why l need a foreign partner is that, as an Arab woman, the tradition forbids me to run any business with my son (Saadeddine). Since he was not aware of the money from the very first beginning.When I receive your positive response I will then give you details of the Finance firm, and the amount involves. Best regards and God bless, Mrs.Nazek Rafiq Hariri _______________________________________________ No banners. No pop-ups. No kidding. Make My Way your home on the Web - http://www.myway.com

Reply me with this alternative email address The corporate Head Office Standard Trust Bank PLC Plot 1662 Victoria Island, Lagos, Nigeria rev_martin_williams@yahoo.com.mx revmartinwilliams@mails.at revmartinwilliams@pif.ca Tel-234-802-369-6160 Attention.Sir, I am Mr. Mathew Alfred, the Manager funds release with Standard Trust Bank(plc), I am the accountant in charge of Mr Moris Miller account whoused to work with a Multi-National oil Firm in Nigeria. Here in aftershall be referred to as my client On April 21, 2002, my client,his wife, and their three children were involved in a car accidentalong Sagamu express way. All occupants of the vehicle unfortunatelylost their lives. Since then I have made several inquiries to locateany of my clients extended Relatives, this has also provedunsuccessful. After these several unsuccessful attempts, I decided tocontact you to assist in receiving the money left behind by myclient before they Get confiscated or declared unserviceable by thebank where this huge deposits were lodged, particularly the StandardTrust Bank (plc) where the deceased had an account valued at about ($12million u.s dollars) has Issued me a notice to provide the next of kinor have the account confiscated within the next Seven officialworking days.Since I have been unsuccessful in locating the relativesfor over 4 years now I seek your consent to present you as the next ofkin of the deceased so that the proceeds of this account valued at ($12million u.s dollars) can be paid into your account and then you andme Can share the money.60% to me and 40% to you . All I require isyour honest co-operation to enable us see this deal through.I guaranteethat this will be executed under a legitimate arrangement that willprotect you from any breach of the law and i hope the fund arrives youraccount in latest 7 banking days from the date of the receipt of thefollowing informations: 1. YOUR NAME:.. 2. YOUR FULL ADDRESS:.. 3. YOUR PHONE:.. 4. FAX:.. 5. AGE:.. 6. SEX:.. 7. YOUR OCCUPATION:.. and Telephoneand fax number for easy commncation. The above informations will enableme apply for payment into your account. Call me or Please get in touchwith me by my email. rev_martin_williams@yahoo.com.mx revmartinwilliams@mails.at revmartinwilliams@pif.ca Best regards. Mr Mathew Alfred. ---------------------------------------------- Das ist ein Service von austria.com

>From The Desk Of Ben Coroma Esq, Senior Staff In FileDepartment, African Development Bank A.D.B OuagadougouBurkina-Faso West Africa. Call me with this number (00226-78857597) PLANE CRASH WEB SITE...http://news.bbc.co.uk/1/hi/world/europe/859479.stm ("REMITTANCE OF $15 MILLION U.S.A DOLLARS CONFIDENTIAL IS THECASE") Compliment Of The Season, On a very good day. I am (Ben Coroma Esq),asenior staff in file department in African developent bank (ADB).I gotyour contact from a tourist from your country who was in this country and transacted a business with our bank. When i was searching for aforeign partner i assured of your capability and reliability to champion this businees opportunity when i prayed to God or Allah about you.In my department we discovered an abandoned sum of $ 15 million U.S.A dollars( fifteen million U.S.A dollars) . In an account that belongs to one ofour foreign customer who died along with his entire family in Monday 31st July 2000 in a plane crash. Since we got information about his death, we have been expecting his next of kin to come over and claim hismoney because we can not release it unless somebody applies for it asnext of kin or relation to the deceased as indicated in our banking guidelines, but unfortunately we learnt that all his supposed next ofkin or relation died along side with him at the plane crash leaving nobody behind for the claim. It is therefore upon this discovery that Iand one official in my department now decided to make this businness proposal to you and release the money to you as the next of kin or relation to the deceased for safety and subsequent disbursement since nobody is coming for it and we don.t want this money to go into the bank treasury as unclaimed bill. The Banking law and guideline here stipulates that if such money remained unclamed after five years, the money will be transfered into the Bank treasury as unclaimed fund. The request of foreigner as next of kin in this business is occasioned by the fact that the customer was a foreigner, and a Burkinabe cannot standas next of kin to a foreigner. We agree that 30 % of this money will befor you as foreign partner, in respect to the provision of a foreign account, 10 % will be set aside for expenses incured during the business and 60 % would be for me and my woman colleague. There after I and my colleague will visit your country for disbursement according to the percentages indicated. Therefore to enable the immediate trnansfer ofthis fund to you as arranged, you must apply first to the bank asrelations or next of kin of the deceased indicating your bank name, yourbank account number, your private telephone and fax number for easy and effective communication and location where the money will be remitted. Upon receipt of your reply, I will send to you by fax or emailthe text of the application I will not fail to bring to your notice that this transaction is hitch free and that you should not entertain any atom of fear as all required arrangements have been made forthetransfer. You should contact me on this email( (00226-7885 7597)immediately as soon as you receive this letter. Trusting to hear fromyou immediately. Your's faithfully, Ben Coroma (Esq.) POST SCRITUM:You have to keep everything secret as to enable the transfer to move very smoothly in to the account you will prove to the bank.As you finished reading this letter call me immediately so that we discuss very well over this business.Please call me and inform me that you received my mail, because i don't go to net always

ATTN: HELPER. (STRICTLY CONFIDENTIAL) FROM THE DESK OF ( MR. MOHAME KABIRO) AUDITING AND ACCOUNTING UNIT /FOREIGN REMITTANCE DEPT. AFRICAN DEVELOPMENT BANK (A.D.B)OUAGADOUGOU -BF REQUEST FOR THE URGENT TRANSFER OF THE SUM (US$10.5million) ONLY INTO YOUR ACCOUNT. You may be surprise to receive this message from me since you don't know me in person, but for the purpose of introduction., I got your impressive information through an international business equiry . But I respectfully insist you read crefully as I am optimistic it will open doors for unimaginable financial reward for both us. This business transaction might not fall within the wide spectrum of your business activities ,but I plead your assistance ,as your flair for profitable business is needed . Permit me to introduce myself. I am MR. MOHAME KABIRO. the Manager of auditing and accounting unit at the foreign remittance department of AFRICAN DEVELOPMENT BANK . In My department I discovered an abandoned sum of$ 10.5m US dollars . In an account that belongs to one of our foreign customer who died along with his entire family in november 2002 in a plane crash. Since I got information about his death, I have been expecting his next of kin to come over and claim his money because wecannot release it unless somebody applies for it as next of kin or relation to the deceased anindicated in our banking guidelines but unfortunately I learnt that all his supposed next of kin or relation died alongside with him at the planecrash leaving nobody behind for the claim. It is therefore upon this discovery that I and other officials in my department now decided to make businness proposal to you and release the money to you as the next of kin or relation to the deceased for safety and subsequent disbursement since nobody is coming for it and I don?t want this money to go into the Bank treasury as unclaimed Bill. The Banking law and guideline here stipulates that if such money remained unclamed after five years, the money will be transfered into the Bank treasury as unclaimed fund. The request of foreigner as next of kin in this business is occasioned bythe fact that the customer was a foreigner and a Burkinabe cannot stand as next of kin to a foreigner. I agree that 30 % of this money will be for you as foreign partner, inrespect to the provision of a foreign account, 10 %will be set aside for expenses incured during the business and 60 % would be for me . There after I will visit your country with my family for disbursement according to the percentages indicated. Therefore to enable the immediate trnansfer of this fund to you as arranged, you must apply first to the bank as relations or next of kin of the deceased indicating your bank name, your bank account number, your private telephone and fax number for easy and effective communication and location where in the money will be remitted . On your acceptance, I will send to the text of application by fax or by email which you are going to apply to the bank ; and provide materials confirmation references and inquiries regarding payment formalities from the payment Agency. I willbe handling official protocols here and expect you to undertake international responsibilities as I am assuring you of a risk free transaction provided you display maturity. Therefore, if you are willing and interested to render the needed assistance, endeavor to reply through my email address . Thanking you in anticipation of your kind considerations. Yours sincerely. MR. MOHAME KABIRO. TEL 00226 76 61 65 94 _________________________________________________________________ Windows Live Messenger : venez tester la version bêta ! http://www.ideas.live.com/programpage.aspx?versionId=5d21c51a-b161-4314-9b0e-4911fb2b2e6d

FROM:MR DESMOND KOFFI ECO BANK ,Dkr Senegal. Rue du Gouverneur Bayol Dakar Senegal. Swift: ECOCBKJJ Telex : 6171 ECOBNK Attn:Dear Sir , RE:TRANSFER OF (USD 18.6 MILLION) ---------------------------------------------------------- In order to transfer out (USD 18.6 MILLION) United States Dollars) from ECOBANK .I have the courage to ask for your assistance to handle this important and confidential business believing that you will never let me down either now or in future. I am Mr Desmond Koffi , the manager of ECO-BANK here in dakar senegal. there is an account opened in this bank in 1982 and since 2001 nobody has operated on this account again. After going through some old files in the records, I discovered that if I do not remit this money out urgently it will be forfeited for nothing. The owner of this account is a foreigner, and he was a miner at CIVOTT GOLD MINNING SARL. and he was a Geologist by profession and he died since 1992. No other person knows about this account or any thing concerning it, the account has no other beneficiary and my investigation proved to me as well that this company does not know anything about this account and the amount involved is (USD 18.6 M) United States Dollars). I want to transfer the [USD18.6 M] United States Dollars into a safe foreigners partner abroad , but I don't know any foreigner, I am only contacting you as a foreigner because this money can not be approved to any africa person here, but can only be approved to any foreign person because the money is in us dollars and the former owner of the account is a foreigner too.I know that this message will come to you as a surprise as we don't know ourselves before,but besure that it is real and a genuine business. You are the only person that I have contacted in this business, so please reply urgently so that I will inform you the next step to take urgently. Send also your private telephone and fax number . I want us to meet face to face or sign a binding agreement to bind us together so that you can receive this money in your country in cash through our diplomat that we used to air lift funds to shell and chevron oil companies in europe and america. I will fly to your country for withdrawal and sharing and other investments after you have confirmed the money in to your account, I am contacting you because of the need to involve a foreigner with foreign foreign address as beneficiary. I need your full co-operation to make this work fine because the management is ready to approve this payment to any foreigner who has correct information of this fund, which I will give to you later immediately, if you are able and with capability to handle such amount in strict confidence and trust according to my instructions and advice for our mutual benefit because this opportunity will never come again in my life. I need truthful person in this business because I don't want to make mistake I need your strong assurance and trust. With my position now in the office I can transfer this money to any foreigner's reliable person, intact pending my physical arrival in your country for sharing. and I want to remaind you that your share has been carculated at 35% of the total sum.I waiting for your urgent reply so that I will give you more informations about this transaction on how you can receive this money in your country. Mr. Desmond Koffi.

FROM: Sgt. Jennifer Leary To whom it may concern. I am an American soldier, I am serving in the military of the 1st Armored Division in Iraq, as you know we are being attacked by insurgents everyday and car bombs. We managed to move funds belonging to Saddam Hussein's family. The total amount is US$7.2Million dollars in cash, mostly 100 dollar bills. We want to move this money to you, so that you may invest it for us and keep our share for banking.We will take 60%, my partner and I. You take the other 40%. No strings attached, just help us move it out of Iraq, Iraq is a war zone. We plan on using diplomatic courier and shipping the money out in one large silver box, using diplomatic immunity. If you are interested I will send you the full details, my job is to find a good partner that we can trust and that will assist us. Can I trust you? When you receive this letter, kindly send me an e-mail signifying your interest including your most confidential telephone/fax numbers for quick communication also your contact details. This business is risk free. The box can be shipped out in 48hrs. Respectfully, Sgt. Jennifer Leary Private Email: jenniferleary25@aim.com

SPANISH LANGUAGE

DE: Sgt. Jennifer Leary A quien pueda interesar. Soy soldado americano, Estoy desempen'ando servicios en los militares del Primero División armada en Iraq, como usted sabe cerca nos están atacando insurrectos diarios y bombas de coche. Manejamos mover los fondos que pertenecían a la familia de Saddam Hussein. la cantidad total es dólares de US$7.2Million en efectivo, sobre todo 100 cuentas de dólar. Deseamos mover este dinero a usted, de modo que usted pueda invertirlo para nosotros y guarde nuestra parte para las actividades bancarias.Tomaremos el 60%, mi socio y yo. Usted toma el otro 40%. Ningunas secuencias unidas, justo ayúdenos a moverlo de Iraq, Iraq es una zona de la guerra. Planeamos en usar el mensajero diplomático y enviar el dinero hacia fuera en una caja de plata grande, usar inmunidad diplomática. Si usted soy interesado le enviaré los detalles completos, mi trabajo está al hallazgo a buen socio a que podemos confiar en y que nos asistirá. ¿Puedo confiarle en? Cuando usted recibe esta letra, amablemente envíeme significar del E-mail su interés incluyendo su teléfono más confidencial números de fax para comunicación rápida también sus detalles del contacto. Este negocio es riesgo libremente. La caja se puede enviar hacia fuera en 48hrs. Respetuosamente, Sgt. Jennifer Leary Email Privado: jenniferleary25@aim.com

FRENCH LANGUAGE

DE : Sgt. Jennifer Leary À qui de droit. Je suis un soldat américain, Je sers dans les militaires du 1er Division blindée en Irak, comme vous savez nous sommes attaqués près insurgés journaliers et bombes de voiture. Nous sommes parvenus à déplacer des fonds appartenant à la famille de Saddam Hussein. le montant total est des dollars d'USS7.2Million comptant, la plupart du temps 100 billets d'un dollar. Nous voulons déplacer cet argent à vous, de sorte que vous puissiez l'investir pour nous et gardez notre part pour des opérations bancaires.Nous prendrons 60%, mon associé et I. Vous prenez l'autre 40%. Aucunes cordes jointes, juste aidez-nous à le déplacer hors de l'Irak, L'Irak est une zone de guerre. Nous projetons sur employer le courier diplomatique et l'expédition l'argent dehors dans une grande boîte argentée, employer l'immunité diplomatique. Si vous suis intéressé je vous enverrai les détails complets, mon travail est à la trouvaille a bon associé au lequel nous pouvons faire confiance et qui nous aidera. Est-ce que je peux vous faire confiance ? Quand vous recevez cette lettre, nous vous saurions gré de m'envoyer signifier de E-mail votre intérêt comprenant votre téléphone plus confidentielnuméros de fax pour communication rapide aussi vos détails de contact. Ces affaires sont risque librement. La boîte peut être embarquée dehors dans 48hrs. Avec respect, Sgt. Jennifer Leary Email Privé : jenniferleary25@aim.com

I am Mr. Mccallum Graeme, Institutional Fund Services, Middle East and Africa,HSBC Bank PLC, London International Branch, On resumption of duties after the Christmas and New year celebration i discovered that one of my bank customer,Mr. JOSHUA WANG ,an Indonesia by birth , a consultant/contractor with the military relief Group, a charity organization ato the United Nation( UN), was one of the victims of the TSUNAMI disaster in the Asia World, he has being a private resident here in London for 3 years, made a numbered time (Fixed) Deposit, valued at BPS6,500,000.00 (Six Million, Five Hundred Thousand Great British Pounds Sterling) for twelve calendar months in my Branch. As representative with contacts in the Middle East/Africa,upon the tsunami disaster in his home country of Indonesia, in which he was on a private visit to see his sick old parents, i have made personal contacts to his resident here in London and through some foreign mission in Indonesia, and has discovered that he and his entire family perished in the said natural disaster in his local community in Indonesia. On further investigation, it also discovered that he died without making a WILL (En-testate) and all attempts to trace his next of kin was fruitless, it was discovered in the Late Mr. JOSHUA WANG bank papers that the only persons stated as his entitled next of kin is his only wife, who also died with him in the disaster,so presently their is no persons to declare as the next of kin to the said fund and as it stand now , No person will ever come forward to claim it. As the bank papers/documents have only his late wife name, since they have no child before their sudden death. In accordance with the Banking Federal Laws and constitution, the money will revert to the ownership of the Government if nobody applies as the next of Kin to claim the funds within certain period.Consequently, I shall present you as a foreign partner to stand in as the next of kin to late Mr.JOSHUA WANG so that you and I can benefit from the fruits of this old man's labor and also donate certain portion of the fund to all victims of the Tsunami disasters through humanitarian Organization. Be informed that i have in my capacity/position carefully moved this fund into the Vault of a Security and Finance Company here in London that have Branches all over Europe/America where this fund can be claim. Upon acceptance of this proposal, We shall employ the services of a solicitor for the drafting of the LAST WILL & TESTAMENT of Late Mr.Joshua Wang and to obtain all other relevant papers in your name for the necessary documentation for payment approval in my bank headquarters in your favor. I guarantee that this will be executed under legitimate arrangement that will protect you from any breach of the law as I will use my position as the senior Bank's personnel in the Institutional fund services, Middle East and Africa, HSBC BANK PLC, to secure pprovals and guarantee the successful execution of this transaction. Please be informed that your utmost confidentiality is required. If this interests you, please reply me immediately and please include your private phone number for voice contact and fax number so that I can provide you with more details and relevant documents that will help you understand the transaction better. Awaiting your urgent reply through my only private email: mgraeme@wanadoo.es or m4470g@netscape.net Thanks, Best regards, McCallum Graeme

Dear Sir, Compliments of the day, before I proceed, I must be grateful to introduce myself. I am Mr. Eddy G. Ibe, the son of the late Gen. Robert Ibe Guere of the then military government of Ivory Coast, prior to the time of crisis which is presently on I got your contact from a directory I have just acquired. Due to my position, as the son and benefficiary to the late General, I have been able to come away with a reasonable sum of money after the brutal murder of my parents by my father's political opponents, this money belongs to my father and is in the total sum of 19.8 million US$ of which I have the tendency to invest it in a company with good line of products like your own company and with potential for a good capital returns, on behalf of myself and the remaining members of my family. Since your country is one of the good investor friendly nations in the world, I have decidedto seek your assistance for me to transfer this funds to your country and run business over there, for the mutual benefit of both of us and my entire family. I would therefore like you to help me in every possible way in securing this funds in your country. Furthermore I will like you to assist me in finding a good business that I will invest this fund. However upon acceptance you will be required to contact me through my personal e-mail address as above (eddy37sure@she.com ) for security reason in which you will be informed and get update about the current arrangement i have made so far on how totransfer the money from Bangkok-Thailand to your account through a bank account that you will open in your name here. In view of your participation, I am ready to give you a good negotiable percentage for your assistance of which the trustee fee range in my country is between to 5% to 7% of the actual money or better still commit it into a joint venture project. Be assured that you stand no risk of any kind as the fund belongs to me and the rest of my family now, of which i am the sole benefficiary and trustee on behalf of my younger ones who are currently on assylum some where. As soon as I get your consent, I will contact my lawyer to start making arrangement on how to change the ownership of the consignment into your name, for easy transfer of the money out of here, since you will be my trustee to the transaction and thereafter transfer to your country's foreign account and i will finally come over to your country for all the final arrangements. I strongly believe that associating with you to embark on this and other business ventures will derive a huge success hereafter. If you have any question do not hesitate to include same in your reply. Best reards, Mr. Eddy

From:Mrs Amina Dhari Ali al-Fayadh UNHCR, Udomthani, Thailand mrs_aishatuhassan@yahoo.com Tel 00 (66)-68943653 Attention: The Managing Director, Thank you for the attention being given to go through my mail. Please be patient and read my message to you. With a very desperate need for assistance, I have summoned up courage to contact you. Before I proceed , Kindly allow me to give you a brief introduction about myself and background to enable you know me better. My name is Mrs Amina Dhari Ali al-Fayadh, an Iraqi refugee. My late husband was until recently, Iraqi Member of Parliament and National Assembly legislator. I am 58 years old, now receiving treatment in hospital because of my illness which has lasted for 4 years now. It’s quite obvious that I won’t live Longer according to my doctor, as I am suffering from my kidney transplant. My late husband, his two bodyguards and my first Son was killed in a suicide car bomber while traveling to parliament from our farm in Rashidiya.During the period of our marriage we had two male children late Musa and Rashidi who is taking care of me now. Prior to this last serious crisis that is still ravaging in my country which recently led to the misfortune death of my husband, my son and disterblization our goverment, we were able to come over here in Thailand. I was terrified of the situation and because of this I and my Son were able to escaped out of the country with the help of united nations peacekeeping force. After the death of my husband, I inherited the sum of USD$6.5million which my late husband deposited with a Security Finance Company in Thailand for safety. The doctor has advised that I may not live long because my illness has gotten to a bad stage, so I now decided to contact you to assist my son to claim this money from where it was deposited and guide him for investment in your country as you might have more business / investment experience more than him. Having being aware of your country's tremendous economic growth, I decided to contact you.Please kindly guide and assist us in making the right investment. I would need your advice, guidiance and assistance to invest this fund properly and profitable. I strongly believe that with your good experience as a potential businessman you would be in position in guiding my son to a sucessful exploration of the investment potentials of your country , which guarantees good capital returns and human security. As a result of this I can take you in confidence basically because of the source of the fund hereby believing that your assistance will be profitable to us. In view of your participate, I am ready to give you a good negotiable percentage for your assistance as you shall give every needed assistance is making sure the said fund is successfully transffered to your country without any hitch . Lastly, I honestly pray that this money when transferred to your country will be used for the said purpose of investing in the industry, because I have come to find out that wealth acquisition without Allah is vanity upon vanity. I await your urgent reply to enable me up-date you with more information and how to proceed. Do feel free to ask me any question if you wish to as my husbands death has blocked every trace of this money from us, the documentations relating to the deposit of this fund are all intact with my son for your verification . Please include you private contact telephone number and private e-mail when replying. I await to hearing from you soonest. Wassalam and Ashkurit. Sincerely Yours , Mrs Amina Dhari Ali al-Fayadh

From: Jerome Williams Lewis Esq. The inspiration to contact you is simply divine providence,I am making this proposition because I have to seek the partnership of a resource person to help me realise this project. I am Jerome Williams Lewis Esq. a solicitor and investment consultant based in london, United Kindom. I was attending a business luncheon in Berlin,Germany and I got introduced to the renowned German businessman and property mogul, Mr Andreas Schranner(of the blessed memory). He engaged my services as attorney and investment consultant and my primary assignment was to spearhead his investment forays in the United Kingdom.three months later I invited him to London and under my professional guidance and based on my advice he made a fixed deposit of 30,000,000,00EUR at with security companies in Germany and Netherlands. This deposit was for 12months and upon maturity I made effort to contact my client, I could not reach him or any member of his family. I was forced to travel to germany and there I got the tragic news that on July 25TH, 2000, my client Mr Andreas Schranner, his wife maria, their daughter eich and husband christian and their two children perished in the Air France concorde New York bound flight; please click here: http://news.bbc.co.uk/1/hi/world/europe/859479.stm I have made effort to locate any member of his family with strong biological links to my late client without success. The search to find a close relation is one that has consumed time and resources.The institution is asking me to either present a next of kin to late Andreas Schranner or forfiet the depsosit. My proposal is to you as next of kin to late Andreas Schranner and process the deposit and collect the deposits for our mutual benefit. My capacity as solicitor/investment consultant to my late client gives me the discretion to package and transfer the deposit to you. I will give you 30% for your effort, 60% for me and 10% for Charity and Tsunami Victims. It will amount to injustice if i do not take this decisive step to secure this deposit, and invest it The late Schranner was also a friend in addition to our business relationship. I will wait for your reaction and response and then together we can jumpstart this project and nurture it to reality. Please, make sure you respond through this my confidential email address: williamsjruphus@katamail.com or williamsruphuseq@jmail.co.za Your swift response is anticipated. Yours faithfully Jerome Williams Lewis Esq.

From: Mrs.Suha Aisha Arafat [mailto:suhaarafat@easyinfomail.co.za] Greetings from Palestine, I am sorry to disturb your peace as I konw you are not expecting to hear from some one like me. You will be compelled to help me once you have heard what I have to say to you. I am Mrs. SUHA ARAFAT, the wife of YASSER ARAFAT, the Palestinian leader who died recently in Paris. You must have heard over the media reports and the Internet on the discovery of some fund in my husband secret bank accounts and companies and the allegations of some huge sums of money deposited by my husband in my name of which I have refuses to disclose or give up to the corrupt Palestine Government. In fact, the total sum allegedly discovered by the Government so far is about $6.5 Billion Dollars. Please visit the BBC news broadcast below for better understanding of what I am talking about; http://news.bbc.co.uk/1/hi/world/middle_east/3479937.stm http://news.bbc.co.uk/1/hi/world/middle_east/3995769.stm I have deposited the sum of 32 million dollars with a private security firm abroad whose name is withheld for now until we open communication the reason why I deposited this.32 million dollars to a security company was because every transfer that goes into my bank account has being monitored by the government. I shall be grateful if you could receive this fund into your bank account for safekeeping and any Investment opportunity. This arrangement is known to you and my personal Attorney. He might be dealing with you directly for security reasons as the case may be. In addition, please note that there will be no risky of any kind from your part as every arrangement for smoothly transfer has being made by my legal adviser. If you are willing to assist me, we will have to negotiate on your Percentage share of the $32,000,000 that will be kept in your position for a while and invested in your name pending when my Daughter, Zahra, will come off age and take full responsibility of her Family Estate/inheritance. Please note that this is an excellent opportunity that comes once in lifetime and more so, if you are honest, I am going to entrust more funds in your care as this is one of the legacy we keep for our children. In case you do not accept, please do not let me out to the security and international media as I am giving you this information in total trust and confidence I will greatly appreciate if you accept my proposal in good faith. Please expedite action and all response to my e-mail address below. Yours sincerely, Mrs. Suha Aisha Arafat Email. suhaarafat@easyinfomail.co.za _________________________________________________________________ Discover the magic of RSS feeds at MSN South Africa! http://za.msn.com/

>From Mr.kenny paul TELEPHONE:+44-704-012-4656 FAX NUMBER:+44-8717205745 We are Diplomatic Corp that holds special and valuable consignments for reputable clients that are honest and trustworthy.We work in collaboration with top firms all over the world as we have earned a name as a service whose hallmarks in reliability and confidentiality are revered. International missions, Diplomats, Embassies of the world have used our services to satisfaction. A benefactor has mandated me to get someone that can assist her and her family in retrieving her package containing some amountof money from a Diplomatic Corp in Europe. The benefactor and her children have been confined only totheir country home and all their calls and movements aremonitored, as a result,its absoultely impossible for them to do anything asregards retrieving the money. Their only means of communication is via internet and youare being contacted because yourassistance is needed in claiming the funds on their behalf. The amount was accrued fromDiamond sales over a period of six years and its USD75M (Seventy Five Million U. S.Dollars). These funds are fully free of any liens, or encumbrances and are clean, clear and has no criminal origin. Thefunds have nothing to do with any form of illegality and all documentations needed to prove the source of the funds were submitted when the funds were being deposited and these documents would prove the source of the funds and authenticate the fact that the funds are clean and has no links whatsoever with either drugs orterrorism. For your assistance in this transaction,the benefactor and her Children have agreed to give you 30% of the total amount of money which is equivalent to US$22.5 Million (Twenty Two Million,Five Hundred Thousand United States Dollars) and this role simply entails retrieving the funds on their behalf from the Diplomats in Europe and all the information needed to claim the funds would be sentto you as soon as you indicate your interest in assisting them as well as providing the following information to facilitate the smooth conclusion of the transaction. 1) Your Full Name: _________________________ 2) Your Address: _______________________________ 3) Your Telephone Number: ________________________ 4) Your Fax Number: __________________________ 5) Your Mobile Number: _____________________________ 6) The Name of the Residence: _____________________ 7) Your Age: _____________________________________ 8)Your Country__________________ Iawait your response Urgently. Mr.kenny paul TELEPHONE:+44-704-012-4656 FAX NUMBER:+44-8717205745 ****PRIVATE & CONFIDENTIAL***** This e-mail and any attached files are confidential and may be legally privileged. If you are not the addressee, any disclosure, reproduction, copying, distribution, or other dissemination or use of this communication is strictly prohibited Mr.kenny paul

FROM: OFFICE OF REVD.FR David CLARK DIRECTOR SPECIAL DUTIES,UNITED NATIONS IN CONJUNCTION WITH THE INTERNATIONAL MONETARY FUND WORLD BANK SPECIAL DUTIES,OFFICE DAKAR,SENEGAL. TEL:+221-448-8469 EMAIL: rev.davclk2@katamail.com Dear Friend. I am Rev. Fr. David Clark, a senior staff with the UN special duties office,my office monitors and controls the affairs of all banks and financial institutions. I have before me list of funds, which could not be transferred to some nominated accounts as these accounts have been identified either as ghost accounts, unclaimed deposits and over-invoiced sum etc; I have the opportunity to write you based on the instructions among others i received days ago from the officer in the computer section in person of Engineer Peter Cliff,to bring out part of your total pending payment with reference number(LM-05-371) amounting US$10 million.The (Ten Million Dollars) is been arranged in a security-proof box weighing 75kg. In order to get the box shipped to you. As I found out that you have almost met all the statutory requirements in respect of your pending payment. The problems you are having is that of interest groups. A lot of people are interested in your payment and those people are merely doing paper works with you and that explains why you receive different kinds of untrue fax and phone messages from different people everyday. Also we found out that some of the officials of the parastatals have been extorting a lot of money from you with the pretext of helping you receive your money. I can assure you this will keep happening if you do not do away with those officers. For security reasons you do not have to tell anybody that your have your payment on the way until the payment gets to you. The said payment is been arranged in a security-proof box weighing 75kg. In order to get this box shipped to you,the(CSO)and i Yesterday went to this four courier companies Dhl, Ems, FedEx and Ups to make arrangements on how to get the box shipped to you by courier, but to no avail the above courier companies all made us to understand that they will have to open the box for inspection by the customs before shipment. This is something we want to avoid because this box is been padded with synthetic nylon and to open it you will have to cut the pad before you will meet the button that you will press to open the dial code-lock. There is no way you can open the box and be able to close it again because it was padded with machine. We told the courier services that the box contained film materials and when open will spoil the materials. <N:B> we did not declare money because courier does not carry money. Today a friend of mine who is a diplomat disclosed to me that there is a security courier service company that is specialized in sending diplomatic materials and information from one country to another, which also has diplomatic immunity and consignment such as this cannot be checked by any customs anywhere in the world. I have therefore met the official of the security courier service and concluded shipping arrangement with them, which they will commence as soon as I have your go ahead order. The diplomat who will be bringing in this consignment to you is an expert and has been in this line of work for many years now so we have Notting to worry about. After all arrangements we have concluded that you must donate Five Hundred Thousand United States dollars (US$500,000.00) to any charity organisation I designate as soon as you receive your money. To this effect, you will send to us a promissory note for the donation along with your address where you will like the box to be delivered to by the courier. Please maintain topmost secrecy as it may cause a lot of problems if found out that we are using this way to help you. You are advised not to inform anyone about this until you received your money. Am helping you on this because something in me is tells me that you are an honest person. When you conclude this and you send fufill the agreement, we will help to ship the final part of your money to you. May God be with you as i await your response. Feel free to call me if you will like us to discuses more. Yours Faithfully, Revd. Fr. David Clark. Director, Special Duties.UN/WBF. TEL:+221-448-8469

Sir, I was privileged to come across your contact through my personal check with your country Investment Portal and I decided that I should establish a communication with you to acquiring some information on lucrative investment or establishment in your country. Be it as it may, I will appreciate if you can be of good assistance to me as I am willing to invest my money with you in your country provided I will have a good partner or investor as well fund manager who will guild on this business framework and as thus, share with me the dividend in any venture which we have considered lucrative to invest in and I have not managed any business before but have always dream of running my own establishment hence my desire to recapitalize in your country Investment market either in oil or real estate. Further to this, I will like to give you a little more information about me, I am an American but married into the Sharjah Royal Family here in Sharjah United Arab Emirate, but at the moment undergoing a divorce case with my husband through the sharia court and hopefully will get this matter over within a couple of weeks and that is why I want to calve a niche for myself to be able to continue with my life and make my life meaningful when I leave my husband’s family. The funds I intend to invest with you is currently in a UAE bank here as was deposited by my late father who worked before he died as a chemical engineer in the Saudi Oil Corporation ARAMCO and later the Emirate National Oil Corporation ENOC. My reason of trying to establish my own business is necessitated by the advent of my divorce suite with my husband and according to the sharjah marital law here, if my husband family gets any knowledge of the funds in the bank, they will take possession of the funds since my father used my name as the next of kin. It is my wish to handle this matter privately under the most cautious legal arrangement to get the funds into your possession before we can commence any trade deal and therefore demand that you kindly give me a brief information about you with pictures, contact address and telephone numbers incase I want to call you . Pls can you tell me if you can deal with my lawyer who practice in Abu Dhabi – U.A.E as the funds I wish to invest into the business is in a bank there and I will like to get you introduced to my lawyer who is also an American and works with the emirate international law firm. the money in question (US$9,750,000) was deposited into the bank about two years back before my father died of heart failure and ever since his death, my relationship with my husband has gone bad due to the fact that I’ve been married to him for six years now and we have no issue. My lawyer advised that what we shall do is to portray you as an investor who has given that money to my father before he died for a crude oil lifting from the Saudi oil corporation but the deal was thwarted due the sudden death of my father. By this strategy, the lawyer will present some letter of administration and application to the bank for the release of the funds to you under the emirate inheritance law. This logistics is to get the funds transferred to you as the bonafide owner of the funds to avoid any implications that will not permit me as being married to the royal family to possess such chattel or estate of my late father in conformity with the sharia marital law. So I hope you understand very well, the strategies and where you don’t quite comprehend, do ask me for more clarifications and for your involvement I will pay you 15% of the total money for your consultancy and then we can invest the rest still under your supervision.Please reply me at info_alqaspat@z6.com I await your utmost response. Mrs. Patricia Khalid ibn Saqr al Qasseemi

FROM: MR. KOFI MENSAH INTERNATIONAL COMMERCIAL BANK TEMA ACCRA GHANA Dear friend, My name is Mr. Kenneth Baafi, I am the regional manager of the International Commercial Bank Tema Accra Ghana I got your information during my search through the Internet. I am 44 years of age and married with three lovely kids. It may interest you to hear that I am a man of PEACE and don't want problem, I only hope we can assist each other. If you don't want this business offer kindly forget it, as I will not contact you again. I have packaged a financial transaction that will benefit both of us, as the regional manager of the International Commercial Bank it is my duty to send in a financial report to my head office in the capital city Accra at the end of each year. On the course of the last year 2005 end of year report, I discovered that my branch in which I am the manager made Three Million Five Hundred Thousand Dollars [US$3,500.000.00] which my head office are not aware of and will never be aware of. I have since place this fund on what we call SUSPENSE ACCOUNT without any beneficiary. As an officer of the bank I can not be directly connected to this money, so this informed my contacting you for us to work so that you can assist receive this money into you bank account for us to SHARE. While you will have 30% of the total fund. Note there are practically no risk involved, it will be bank to bank transfer, all I need from you is to stand claim as the original depositor of this fund who made the deposit with our branch so that my Head office can order the transfer to your designated bank account. If you accept this offer to work with me, I will appreciate it very much. As soon as I receive your response I will details you on how we can achieve it successfully. Best regards, Mr. Kenneth Baafi

OFFICE OF REVD.FR THOMAS DOUGLAS DIRECTOR SPECIAL DUTIES, UNITED NATIONS ORGANISATION IN CONJUNCTION WITH THE INTERNATIONAL MONETARY FUND WORLD BANK FACT-FINDING & SPECIAL DUTIES OFFICE DAKAR, SENEGAL. TEL: +221 4183317 Email:Revduglas@yahoo.fr Dear Friend. I am Revd. Fr. Thomas Douglas, a senior staff with the World Bank fact finding & special duties office. I am writing you this letter based on the fact that cool penny is better than millions of dollars means it's better for one to live and die poor honest man than a rich dishonest one. I and the Chief security officer (CSO) of this organisation have arranged with an officer in the computer section the person of Engineer Peter Cliff to bring out part of your total pending payment with reference number (LM-05-371) amounting to US$10 million. Why we did this is because according to information gathered from the bank’s security computer, you have been waiting for a long time to receive this payment without success. As I found out that you have almost met all the statutory requirements in respect of your pending payment. The problems you are having is that of interest groups. A lot of people are interested in your payment and those people are merely doing paper works with you and that explains why you receive different kinds of untrue fax and phone messages from different people everyday. Also we found out that some of the officials of the parastatals have been extorting a lot of money from you with the pretext of helping you receive your money. I can assure you this will keep happening if you do not do away with those officers. For security reasons you do not have to tell anybody that your have your payment on the way until the payment gets to you. The said payment is been arranged in a security-proof box weighing 75kg. In order to get this box shipped to you I and the (CSO) Yesterday went to this four courier companies Dhl, Ems, FedEx and Ups to make arrangements on how to get the box shipped to you by courier, but to no avail the above courier companies all made us to understand that they will have to open the box for inspection by the customs before shipment. This is something we want to avoid because this box is been padded with synthetic nylon and to open it you will have to cut the pad before you will meet the button that you will press to open the dial code-lock. There is no way you can open the box and be able to close it again because it was padded with machine. We told the courier services that the box contained film materials and when open will spoil the materials. we did not declare money because courier does not carry money. Today a friend of mine who is a diplomat disclosed to me that there is a security courier service company that is specialised in sending diplomatic materials and information from one country to another, which also has diplomatic immunity and consignment such as this cannot be checked by any customs anywhere in the world. I have therefore met the official of the security courier service and concluded shipping arrangement with them, which they will commence as soon as I have your go ahead order. The diplomat who will be bring in this consignment to you is an expert and has been in this line of work for many years now so we have Notting to worry about. After all arrangements we have concluded that you must donate Five Hundred Thousand United States dollars (US$500,000.00) to any charity organisation I designate as soon as you receive your money. To this effect, you will send to us a promissory note for the donation along with your address where you will like the box to be delivered to by the courier. Please maintain topmost secrecy as it may cause a lot of problems if found out that we are using this way to help you. You are advised not to inform anyone about this until you received your money. Am helping you on this because something in me is tells me that you are an honest person. When you conclude this and you send our promise, we will help to ship the final part of your money to you. May God be with you as i wait for your response Feel free to call me if you will like us to discuses more on this TEL: +221 4183317. Yours Faithfully Revd. Fr. Thomas Douglas Director, Special Duties. UNO/WBF

Dearest in Christ, pls treat with a honest mind Calvary greeting to you and your family. My name is Mrs bene jones, a scottish, but I am married to Mr jones who is the Managing Director of Shell Petro-Chemical Company, before he died in the plane crash of Oct 23, 2005 with Bellview Airlines twin-engine Boeing 737] with other passengers aboard all 117 passage died, as you can confirm it yourself through this website http://edition.cnn. com/2005/WORLD/africa/10/23/nigeria.plane/ http://www.washingtonpost. com/wpdyn/content/article/2005/10/23/AR2005102300368.html We were married for eleven years without a child. Before the death we were both born again Christians. When my late husband was alive we deposited the sum of USD$16.5Million (Sixteen Million Five hundred thosand U.S. Dollars) with one of good bank here in Nigeria. Presently, this money is still with Union Bank of Nigeria. Recently, my Doctor told me that I would not last for the next three months due to cancer problem. Though what disturbs me most is my stroke. Having known my condition I decided to donate this fund to church or better still Christian individual that will utilize this money the way I am going to instruct here in. I want a church that will use this fund to churches, orphanages, Research centres and widows propagating the word of God and to ensured that the house of God is maintained. The Bible made us to understand that blessed is the hand that griveth. I took this decision because I don't have any child that will inherit this money and my husband relatives are not Christians and I don;t want my family hard earned money to be misused by unbelievers.I don't want a situation where this money will be used in an ungodly manner. Hence the reason for taking this bold decision. I am not afraid of death hence I know where I am going. I know that I am going to be in the bosom of the Lord. Exodus 14 VS 14 says that the lord will fight my case and I shall hold my peace. I don't need any telephone communication in this regard because of my health because of the presence of my family relatives around me always. I don't want them to know about this development.With God all things are possible. As soon as I receive your reply. Ishall give you the contact information of the bank and whom to contact. I will also need to get a reliable attorney to assist you as the new beneficiary of this fund. I want you and the church to always pray for me because the lord is my shepherd. My happiness is that I lived a life of a worthy Christian.Whoever that wants to serve the Lord must serve him in spirit and truth. Please always be prayerful all through your life. Any delay in your reply will give me room in sourcing for a Christian individual for this same purpose. Please assure me that you will act Accordingly as I stated here. Expecting to hearing from you, reply back to my alternative email for security purpose. evangelistbenejones@yahoo.com.hk Remain blessed in the name of the Lord. Yours in Christ, Sister bene jones

Attn: Sir, I am Prince Danladi A. Kabila Jr, Cousin to the late president of the Democratic Republic of Congo (DRC) formerly known as Zaire, who was assassinated in January 2001 by his bodyguard. I came across your contact via a missionary that visited our asylum Camp, but I did not disclose the nature of this transaction to her because of the secrecy involved. Accordingly, I will like to inform you that this is note a bragging because it will look too cheap and surprised to you from the way I have contacting you to assist me in making this transaction a success. Due to the war raged in our Republic, the late President, Laurent Kabila was using me, through diplomatic means, to send money out of the Republic because of the fear that a coup de tat may take place at any time. I did this on two consecutive occasions, on the third trip, myself and some aides decided to divert the delivery, which amounted to US$30Million (Thirty Million United states Dollars). I am presently in exile, because of exactly what happened to my late cousin, former President Laurent Desire Kabila, May his soul rest in peace. I have since deposited the money into a Security Company in one of the European Country that will be disclosed to you upon your acceptance to assist me, but the real content of the deposited box containing this fund was not disclosed to them for Security reason. Due to shortcomings and restrictions prevailing in here regarding refugee policy, I came up with the idea of foreign investment for the fund, with the possibility of a joint stock venture with a foreign partner, outside the continent of Africa. My main aim and objective of contacting you is to ask for your assistance in retrieve the said fund from the private firm where it was deposited and transfer it into your private or company&#8217;s account in your country. There is no risk involved, as this is confidential. I have decided to let you have 25% of the total amount of the fund, 5% is for expenses that will be incurred during the transaction, and the remaining 70% of the fund is for myself, which I would like to invest in your country. If you can be trusted and interested, please contact me on the below e-mail as soon as possible:private_danladi@yahoo.com.au On the receipt of your acceptance mail, I shall give you more clarification on the modalities needed for the successful completion of this transaction. Best regards, Prince Danladi A. Kabila Jr. ___________________________________________________________ Like being first? Check out the all-new Yahoo! Mail today. http://uk.docs.yahoo.com/nowyoucan.html

This is a Brand New Compnay Never Marketed Before. We have seen these types move 4.00 in the first day of marketing. We Expect the 6th to be unbelieveable. THIS IS A SOLID COMPANY. PETROSUN DRILLING (PSUD) Current Price: 1.30 Up .05 Friday without any marketing! Current News PetroSun Announces Formation of Algae BioFuels PetroSun Drilling Inc. (PSUD - News), an emerging provider of oilfield services to major and independent producers of oil and natural gas, announced today that the company has formed Algae BioFuels Inc. as a wholly owned subsidiary. Algae BioFuels will be engaged in the research and development of algae cultivation as an energy source in the production of biodiesel, an economically feasible and eco-friendly alternative to petroleum-based transportation fuels. The R&D and production facilities for Algae BioFuels will be based in Arizona and Australia. "PetroSun's formation of Algae BioFuels is a forward-looking strategy," said L. Rayfield Wright, president of PetroSun. "The 0pp0rtunity to produce a renewable energy product that will assist in providing a healthier planet for future generations cannot be ignored." Biofuel is any fuel that is derived from biomass -- which contains recently living organisms or their metabolic byproducts. Biofuel is a renewable energy source, unlike other natural resources such as petroleum, coal and nuclear fuels. Agricultural products specifically grown for use as biofuels include corn and soybeans. Extensive research is currently being conducted to determine the utilization of microalgae as an energy source, with applications being developed for biodiesel, ethanol, methanol, methane and even hydrogen. Independent studies have demonstrated that algae is capable of producing 30 times more oil per acre than the current crops now utilized for the production of biofuels. Algae biofuel contains no sulfur, is non-toxic and highly biodegradable. The Office of Fuels Development, a division of the Department of Energy, funded a program from 1978 through 1996 under the National Renewable Energy Laboratory known as the "Aquatic Species Program." The focus of this program was to investigate high-oil algae that could be grown specifically for the purpose of wide-scale biodiesel production. Some species of algae are ideally suited to biodiesel production due to their high oil content, in excess of 50%, and extremely rapid growth rates. One of the biggest advantages of biodiesel, compared to many other alternative transportation fuels, is that it can be used in existing diesel engines, which relieves automotive manufacturers of having to make costly engine modifications. Biodiesel can also be mixed, at any ratio, with conventional petroleum diesel. As a result, the alternative fuel can be used in the current distribution infrastructure, replacing petroleum diesel either wholly, or as a diesel fuel blend with minimal integration costs. About PetroSun PetroSun's current operations are concentrated in the Ark-La-Tex region with plans to expand into New Mexico, Arizona, Utah and Australia in 2006. PetroSun provides a comprehensive array of products and services to the oil industry. The company's cutting-edge technologies, combined with a proven ability to apply them effectively and safely within a disciplined ROI framework, creates long-term value for PetroSun shareholders and partners. PetroSun is headquartered in Phoenix.

Backley Bank London W6 0NB Zenith House Road London NW9 6EE (26,000,000.00 USD twenty six million United States Dollars) ********************************************************** *********** I am Robert pollol i have a deal of inheritance.I want to transfer (26,000,000.00 USD) twenty six million United States Dollars from a Prime Bank here in London to an oversea account. First, I must solicit your strictest confidence in this transaction. This is by virtue of it's nature as being utterly confidential. I am sure and have confidence of your ability and reliability to prosecute a transaction of this great magnitude. I solicit your assistance to enable us transfer the said amount into your safe account for unward investment. You can either provide us with an existing account or to set up a new Bank account immediately to receive this money, even an empty a/c can serve to receive this money, as long as you will remain honest to me till the end of this important business trusting in you and believing that you will never let me down either now or in future. I am the personal account officer to the great late INDUSTRIALIST who has an account in one of the top banks here in london. The account was opened in 1993 and he died in 1993 without a written or oral WILL and since 2003 nobody has operated on this account again hence the money is floating and if I do not remit this money out urgently it will be forfeited for nothing. The owner of this account is a foreigner and no other person knows about this account or anything concerning it, the account has no other beneficiary and until his death he was the manager of the company.My investigation through the National immigration department proved to me as well that he was single as at the time of his entry into the Republic of South Africa. The amount in this account is USD$26 Million (Twenty Six Million United States Dollars ) only. As a matter of fact, I have decided to transfer this fund abroad for investment. Your assistance as a foreigner is necessary because the management of the bank will welcome any foreigner who has correct information to this account which I will give to you immediately, if you are interested to do this business with me.There is no risk in this business. With my position and my personal contact with the manager of the bank, the money can be transferred to any account you can provide with assurance that this money will be intact pending my physical arrival in your country for sharing. We will start the first transfer with Six million [$6,000.000] to testrun your account. Upon successful transfer without any disappointment from your side, we shall re-apply for the payment of the remaining balance of $26 Million to your account. I am only contacting you as a foreigner because this money can not be approved to a local person here, but can only be pproved to any foreigner who has the correct nformation of the account which I will provide for you. So you should provide me with your correct account details where you will like the fund to be transferred or you can set up a new account for the transfer even an empty account is okay. At the conclussion of the transfer you will take 35%,5% will be for any expenses both parties incurred in the process of this business and the remaining 60% will be for me. As soon as I hear from you and upon your strong assurance that you will not let me down once the fund goes into your account I will then start the processing of the transfer of the fund to your account without further delay. Contact me urgently via email for further details. full name................. sate/country................. account number................... bank name:........................ bank address:..................... Your Tel phone......................... Fax............... .............. Thanks. Yours Faithfully, Robert pollol

READ MY MESSAGE I know that this mail will come to you as a surprise, I am HANSON MILLS,the manager, bill and exchange department, HSBC BANK Rye Lane Branch London UK In my department we discovered an abandoned sum of 800,000.00 POUNDS (EIGHT Hundred Thousand POUNDS) in an account belonging to one of our foreign customers(ROBERT GANDESBERY,), who died along with his entire family on Monday, 31 July, 2000 in a plane crash in Paris. Please visit this site for the story line http://news. bbc.co.uk/1/hi/world/europe/859479.stm Since we got information about his death, we have been expecting his next of kin/relations to come over and claim his money because we cannot release it unless some body applies for it as next of kin or relation to the deceased as indicated in our banking guidelines and laws, but unfortunately we learnt that all his supposed next of kin or relation died alongside with him at the plane crash leaving nobody behind for the claim. It is upon this discovery that I now decided to make this business proposal to you, and for you to act as the next of kin to enable us release the money to you. The banking law and guideline here stipulates that if such money remained unclaimed after Six years, the money will be transferred into the bank treasury as unclaimed fund. We have agreed that 30% of this money will be for you for all the assistance and commitment you will put in to the transaction 10% will be set aside for all expenses incurred during the business and 50% would be for me. Please note that as soon as the transaction is completed I shall proceed immediately to your country for disbursement and possible investment possibilities. Please note also that upon receipt of your reply, I shall let you know the processes we shall take to realize these dreams. I will not fail to bring to your notice that this transaction is hitch-free and that you should not entertain any atom of fear as all required arrangements have been made for proper execution of the transaction. Trusting to hear from you immediately. Thanks Hanson Mills

DEAR FRIEND, I AM DR. AMARACHI SAVIMBI, A FAMILY BROTHER TO THE LATE GENERAL JONAS SAVIMBI, LEADER OF THE ANGOLAN UNITA REBEL WHO WAS SHOT DEAD ON MONDAY 25TH FEBUARY 2002 BY THE OPPOSING FORCES OF ANGOLAN ARMY. FOR THE PAST YEARS NOW OUR COUNTRY HAVE BEEN IN POLITICAL CRISIS AND CONFLITS BETWEEN THE UNITA REBEL AND GOVERMENT ALLIED FORCES. AS A MATTER OF FACT,BEFORE THE DEATH OF GENERAL JONAS SAVIMBI, I WAS GIVEN US$20.8MILLION DOLLARS,AND KARAT DIAMOND AND GOLD DUST FOR PURCHASING ARMUNATIONS FROM RUSSIA AND A MINI LAFEYETTE FRIGATE FROM UKRAIN. I CONSIDERED IT A GREAT OPPORTUNITY AS HE IS NOW LATE CONSPHICATED THE PACKAGE AND DIVERTED IT TO ACCRA-GHANA IN WEST AFRICAN NATION, WHERE IT HAS BEEN DEPOSITED IN A TRUST COMPANY ON A SPECIAL ARRANGEMENT AS A TREASURE. PLEASE TAKE A LOOK AT THIS WEB PAGE FOR IT SAYS IT ALL. http://news.bbc.co.uk/hi/english/world/africa/newsid_1839000/1839252.stm THEREFOR, MY AIM OF CONTACTING YOU IS FOR YOU TO ASSIST ME WITH YOUR PERSONALITY AND INFLUENCE TO TRANSFER AND SECURE THE SAID TREASURE OVER TO YOUR COUNTRY, INTO YOUR POSSESSION. I HAVE THE AMBITION OF INVESTING THIS MONEY AND AS WELL KEEPING A LONG LASTING RELATIONSHIP WITH YOU. PRESENTLY, I AM IN DUBAI, UNITED ARAB EMIRATES, WHERE I HAVE BEEN IN HIDE-OUT FOR SOMETIME NOW,I WAS SENT ON THIS ASSIGNMENT BEFOR HIS DEATH. I WOULD LIKE TO APPEAL TO YOU THAT TIME IS NOT MY FRIEND AS I AM ANXIOUSLY LOOKING FOR A RESPONSIBLE, RELIABLE AND HONEST PERSON TO ACT AS THE BENEFICIARY SO THAT I WILL TRANSFER THIS TREASURE OUT OF AFRICA BECAUSE I AM NOT SAFE HERE IN DUBAI,IF YOU CAN SINCERELY ASSIST ME TOWARDS MY PROPOSAL, WITH ALL YOUR TRUST, WE SHALL DISCUSS ABOUT YOUR PERCENTAGE SHARE FIRST AS SOON AS I RECEIVE YOUR URGENT AND POSITIVE REPLY. PLEASE KINDLY, HANDLE THIS PROPOSAL WITH UTMOST SECRECY AND CONFIDENTIAL AS ALL THE NECESSARY DOCUMENTS AND PROVES AS REGARDS TO THIS TREASURE WILL BE FORWARDED TO YOU ON YOUR REQUEST. HOPING THAT OUR TRANSACTION WILL BE CONSIDERED WITH EVERY CONFIDENTIALITY. DIRECT YOUR REPLY TO THIS MAIL BOX: info.savimbi1950@yahoo.fr THANK AND GOD BLESS YOU. DR. AMARACHI. SAVIMBI.

>From Mr.Roland Nulget Po box 3038, 57 Victoria street, London SW1H, London Attention Please, I feel obliged writing this mail to you. I am not quite exposed to foreign business and friends hence i write to you with hope and trust that you will welcome my mail without being bias and that you will be trust worthy to me. In order to transfer out 12,500,000.00 ( Twelve million, five hundred thousand British pounds) from our bank(Firm). I have the courage to look for a reliable and Honest Person who will be capable of handling this Important Business transaction,believing that you will never let me down either now or in Future. The owner of this account is Mr. David Hagen foreigner and the Manager Of petrol chemical service, a chemical engineer by Profession and he died since 1990.the account has no other beneficiary And my Investigation proved to me as well that his company does not know anything About this account. I want to transfer this money into a safe foreign account abroad but i Don't know any foreigner, i know that this message will come to you as a surprise as we have not had any correspondence before and you have to admit that we don't know ourselves before,but due to the strict confident and your versatility in business that motivated my interest to seek your co-op ration in this business magnitude of this nature and by your 99.9% reliability and straight forwardness given about you that sticked my interest in revealing this top secreat to you. But be sure that it is real And A Genuine business as I believe in God that you will never let me down in this transaction till the fund is remitted to your nominated account while i will travel to your respective country to collect my own share of the money, and we have concluded that at the conclusion of this business,you will be offer 25% of the total amount while 60% will be for me and the rest of 15% will be for any expenses both party will incur in the process of transacting this business. I look forward to your earliest reply by email for more details. Reply to ; auditor@freeweb.org Best regards Mr.Roland This message is for the designated recipient only and may contain privileged, proprietary, or otherwise private information. If you have received it in error, please notify the sender immediately and delete the original. Any other use of the email by you is prohibited.

URGENT RESPONSE NEEDED FROM: BRIAN SMITH Dear friend, I am Brian Smith Esq, my client is one of the top Managers of Midland Bank London Branch and his colleague in the same bank here in the United Kingdom have an urgentand very confidential business proposition for you. On June 6th, 2001, a Chinese business man, Mr.CHOW LIU, deposited in his personal safety deposit vault currency valued at £17,500,000.00 (Seventeen Million, Five Hundred Thousand British Pound Sterling) in my client's branch. Upon expiration of the period of leasehold of his safety deposit vault two years ago, my client sent a routine notification to his forwarding address but got no reply. Some months ago, a reminder was sent and finally it was discovered he had passed away. On further investigation, it was discovered that he did not leave a WILL and all attempts to trace his next of kin were fruitless. Further investigations revealed that Mr. CHOW LIU did not declare any next-of- kin in all his official documents in my clients' bank. This sum of £17,500,000.00 is still in the Vault which was opened and the keys changed upon the expiration of the period of leaseholdby myclients. Consequently, my proposal is that myclients will like you as a foreigner to stand in as the next of kin to Mr. CHOW LIU. This is simple. I will like you to provide me immediately with your full names and address so that by virtue of my position as an attorney, I will prepare the necessary documents and affidavits, which will put you in place as the next of kin. I shall do the drafting and notarization of the WILL and obtain the necessary documents and letter of probate/administration in your favor form the shipment of the funds through a courrier company to you. The money will be shipped by courier to you for us to share in the ratio of 80% for me and my clients and 20% for you. I hope that is okay. There is no risk at all as all the paperwork for this transaction will be done by me as an attorney and the position of my client as the Branch Manager guarantees the successful execution of this transaction. If you areinterested, please reply immediately via email:- brian_smith650@hotmail.com If on the other hand you are not interested please disregard this mail and I will not contact you again. Upon your response, I shall then provide you with my phone number, more details of the transaction and the relevant documents that will help you understand. Please observe utmost confidentiality and be restassured that this transaction would be most profitable for all of us. Best regards, Brian Smith (Esq).

FROM THE DESK OF DAN ASANTE SENIOR STAFF IN FILE DEPARTMENT, INTERNATIONAL COMMERCIAL BANK I.C.B ACCRA,GHANA.WEST AFRICA. PLANE CRASH WEB SITE HTTP://WWW.CNN.COM/2003/WORLD/AFRICA/12/26/BENIN.CRASH/INDEX.HTML ( "REMITTANCE OF $15 MILLION U.S.A DOLLARS CONFIDENTIAL IS THE CASE") COMPLIMENT OF THE SEASON, ON A VERY GOOD DAY. I AM (DAN ASANTE) A SENIOR STAFF IN FILE DEPARTMENT IN INTERNATIONAL COMMERCIAL BANK(I.C.B).I GOT YOUR CONTACT FROM A YAHOO TOURIST SEARCH.WHEN I WAS SEARCHING FOR A FOREIGN PARTNER I ASSURED OF YOUR CAPABILITY AND RELIABILITY TO CHAMPION THIS BUSINEES OPPORTUNITY WHEN I PRAYED TO GOD OR ALLAH ABOUT YOU.IN MY DEPARTMENT WE DISCOVERED AN ABANDONED SUM OF $ 15 MILLION U.S.A DOLLARS ( FIFTEEN MILLION U.S.A DOLLARS) . IN AN ACCOUNT THAT BELONGS TO ONE OF OUR FOREIGN CUSTOMER WHO DIED ALONG WITH HIS ENTIRE FAMILY IN (FRIDAY DECEMBER 26,2003 ) IN A PLANE CRASH. SINCE WE GOT INFORMATION ABOUT HIS DEATH, WE HAVE BEEN EXPECTING HIS NEXT OF KIN TO COME OVER AND CLAIM HIS MONEY BECAUSE WE CANNOT RELEASE IT UNLESS SOMEBODY APPLIES FOR IT AS NEXT OF KIN OR RELATION TO THE DECEASED AS INDICATED IN OUR BANKING GUIDELINES, BUT UNFORTUNATELY WE LEARNT THAT ALL HIS SUPPOSED NEXT OF KIN OR RELATION DIED ALONGSIDE WITH HIM AT THE PLANE CRASH LEAVING NOBODY BEHIND FOR THE CLAIM. IT IS THEREFORE UPON THIS DISCOVERY THAT I AND ONE OFFICIAL IN MY DEPARTMENT NOW DECIDED TO MAKE THIS BUSINNESS PROPOSAL TO YOU AND RELEASE THE MONEY TO YOU AS THE NEXT OF KIN OR RELATION TO THE DECEASED FOR SAFETY AND SUBSEQUENT DISBURSEMENT SINCE NOBODY IS COMING FOR IT AND WE DONT WANT THIS MONEY TO GO INTO THE BANK TREASURY AS UNCLAIMED BILL. THE BANKING LAW AND GUIDELINE HERE STIPULATES THAT IF SUCH MONEY REMAINED UNCLAMED AFTER FIVE YEARS, THE MONEY WILL BE TRANSFERED INTO THE BANK TREASURY AS UNCLAIMED FUND. THE REQUEST OF FOREIGNER AS NEXT OF KIN IN THIS BUSINESS IS OCCASIONED BY THE FACT THAT THE CUSTOMER WAS A FOREIGNER, AND A GHANAIAN CANNOT STAND AS NEXT OF KIN TO A FOREIGNER. WE AGREE THAT 40 % OF THIS MONEY WILL BE FOR YOU AS FOREIGN PARTNER, IN RESPECT TO THE PROVISION OF A FOREIGN ACCOUNT, 10 % WILL BE SET ASIDE FOR EXPENSES INCURED DURING THE BUSINESS AND 50 % WOULD BE FOR THERE AFTER I WILL VISIT YOUR COUNTRY FOR DISBURSEMENT ACCORDING TO THE PERCENTAGES INDICATED.THEREFORE TO ENABLE THE IMMEDIATE TRNANSFER OF THIS FUND TO YOU ASARRANGED, YOU MUST APPLY FIRST TO THE BANK AS RELATIONS OR NEXT OF KIN OF THE DECEASED INDICATING YOUR BANK NAME, YOUR BANK ACCOUNT NUMBER, YOUR PRIVATE TELEPHONE AND FAX NUMBER FOR EASY AND EFFECTIVE COMMUNICATION AND LOCATION WHERE THE MONEY WILL BE REMITTED.UPON RECEIPT OF YOUR REPLY, I WILL SEND TO YOU BY FAX OR EMAIL THE TEXT OF THE APPLICATION I WILL NOT FAIL TO BRING TO YOUR NOTICE THAT THIS TRANSACTION IS HITCH FREE AND THAT YOU SHOULD NOT ENTERTAIN ANY ATOM OF FEAR AS ALL REQUIRED ARRANGEMENTS HAVE BEEN MADE FOR THE TRANSFER. YOU SHOULD CONTACT ME.IMMEDIATELY AS SOON AS YOU RECEIVE THIS LETTER. TRUSTING TO HEAR FROM YOUIMMEDIATELY. YOURS FAITHFULLY, DAN ASANTE ALTERNATIVE EMAIL:danasante777@yahoo.com POST SCRITUM:YOU HAVE TO KEEP EVERYTHING SECRET AS TOENABLE THE TRANSFER TO MOVE VERY SMOOTHLY IN TO THE ACCOUNT YOU WILLPROVE TO THE BANK.AS YOU FINISHED READING THIS LETTER GET BACK TO ME IMMEDIATELY SO THAT WE DISCUSS VERY WELL OVER THIS BUSINESS. ....................................................................................... _________________________________________________________________ Express yourself instantly with MSN Messenger! Download today it's FREE! http://messenger.msn.click-url.com/go/onm00200471ave/direct/01/

Dear Friend, Good day and Compliments. I am writing this letter in confidence believing that if it is the wish of God for you to help me and my family,God almighty will bless and reward you aboundantly and you would never regreat this. I am a female student from University of Burkina-Faso,Ouagadougou.I am 25 yrs old.I'd like any person who can be caring,loving and home oriented.I will love to have a long-term relationship with you and to know more about you.I would like to build up a solid foundation with you in time coming if you can be able to help me in this transaction. Well,my father died on 5th May 2005 and left I and my junior brother behind. He was a king, which our town citizens titled him over sixteen years before his death. I was a princess to him and I am the only person who can take care of his wealth now because my junior brother is still young and my mother is not literate enough to know all my father's wealth. He left the sum of USD 7,350, 000.00 dollars (seven Million, Three Hundred and Fifty Thousand US Dollars),in a security company.This money was annually paid into my late fathers account from Shell petroleum development company(SPDC)and chevron oil company operating in our locality for the compensation of youth and community development in our jurisdiction. I don't know how and what I will do to invest this money somewhere in abroad,so that my father's kindred will not take over what belongs to my father and our family,which they were planning to do without my present because I am a female as stated by our culture in the town. Now,I urgently need your humble assistance to move this money from the security company to your bank account and I strongly believe that by the grace of God,you will help me invest this money wisely. I am ready to pay 20% of the total amount to you if you help us in this transaction and another 10% interest of Annual After Income to you,for handling this transaction for us,which you will strongly have absolute control over. If you can handle this project sincerely and also willing to assist me in lifting this fund,kindly reach me.You can reach me through this email id.(princess_silvee2006@yahoo.com). Please, note that this transaction is 100% risk free and I hope to commence the transaction as quick as possible, I will send you my picture as soon as I hear from you. Yours sincerely, Princess Silvee. _________________________________________________________________ Express yourself instantly with MSN Messenger! Download today it's FREE! http://messenger.msn.click-url.com/go/onm00200471ave/direct/01/

FROM: Miss L. B. CHRISTOPHER MISSIONARY QUARTERS A15 CHURCH ROAD ACCRA GHANA PLS SEND REPLY TO MY PRIVATE BOX chr_2006@walla.com Dear respectful one I feel good contacting you today I have read from your add in Internet knowing quiet well that this contact will bring a lasting relationship. With regard to your reputation and co-worshipper of God who will not disappoint me nor deny me in faith, I am directing this letter of assistance to you. I am Miss Louisa. Christopher the only daughter of Mr.Christopher from Republic of Zimbabwe in desire to get somebody who will safe guard my interest, that of my junior brother (Louis) and this money.Briefly, our father Mr. Christopher was a Gold and Cocoa merchant who based in Lome Togo, Abidjan cote d'Ivoire, and had a branch office here in Accra Ghana.My father was a wealthy Gold/Cocoa merchant who has business in many countries in Europe, America and Asian countries.According to my father, my own mother Died when I was about six years of age, which means that I did not even know my mother very well.The story is that my father Mr. Christopher was Poisoned to death by his business associates about seven months ago, and he died in a private hospital here in Accra Ghana. But when he was about to die, he called us beside his sick bed and told us that he deposited the sum of fifty Two Million Seven Hundred Thousand United States Dollars (US$52.700,000) with a local bank there in Accra, the economic and administrative capital of Republic of Ghana.This money was kept for us in my name, his only daughter. Right now I am a first year student of business management in one of the University here.My only problem now is that since my father has been poisoned to death by his business Associates, I don't even trust any other person here again including my father's brothers and sisters.Right now, I want you to help us in the following ways: 1)I want you to provide a personal / company's bank Account where this amount here he deposited the sum of fifty Two Million Seven Hundred Thousand United States Dollars (US$52.700,000) into your account. 2) You are going to be the manager of this fund and Also my personal guardian until I finished my studies. 3)You are going to procure admissions for us to continue our studies in one of the known university in your country. 4) You are going to receive 15% of the total sum for providing a bank account for this transfer. 5) That you must prepare immediately to make a working visit to ACCRA GHANA here so that me and you can see each other and we can then do the transfer at the same time and I will go back with you to your country. We hope to receive your early response, as it will Encourage us, to stop establishing further contacts as It regards to this subject matters, so that we will furnish you With a private phone number where you can reach us Direct, on receipt of your positive response.For your information, this place we staying now is a House of a church sister who saw our condition and Decided to house us for a while. THIS BUSINESS IS HIGHLY CONFIDENTIAL BECAUSE NONE OF OUR LATE FATHER'S BROTHERS AND SISTERS KNOWS ABOUT THIS TRANSACTION. Waiting to hear from you soon Pls Send reply to my private email box: chr_2006@walla. com Thanks for your understanding, Miss L.B. Christopher

Greetings, A very good day to you. I may have to trouble your sense of personal achievement and reward for an opportunity properly taken advantage of. I am Mr. Michael Jay Ramsey, a representative and an attorney to Kenneth Lay, the former chairman & CEO, Enron Corp. Industry: Energy & Natural Resources Home. He deposited (US $21,000,000.00) with me when he was in power as the chairman of the Corp. I am contacting you because I want you to deal with the Finance house and claim the money on my behalf since I have declared that the Funds belong to my foreign business partner. You shall also be required to assist me in investment in your country. I hope to trust you as a God fearing person who will not sit on this money when you claim it, rather assist me properly, shared in these percentages, 60% to me and 40% to you. When I receive your positive response I will let you Know where the Finance house is and the document's to lay claims to the funds, which is very important. What I need is for you to indicate your interest that you will assist us by receiving the money on my behalf in Europe. For this, you shall be considered to be the beneficiary to the funds. The project in brief, is that the funds with which we intend to carry out our proposed investments in your country, is presently in the custody of a finance house in Europe. I do not want the government of my Country to know about the money because they will believe I got the money from the sales of Enron stock when my client was the Chairman & C.E.O. of Enron Corp. Once I have your details in full, the finance house will contact you for Release of the funds to your account As soon as payment is effected, and the amount mentioned above is successfully transferred into your account, I intend to use my own share in acquiring some estates in your country.For this too, you shall also be the overseas manager of all our properties and you will be paid based on a certain percentage agreed on by both parties. I guarantee you that this will be executed under a legitimate arrangement that will protect you from any breach of the law. Please get in touch with me urgently via E-mail: m_ramsey10@yahoo.co.uk> I am presently in the United Kingdom. Please, provide me the following: 1. Full Name........ 2. Your Telephone Number and Fax Number..... 3. Your Contact Address...... 4. Occupation....... 5. Company Name..... 6. Age..... As soon as I receive these details, we can discuss further herein this transaction. Thanks in advance Michael Jay Ramsey. 欢迎使用 ISM Gmail ---------------------------------- Gmail 中国社区 please visit http://bbs.gmail.cn>

>From Mamou mouna mbulu Coordinator of the northern states Programmes Subject: BUSINESS/INVESTMENT PROPOSAL CLASSIFIED DEAL, Dear Sir, I am Mamou Mouna Mbulu,Bank personnel of the above mentioned Bank Annexe. I got your contact from a very confidential source and I wish to maitain this confidentiality. Actually,I decided to send you this proposal directly.for your appraisal on bussiness proposition for you & for our overall mutual interest. I am currently the coordinator on technical cooperation and procurement officer to the Bank Of African Development and the African funds development.Projects/contract awards. I need your assurance to help conclude a very good transaction wish i feel you will be very much interested BUSINESS I am currently in need of a foreign partner to assist me to be the beneficiary of the total sum of $5,200.000 USD. The money was deposited with BIAO bank in Abidjan by the late general Guie that was assasinated during the last recent failed coup de etat that happened in Ivory coast. he made me the depositor but I can not withdraw this money myself. So right now, I wsih to resign which is must if I secure you affirmative assurance to be able to front for me as my foreign business partner to act as the beneficiary of this money . I have already transfer this money from BIAO to another bank called BICICI in Burkina faso which is now programmed for onward transfer to any name which I shall submit to the bank as the beneficiary of this fund. This is strictly confidential and only between me and you alone. I shall send to you the check as soon as I am able to recieve your favourable response right away. Please this is not a scam as you may think, just remove doubt. this is real A bank account in any part of the world,which you will provide to facilitate the transfer of this money to you as the beneficiary. The money will be paid into your account for us to share in the ratio of 60% for me , 30% for you and 10% for expencies .There is no risk at all as my position will do the paperwork for this transaction as the branch manager guarantees the successful execution of this transaction.If you are interested,please reply immediately via this private email address and also forward to me your telephone number and fax number for easy communication. Upon your response,I shall then provide you with more details and relevant documents that will help you understand.PLEASE OBSERVE UTMOST CONFIDENTIALITY,and be rest assured that this would be most profitable for both of us because I shall require your assistance to invest my share in your country. Awaiting your urgent reply via this email above,please save me the anxiety of endless waiting. God bless you. Mamou Mouna Mbulu ADB BANK PLC _________________________________________________________________ MSN Hotmail : créez votre adresse e-mail gratuite & à vie ! http://www.msn.fr/newhotmail/Default.asp?Ath=f

Hello, My name is Mrs. Catherine O‘Connor. I trained and work as an external auditor for the International Financial Services Ltd for Anglo Irish Bank. Working as part of a bigger team that covers the entire Republic of Ireland region. I have taken pains to find your contact through personal endeavours. On routine audit check last month, I discovered some investment accounts that has been dormant for the last twelve(12) years. All the accounts belonging to a single holder with monies totalling a little above ($17.1 Million United States Dollars) plus interest. Banking regulation/legislation in Ireland demand that I notify the fiscal authorities after a statutory time period of twelve years when dormant accounts of this type are called in by the monetary regulatory bodies. The above set of facts underscores my reason of writing and making the following proposal. My investigations of the said account reveals that the investor died in 1993—the exact time the account was last operated, I can confirm with certainty that the said investor died interstate and no next–of–kin to his estate has been found or has come forward all these years. I am of the settled conviction that using my insider leverage, I, working with you can secure the funds in the account for us instead of allowing it pass as an unclaimed funds into the coffers of the Irish Government. This is especially possible as you bear the same LAST NAME to the said investor, and can stand as his extended relative. This exactly is why I crave your participation and co-operation. I have seized all relevant documents (Legal and Banking) that will facilitate our putting you forward as the claimant/beneficiary of the funds and ultimately transfer the money to any account nominated by you. Of course you shall be handsomely rewarded for your part in this transaction as the people I am working with have agreed to allocate a 30% of the total funds for your efforts, less any expenses. I shall however leave out the finer details of this transaction till I receive an affirmation of your desire to participate. Be assured that me and my colleagues are on top of the situation. There will be no risk involved whatsoever if you agree to come on board. Needless to say, UTMOST CONFIDENTIALITY is of vital importance if we are to successfully reap the immense benefits of this transaction. To maintain the level of security required to see this transaction come to a successful conclusion, I have intentionally left out the finer details. To affirm your willingness and cooperation to my proposal please contact me through email, telephone/fax stating the followings for my confirmation: (1) Full Name; (2) Telephone and Fax Number; (3) Postal Address (4) Occupation; (5) Date of Birth; Your prompt response will be highly appreciated. Thank you, Mrs. Catherine O’Connor International Financial Services Ltd, Custom House Plaza, Block 4, Floor 3, IFSC, Dublin 1. Private/Fax: +353 (01)6335764. cathyocon_nor55ie@myway.com or cathyocon_nor4@myway.com .

FROM: MR WILLIAMS KABILA TEL/FAX :+27-73-469-3435 SIR, URGENT BUSINESS PROPOSAL SORRY FOR THE SURPRISE PROPOSAL, BUT EXCUSE ME,DUE TO MY DESPIRATION IN SEEKING AN URGENT ASSISTANCE. MY NAME IS WILLIAMS KABILA,YOUNGER BROTHER TO THE LATE (DRC)DEMOCRATIC REPUBLIC OF CONGO PRESIDENT LAURENT KABILA. SHORTLY BEFORE HIS DEATH HE GAVE ME THE AUTHORITY TO GO AND RELEASE A BOX IN A SECURITY COMPANY IN SOUTH AFRICA,WHERE HE DEPOSITED THE SUM OF US$31M(THIRTY ONE MILLION UNITED STATE DOLLARS). ALTHOUGH THE SECURITY COMPANY KNOWS THE CONTENT OF THE BOX AS VALUABLE DOCUMENT, I WAS ABLE TO SECURE THE RELEASE WITH THE AUTHORITY OF MY BROTHER. WHILE WAITING FOR THE PILOT OF ONEOFAIRLINES,CONTRACTED BY MY BROTHER TO FLY THE MONEY BACK HOME TO THE DRC,I HEARD OF MY BROTHERS ASSASINATION. AS A RESULT ,I REDEPOSITED THE MONEY IN ANOTHER SECURITY COMPANY IN MY NAME AS BANKING DOCUMENT AND I DECIDED TO WAIT AND SEE IF THE NEW GOVERNMENT HEADED BY HIS SON WILL SEARCH FOR THE MONEY,BUT UPTILL NOW,NOTHING HAS BEEN SAID ABOUT THE MONEY WHICH MEANS IT IS NOT RECORDED, I WAS ADVISED BY A CLOSE FRIEND TO TRANSFER THIS MONEY OUT OF SOUTH AFRICA INTO A FORIGN ACCOUNT AS QUICKLY AS POSSIBLE.WHILE IN SEARCH OF A TRUSTED FORIGN PARTNER,I GOT YOURCONTACT THROUGH YOUR TRADE MISSION. PLEASE KINDLY ASSIST ME.IN THIS REGARD .20%(PERCENT)OF THE MONEY IS FOR YOUR ASSISTANCE. 5% (PERCENT) IS EARMARKED FOR ANY PREPOST EXPENSES THAT MAY OCCUR ON BOTH SIDES IN THE CAUSE OF TRANSFER.THE BALANCE 75%PERCENT IS FOR ME. MEANWHILE,I HAVE APPLIED FOR POLITICAL ASYLUM HERE IN SOUTH AFRICA,AS I AWAIT YOUR URGENT ASSISTANCE. PLEASE, DO CONTACT ME ON MY PHONE NUMBER ABOVE FIRST BEFORE SENDING ME AN EMAIL ON THIS EMAIL ADDRESS (williamskabila_34@yahoo.co.in) IF YOU ARE SINCERELY WILLING TO HELP ME. THANKS AND GOD BLESS IN ALL YOUR ENDEVOURES. MR WILLIAMS KABILA.

From:Ms.Maria Sara Akim. I Am A Liberia. But Am In refugee camp. Abidja Cote D' Ivoire Email:maria_sakim@yahoo.fr Confidential Dear One: I am a girl of 19 years old my name is (Ms.Maria Sara Akim ).the only duther/child of (Dr Dickson Akim Gift),fromliberia. I am an orhpan being that I lost my parents a couple of years ago during the last war in liberia.and now i am here in Abidjan cote d ivoire at the refugee camp again in my life due to the political uprising here in Cote d'Ivoire. The death of my farther has exposing me to danger. My late Father was a serving director of the Cocoa exporting board until his death .both my father and mother was killed during the last rebels war in my conutry liberia.But before there death My father (Dr Dickson Akim Gift), revealed to me that he deposited the sum of ($12.5 Million US Dollars) in a bank here in abidjan cote d'ivoire which he wrote on how he deposited the money on it he said it is for importation of cocoa processing machine and i will like to invest the money to your country. The money was deposited by my late father name on which he did not declear any name as his foreign partner/beneficiary to the bank with this i want you to stand as his foreign partner/beneficiary, for the bank here to use your name to transfer the money out from Abidjan Cote D'Ivoire due to the political war here.I want you to do me a favour to receive this funds to a safe account in your country or any safer place as the foreign partner/beneficiary I have plans to do investment in your country, like real estate houses and private school or importation of raw materials. You will help me Get a visa to your country for residence in order for us to continue invest the fund in a viable business venture and you will also get a school for me, so that i will finish my education there.If you are willing to assist me, please let me know immediately and provide your following information below: _House/address........... _Your Telephone................ _State Country..................... Upon your assistance out of the 100% of the money we will share 45%,45%,and 10% will be for any expencess all i need from your is honesty and you will promise me that you will not run away with my father's money. I will send to you all the documentation that prove the source of the fund before the transfer. Your earliest response to this letter will be appreciated.I require you to treat this letter with the utmost urgency.If you are not interested,please delete this letter so that I can scout for another competent partner to conclude this transaction. Thank's and best regards. Ms.Maria Sara Akim. -------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- Nueva Barra de Herramientas de OZÚ. Navega Más facilmente por Internet. ¡Descargatela gratis! http://barra.ozu.es/ -------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- Correo enviado desde http://www.ozu.es

FROM MR. ROBIN CLARK UNITY TRUST BANK PLC (London) THIRD FLOOR/CONGRESS HOUSE, 23/28 GREAT RUSSELL ST,SOHO, LONDON, WC1B 3UB UNITED KINGDOM REQUEST FOR URGENT TRANSACTION RELATIONSHIP DEAR, FIRST, I MUST SOLICIT YOUR STRICTEST CONFIDENCE IN THIS TRANSACTION. THIS IS BY VIRTUE OF ITS NATURE AS BEING UTTERLY CONFIDENTIAL AND 'TOP SECRET'. I AM SURE AND HAVE CONFIDENCE OF YOUR ABILITY AND RELIABILITY TO PROSECUTE A TRANSACTION OF THIS GREAT MAGNITUDE INVOLVING A PENDING TRANSACTION REQUIRING MAXIIMUM CONFIDENCE. IAM A TOP OFFICIAL OF THE UNITY TRUST BANK PLC HERE IN UNITED KINGDOM AND AN ACCOUNTS SUPERVISOR TO DR ALLEN SMITH WHO IS NOW LATE SINCE LAST THREE YEARS AGO WITHOUT ANY NEXT OF KIN TO HIS ACCOUNT, NOW I WANT TO TRANSFER THIS FUNDS WHICH ARE PRESENTLY TRAPPED IN THE BANK HERE. IN ORDER TO COMMENCE THIS BUSINESS I SOLICIT YOUR ASSISTANCE TO ENABLE ME TRANSFER INTO YOUR ACCOUNT THE SAID TRAPPED FUNDS. HOWEVER, BY VIRTUE OF MY POSITION AS CIVIL SERVANT AND MEMBER OF THIS BANK, I CANNOT ACQUIRE THIS MONEY IN MY NAME. I HAVE THEREFORE, IAM CONTACTING YOU AS A MATTER OF TRUST IN ORDER TO TRANSFER THE SUM OF US$21,320,000.00(TWENTY ONE MILLION, THREE HUNDRED AND TWENTY THOUSAND U.S DOLLARS). HENCE IAM WRITING YOU THIS LETTER. I HAVE AGREED TO SHARE THE MONEY THUS; 1. 20% FOR YOU THE ACCOUNT OWNER 2. 70% FOR ME 3. 10% TO BE USED IN SETTLING TAXATION AND ALL LOCAL AND FOREIGN EXPENSES. IT IS FROM THE 70% THAT I WISH TO COMMENCE A JOINT BUSINESS WITH YOU THERE IN YOUR COUNTRY. PLEASE, NOTE THAT THIS TRANSACTION IS 100% SAFE AND I HOPE TO FINISH THE TRANSFER LATEST SEVEN (7) BANKING DAYS FROM THE DATE OF THE RECEIPT OF THE FOLLOWING INFORMATIONS: YOUR FULL NAME AND ADDRESS, PHONE AND FAX NUMBER, BANK DETAILS AND YOUR STATUS THE ABOVE INFORMATIONS WILL ENABLE ME WRITE LETTERS OF CLAIM AND NEXT OF KIN DESCRIPTION RESPECTIVELY. THIS WAY WE WILL USE YOUR NAME TO APPLY FOR PAYMENT AND RE-AWARD THE BENEFICARY IN YOUR NAME AS THE NEXT OF KIN TO THE LATE BENEFICIARY. IAM LOOKING FORWARD TO DOING THIS BUSINESS WITH YOU AND SOLICIT YOUR CONFIDENTIALITY IN THIS TRANSATION. PLEASE ACKNOWLEDGE THE RECEIPT OF THIS LETTER USING THE ABOVE EMAIL ADDRESS . I WILL SEND YOU DETAILED INFORMATION OF THIS PENDING PROJECT WHEN I HAVE HEARD FROM YOU. YOURS FAITHFULLY, MR ROBIN HANS CLARK

Dear Friend, I am Mr.Vincent Nicholas, I am an accountant with the HSBC BANK UK.I am very sorry if this is an inconvinience in any way, just that i need you to see me through with this transfer. This business request may seem strange, but I crave your indulgence and pray you view it seriously as I am convinced that you would be capable to provide me with a solution to a money transfer. On June 16, 2000, a German property magnate Mr. Andrea Schranner made a numbered time (fixed) deposit for twelve calendar months,valued at £6,500,000.00(Six Million Five Hundred Thousand Pounds Sterling )in my branch upon maturity. I sent a routine notification to his forwarding address but got no reply. After a month, we sent a reminder and finally we discovered from his contract employers (the Petroleum Corporation) that Mr. Andrea Schranner died in an air crash with his family. On further investigation, I found out that he died without making a will and attempts to trace his next of kin were fruitless. I therefore made further investigation and discovered that Mr. Andrea Schranner did not declare any next of kin or relations in all his official documents, including his bank deposit paperwork. This sum of £6,500,000.00 and the interest is being rolled over with the principal sum at the end of each year. No one will ever come forward to claim it .According to British law, at the expiration of 7 years, the money will revert to the ownership of the Bristish Government if nobody applies to claim the fund. Consequently, my proposal is that I will like you as a foreigner to stand as the next of kin to Mr. Andrea Schranner. This is simple, I will like you to provide immediately your full name and address so that an accredited Attorney working with the bank here will prepare the necessary documents and affidavits which will put you in place as the next of kin.We shall employ the service of two attorneys for the drafting and notarization of the will and obtain the necessary documents and letter of probate administration in your favour for the transfer into any bank account in any part of the world which you will provide.We will then facilitate the transfer of this money to you as the beneficiary/next of kin.The money will be paid into your account for us to share in ratio of 50% for me and 30% for you and 10 % will be set aside to ofset any expenses incured during the business , while the other 10% will go to charity organisation. There is no risk at all,the paperwork for this transaction will be done by the attorney and my position as an accountant in the bank with the help of the branch Manager guarantees the successful execution of this transaction. Please reply immediately via the private email address below to show your interest , upon your responses, I shall provide you with more details and relevant documents that will help you understand the transaction. Please observe utmost confidentiality and be rest assured that this transaction would be most profitable for both of us because I shall require your assistance to invest my share of this money in your country. Please upon the receipt of this mail message, send to me the following to enable me start the processing of the fund transfer into your bank account: 1.) Your full name and address, 2.) Your company name and address if any,. 3.) Your private / official telephone and fax number. Awaiting your Urgent Reply via my email: vinnicole@mixmail.com and call me for discussions in regards on my personal telephone number on +447024075148 Thanks and God bless. Best regards Mr Vincent Nicholas.

Bsmillahir Rahmaanir Raheem, Assalam Alaikum, Wasalaam toyou,and how are you doing?. My intention of contacting you is to solicit your assistance for a project, which will be mutually beneficial. Though I know my decision to contact you is to a large extent unconventional, the prevailing circumstances necessitated my action. I am Muayed Abdul Faisal. I am son to Late Mallam Mustafa Abdul Faisal of blessed memory was an oil explorer in Libya and Kuwait for twelve years before hedied in the year 2000. He died after a brief illness that lasted for only four days. Before his death we were both devoted Muslims. Since his death I too have been battling with both Cancer problems.When my late Father was alive he made a huge deposit in millions of US dollars with a Deposit Company in oversea. (I will tell you the amount as we proceed). Recently, my doctor told me that I have only few months to live due to cancer problem. Though what disturbs me most is my stroke sickness. Having known mycondition I decided to donate this fund to either a Muslim organization or devoted Muslim individual that will utilize this money the way I am going to instruct herein. My parents died at a tender age and i was brought up in the orphanage through the help of a devouted muslim.I want this Muslim organization or individual to use this money in all sincerity to fund mosques, orphanages, widows, and also propagatingthe word of ALLAH and to ensure that the society upholds the views and belief of the Holy Quran. The Holy Quran emphasizes so much on ALLAH'S benevolence and thishas encouraged me to take the bold step. I took this decision because I don't have any child that will inherit this money and my relatives are into some radical Organizations and I don't want a situation where this money will be used in an Unholy manner. Hence the reasons for this bold decision, I know that after death I will be with ALLAH the most beneficent andthe most merciful. I don't need any telephone communication in this regard because of my health, because of the presence of my relatives around me always. I don't want them to know about this development. With ALLAH all things are possible. As soon as I receive your reply I shall give you the contact information of the Deposit Company in oversea where the money was deposited. I will also issue a letter ofauthority to the Deposit Company authorizing them that the said fund have being willed to you and a copy of such authorization will be forwarded to you. I want you and theMuslim community where you reside to always pray for me. My happiness is that I lived a true devoted Muslims worthy of emulation, Whoever that wants to serve ALLAH must serve him in truth and in fairness. I will not stipulate any precise amount to reward you, as it will have to be on pre-negotiated terms, based on your level of involvement. Please always beprayerful all through your life. Any delay in your reply will give room in sourcing for a Muslim organization or a devoted Muslim for this same purpose. Until I hear from you by email, my dreams will rest squarely on your Shoulders. May the Almighty ALLAH continue to guide and protect you. Wasalaam Muayed Abdul Faisal,

FROM THE DESK OF:MR.BARR PIKOLO COKER GENERAL AUDITOR OF STANDARD EXCITE BANK LAGOS NIGERIA WEST AFRICA. EMAIL ADDRESS:barri_pikolo07@yahoo.com STRICTLY CONFIDENTIAL JOINT VENTURE PARTNERSHIP INTRODUCTION: My Dear Friend, I am Mr.Barri Pikolo Coker the auditor general of STANDARD EXCITE BANK in Nigeria.I got your contact from your country business guide as a reliable person.I want to transferto overseas ($26,000.000.00 USD)from STANDARD EXCITE BANK inLagos Nigeria west Africa, I want to ask you to quietly look for a reliable and honest person who will be capable and fit to provide either an existing bank account or to set up a new Bank a/c immediately to receive this money, even an empty a/c can serve to receive this money, as long as you will remain honest to me till the end of this important business trusting in you and believing in God that you will never let me down either now or in future. During the course of my auditing I discovered a floating fund in an account opened in this bank in1990 and since then till 2006 nobody has operated on this account again, after going through some old files in the records I discovered that the owner of the account died without a [heir]hence the money is floating and if I do not remit this money out urgently it will be forfeited for nothing.The owner of this account is Mr. Adam.B.Husrt , a foreigner, and an industrialist,he died, since 1993 and no other person knows about this account or any thing concerning it,the account has no other beneficiary and my investigation proved to me aswell that Adams.B. Husrt until his death he was a director of Diamond Safari(PTY)SA.With account number #5005874CB1000.I have kept the information secret within myself to enable me look for any foreign partner of my choice who will assist me receive this funds. However, every legal steps will be put in place to obtain all legal approvals for onward transfer of this money to your account with appropriate clearance from the relevant ministries and foreign exchange departments.We will sign a binding agreement, to bind us together and to build amount of confidence and trust between us. I am revealing this to you with believe in God that you will never let me down in this business. Your urgent reply will be highly appreciated to enable me inform you of the next step to take urgently because this transaction will be actualize within 14 working days. All I need is your full co-operation to make this work fine. because, the STANDARD EXCITE BANK management is ready to,approve this payment to any foreigner who has correct information of this account, which I will give to you,upon your positive response and once I am convinced that you are willing and ready to handle this deal. With my influence in this bank we can transfer this money to any foreign reliable account which you can provide with assurance that this money will be intact pending my physical arrival in your country for sharing.I will be monitoring the whole situations here in the bank until you confirm this funds in your account. Then i will destroy all documents of transaction immediately we receive this money leaving no trace to any place.I will apply for annual leave to get visa immediately I hear from you that you are ready to act and receive this funds in your account. At the conclusion of this business, you will be given 40% of the total amount,55% will be for me, while 5% will be for expenses incurred during the process of transferring. I look forward to your earliest reply. Thanks Yours faithfully, Mr.Barri Pikolo Coker

Dear Sir Good day to you.It is my pleasure to write you this letter and at the same time, thank you for creating time to go through my message.I know you maybe wondering how i got your address but permit me to tell you that i got your contact from your country's business directory and after going through your profile and much delibration, i decided to contact you immidiately, for this noble transaction.My name is Eng. Mrs. Victoria Lulu,A widow and from the nationality of Sierra Leone in west african war torne nation. My self and my husband worked in the country's biggest diamond minning coporation in which he was in charge of accounts while i was a minning engineer. so when the war broke out and the pandemonium that followed, i had to escape with my son and some cash, immidiatelly after the brutal murder of my husband which is after he was accused of financial mismanagement by the rabell leader and head of millitery junta,Mr Forday Sankoh.Although he (Sankoh) claimed to be unconnected to the killing but after all i experienced from the rabells, I think i had to ran for the safty of myself and my son,with The cash which is the sum of $19.8million dollar. My reason for contacting you is to solicit for your assistance and to stand as my trustee in having this cash successfully moved to your country, where i will have to invest it in a good business or if accepted by you, from a joint venture business with you, for the mutual benefit of both of us. Although am still very ready to pay you as a trustee or rather commit it same to the joint venture collaboration.Back in my country, trustee fee is within the range of 5 to 7% of the total fund. Upon your acceptance and willingness to stand as my trustee in handling this transaction, please do reply this mail, by contacting me strickly on this mail address as this mail using was the one myself and my husband were using when he was still alive. please i urge you to handle this transaction with utmost confidentiality as the future of my self and my son solelly depends on the success of this transaction.I look forward to hearing from you very soon. Thanks in advance for your co-orperation. Best Regards From, Mrss Victoria Lulu.

CONTRACTS VERIFICATION N. N. P. C ATTN: PRESIDENT/CEO Dear friend, l am Dr Mallam Galadima., the contracts verification manager of Nigeria National Petroleum Corporation (NNPC), Because of my position and that of other strategic officials who are heads in their Departments, we have in our possession, since 2001 the sum of US$400M Dolllars (Four hundred million United States Dollars) which we emassed through over invoicing of foreign contracts fully executed and commissioned with the different foreign contractors duely paid their full contract amounts. We have made several fruitless moves to transfer this fund abroad for our mutual benefits. One in 2002 when one Mr. Lambert Brown of the United States of America, living at No 125 N. Kinsley Ave. Ocean City, NJ 082216, ran away with our US$65M Dollars after the fund has been transfered into his account. lt was unbelievable, shocking and hypertensive that when we went there to claim our share of the fund, we were told that nobody with that name was living in that house and that the former occupant of the flat moved away few weeks ago to an unkown house. This is how we lost US$65M Dollars to the heartless Mr. Lambert Brown. The second attempt was when in 2003, we decided to carry US$50M dollars in cash through the Lagos lnternational Airport but was stopped by the Nigerian Custom Officers who seized the fund till date . This is how we lost another US$50M Dollars to the Nigerian Custom. Following the peaceful life ushered in by the current democratic dispensation in Nigeria, l and my colleages have decided to transfer the sum of US$22M (Twenty Two Million dollars) into a foreign account operated by a foreigner for our mutual benefits. By this letter, l request your assistance in transferring and safeguarding the sum of US$22M Dollars for our mutual benefits. For assisting us in transferring and safeguarding this fund, you will be entitled to 35% of the total sum 5% will be set aside for charity and philantropic purposes 57% belongs to me and my colleagues while 3% will go for reimbursement of all expenses made by both parties. However, l want you to be human and humane so that you do not become this second Mr. Lambert Brown of the United States. lt is imperative to note that this transaction is risk free as all modalities for the successful transfer of this fund have been perfected by my colleagues in the relevant ministries. However, we should see absolute confidentiality as our watchword throughout the course of this transaction for we are civil servants and will equally not like the 2002 event to redramatise itself. l will not be ungrateful if you can urgently furnish me with your private telephone, fax and mobile numbers and name of beneficiary with the telex numbers of the receiving bank. These will enable us speed up the claim of the fund and eventual transfer into your nominated account. Please reply via this alternative email address:mallamgaladima59@yahoo.com Looking forward to hear from you soonest. Dr.Mallam Galadima

Dear Friend, I know that this mail will come to you as a surprise as we have never met before.My name is Dr.Yacube Akim.I am the bill and exchange manager in African Development Bank.I Hoped that you will not expose or betray this trust and confident that I am about to repose on you for the mutual benefit of our both families. I am writing in respect of a foreign customer of our Bank who perished along with his next of kin with Korean Air Line, flight number 801 with the whole passengers on 6th of augustus 1997 and for your perusal you can view this site http://www.cnn.com/WORLD/9708/06/guam.passenger.list Since the demise of this our customer, I personally has watched with keen interest to see the next of kin but all has proved abortive as no one has come to claim his funds of US$8.3M (Eight Million Three Hundred Thoudsand United States Dollars) which has been with our branch for a very long time. On this note, I decided to seek for whom his name shall be used as the Next of Kin since nobody is coming for the fund again.The Banking ethics here does not allow such money to stay more than 10 years, because the money will be recalled to the Bank treasury as unclaimed fund after this period. In view of this I got your contact through the internet when I was making a research on a foreigner that I will use in this great opportunity because i dont want the money to be recalled to our Bank treasury as uncliamed fund.I have also agreed to offer 40% of the total sum and the rest 60% will be for me. The reason for a foreigner in the business is for the fact that the deceased man was a foreigner and it is not authorized by the law guiding our Bank for a citizen of this country to make the claim of the fund.So the request of you as a foreigner is necessary to apply for the release and transfer of the fund smoothly into your reliable Bank account as the surving relation to the deceased. If you are really sure of your integerity, trustworthy and confidentiality, and accept not to cheat or disappoint me after this business, reply with your telephone and fax numbers and banking account details where you wish to receive the fund. Upon receipt of the above mentioned informations,indicating your interest in the business,I will send you by fax or e-mail a letter of application which you will type and send back to our bank to enable us start this transaction. I will not fail to bring to your notice that this business is hitch free and dont have any negative impact.You should not entertain any fear as all modalities for the smooth and easy transfer of this fund has been finalized, this transaction will be completed within 14 bank working days immediately we start the business. Waiting for your urgent response and please kindly delete if you are not interested. Regards, Dr.Yacube Akim African Development Bank. _________________________________________________________________ MSN Hotmail : créez votre adresse e-mail gratuite & à vie ! http://www.msn.fr/newhotmail/Default.asp?Ath=f

Attn: Sir/Madam, {HIGHLY CONFIDENTIAL} (RE: TRANSFER OF (THIRTY SIX MILLION SEVEN HUNDRED AND FIFTY NINE THOUSAND POUNDS STERLINGS) RE: TRANSFER OF 36,759,000.00 MILLION POUNDS TO YOUR ACCOUNT. My name is Mr.Jason Leicester and I work in the International Operation Department in a Bank here in London. I feel quite safe dealing with you in this important business.Though, this medium (Internet) has been greatly abused, I choose to reach you through it because it still remains the fastest medium of communication. However, this correspondence is unofficial and private, and it should be treated as such. At first I will like to assure you that this transaction is 100% risk and trouble free to both parties. WE WANT TO TRANSFER OUT MONEY FROM OUR BANK HERE IN LONDON. THE FUND FOR TRANSFER IS OF CLEAN ORIGIN. THE OWNER OF THIS ACCOUNT IS A FOREIGNER, a program leader.Until his death,The Late Prime Minister, Mr. Rafik Hariri, has a huge investment here in the United Kingdom and all over the world, as a matter of fact he has the sum of(THIRTY SIX MILLION SEVEN HUNDRED AND FIFTY NINE THOUSAND POUNDS STERLINGS) in his account here in London which he deposited as a family valuables.The family do not know about this deposit.I was on a routine inspection that I discovered a dormant domiciliary account with a BAL. Of (THIRTY SIX MILLION SEVEN HUNDRED AND FIFTY NINE THOUSAND POUNDS STERLINGS) on further discreet investigation, I also discovered that the account holder has passed away (dead) leaving no beneficiary to the account. The bank will approve this money to any foreigner because the former operator of the a/c is a foreigner. I am certainly sure that nobody will come again for the claim of this money. A foreigner can only claim this money with legal claims to the account Holder, Therefore I need your cooperation in this transaction. I will provide all necessary information needed in order to claim this money.Hoping in God that you will never let me down now and in future.o.k! Rafik Bahaa Edine Hariri (November 1, 1944 - February 14, 2005), married to Nazek Audi Hariri, was a Lebanese self-made billionaire and business tycoon, and was five times Prime Minister of Lebanon (1992-1998 and 2000-2004) before his last resignation from office on October 20, 2004. The late Rafik Hariri died on February 14, 2005 when explosives equivalent to around 300 kg of C4 were detonated as his motorcade drove past the Saint George Hotel in the Lebanese capital, for more information please log on to (http: //www.hariri.info/) I WANT TO TRANSFER THIS MONEY INTO A SAFE FOREIGN ACCOUNT ABROAD BUT I DON'T KNOW ANY FOREIGNER WHOM I CAN TRUST, I KNOW THAT THIS MESSAGE WILL COME TO YOU AS A SURPRISE AS WE DON'T KNOW OURSELVES BEFORE, BUT BE SURE THAT IT IS REAL AND A GENUINE BUSINESS. I CONTACT YOU BELIEVING THAT YOU WILL NOT LET ME DOWN ONCE THE FUND GOES INTO YOUR ACCOUNT. Best Regards Mr.Jason Leicester .

Dear Friend Good day to you, My name is Irvin Shawn I am an American soldier, serving in the military with the Third infantry Division in Iraq. Three years ago, we discovered some huge amount of money in Baghdad neighbourhood belonging to Saddam Hussein, I smuggled some part of these funds in two trunk boxes out of Baghdad, which is being kept safe in a secured finance company in Europe. You can go to this web link to read about events that took place here: <http://news.bbc.co.uk/2/hi/middle_east/2988455.stm> Basically, am writing you due to the situation I found myself and can not return back to America again because I was among five US soldiers questioned by military officials after some of that money was allegedly stolen, as I have absconded from US military and am now in exile. I have killed in war and I found no peace anymore in where I am right now as I have been declared wanted by US Military.I have decided to look for someone like you to help me retrieve these funds from Finance Company in Europe and disburse this funds to any charity organisation on earth as I know that this will only be a way Almighty God can forgive me in all human killing I encounter during war. In honesty, after claiming these two trunk boxes from security company in Europe, you shall have 50% of total funds, disburse 50% to five charity organisations on planet earth. Each box contain the sum of fifteen million United States Dollars. I do not want any money from these funds rather than spending all on humanity for me to have forgiveness of sins from Almighty God who seeth us all from above and that is why you must do this in honesty and trust, I shall seek for an assylum in any part of the world outside United States of America because I can not return back to my lovely country and I have been diagnosed of Cancer of Lungs and Oesophagus due to Bomb explosure I inhale duing my escape our of war I will send you certificates of deposit to enable you lay claim to these boxes on my behalf as soon as I hear from you. My watch word is to trust you and ensure confidentiality, when you receive this letter, kindly reply me via this e-mail below:lrsha242@aim.com signifying your interest including your confidential telephone/fax numbers for quick communication and also your contact details (Job title and occupation). Respectfully submitted Sgt. Irvin Shawn. (lrsha242@aim.com) SINCERITY AND TRUST.